Miguel, come here.
- Hi, Calista.
- Hi.
Um, what is it?
I don't know.
Please, Calista, let me see.
Um... no.
Please, let me see.
No.
Okay, for your birthday.
Wow. Thanks.
You can't open it today.
Tomorrow.
Okay, tomorrow.
- Bye.
Oscar.
Take your share.
That's too much.
That's more than fair,
my friend.
Papai!
Son!
Miguel!
Calista's not with you?
Um, no, she's in the village.
Oh, okay.
Are you coming to my house
tomorrow?
Of course I am.
It's your birthday.
Here you go.
Thank you.
- See you tomorrow.
Luis, Marcos.
How was school?
Good.
Can I fish with you tomorrow?
You have school, Miguel.
Please.
We'll see.
That's a good one.
Race you!
Hi, Mamae!
How was school today?
Good.
Are these for the market?
Yes, love, don't touch it.
Why do they always
have to be for the market?
But I'm making you something
special for tomorrow.
Please, Mama, can I have
one guava sweet?
After dinner.
Someone's excited
for your birthday?
Just Calista.
Miguel, don't forget
your homework.
Papai?
Please let me go with
you tomorrow.
We'll see in the morning.
But you have to finish your
homework first.
Papai, I have to
tell you something.
What's that?
You smell...
...like stinky fish.
You do.
Well, I'm going to get
both of you stinky!
Joao, no!
Time for bed.
Oh, not yet, Mamae.
Good night, son.
Good morning.
Papai?
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Can we go now?
I'm not sure.
The clouds are changing.
Please, Papai.
You are a persistent one,
my son.
- Push.
- Okay.
Hold on.
- We are going back.
- Papai, no!
- You promised!
Miguel.
Hold on!
Papai!
Miguel!
Miguel! Miguel.
Oh, look at them.
The migration
has begun, Stephanie.
Look! There they go!
That's okay.
It's all right.
Joao?
- Why bother?
- He'll come around one day.
I don't think so.
We're still his friends.
So you tell him that.
If he talked to us,
we would.
That old man is broken and
nothing's fixing him.
Oscar.
Wait, I know.
Stay, stay here.
Okay, what do I have?
Ah.
Don't move.
Here. Here.
One more.
Your last one.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't move.
I will get you clean.
Ah. Yeah.
Yes, yes.
Look at this oil on you.
Yes.
No.
Yeah, yeah.
No, yes.
You're doing well.
Thank you, Calista.
You're welcome.
Here we go.
Mamai!
Hey, baby.
All done with school.
Yes.
We miss your guava sweets.
Mamae said
you make the best ones.
Thank you.
- Bye.
- Hello.
- How was it?
Oh, it was too hot.
Hmm.
Wait. Wait.
What is that?
Joao?
Wait.
What's in there?
Why is a penguin in our home?
It needs our help.
- What?
- Yes.
He was covered in oil
and barely alive.
Uh-huh. That's why the oil
is all over my kitchen.
Yes.
That penguin cannot stay.
I can't even use my bathroom.
It's going to be fine.
I fix him up, he leaves.
Mm-mm.
He needs
a few days, to rest.
Wait! Wait!
A few days.
Keep still.
Wait, there is oil everywhere.
Yes. Everywhere.
Yeah.
Don't move, no, don't move.
Don't do that.
My goodness.
I have this for you.
No, no, no, no, no.
- Watch it.
- Here you go.
No, this one is dirty.
Wait, come, come,
come with me. Come.
Yeah.
Hold him, please,
hold him.
I'm coming.
What are you doing?
Joao.
Hurry up, Joao, hurry up.
What are you doing?
- Here.
- Joao.
It's okay, it's all right.
Yeah.
For the penguin... again?
Yes.
He needs to get stronger.
How can I make breakfast?
It's been a week, Joao.
One more week.
Come on, don't be scared.
You know,
when you get
your good feathers,
you can go, okay?
Hey.
Look what I have for you.
Come.
Yes. Yes.
Good.
Come, come.
Come up here.
Yeah, let's have a look.
Don't move, no, stay here.
Stay here.
Ah, good.
Very good.
Take it easy.
What?
Lucia, come back.
It's a penguin!
Can I talk to him?
He's shy.
Ola, penguin!
What is it?
It's a penguin!
Lucia, it's time to head home.
Look, Mamae! It's true!
Oh?
Ola, Calista.
Ola.
I've never seen
a penguin before.
What's his name?
He doesn't have one.
I think...
his name...
should be DinDim! Yes! DinDim.
DinDim?
Okay.
DinDim.
DinDim?
Nice to meet you, DinDim.
Where are you taking him?
Back out there.
Do you have to?
He needs to go home.
Will you see him again?
No.
Well, let's say
good-bye, then.
Okay. Bye, DinDim.
Come, baby.
Bye, Calista.
I'm sad for Joao.
DinDim.
How about that?
Here.
Stay here.
No. No.
You can't come with me.
You need to go home.
Go away.
Don't come with me.
You are a persistent one.
Really.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You did what was best
for the penguin.
For DinDim.
For what?
Lucia gave him a name.
DinDim.
You spoke to Lucia?
Yes, DinDim.
I like it.
Where are you going?
Ah.
DinDim?
Is that you?
What happened?
I don't know,
he came home.
Oh. Home?
Yes, he thinks it is.
Yes.
How far did you take him?
To the cave,
on the outer island.
And he came back?
DinDim came back.
Yes, here.
You're really hungry.
What is that?
Where did it come from?
Joao, who is this?
This is DinDim!
What?
DinDim.
My granddaughter just
named him that.
Yes.
I need some fish.
It's for him.
Small ones, please.
Hold on there, DinDim!
They are too big for you.
Here.
Hey, good boy, Din Dim.
Look at this.
Pretty bad.
Take this other one.
Where did you get him?
On the beach,
about a month ago.
Soaked in oil.
He's lucky he found you.
I am lucky.
Ask him if he's going
to keep him.
Maybe you should ask.
He does what
he wants, you know?
He is free.
You know, guys,
I was remembering
that time, we were kids,
and we saw a shark.
Something very big...
remember that?
I remember.
We came back so fast.
No one believed us.
You were there too, Joao.
Oscar, too!
I don't remember.
No. No.
Thanks for the fish.
DinDim?
Joao.
What did you do?
It is for the penguin.
Everything is for the penguin.
Hey!
Dindim! Dindim!
DinDim!
Breakfast!
DinDim?
Here, here.
This way, little guy.
This one's taking
his sweet time.
Careful.
He went right in.
Perfect.
I got it.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
Take him out.
Let's weigh him.
Yes.
Come, little guy.
Okay.
- Five kilos.
- Impressive.
Okay, okay. Shh, shh, shh.
Steady, there.
Okay, we're almost done.
Sixty-four centimeters long.
Twenty centimeters wide.
Got it.
He's so friendly.
Do they normally do that?
No.
No, it's not normal,
it's abnormal.
Hand me a tag, please.
Steph?
Come on, little guy.
Hold him tight.
Okay.
He's very calm.
Shh, shh, shh.
There, now we are friends.
Fish bribe.
Works every time.
Okay.
There you go.
Is he okay?
He will try to shake it off.
He'll be fine.
Stephanie,
let's go match his nest.
- Can you grab the nest tag?
- Yeah.
What's this all over his nest?
Is it trash?
Interesting.
It's a look.
It's quite different.
It's highly abnormal.
Abnormal is so negative.
Should we help him
clear out some of the trash?
He looks well.
He doesn't
seem to be eating it.
Let not interfere.
He's smart.
Joao, don't do it.
Here.
They always find their
way back, don't they?
Same nest, same mate.
The mystery of penguin GPS.
It could be smell.
Or a special protein
in their eyes?
A photoreceptor?
That's quite a penguin
super power if that's proven.
Penguins obviously have
super powers.
They are flightless birds,
up against terrible
environmental stressors.
Oh, you're such a pessimist.
Realist.
There must be something else.
Actually, my theory is...
they learn to adapt.
So adaptation is their
superpower?
Do I have it right?
No, they don't have
superpowers.
Carlos, relax.
I'm just saying, it's a
teaching moment.
She's kidding.
Is this for me?
Thank you.
Carlos, do we have
the camera with us?
Yeah.
You have...
Hey.
You are very odd,
little bird.
I like you.
Let's go.
DinDim?
Maria!
Maria, look at that.
He's back?
After all this time?
What is that thing?
What?
The red thing.
I don't know.
Are you hungry? Eh?
Of course.
This one is beautiful.
Thank you, sweetie.
You're so nice.
What?
DinDim's back!
Joao is in the village.
It's a penguin.
Ola.
Hello, Joao.
I can't believe it.
It's a penguin!
Look at them.
DinDim!
Good to see you, Joao.
Ola.
Oh, wow.
I've never seen
something so cute.
He so cute.
He's so special.
Is he your pet?
Not my pet.
He's my friend.
He chooses to be with Joao.
With us, he chooses
to be with us.
It's okay, DinDim.
What did you call him?
DinDim.
This is DinDim.
Hi.
Hi, DinDim.
Hi, listen to this story.
This is DinDim,
a little penguin
who comes to our
village every year.
Adriana, Adriana.
You have to see this.
I sent you the link.
Excuse me.
You won't believe it.
Okay, I was doing something.
Hi...
Look!
Four million views.
What?
He's famous.
Who's famous?
Look.
The penguin.
...this same house
to visit his friend, Joao,
a fisherman who saved him.
Hmm, I don't know,
that's... that's not right.
It's kind of sweet.
Even you have to
admit that, Carlos.
That guy is way off course.
Look at this.
I bet it's one of ours.
I am not a betting man,
but if I was,
I would not
bet on that, really.
It could be from anywhere.
It's true.
He's awfully far
to be one of ours.
We have to check.
Do you they say
where he's from in Brazil?
Um...
It's a tropical place.
Yeah, a place called Ilha
Grande near Rio de Janeiro.
This is very interesting.
What is he doing so far away
and so far north?
Lost?
He's lost looking for food?
Chased by predators?
He's quite comfortable
with humans.
Look at this.
He's so cute!
Hello, Paulo.
How is Rio?
Listen, I need a favor.
There's a video I just watched
of a Magellanic
penguin in Ilha...
Yes!
Yes, that's the one.
Can you go there?
I need you to get
the tag number.
It's a long shot,
but I would like to know
if he's one of ours.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Thank you so much,
Paulo.
What was that?
It's how we are going to
figure this out.
Great!
How much should we bet?
How much?
Well done.
Okay, it's fascinating,
but we have to work.
- Okay.
- Go, go, go.
Okay.
Hello? Is anyone home?
Yes?
Ooh, ooh.
Hi, um, sorry to bother you,
I'm Paulo,
and I would like to talk
to you about the penguin.
What about him?
Thank you for the water.
What can we do for you, Paulo?
Well, there's something.
I was contacted
by my friend Adriana.
She's a Marine Biologist
in Argentina.
And she saw the video.
What video?
The video of you and the
penguin... I mean DinDim.
It went viral.
So?
Well, a lot of people around
the world have seen it.
Mmm. Delicious.
Why are you here?
Well, Adriana asked me
to check
the penguin's tag number.
Why?
Are you going to take him?
No, no, no, no.
I'm not here to cause any
trouble, I promise.
Joao, it's okay.
K-2-6.
- K-2-6.
- 1-0-9.
- One?
- Zero, nine.
Zero, nine.
Thank you.
Listen.
I would love to do
a television interview
with you.
No.
No interview.
Be polite, hmm?
I'm a freelance journalist,
and I've worked
for many publications.
We are ordinary people.
Yes, I understand.
It's just a penguin.
Yeah, but I want
to reassure you...
We've lived a quiet life.
That's what Joao means.
I think the whole world
will be interested
in the story of
you and DinDim.
No.
Okay, thank you.
It was a pleasure to meet
DinDim, and you both,
- of course.
- Thank you.
Um, Joao.
This... whatever this is...
You and DinDim have
quite a friendship.
And it gives me hope,
you know.
That's all,
it's made my day and...
thank you.
I needed it.
He's a persistent man.
Paulo!
Yes?
One thing you need to know
for the interview.
DinDim comes and goes
as he pleases.
As he pleases.
Thank you.
Okay, good.
Yes, got it.
Thank you, Paulo.
I owe you one.
Stephanie,
can you pull up the file?
- Yes.
- Okay, here it is.
K...
K-26-1-0-9.
Here.
That's incredible.
It's one of ours.
And you have a note here.
Look.
Are you kidding?
What is it?
It's the one.
The abnormal one?
Unique. Unique.
I knew we should've bet.
Hey.
Hello, DinDim.
Hello?
Ola.
Hi, Maria.
- Hi. Hi.
- How are you?
Mm, something smells good.
Thank you.
I made a big pot
of stew for everybody.
Hopefully I've made enough.
Welcome. Welcome.
Hi, Joao,
nice seeing you again.
- Ola.
This is my crew.
Okay?
Hi, Joao! Hi, DinDim!
Joao, please, over here.
Tell us about DinDim.
Yes.
The last couple of years,
he showed up in June,
and he went away in December.
He comes and goes
as he pleases.
Do you think
he'll keep coming back?
Yes. I think so.
He's always
so happy to see Joao.
The little penguin
travels 5,000 miles
every year between
Patagonia and Ilha Grande
to visit his friend Joao.
Yeah.
One minute.
It's the boss.
Yes, Kim, how are you?
I'm good.
I hope things
are going well in the field.
Can I share some news?
Sure, what's going on?
You know the penguin that
you told me about? DinDim?
Our team wants him to live
here at the University,
in the observation lab.
No, not DinDim.
Why?
I don't think
he would do well.
We would like to study
his human interactions.
He actually seems
to look for it.
Well, yes.
But he does fine
with penguins, too.
But we have ten Magellanic
penguins here now.
He will do great.
The board will make
a decision in a few weeks.
There may be a grant
for you and your team.
I will get back to you.
Okay.
Bye, Adriana.
Hey, we were looking for you.
Is everything okay?
We could use the grant.
Yeah.
We could upgrade
our equipment,
help more penguins.
Really?
I don't know.
The question is,
what's best for DinDim?
That man in Brazil,
he says he comes and goes.
He'll have human
and penguin contact.
He'll be happy.
How do you know that?
He seems perfectly happy now,
and can live in both worlds.
Look... this nest
is far away from the sea.
They are all grown up
and ready to migrate.
Adriana?
Hello, Adriana.
It's been difficult
to reach you.
I know the season is ending,
so I want to let you know we
have decided to take DinDim.
I promise we will keep him
safe and happy.
That's a mistake.
You will need to bring him
in the next couple of days.
I'm sure you understand.
By the way, you got the grant.
Thanks, Adriana.
Hi, DinDim.
Here.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Coming.
- Joao.
- Paulo.
My friend.
Welcome back.
- Maria, nice to see you.
- Paulo.
I made a special guava
sweet for everybody, okay?
It's beautiful.
Yeah, we hope you aren't
waiting too long for DinDim.
No, it's okay.
We have a nice place
in town, thank you.
He should be here soon.
We are so excited to see
DinDim again.
Thank you for having us.
You are welcome.
Guys, are you okay?
Can we start?
All right.
This way, here.
Look.
I built this for him.
Right.
Yes, he made it his home.
He built it like a burrow,
a penguin's version of a nest.
Excuse me.
Oh, look at that.
He even has a gift for you.
- Do you want to check him?
- He's fine.
I'll take care of
the paperwork.
Okay.
Hello.
Hello, how are you?
Thank you.
- Adriana.
- Yes?
Where is the penguin?
I don't know.
What do you mean
you don't know?
You left the door open.
But he was in a crate,
how did he get out?
You know me,
I don't interfere.
Okay, great.
Just great.
I told you he was different.
Yeah, I can see that.
He's an escape artist.
He knows how to adapt,
which is critical
for his survival.
He'll be fine.
It's good to see you.
Here, help me.
Okay.
Hello, Maria.
- Nice to see you.
Hello.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Hi, what's your name?
Lucia.
Lucia. Lucia,
I heard you named the penguin.
Yes! DinDim!
Is he coming?
Of course he is.
He'll show up.
Darling, let's go.
It's getting late.
Sorry, Joao.
Bye, Maria, see you.
Let's go home, okay?
Well, waiting is half the fun.
For whom?
Tomorrow, Joao.
He's never been this late.
I'm sorry, Maria.
Joao.
Joao. Joao.
You're having dreams.
Do you want some water?
Thank you.
DinDim had this.
I know what it is.
Yes.
What?
It was from Calista,
from a long time ago.
Calista?
Open it.
Hi, Maria.
We've been so worried
these last two weeks.
Hi, Maria.
Hello.
We've been praying for you
and Joao and DinDim.
I have to find him.
I need to know
I tried everything.
Everything.
I never thought
it was your fault.
Never.
Joao, what are you doing?
I have to find DinDim.
Oscar.
I need your help.
DinDim.
Joao needs our help.
Let's get the boats ready!
Okay, then, let's go.
Row, row, guys!
Let's go!
Let's go.
Come on!
Towards the left!
DinDim!
Come.
It's hard to see.
DinDim!
He's not here.
Do you see him?
Nothing here, Joao!
DinDim! DinDim!
There!
It's just seaweed.
Let's speed up!
Let's try further west!
DinDim!
He didn't make it.
Time to head back!
Let's go home.
It's time to go home!
- Let's turn around.
- Time to go.
I'm sorry, Joao.
It's okay.
Let's try behind the island.
Let's get closer.
There! Over there!
Look!
Do you see him?
There!
Wait, Joao...
Take him.
Come on, Joao.
Give him, give him to me.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Forgive me,
forgive me.
No.
Please.
Here, try some fish.
- Give him some more.
- Give him some more bait.
Take it.
More, more.
He's back, he's back.
Good to see you,
good to see you.
Welcome, Luis!
- My God, it's guava sweet!
- Hi!
- This is for you.
I propose a toast.
- For DinDim!
- DinDim!
- For DinDim.
- For DinDim, yes.
Yeah, we toast.
Hello, DinDim!
Everybody's waiting for you!
Come on, let's go!
Hello, DinDim.
Welcome.
See you next time,
my friend.