BOY 1: Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Look, look, look.
BOY 2: I got you. I got you.
- That's too easy. It's too easy.
- Are you talking?
- BOY 3: Let's go, let's go.
BOY 4: He ain't goin' nowhere.
He ain't goin' nowhere.
Let's go, Key. Let's go, Key.
PLAYERS CHEERING
- KEENAN: Let's go!
- All the way.
- Why ain't you tighten up, bro?
- Calm down, bro.
Yeah, where you at, Zay?
It's tie game, baby.
- You ain't won yet. Let's go!
- BOY 3: Yo, man.
Come in, come in, come in.
- BOY 3: I'm here.
- Watch, watch. Over here.
BOY 5: What you doing?
Zay. Zay. Watch out.
ISAIAH SCREAMS
- Let's go!
- BOY 3: Let's go, boy.
- Yes, sir!
- BOTH: One, two, three.
- Yo, man.
- Yeah! Hey.
- EXCLAIMS Zay.
- That's game, baby. That's game!
- Yeah. Zay.
GUNSHOTS ON TV
ISAIAH: Hey, Dre,
you got two guys coming in.
ANDRE: I see 'em.
- Yo, Jamal, where you at?
- JAMAL: Yo, I'm pickin' up loot.
Isaiah, can you come help me?
ANDRE: Hey, hey, shots left.
Shots left. Come help me.
Yo, Jamal, build up.
- JAMAL: Oh, he got me.
- CYNTHIA: Isaiah?
Yo, Dre, you got a med kit?
ANDRE: Yeah, cover me.
- BOMB EXPLODES
- GUNSHOTS CONTINUE
Isaiah?
Dude, are you serious?
ANDRE: I'm down, man. He got me.
That's my bad.
He came out of nowhere.
CYNTHIA: Isaiah Tyrone Wright!
JAMAL: Let's run it back, man.
We are not ending on that.
Look, I gotta go.
I'll catch you later.
Could you not hear me?
Uh, I was in the middle
of a game. I can't pause it.
Boy, I don't care nothing
about no games.
You're always
in the middle of a game.
You want to tell me
why our trash can is still full?
Did you at least
start your laundry?
Not yet.
Is your room clean?
No, I'm about to do that
right now.
Okay, listen.
I'm tired of having
this same conversation
over and over again.
You are 19 years old.
That means
it's time for you to step up.
If you don't want to
go to college, that's fine,
but you're gonna get a job,
'cause let me tell you
what you're not gonna do.
You're not gonna sit around here
living off of your mother,
not when you're fully capable
of taking on
some of this responsibility
yourself.
Isaiah, I love you,
but if you're going to
live here,
you're gonna pay me rent here.
You're not gonna spend
all your graduation money
on sneakers and video games.
Rent? You gonna make me pay
to live in my own house?
Your house?
SCOFFS
You are my son,
but I'm giving you one month
to find a job,
or you can find
one of your little friends
that's gonna let you
sleep on they couch for free.
SIGHS
Oh, God, help me.
And help him.
LAUGHS
ISAIAH: Look, I told you, man.
It's been sitting here
since I was nine.
KEENAN EXHALES
Your grandfather drove this?
Well, my mom said it was
in bad shape when he got it.
He was gonna fix it up
with my dad.
Then my dad told me
he was gonna fix it up with me.
And this is the way he left it.
Like everything else.
You know, if I could get
something for it, I'd sell it.
Well, if you looking for a job,
you better find one
that's close.
'Cause you ain't driving this.
Yeah, obviously.
HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING
- Thank you so much.
- Of course, have a blessed day.
You, too.
Excuse me.
Oh. Hi there.
What can I get for you?
Hey, what's your name?
Uh, my name is Abigail.
Is this your first time
in our shop?
Yeah, this is
my first time here,
but, um, you know how to make
good coffee, Abigail?
I mean, our customers
seem to think so.
Uh-huh.
You live around here?
Um, yeah.
But I... I don't really...
- You don't?
- Hi.
Can I help you?
Nah. I mean, you good, man.
I'm just trying to talk
to the young lady right here.
CHUCKLES You feel me?
Hmm. Yeah. That's my daughter.
I'd like to know
if you're interested
in getting a coffee today?
ISAIAH: No.
I mean, to be honest,
it's really not my thing, so...
Hmm. Well,
then you need to move on.
What? Man, you can't just
kick me outta here.
I ain't did nothin' wrong.
Well, like I said, if you're
not here to get coffee today,
then you need to be on your way.
Look, what's your problem, man?
You can't just come out here
and threaten me.
I ain't committing
no crime. Huh?
Do I look like
a criminal to you?
Okay.
Let me tell you something,
I would like for you to leave.
I need for you
to leave my shop right now.
Or what,
you think I'm beneath you? Hmm?
Get out.
Go on.
I'm going.
And I won't be back, either.
Believe that.
HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING
Hi. Can I help you?
Uh, I'd like to apply for a job.
Okay. Well, is there a certain
type of job you're looking for?
Nah, I just, you know,
wanna see what you got.
Okay, well...
Here's an application,
if you'd like to fill it out.
Hello there, young man.
How are you doing today?
I'm good.
You interested
in some fitness equipment?
I don't know, man. Maybe.
Well, I'd be happy
to talk to you if you'd like.
Hey, look, man, I'm just trying
to see about a job, all right?
That's why I'm filling this out.
I ain't here to buy nothing.
What, you a salesman
for this company?
I'm the president.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where you going?
Well, I ain't gonna
get a job now.
What's your name?
SIGHS
Joshua Moore.
Will you tell me your name?
Isaiah.
Good to meet you, Isaiah.
You got lunch plans?
What?
I can buy you lunch.
We could talk?
- Are you being for real?
- I am.
And, Mr. Moore,
would you like your usual today?
You got it.
All right, sounds good.
I will be back shortly.
So,
tell me about yourself, Isaiah.
I mean, I'm 19.
I just need a job, you know.
You have family here?
It's just me and my mom.
She owns a hair salon
off of Heartwood.
College plans?
SIGHS Naw, that ain't me.
LAUGHS Okay. Well...
five years from now,
where do you wanna be?
Five years? Um...
I don't know. I'm just
taking it a day at a time.
Well, Isaiah...
if you're available to work,
we can discuss options
in my company.
But I want to ask you
a few questions first.
Now, if you wanna take some time
to think about your answers,
we can get together and talk
again when you're ready.
My questions are these.
In what ways do you want to grow
in the next year?
What kind of man
do you want to be?
And what do you want
people to think
when they see you coming?
I'll tell you what I think.
You either help at home
to the degree
you adding value like a job,
or you get a job
that funds the value
of your home to the degree
it equals the work at home
you would have done.
- Yes, ma'am.
- CYNTHIA: Girl, what?
You lost me. You're gonna
have to say that again.
KEISHA: Cynthia.
Honey, I agree.
You need to draw a line
in the sand.
Well, I'm just trying
to figure out how to balance
helping him know
I understand him,
but still pushing him
to become an adult.
And that is not easy.
You're on the right track, girl.
He's got to step up
and step out,
'cause you can step in
and speak up about him
not stepping up,
but you don't want to overstep
the main step of loving him.
Yes, ma'am. That's exactly
what I was thinking, girl.
Okay. You two must be
at a higher level,
but I'mma catch up.
Oh. Here he comes now.
- WOMAN: Hey, Isaiah.
- Hey.
Isaiah, you walk here?
Oh, it's just one mile
from the house.
But, um, I need to use your car.
I found a couple places online
that are hiring, so...
Well, okay, but I need you
back here by 5:00.
I'm picking up a case of product
from Maxwell's at 5:15,
and they're staying open late
for me.
- So, you can't be late.
- I won't.
Isaiah. Five o'clock.
I'll be here.
- I'm not playing with you.
- ISAIAH: Yes, ma'am.
- Bye, Isaiah.
- ISAIAH: Bye, y'all.
Cute boy.
He sure favors his daddy.
KEISHA: Hmm, he do.
Oh, ain't he working
as a truck driver now?
Girl, I don't know
what Darren is doing.
I don't wanna talk
about no Darren.
LAUGHS
CELL PHONE RINGING
- Yo, Jamal.
- JAMAL: What's up, man?
We're heading to the park.
Come ball with us.
Look, nah, man. Nah.
I'm looking for a job.
\an8Dude, you can do that any time.
We need you for two-on-two.
\an8Look, naw, man.
I can't right now.
Come on, Zay.
Just give me an hour.
\an8Look, one hour, man.
RAP MUSIC PLAYING
- JAMAL: Zay, break the screen.
- No. No.
He can't shoot. He can't shoot.
He can't shoot.
RINGING
ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY
RINGING CONTINUES
What you gonna do, man?
No.
WHOOPS
- ANDRE: Come on. Come on.
- There we go.
Hey, that's two up.
Next game wins.
All right, let's run it back.
Come on, baby!
- ANDRE: Come on. Come on.
- JAMAL: In the post.
Hey, hold on.
Hold up, what time is it?
I don't know.
I left my phone in the car.
Yo, I gotta go!
Yo, Zay.
- Zay, we got one more game, bro.
- ANDRE: Come on, Zay.
Zay!
- Come on, Zay.
- Hey, that means we won.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, I...
- I lost track of time.
- I'm driving.
It's 5:39.
Maxwell's stayed open
for 30 extra minutes,
only to have me not show up.
And now,
now I gotta push back
my appointments,
and I have to hope...
Oh, boy, you better hope
they give me
the same discount tomorrow
they were planning
on giving me today.
I called them three times
asking them
for five extra minutes.
- Five extra minutes.
- Mom, I said I was sorry.
I let you use my car.
You turned around
and made me look irresponsible.
And why are you so sweaty?
LAUGHS IN DISBELIEF
Oh, no, you didn't.
No, you didn't.
You lied to me?
You told me you were
going to look for a job.
I was. They were closed.
What am I supposed to do?
What are you...
You're supposed to keep looking!
Not give up at
the first sign of inconvenience.
That's something right there
your father would do.
- Well, I ain't him!
- You acting like him.
Boy.
Ooh.
CYNTHIA: I don't know, Liz.
I mean, seriously,
there are moments
when I just feel like
I'm gonna lose it.
Yeah, I mean, I love that boy
with my whole heart,
but I literally cannot be
his mother and his father.
No, I get it. I do get it.
Yeah, I'm just...
I'm asking you to pray for him.
And for me.
Our top three
distribution accounts
are the same as last year.
GymFit is still number one
at 4.5 million a year.
But with their president
stepping down,
that's also our main concern.
Our five-year agreement
with them is up next summer.
Yeah. Any word on their vote?
They haven't announced
anything yet,
but we're ready to connect
as soon as they do.
If we lose
that GymFit account...
If we lose the GymFit account,
I'd say you have
about four months
before you'd have to start
making some difficult choices.
One more thing
I need to bring up.
Slayer Sports,
they're developing
a line of niche equipment
that will directly
compete with us.
I don't know
how soon they'll be ready,
but we need
to keep an eye on them.
Hey, I agree.
- Thank you, Emmett.
- No problem.
- KNOCK ON DOOR
- RECEPTIONIST: Mr. Moore.
There's a young man,
Isaiah Wright, here to see you.
- Yes, I'll be right out.
- RECEPTIONIST: Okay.
Isaiah?
How are you?
Oh. I'm good.
Uh, I just wanted to talk to you
for a minute.
I've been thinking
about your questions.
Okay. I'd love
to hear your thoughts.
Yeah. Um...
You know, as far as, you know,
how I wanna grow this next year,
I guess, you know, I wanna learn
to take on more responsibility
and, you know,
learn some new skills.
That's good.
And then you asked,
you know,
what kind of man I wanna be,
and I want to be a good man,
you know,
someone that can
get the job done.
Also, you asked, um,
you know,
what I want people to think,
when they see me coming.
And, um, I want them to see
someone they respect. So...
Yeah, that's, uh... That's it.
Okay.
So, are you looking
for full-time work or part-time?
Uh...
Well, CLICKS TONGUE
start part-time.
Okay.
Would you be willing
to meet with me twice a week
for some mentoring
before your shift starts?
Mentoring? Like for this job?
Well, yes.
But also, some life principles.
Things that you could use
no matter where you're working.
I mean, yeah.
CHUCKLES I guess.
Yeah.
Well, let's go
to the factory floor
and I'll show you
what we have available.
I'll connect you with a manager
and finish
the interview process.
- Cool.
- Good?
- Yeah.
- All right.
So, what happens in here?
Well, I'll show you the packing
and shipping division first.
Division? CHUCKLES
How big is this place?
BEEPS
Oh.
We make 205 different products
for the fitness arena.
Weights, treadmills, jump ropes,
almost everything in between.
We store the pieces
and then we supply distributors
with all the parts
to assemble and sell.
Each day, we fill
600 to 800 orders.
How many people work here?
JOSHUA: In this area, 24.
Todd.
- How you doing?
- Mr. Moore, I'm fine.
- How are you?
- I am good, thank you.
This is Isaiah Wright.
When you have the time,
I want you to take him
through the interview process
for part-time work.
Okay.
I'll show him around
and bring him back to you.
Yes, sir.
It's taken me 21 years
to get here.
It's been hard,
but God's been good.
- Yeah.
- MACHINE BEEPS
Oh.
CHUCKLES It's not gonna
run into you,
the scanners will see you
and stop the cart.
Yo, that's... that's crazy, man.
How many of these you got?
We got 10 floor robots
and 75 storage robots,
all programmed by our engineers.
- Oh, nice. Nice.
- Come on.
Take a look.
I ain't never seen
nothing like this.
Cody.
How are they rolling?
Well, none of them
called in sick today,
- so I'm feeling pretty good.
- BOTH LAUGH
This is Isaiah.
Give him a quick explanation
of the system.
- Hey, man. Uh...
- Oh.
Yeah.
Well, CLEARS THROAT basically,
when an order comes in,
one of the bots will pick it up
and take it over
to its specific port.
And then it'll go down
to a conveyer belt
and be placed in a box
that's specifically designed
for that product.
And then it's then labeled
and stacked for shipping.
They're like my best friends.
LAUGHS You got all that?
- Um, yeah.
- LAUGHS
- Thank you, Cody.
- Uh, yes, sir.
- Keep it up.
- Yeah.
- Come on, follow me.
- Good to see you.
- Janelle?
- Yes?
May I introduce you to someone?
Of course.
- Hello there.
- This is Isaiah Wright.
We're talking about him
working part-time with us.
- Nice to meet you, Isaiah.
- Good to meet you.
Janelle oversees
the human resources department.
She has put up with me
since the first day we opened,
and knows about just as much
as I do around here.
But I don't work
as many hours as he does.
And he needs to learn to push
the pause button sometime
and come home with me.
We've also been married
for 35 years.
ALL LAUGHING
- Gotcha.
- JANELLE: Gotcha.
Yeah, you should have
seen your face. LAUGHING
That's what's up.
TODD: And our
only part-time opening
is Monday, Wednesdays,
and Fridays from 9:00 to 5:00.
- That'll work?
- Yeah.
Okay. Your training starts
on Monday. Please, be on time.
It takes everyone here
to stay on track.
And this is your key card.
Don't lose it.
SIZZLING
- Hey.
What'd you do today?
Not much.
Just stopped by Moore Fitness.
Moore Fitness?
Why?
You know, they were,
you know, hiring some guy. Yeah.
Who?
This guy. LAUGHS
Oh, my goodness!
Isaiah,
- you got a job at Moore Fitness?
- Yes, ma'am.
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
- When do you start?
- 9:00 a.m. Monday.
That's what I'm talking about.
You have made my day.
Ooh. Do you know that
he helped your Uncle Tony
for several years?
- Uncle T? Uncle Tony?
- Mm-hmm.
He discipled him, helped him
with his work and stuff.
Discipled him?
What does that mean?
You know,
it's like when one person...
It's... It's kind of...
You need to
come to church with me.
Ma, we already
talked about this.
Church? That's...
That's your thing.
Isaiah, God wants you
to know Him.
And I ain't hiding from Him.
I'm right here and He can
find me if he wants to.
But I ain't gotta go to a church
building for Him to see me.
Okay, okay.
Are you gonna see Mr. Moore
very frequently on your job?
Yeah. He wants to meet,
you know, twice a week
before my shift for mentoring.
- Something like that.
- Oh.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Dinner will be ready
in 10 minutes.
All right.
Oh, Lord. I see what you're
doing. I see what you're doing.
I see you working. Ooh!
Oh, draw him to you, Lord.
Just draw him to you.
JOSHUA: I want each employee
to remember...
I'm responsible
for this company.
And I want those
under my leadership
to help me do well.
The same way
that they will want others
under their leadership to help
them do well in the future.
So, treat others the way
you want to be treated.
Even if you don't like them,
give those in authority
the same respect
that you'd want them
to give you.
Got it?
Yeah. I got it.
All right, this is where
the magic happens.
- Wanda has to make sure...
- Hi.
...that each box
is properly sealed for delivery.
Then, Diego and Carlos,
they add a label and they stack
each box for shipping.
But each of them
knows how to work every station,
so they can rotate if need be.
- Hey, man.
- ISAIAH: What's up?
SPEAKING SPANISH
IN ENGLISH So, we're gonna
start you in this section
for now.
I want you to watch these guys
and try it out for experience.
Then once you get
the hang of it,
we'll move you
to the next section.
Come on, let's get you started.
GUNS FIRING ON TV
Isaiah, you've been
on that game all day.
It was my day off.
Don't you have work tomorrow?
Uh, yeah. I... I got it.
Boy, it's after midnight.
- Ma, I got it.
- GUNS FIRING
SIGHS
CELL PHONE VIBRATING
GRUNTS
GASPS
INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING
GRUNTS Come on, man.
Thank you.
Hey, sorry, man.
I can... I can take over.
You got an emergency?
Nah, man. It's my bad.
- Where's your work vest?
- Oh.
- Yeah. I gotta go get that.
- Have you even clocked in yet?
Not yet.
Isaiah, you're 45 minutes late
and it's your third day.
I can't do my job
when I'm covering for you!
No, and it doesn't matter.
LeBron has a championship
with every team he's played for.
Okay, how is that impressive?
Okay, Jordan made it
to the Finals six times.
How many times did he win?
- Six times!
MAN: Only with the Bulls, okay?
LeBron won with Miami,
Cleveland...
Isaiah, Mr. Moore would like to
see you in the conference room.
CURTIS: Okay,
Michael Jeffrey Jordan
elevated the whole
basketball game.
This is way more aggressive
than we expected.
I mean, it is a smaller account.
It's 40,000 a year,
so it won't hurt us much.
But we need to shore up
our larger accounts.
Yeah.
I had never even heard
of Slayer Sports six months ago.
They've got backing
and they're hungry.
But we don't need them
taking more from us,
so I'll keep you updated.
I had breakfast for you
this morning.
What happened?
I, um...
I overslept.
I forgot to set my alarm.
Okay.
Well, you have a lukewarm
breakfast burrito, orange juice
and cold hash browns
if you want.
Nah, nah. I'm good.
You know, actually,
I'm starving, so...
Some thoughts for today.
When you miss your commitments,
it's hard not to see it
as disrespectful.
When you're 45 minutes
late for work,
it forces people
to have to cover for you.
And if you have a good reason,
they'll be fine.
If not,
they'll feel disrespected.
You don't need people wondering
if you can do your job.
You need them believing
that you can do your job,
and respecting you
for doing it well.
So, let me be blunt.
A big part of becoming a man
is showing up.
Can you do that, Isaiah?
Yes, sir.
So, I suggest that
you plan ahead.
Get the rest you need,
set your alarm,
and give yourself
the time to get here.
That shows respect for others.
And whenever
you're supposed to be here,
show up.
WOMAN: He just started
working there?
CYNTHIA: Yes!
And he didn't even wanna tell me
what happened yesterday.
But you know what? I could tell
by the look on his face
that something was wrong.
See, when it's your child,
you can tell it on their face.
All I'm saying is Darren was
way too flippant with his jobs
and he kept losing 'em.
So, I'mma tell you
what I'm not gonna do
is sit by and watch Isaiah
start doing the same thing.
- KEISHA: Right.
- It's not happening.
He's already dealing
with so much anger
in his heart towards his father,
so, seriously,
I just need some prayer support.
That's why
you called your sister.
Yeah. That's exactly why.
She's gonna be here any minute.
And I'm so glad
'cause I need to see her.
DANIELLE: Hey, Aunt Cynthia.
Danielle! Oh, my goodness.
I did not know that you were
coming. What a surprise.
I thought you were at college.
Girl, how are you doing?
DANIELLE: I'm good.
I'm just on break.
- Mom's parking the car.
- Okay. All right.
- Hey, Danielle baby.
- Hey.
CYNTHIA: Elizabeth! Oh!
ELIZABETH: Hey, sis.
Girl, it is so good to see you.
It has been too long.
I love it when my sister
comes to see me.
Okay, have a seat.
I'mma get you a cup of coffee.
ELIZABETH: Thank you.
Hey, ladies.
- How are y'all doing?
- Hey there.
- Honey, that bag.
- ELIZABETH: Good to see y'all.
And them pants,
my thighs can't get in.
WOMAN: Stop it.
Now, Danielle,
do you still like caramel?
- You remembered.
- Of course I did.
- Now, Liz, is she coming?
- Thank you. Yes, she's here.
She's just in the car
finishing up a phone call.
So, who is this again?
Well, when my sister tells me
that she needs prayer support,
honey, I bring prayer support.
CLARA: Hey.
Am I in the right place?
Miss Clara. Yes, you are.
- I'm so glad to see you.
- Oh.
Hello, sweet Cynthia.
How you doing, darling?
I'm doing better
now that you're here.
- Please, come sit with us.
- Okay. All right, darling.
So, Isaiah is not running away
from responsibility.
He just hasn't learned
how to embrace it.
That's good.
He gotta embrace it.
But what I'm saying is
he hasn't had a good man
in the home to be a role model.
So, he just sees me
taking care of everything,
but no matter how much I do,
it's hard for a woman
to call out the man in her son.
- KEISHA: True.
- You know, Tony's been helpful,
but he lives an hour away
on the other side of Charlotte.
I just want to cover him
in prayer.
But it's not like
it's an emergency.
Like, he has time.
We don't have to act like
this is overly urgent, right?
Oh, yes, we do, dear heart.
We can't treat prayer
like it's some spare tire
that you only pull out
in an emergency. No.
Prayer has to be
more like the steering wheel
that you hold tightly every day,
no matter where you are going.
Mm-hmm. Now, that's good.
That's good.
Well, look,
all I meant was that...
Shh. Listen,
shut your mouth now.
This woman
is on a whole 'nother level.
- Okay.
- Well, if I may...
I suggest that we start
by praising the Lord
for who He is.
ELIZABETH: Hallelujah.
And then we pray that the Lord
will open Isaiah's eyes
so that he could see himself
the way that the Lord sees him.
And that he would
realize his need for the Lord.
And that the Lord
would capture his heart...
KEISHA: Yes.
...and build him up
to be the man
that the Lord wants him to be.
Mm-hmm! Now, that is good!
Miss Clara, I need you
to come by here more often.
Keisha needs you.
- CLARA: And anyone, Lord...
- WOMAN: Thank you.
...that the enemy might
try to use to pull him away.
WOMAN: Yes. Do it, Father.
Yes, Father, thank you.
CLARA: Lord, put your hand
on his life...
WOMAN: Yes.
- CLARA: ...and help him, God.
- Hey, can I help you?
Yeah, is this a hair salon
or a prayer salon?
- CLARA: Lord, stir him up.
- CYNTHIA: Well, today it's both.
What do you need?
CLARA: Stir him up
to want to know you, Jesus.
- I need both.
- CLARA: Yes.
Girl, you wanna join us?
- Yeah, my edges need to be...
- Come.
- ...delivered and set free.
- Come on.
I need both.
Whoa. Isaiah is in the building.
- Hey.
- You're 15 minutes early.
Yeah, trying not to be
late again.
No, we're not gonna
do that again.
- No. No, sir.
- All right, guess what?
You've got a hot breakfast
this time.
Okay. Yeah, I could smell it
from the parking lot.
- From the parking lot?
- Hey.
BOTH LAUGHING
So, eventually,
I learned to listen.
It's embarrassing
to think about it now.
How at 24, I thought I could
have figured out life by myself.
But when you fall on your face
as many times as I did,
you finally realize
it's better to learn from
the mistakes of other people
than to continually
make your own.
- LAUGHS
- Yeah, I get that.
Oh, man, I used to get
into arguments all the time.
I thought I looked like a big
man, standing my ground.
Then my mother said something
to me that I've never forgotten.
She said,
"You need to be
more of a fountain than a drain,
"and you need to start giving
more than you're taking."
The more I thought about it...
I was using people
to reach my own goals,
without loving them at all.
And that's the thought
that I have for you today.
Adopt that mentality.
Be a fountain, not a drain.
I want to read you something.
It's out of Galatians 5.
"For you have been
called to live in freedom,
"my brothers and sisters.
"But don't use your freedom
to satisfy your sinful nature.
"Instead, use your freedom
to serve one another in love.
"For the whole law can be summed
up in this one command.
"Love your neighbor
as yourself."
What do you mean
by "sinful nature"?
Hmm.
Well, the Bible tells us
that we all
have a sinful nature.
Selfishness, pride,
greed, bitterness.
Yet God still loves us.
So, he sent his son, Jesus,
to die on the cross
to pay the debt
that we owed for sin.
Then he raised Jesus
from the dead,
so that we could be in
a right relationship with Him,
if we put our faith in Jesus.
He is our way to freedom.
When we follow Jesus
and devote ourselves to him,
he bears fruit through us
that gives God glory.
Love, joy, peace,
patience, kindness,
goodness, faithfulness,
gentleness, self-control.
Hmm.
That's what He wants us to do.
That's the kind of man
I want to be.
I'll tell you what.
If you're interested,
join me this Saturday.
My church
has an outreach downtown.
Every month, we get together
and we give out food
to people who are struggling.
We usually start at 9:00.
You do this?
Every month. We help sponsor it.
Come on, man.
Hey, if you'd like,
I'll pick you up.
Yeah. I'm down.
All right. LAUGHS
CHRISTIAN HIP-HOP MUSIC
PLAYING
INAUDIBLE
Hey, you okay?
Yeah. I, uh...
I just never did
anything like this before.
- JOSHUA LAUGHS
- Well, you did good.
A lot of people
got helped today.
Isaiah, you want to
join us for dinner?
It's my turn to cook.
I'm not as good as Janelle,
but it shouldn't be too bad.
Don't believe that.
He's very good.
- Hey, yeah, I'm down.
- Well, you guys wait here.
I'll get the car
and we'll head to the house.
JANELLE: Sometimes
being the president
means business calls
on the weekend.
No, I understand.
Hey, who's this?
That is our son Jalen.
Oh, what? I didn't know
you had a son.
I mean, where's he at?
Jalen died at 17.
Oh, I'm...
I'm sorry. I...
I didn't realize.
It's okay, Isaiah.
When Jalen was growing up,
Joshua was so driven in business
to be a success.
And it tested our marriage.
One evening, Jalen went to ride
with his friends to a party,
and a drunk driver
ran a red light
and hit them on his side.
We never got to say goodbye.
For a while,
Joshua blamed everybody,
even me.
It almost ended our marriage.
One of the older men
in our church,
a mechanic,
reached out to Joshua
and started meeting with him.
And he helped Joshua
reshape his entire view
of life and faith
according to the Bible.
And that's when I saw my husband
become a disciple
of Jesus Christ.
It changed him.
So, we don't just
call ourselves Christians.
We are devoted to Jesus.
And we will do anything
He calls us to do.
"For all have sinned
"and fall short
of the glory of God.
"But God demonstrates
His own love for us in this...
"while we were still sinners,
Christ died for us.
"For the wages of sin is death,
"but the gift of God
is eternal life
"in Christ Jesus our Lord.
"If you declare with your mouth
'Jesus is Lord'
"and believe in your heart
"that God raised him
from the dead,
"you will be saved.
"For it is with your heart
that you believe,
"and it is with your mouth
"that you profess your faith
and are saved.
\an8"For everyone who calls
on the name of the Lord
\an8"will be saved."
EXHALES DEEPLY
Help me, Jesus.
Isaiah?
Hey, I'm sorry I'm so late.
I got a plate for you.
Nah, it's cool.
I was with your aunt and a bunch
of women at the salon
and we were praying
and I just completely
lost track of time.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Um...
I was, uh...
I was praying, too.
What were you praying about?
Um...
You know, um...
I've been trying
to figure things out...
by myself...
and now I realize that, uh...
I need Jesus.
You know, to save me and...
Yeah, so I asked Him.
Isaiah.
Oh, Isaiah, I've been
praying about this.
Praise the Lord.
Oh, thank you, Jesus.
Oh, my goodness.
Okay. Oh, my goodness.
I've been looking forward
to this for so long.
- I'm sorry. I just...
- All right. It's cool. Um...
EXHALES
I don't know what took me
so long. You know?
Do you know
what we were praying for?
What?
We were praying for you.
Thanks, Ma. I love you.
I love you so much, baby.
I love you so much.
INAUDIBLE
ISAIAH: Hey.
- GRUNTS ENTHUSIASTICALLY
- Yeah.
LAUGHS
Isaiah.
You are my brother in Christ.
All right, all right,
but there's more, right?
Well, yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yes.
Well, you should be baptized.
And we need to talk
about discipleship.
Yeah, I want to talk about that.
So, I read, like, half
the New Testament yesterday,
and, you know, all of the faith,
miracle stuff
was done by disciples
or people close to Jesus.
So, if I'm doing this,
I want all of it.
Not many people think the way
that you're thinking.
People want salvation,
believing in Jesus.
But very few people want
to follow him into discipleship.
Why?
There's a cost to discipleship.
Jesus says in Luke Chapter 9...
"Whoever wants to be my disciple
"must deny themselves,
take up their cross daily,
"and follow me."
"Take up your cross daily,"
what does that mean?
That means
something's gonna die.
It could be habits,
agenda, goals...
whatever stands in the way
of your relationship with him,
your obedience to him.
Your main priority as a disciple
is not living
to please yourself,
it's living for Him.
Being devoted to Him,
knowing Him.
When I put my faith in Jesus,
I became a Christian.
Then I wanted to grow
as a disciple,
but I had so many other things
in my life.
It's as if
my plate was already full.
But he did something CHUCKLES
that I just didn't expect.
What?
He asked me to give up golf.
Golf? That...
That ain't a bad thing.
No, it's not.
But I loved it.
It had too high of a priority
in my life.
I played every chance I got,
and one day, the Lord
reminded me of my request,
and I realized
I wasn't making any more room
for Him in my life.
So, I gave up
my devotion to golf
and replaced it with more time
with Him and His Word.
I went from playing
two to three times a week
to two to three times a year.
What? CHUCKLES
I'll say this...
there's a cost
to following Jesus,
but it is a hundred percent
worth it.
Hmm.
And He died for me,
so how could He not be
worth everything?
He's worth everything.
You know what?
I want to introduce you
to a small group of men
that mean the world to me.
I think you'd enjoy
meeting them.
Yeah.
Let's do a quick
greeting exercise.
Come on. Stand up here with me.
A greeting exercise?
Come on.
When I met you,
I could barely get you
to look at me in the eye
and give me a handshake.
We're gonna practice that
right now.
- CLEARS THROAT
- Are you for real?
Walk up to me
and introduce yourself.
- Hey, I'm Isaiah.
- BOTH LAUGH
Okay, okay.
I guess that's all right.
Something to remember.
When you meet someone,
you're communicating something
about yourself
and how you see them.
Everyone wants to be valued.
Men, especially,
want to be respected.
So, when you greet someone,
look at them in the eye
as a confident young man.
Not arrogantly, but confidently.
Say your name,
give them a strong handshake,
and then respect them
by learning their name.
Okay.
We're gonna do that
like it's the first time.
Okay.
Hello, sir. I'm Isaiah Wright.
Nice to meet you, Isaiah.
I'm Joshua Moore.
Good to meet you, Mr. Moore.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Much better.
Much better. LAUGHS
BEEPING
Wow. You're getting really good
at this, Isaiah.
Well, not as good as you.
You're the fastest one
here, Wanda.
TODD: Okay, Isaiah.
- You're doing pretty good here.
- Thanks, man.
Let's move you to a new section,
get you some more experience.
Follow me.
WANDA: Whoo-hoo! LAUGHS
- SPEAKS SPANISH
- IN ENGLISH Hey, man.
WANDA: Aw!
JOSHUA: Honey, I'm leaving.
Do the guys
know that he's coming?
They do.
- I'm excited for him.
- Me, too. I'm picking him up.
JANELLE: Mm.
- I love you, woman.
- CHUCKLES I love you, too.
I'll be praying for you.
JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING
Hey, you're gonna enjoy tonight.
Good evening, Mr. Moore.
How are you, sir?
- I'm good, Amy. And you?
- Fine, thank you.
Your guests are here.
I can take you back if you like.
That'd be great.
Thank you, Amy.
- Thanks.
- INDISTINCT CHATTER
- There he is.
- JOSHUA: Hey, Tony.
- TONY: That's my guy.
- LAUGHS
- Good to see you, bro.
- Good to see you too, man.
- How you doing?
- I'm just trying to keep up.
- Come on now. Check you out.
- Just trying to keep up.
- What's up, Zay?
- Uncle Tony.
- BOTH LAUGH
- Man, it's good to see you.
Your mother told us about
the big decision that you made.
- And now you're here.
- Yeah.
- Couldn't be more proud.
- Thank you.
You know, my head's been
spinning like crazy,
but I've been
learning a lot, so...
Yeah, well, you're about
to learn a whole lot more.
- I'm excited.
- Yeah, man. Come on.
Well, gentlemen,
this is a good day.
- ALL: Yeah. It is.
- MAN: Yes, sir.
I want to introduce you
to Isaiah Wright,
who just started working
at Moore Fitness, just recently.
And as of a few days ago
is your brother in Christ.
EXCITED CHATTER
Let's go around our circle
and introduce ourselves.
Well, I'm his uncle,
so he already knows me.
But, Isaiah,
this is Trey and Deon.
- Good to see you.
- DEON: Nice to meet you.
And the gentleman standing
next to them is Benjamin.
But we just call him "Coach B."
We coach these guys
on the football field
and we keep up with them
at the youth group
in church, so...
Isaiah, nice to meet you, man.
- Welcome. Welcome.
- ISAIAH: What's up, Coach?
ALL LAUGH
Isaiah, I'm Jonathan.
I'm on staff
at New Hope Community Church,
and I got my little bro, Levi,
here with me.
He's one
of our college students.
- Nice to meet you, man.
- What's up, bro?
Isaiah, I'm Vaughn,
financial advisor.
And here I have with me
my son, Jerry.
- Nice to meet you, bro.
- Yo, that's the money guy now.
So, if you need anything,
that's where you go.
- You gotta know him.
- VAUGHN: I got you.
My name's Bobby
and I'm a family counselor.
This is Ethan.
And about two weeks ago,
he asked Jesus into his heart.
- Yeah.
- Yes, yes.
And I'm James,
retired military and now I do
a little bit of real estate,
but this is my son, KJ.
And I want to tell you, man,
thank you for helping
with the food distribution
last Saturday.
Brothers, this dude
was working hard.
So, man, we appreciate you, man.
That's right. Good stuff,
good stuff. Very true.
Well, Isaiah,
we are a growing group.
Each man here has strengths
that he invests in other men.
We eat together,
we pray together,
encourage one another,
and we keep
each other accountable
as we follow Jesus.
Isaiah, welcome to The Forge.
INAUDIBLE
TONY: I'm praying, right?
I prayed all night,
and I'm thinking,
"Man, why would God
bring me this far,
"only to come to a financial gap
that was impossible to cross?"
- MAN: That's right.
- TONY: So, I'm confused
but I kept seeking Him.
TAPS TABLE
That's when Hebrews 11:6
just jumped off the page
and punched me in the face.
- ALL LAUGH
- This is where it says,
"Without faith, it's impossible
to please God..."
Yeah. Talk to Him.
"...because anyone
who comes to Him
"must believe that He exists
"and that He rewards those
who earnestly seek Him."
So, I'm thinking about that,
I'm like, man, I realized,
sometimes God allows
these gaps on purpose
because if I could
figure it out for myself,
you know, I'm taking the credit.
ALL LAUGHING
But He will do it in a way
where only He gets the glory.
- Yeah.
- ALL: Mm-hmm.
Fellas, if you're earnestly
seeking him,
then don't be afraid
of the gaps.
- JONATHAN: Yeah.
- That's good.
- BOBBY: Right there.
- That'll preach right here.
That's good stuff,
good stuff, good stuff.
All right, Bobby,
what has God shown you lately?
CHUCKLES You're gonna make me
follow that?
- JOSHUA: Oh, you got to.
- ALL LAUGH
How long y'all been
meeting like this?
- BOBBY: You know, I think God...
- Say what?
How long y'all been
meeting like this?
Oh, man,
Joshua discipled each
of the older guys in this room.
Did it over the last 15 years,
including me several years ago.
He spends about two years
with each guy,
you know,
teaching them how to walk,
walk with the Lord, you know?
But then he encourages us
to invest in someone else
to do the same thing.
So, all the guys
you see in this room,
we're discipling someone, too,
just like he did us.
You know,
just helping them to mold
and shape their faith
and character.
So, that's why we call it
"The Forge," man.
It's just a bunch of guys
who come together,
we grow together,
we eat together.
We share a meal like this
every two weeks, man.
It's one of the most
important things
I've ever done in my life.
- Hmm.
- Glad you're here, man.
INAUDIBLE
"How can a young person
stay pure?
"By obeying your Word.
"I have tried hard to find you,
"don't let me wander
from your commands.
"I have hidden your Word
in my heart,
"that I might not sin
against you."
Lord...
SIGHS
how can I put you first?
Is there anything
I need to get out of the way?
SIGHING Oh.
No.
Oh, come on. Not that.
I know I'm addicted to it,
all right?
Either you're a Lord
or you're not.
And I say...
you're a Lord.
UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING
EXHALES All right. What else?
Let's see what we got here.
All right. Delete.
Deleted.
SIGHS
Yeah, you gotta go.
All right,
you definitely gotta go.
How many I got?
Yo, Jamal.
JAMAL: Dude, we ain't seen you
in three weeks.
We ballin' in 10. You coming?
Yeah. I'm off today. I'm coming.
Oh, it's about time.
All right.
LAUGHING
My son!
He's growing up.
Oh, he's growing up.
MUSIC STOPS
Hey, Isaiah.
Hey, what's that?
This is a portable solar panel.
One of our mission products.
Mission products?
It's the ones you ship out
every now and then, every...
Along with the water filters,
the lanterns, tents,
first aid kits.
I didn't know
this was part of the business.
Well, that's not for profit.
These are given away.
For real?
- Yeah.
- CHUCKLES
So, Moore Fitness functions
off of 90% of its income.
The other 10% is invested
in products like these
for missions
and medical teams, ministry.
That's why
I respect Joshua so much,
even though it sometimes
makes the budget numbers
a little tighter
than I'm used to.
But that's why we have to keep
our top accounts healthy.
They fund all this.
And this is where
you've sent them to?
EMMETT: Forty-six countries
so far.
I mean, he's helped teams
to dig wells and plant gardens,
do flood recovery,
and share the gospel.
That is the mission account.
Hmm.
This is a lot of thank yous.
That's just a sample.
We've gotten thousands.
ISAIAH: Wow.
TODD: So, your job is to confirm
that the order's ready
for pickup
and let the driver sign off
when his truck is loaded
and just follow the form.
JOSHUA: Okay, he's rolling up.
Remember, greet the driver,
'cause sometimes
they need encouragement, too.
Be a fountain, not a drain.
You've got this.
Isaiah.
Get the driver.
TODD: Just, uh...
So, uh...
JOSHUA: Isaiah.
That's... That's my dad.
Let's just go to my office.
Come on.
BREATHING HEAVILY
Look, I'm sorry, man. I...
I didn't mean
to mess up the shipment.
Todd's got it. It's fine.
Hey, come sit with me.
SIGHS
I told myself,
"If I ever saw him again...
"I'd be cool," you know.
He made all these promises.
You know, stop drinking,
get a job,
fix the car,
pick me up from practice.
All lies!
CRYING
I remember...
coming home from school,
and, you know, Mom's crying
and I didn't know what happened.
But after a few days,
I realized,
you know,
he left for good this time.
He took all the money,
and I tried calling him,
left messages,
texted him, and, um...
he never responded.
Then my mom finds out
he cheated on her,
and EXHALES that hurt her.
Man, I wanted
to punch him in the face!
SOBBING
I'm sorry, man.
EXHALES
I know...
what it's like to be angry.
I wanted to get back
at the man who killed my son.
I hated him.
I wanted him to rot in his cell.
- But God sees everything.
- SCOFFS
He sees everything.
And He is the perfect judge.
And he said, "Vengeance is mine,
"I will repay."
But I wouldn't let it go.
So,
I asked God to help me...
and then I made the hardest
decision that I've ever made.
I gave it to God.
And I forgave.
Not because I felt like it.
God has forgiven me of so much.
Who was I to refuse to forgive?
Who am I to ignore what Jesus
did for me on the cross?
So, I'm just
supposed to forgive? Huh?
If you hang on to it...
it's gonna poison you.
EXHALES
When I chose to forgive
and give it to God to handle...
it was like a parking brake
was taken off my life.
And he started
to replace all my pain
with healing.
Look, I have no father.
Yes, you do.
When you gave your life
to Christ,
you became right with God.
And God is not like your daddy.
God is the perfect father.
And God loves you, Isaiah.
He loves you more than you know.
You can trust him.
He loves you deeply.
So, what am I supposed to do?
Trust your perfect
heavenly father...
with your earthly dad.
Choose to forgive.
Not by feelings, by choice.
ISAIAH EXHALES
This is my first journal...
when I decided that
I was going to be
a disciple of Christ...
that I used to help me
want to forgive.
But this is your journal.
Yes, and it's full
of scriptures.
And everything that
God was showing me.
Read it.
JOSHUA: "Repay no one evil
for evil...
"but give thought
"to do what is honorable
in the sight of all.
"Do not say,
'I will repay evil.'
"Wait for the Lord,
and He will deliver you.
"But if you refuse
to forgive others,
"your father
will not forgive your sins.
"The anger of man
does not produce
"the righteousness of God.
"God opposes the proud,
but gives grace to the humble.
"So humble yourselves
under the mighty power of God,
"and at the right time,
He will lift you up in honor.
"Give all your worries
and cares to God,
"for He cares about you.
"Stay alert. Watch out
for your great enemy, the devil.
"He prowls around
like a roaring lion,
"looking for someone to devour.
"In his kindness, God called you
to share in His eternal glory
"by means of Christ Jesus.
"So after you have suffered
a little while,
"He will restore, support,
and strengthen you,
"and He will place you
on a firm foundation.
"All power to Him forever.
Amen."
SIGHS
Okay, Lord. Okay, Jesus.
You've seen everything.
You saw what he did.
You saw what he took.
And you heard what he said!
CRYING But I don't want
to carry this anymore.
I don't want to be bitter.
SOBBING
So, Jesus...
I give it to you.
I choose...
SIGHS
GRUNTING
...I choose to forgive!
I forgive my dad.
I forgive him,
but I ask that you show him
where he stands with you.
You meet him where he's at!
But please, please...
clean me out.
Clean out my heart.
And Lord, please...
bless my mother.
Heal her. Comfort her.
Strengthen her. Protect her.
Walk with her!
Because, Jesus,
you know I love her.
SOBBING
SIGHS
Lord...
you've seen
what she's done for me.
You've heard the prayers
that she's prayed for me.
And you've seen
what she's been through, Lord.
So I ask that you bless her.
And do what you want to do.
And I thank you in advance.
I praise you.
And I worship you, Lord.
BREATH SHAKING
'Cause you are my hope.
You are my strength.
And you...
You are my father.
Thank you. Thank you, Jesus.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Give it to me.
Give it to me, Lord.
SOBBING
Give it to me.
- Thank you, Bobby.
- Yeah.
The gentleman
who took me through
two years of discipleship
showed me an example of my need
for more brothers in Christ.
I'd like to share
that example with you.
Isaiah, step out, please.
Now, this was shaped
with intense heat and pressure
in a forge.
It weighs about 10 pounds.
Take this sword
and hold it out straight.
The more time we spend
with the Word of God in prayer,
following the Lord...
the stronger we get.
Ephesians 6 tells us
that the Word of God
is our sword of the Spirit.
It is our primary weapon.
Now, at first...
you'll feel strong and ready,
able to stand your ground
and face any kind of challenge
that stands in front of you.
But God wants us
to love each other,
encourage one other,
keep each other accountable.
Because the longer
that we try to walk it alone,
the harder it gets.
Isaiah, how's that sword doing?
- It's getting heavy.
- BOBBY: I'm sure it is.
Yeah, it has a tendency
to do that.
Such is life.
And yet, men will try to go
as far as they can
by themselves.
But we need each other,
and God gives us strength
when we stand together.
SIGHS
Now there are times
when you'll have to stand alone.
But don't do it out of pride
or stubbornness.
If you need help, ask.
If you see
a brother in need, help.
Stand with him.
Treat him the way
you want to be treated.
So how's that feel right now?
- Way better.
- ALL LAUGH
Thank you, gentlemen.
Now, Isaiah,
this sword is yours.
It's a gift from all of us.
We encourage you to hang it up
on your wall as a reminder
that even though you can
take a stand on your own...
we need each other.
Thank you.
Isaiah, hey.
You can use that
to hang it on the wall, bud.
- Well, thanks, Bobby.
- Yeah.
Uh... You, uh... You got a place
picked out?
Oh, yeah. It's going
on the wall in my room.
- I did the same.
- Yeah.
How long have you known Joshua?
Um, we've been friends
for over 15 years.
Yeah. He is...
He's one of my closest
friends. Yeah.
Nice. How'd you guys meet?
They tell you
about his son, Jalen?
Oh. Ms. Janelle told me.
That he was killed
by a drunk driver.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Um...
I was... I was that driver.
Yeah. That's how we met.
About a year after the trial...
he came to visit me
with a man
who was discipling him.
And then...
that guy just...
He just kept on coming.
- You know how he is.
- Yeah.
Eventually, he led me to Jesus.
Changed my life.
I was the first one
he discipled.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
DOOR OPENS
ISAIAH: Hey. You need help?
No, this is it. Just testing out
some new products for the salon.
- Did you mow the lawn?
- Oh, yeah.
I had some time
before the meeting tonight.
Well, thank you. It looks great.
Yeah. Did you get
what I sent you?
Mm-mm.
I wanted to send you
my first rent payment.
Isaiah, this is more than
it needs to be.
No, it's what I wanted to do.
And I also wanted to ask you
if I can take you to dinner.
Okay, wait a minute. Hold on.
My son is helping me
around the house,
he's paying me rent,
and you want to take me
on a mama date?
Yes, ma'am. But I do need
to use your car if that's cool.
But I'm saving up for my own.
You know what?
I would claim you as my son
to anybody, anytime, anyplace.
All right.
Well, I'll remember that.
What in the...
What is happening?
- POP MUSIC PLAYING
- INAUDIBLE
MUSIC ENDS
So, I can take
three classes a semester
and I can still
keep my hours here.
Bachelor's degree in business?
Yeah. What do you think?
I like it. CHUCKLES
And the cost?
I'm eligible for one grant,
but I can get
a partial scholarship
if I keep my grades up.
I mean, I can cover the rest,
but I'm ready to get a car.
Yeah. I'm actually
getting excited about it,
but I know it's gonna be hard.
Don't be afraid
of doing hard things
as long as they're worth doing.
Honor the Lord.
- See what He does.
- Yeah.
Well, speaking of hard things...
I... I've been
praying for my dad
and I decided
to write him a letter.
And I mailed it off
to the company
he was driving for, so...
I hope he gets it.
But I said everything
I needed to say.
And if he doesn't respond?
I mean, I've already
given it to the Lord.
And I'm becoming more settled
with the fact that,
you know, God is the father
I need the most.
But thought I'd give it a try,
you know?
You've done well, Isaiah.
No matter what happens,
I know the Lord's
going to bless you.
KNOCK ON DOOR
Sorry to interrupt, sir,
but they now have both.
Slayer Sports got both accounts?
Yes, sir. Again, it's two
of our smaller accounts,
but they are moving fast.
We can keep the mission products
going for now.
But we can't lose
another account.
I think they're gonna go after
GymFit or HighStride.
See if you can get a meeting
with our top three accounts.
I'll fly out and talk to them.
I'll do it.
JOSHUA: I want to do
something tonight
that the older men and I
have been talking about
for a few weeks now.
You younger men
have been walking through
your discipleship so well.
And we want to affirm
each and every one of you
at times in your journey.
Tonight, I want to start...
with Isaiah.
MAN 1: All right.
- Would you step forward?
- MAN 2: All right.
I have some things
I want to say to you.
I have known you now
for a year...
and I have watched you grow
and mature in so many ways.
You have grown in character,
in responsibility,
in your faith,
even in the way
you carry yourself.
- JAMES: Yeah. Yeah.
- JOSHUA LAUGHS
In fact, gentlemen,
if I may be blunt...
a man stands in front of me.
ALL APPLAUDING
Isaiah has embraced Jesus Christ
as his Lord and Savior.
He has worked hard to learn
and to apply biblical principles
to his life.
He has fought
to forgive past hurts
and surrender them to the Lord.
I have watched him
walk as a man.
A godly man.
So, Isaiah,
I want to bless you...
in the name of the Lord.
I bless you...
with respect,
love and friendship
as a brother in Christ.
And I call you a strong,
faith-filled man of wisdom
with a bold future.
From today forward,
may God's hand of goodness
rest upon your life.
May you experience His love...
His forgiveness, His power,
and His provision.
May His blessings cover you...
because you put
your faith in Him.
And may you
now walk in victory...
and never in defeat.
SNIFFLES
I love you.
And I am proud of you.
In the name of Jesus,
our Lord and Savior.
Men of The Forge, join me
and let's pray over him.
- Father God.
- JAMES: Yes. Yes.
May you bless Isaiah,
- our brother in Christ.
- JAMES: Yes.
I ask you to lead him...
Yes.
...to guard him,
fill him with wisdom,
- discernment as he follows you.
- JAMES: Yes. Yes.
Place your hand
upon his life and his heart.
Yes, Lord.
Bless him when he comes in
- and bless him when he goes out.
- MEN: Yes.
Father, bless everything
that he puts his hand to.
I ask you to protect him
from anything that would
pull him away from you.
Put him on the path
that you have chosen for him.
MEN: Yes, Lord.
And may he be
a blessing to others
all the days of his life.
JAMES: Yes.
And I ask this and receive it...
in the name of our Lord
and Savior, Jesus Christ.
JAMES: Yes.
- Amen.
- ALL: Amen.
JOSHUA: Oh.
COACH B: Yeah.
- There you go.
- INDISTINCT CHATTER
- Thank you, brother.
- Congratulations.
I've... I've never felt
like this.
So it was a good day, huh?
Yeah. CHUCKLES
Yeah. It was.
Well, baby, the day ain't over.
What do you mean?
Okay. What is this?
I just got something to show ya.
Can you lift up
the garage door, please?
This...
This is not my car.
This is your car.
How'd you do this?
Um, Joshua, he knows a man
who does this.
And... And...
there's another young man I know
who's been paying me rent
for a little while now.
So, you know,
I've had some extra income
and I've been saving it.
SNIFFLES
BOTH SOBBING
Thank you, Lord.
EXHALES
Thank you, Lord, for my son.
I thank you, Father,
'cause I... I see
what you're doing in his life.
Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Father.
ISAIAH: Yo.
Zay, is this your car?
Let's go, Zay!
Let's go, Zay! Let's go.
Dang, she's beautiful!
What?
- Thank you.
- Thank you! See you then!
- Hey, baby. You ready?
- Ah. Just about to come get you.
Our flight leaves in 90 minutes
for Dallas.
- Okay.
- Joshua, Janelle.
I know you're on your way
to meet with HighStride.
I just need a minute.
I just learned
that Greyson Lance,
the new president of GymFit,
is having a meeting
with Slayer Sports this morning.
And they're trying
to lure him over.
Is he not responding to us?
Well, we've reached out
several times,
just without a relationship.
He's just seeing
what's out there.
Okay, look, we'll fly to GymFit
after we meet with HighStride.
- Okay.
- I don't want to seem desperate.
We need to talk face-to-face.
I was hoping you'd say that.
I will let him know
you're coming.
- Thanks again, Emmett.
- EMMETT: Yeah.
We better pray
all the way there.
JOSHUA: Yeah.
- Thanks. Appreciate it.
- Have a safe one.
CAR DOOR CLOSES
Oh. Hello. How can I help you?
- Hey, how are you?
- I'm fine. Thank you.
Is there something
I can help you with?
Uh...
- By chance, is your father here?
- He is. Um...
Do you need to speak with him?
Yes, please, if it's not
an inconvenience, of course.
Okay. Sure.
Just give me a second.
Thank you.
- MAN: Hello, sir.
- Hi, I'm Isaiah Wright.
Tim Watson.
Pleasure to meet you.
What can I do for you?
Well, uh, I wanted to speak
with you for a moment because
I believe I owe you
an apology, sir.
- An apology?
- Yes, sir.
I was, you know,
very disrespectful to you
and your daughter and...
I'm very, very sorry.
CHUCKLES
Uh, I'm sorry, son.
I don't believe we've ever met.
- So...
- ISAIAH: Yeah, we have.
You know, about a year ago,
I came here,
but not to buy coffee and...
you asked me to leave.
You know, I said some things
that, you know,
I shouldn't have. And...
I apologize.
I mean, to you both. And...
I just hope you can find it
in your heart to forgive me.
Hmm.
- You are not the same young man.
- LAUGHS
No, sir, I'm definitely not.
I can respect the fact
that you've come here
to do this, Isaiah.
And, yes. I can forgive you.
Well, thank you, sir.
That, um...
That means a lot.
I appreciate you for taking
the time to talk with me.
- You are certainly welcome.
- Yeah.
Take care.
Well, that's not somethin'
you see every day.
No, it certainly is not.
JOSHUA: Are you sure?
EMMETT: And he's opening
the door to get the account
based on who can fill the order.
Apparently,
Slayer Sports is saying
they can have it ready
by noon tomorrow.
Are their products
even the same quality?
Well, Greyson Lance says
they consider them equal.
Slayer has matched our prices
and is saying
they can deliver them faster.
So Mr. Lance has asked
for these 3,000 units
as a demonstration
of who can provide them first.
Send me his number.
I gotta talk to this guy.
Please.
Losing GymFit means
closing the mission account
or cutting a third of our crew.
You don't want to
have to pick your poison.
- I'm sending his number.
- Thanks, Emmett.
Could we even
fill an order that fast?
Our crew just worked
an eight-hour shift.
They'd have to work
another 16 hours or more.
Oh, God, show me what to do.
- CARLOS: Crushed it today, man.
- $20 for it.
- TODD: Are you kidding?
- Yeah.
TODD: Why do they
have to have it tomorrow?
EMMETT: It's not that
they have to have it tomorrow.
They're opening the door
to whoever can demonstrate
that they can get the job done
on short notice.
So what are we supposed to do?
I mean, they're notifying us
as we're shutting down
for the weekend.
EMMETT: I'm just saying that
that is a strategic move.
That is a $4.5 million account.
- What's up?
- We...
Our top account, GymFit,
they have a new president
and our five-year agreement
with them is up this month.
Now another company
is saying that they can deliver
comparable fitness products
and faster.
So, GymFit's president
is requesting a 3,000-unit order
to whoever can meet it,
as a test.
- DIEGO: Who's the other company?
- EMMETT: Slayer Sports.
They want our account
and they told GymFit
that they could have the order
ready by noon tomorrow.
And when I think about it,
we're further away,
so if we wanted to beat them,
we would have to have
the order ready
over two hours earlier, man.
It was... It was a slick move.
Yeah, that's real slick.
And there's no way, man.
No, wait. Do we have
the products they want?
Yes, but that's not the problem.
It would take 24 people two days
to fill that order.
- If they worked normal shifts.
- EMMETT: Mm.
Bro, we just got off
an eight-hour shift.
But if we lose that much income,
it's gonna impact all of us.
And it can shut down
the mission account, right?
Yes.
So listen. If Slayer
wants to make that move,
we outplay 'em.
We go all night if we have to
and have the orders
ready by morning.
Whoa, whoa. Isaiah, all night?
We only got six of us.
Seven, including Emmett.
Wait. You're not asking me
to work another 16 hours,
are you?
I'm saying I'm willing
to go the second mile.
We can't just walk out
and do nothing.
But there's no guarantee
that we could fill that order
by morning.
And if Slayer beats us,
we will have stayed up
all night long,
nearly killed ourselves
for nothing.
Look, then let me lead.
I'll take the blame.
And you can tell Mr. Moore
it was all my idea.
I'm in.
Dude, are you serious?
Joshua Moore is the best boss
I've ever had.
He's helped too many people
for me to walk away.
DIEGO: I agree.
I'll do it, too.
Okay.
Well, if we're all in,
I won't be the one to walk out.
But if we're going
for that knockout punch,
we better connect.
Wanda?
You're really doing this?
Can it even be done?
Hey, Wanda. We need you.
This, it can't happen
without you.
I'm in.
- All right.
- SPLUTTERS Isaiah.
If this doesn't work out,
then what are you...
It's on me.
Listen. It's all on me.
All right, man. It's all you.
What do you need?
I need the detailed
product order.
Then we're gonna need some food
and a lot of caffeine.
TODD LAUGHS
Hey, Todd, we also need storage
robots on the second floor!
I can't control those.
I can only program
the floor carts.
We'll need the engineer
for those.
Okay, Isaiah, think.
Okay, think.
TODD: What...
Wait, wait, wait. When do you
have to have this done?
ISAIAH: By morning.
We gotta beat another company
to save our top account
and the mission account.
But we gotta figure out a way
to get the storage robots
working, so just pray for us.
I gotta go. I love you.
LINE BEEPING
LINE RINGING
Well, I can't say that
I've ever prayed
for robots before.
Although last week,
I did pray about my dishwasher.
Uh-huh.
Oh, it's working.
GASPS Oh. Oh.
I... I see.
Tomorrow morning
is an unusual request!
Yes.
I understand.
I'll call you soon.
He's just trying to
establish himself
as a leader
willing to make risky changes.
I can't shut down
the mission account.
I can't do it.
I don't want to
lay off anybody either.
That's just too many hours
to ask our crew to work.
I need to call Emmett.
Joshua, I just pulled up
the security cameras
to take a look
at the storage area.
You need to come see this.
- JOSHUA: Isaiah?
- JANELLE: You do have a crew.
And it looks like they're trying
to fill this order.
To do 3,000, they're gonna
need the storage bots.
Uh, see if you can
reach out to Cody.
We may have to do this remotely.
I'm on it, babe.
- AI: Lock on target.
- GUNS FIRING
Are you still shootin' robots?
Uh, it's just a game, Mom.
Yeah. That looks too real.
So, do you want my help
in the kitchen before I turn in?
Huh? Oh, yeah, I'll come
in there in just a second
when I'm finished with this one.
Okay.
RINGING
Hello?
Cody, this is Janelle Moore.
I'm sorry to call you so late,
but we have
a bit of a situation.
Can you control the storage
robots from where you are?
Uh... The storage?
Yes. Yes, I can!
Wonderful. Would it be possible
to get your help?
One of our competitors
is trying to take away
our largest account,
and we have a team at
the factory trying to stop them.
But we need those robots.
Well, they're undergoing
a firmware update currently,
and I don't have
the order information,
so I don't know
how I would do that.
I can tell you
the number of products
and where they're stored.
But we need to move quickly.
Okay. I can
pull the program up now,
but I'm gonna have to access
the robots one at a time.
We'll take it. And we need
to run 'em at full speed.
Um... Sorry, we've never
done that before.
Well, we're doing that tonight.
SIGHS
Okay. CLEARS THROAT Okay.
Isaiah, without those robots,
we're only gonna be able to do
1,400 units at best!
God, I need those.
Todd!
Who turned those on?
JOSHUA: You got
the first portion,
I'm pulling up the second.
Okay, Cody, we gotta move fast.
You ready?
CODY: Yes, ma'am.
Bot 21 to port 15 for 20 units.
Bots 23 and 24
to port 35 for 30 units each.
Yes.
This is it!
This is what we need.
Curtis, Wanda, we need boxes!
Diego, Carlos,
run the conveyer at full speeds.
Todd, we're gonna start packing!
How is this happening?
Bot 45 to port 19
for eight units.
Joshua, how's it looking?
At this pace,
we'll be short of 3,000.
Cody, can we go faster?
Uh, yes.
I... I'm willing to try.
JANELLE: You let me know
when you need a break,
but we gotta keep movin'.
Yeah.
It's just those six and me.
I'm getting food and drinks
for them right now.
I think it's gonna be
a long night.
JOSHUA: Thank you, Emmett.
Give 'em whatever they need.
We'll help Cody
keep those robots working.
TENSE MUSIC PLAYING
EMMETT: Here we go, fellas,
I got drinks on deck!
Todd? Coffee, here we go.
Curtis. Wanda. Yeah, water?
- Curtis?
- CURTIS: Water.
Water. All right, Isaiah.
Good.
Yeah, that's you.
All right. Coming to you!
CODY'S MOTHER: Are you
still playing that robot game?
These are real robots now, Mom.
Everything is real.
It's all real!
SPLUTTERS What?
Bots 58 and 59 to port five
for 12 units each.
At this pace,
we'll land on 2,780.
I'm making the call.
Um, Cody, let's take
a three-minute break
and come right back.
Will do.
EXHALES
Are you sure?
LINE RINGING
LANCE: Mr. Moore?
Mr. Lance, you said whoever
can have this order ready first
will get this account.
I understand that
you already have
an offer of noon on the table.
We do, and they're closer.
They're working on it right now.
So, to beat that,
you'd have to make it
around 9:30 a.m. your time.
I believe I can have that order
ready at 9:00.
And we're interested in keeping
this account for years to come.
Are you telling me
that you'll have all 3,000 units
ready for pick up?
Mr. Lance, send your trucks.
Hey, that's 1,000!
The record will be 3,000
when we're done.
Yeah, I mean,
3,000 is a long shot.
You guys know that, right?
That's what's so motivating.
We do the impossible!
PRAYING INDISTINCTLY
INAUDIBLE
Bot 75 to port seven
for 15 units.
Cody, that's 2,000.
JANELLE: Cody, you still good?
Yeah. I'm here.
My fingers
are running a marathon,
but I want to cross
the finish line.
Hey! That's 2,000.
Feels like 10,000!
ISAIAH: Hey.
We're doing it.
We've worked faster than anyone
and we're almost
at the finish line,
so let's stay in it.
And remember,
it's not just business
we're keeping.
It's every missionary
and ministry team
that uses water filters,
solar panels, and lanterns
that this company provides.
That's right.
And we have to keep that
available, all right?
And if Mr. Moore could see us...
he'd be so proud.
He can see you.
He's been watching you
for the past 10 hours
from Dallas
over the security cameras.
And they've been working
with Cody this whole time
to keep
the storage robots running.
So that's how
they been doing that?
He texted me earlier.
He said, "I've never been
so proud of this crew.
"They've gone above and beyond
anything I could have asked,
"and I will never forget it."
Look, we gotta push this thing
in the end zone, all right?
- We're not stopping.
- DIEGO: Hey, Mr. Isaiah.
My body is cansado,
but my heart is ready.
Give me caffeine
and I'm with you.
Hey, Wanda, what do you need?
I got enough caffeine in me
to go until next Tuesday, so...
- And Todd?
- Oh, this is beyond crazy.
- How are we gonna stop now, huh?
- Curtis?
Oh, I'm gonna sleep
for about two days after this.
But until then...
let's roll.
INSPIRATIONAL MUSIC PLAYING
Hey, you guys are crushing it!
CELL PHONE PINGS
Hey, Isaiah! The trucks
will be here in 30 minutes!
Yo, we got 30 minutes.
Finish strong. Finish strong!
Bot 8 to port 12
for seven units.
And that's it.
The last 60 orders
are on the conveyer belt.
They have to seal, label,
and stack them.
Cody, it's up to them now.
I can't... I can't go to bed
until I know we've made it.
BEEPING
All right.
- How'd you do that so fast?
- Too many video games.
Isaiah, the trucks
are almost here.
Joshua wants you
to greet the drivers.
I have a jacket in my office
whenever you're ready.
Isaiah, go. We got this.
- Yo. Is that it?
- That's it! We're done!
Hey, it's 8:58!
We got two minutes to spare!
- Let's go!
- TODD: We did it!
Look at them, Janelle.
Look at our team.
Oh, God! Thank you, Jesus!
Oh, God. Cody, we made it!
It's done!
Yes! Come on! Boom! Yes!
Joshua, the order is ready
and the trucks are here.
Hey.
You impressed me, brother.
I didn't think
this was possible.
Hey. You helped me.
We got it done.
ALL LAUGHING
Isaiah. Isaiah!
Greyson Lance is here.
What?
EMMETT: Joshua,
you want to talk to him?
No.
Isaiah's got this.
God, please give me favor.
Mr. Lance.
Good morning. Isaiah Wright.
Welcome to Moore Fitness.
Good morning to you.
You had an early start.
5:00 a.m.
When Mr. Moore said
you'd be ready at 9:00...
I wanted to come see it
for myself.
ISAIAH: I'm glad you did.
We'd love to show you
the company.
Mind if my drivers
check the order?
Absolutely. Be our guest.
We, uh...
We have 3,001 units
ready to load.
So, how in the world
could you have this order ready?
Mr. Lance, your account
means a great deal to us
and we value our partnership
with GymFit,
and we're willing to go
the extra mile to keep that.
We had a small group
that stayed up all night
until the order was done,
and you won't find
a better team anywhere.
And you won't find
a better partner in business
than Joshua Moore.
And as you can see,
it is our privilege
to help you win
and keep this partnership going.
That's pretty bold. I like that.
JOSHUA: Give us
another five years.
Listen,
I'm a competitive person,
but I also want to
trust my partners.
Slayer Sports
tried to slow you down,
yet they're still
working on their order.
So I'm willing to go another
five years with you guys.
ISAIAH: Mr. Lance,
you've seen what we're capable
of with a partial crew,
so, why not be bold
and keep a good thing going?
Let's do seven years.
LANCE: Done.
JANELLE SIGHS
Again, we value your business.
All right, let's load it up!
TRIUMPHANT MUSIC PLAYING
INAUDIBLE
CLARA: So, I understand that
you stayed up all night long
with an army of robots
to save the world.
Well, not the world,
but you know, it...
It turned out
to be a good thing.
And I understand you stayed up
several hours praying for us.
So, I just wanted to say
thank you.
Your mother's been telling me
about how you've been
chasing after the Lord,
becoming a disciple
of Jesus Christ.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm learnin'. CHUCKLES
Well, don't you stop.
Hmm. Never stop.
And you keep your eyes
on the Lord
more than on yourself,
and your heart on heaven
more than this world.
And don't you keep
taking one step forward
and then one step backwards
with your faith,
'cause, baby, that ain't nothing
but the cha-cha.
- ALL LAUGHING
- CLARA: No.
You devote your heart
to following the Lord,
no matter what the cost,
'cause He's worth it.
Yeah. He is worth it.
JOSHUA: Before we close out
our time,
I want to give Isaiah
a moment to share with us.
CLEARS THROAT
I, um...
I've been a part of this group
for a little over a year now,
and I just wanted to say
thank you.
You know,
it's hard to put into words
what this group means to me.
And I've lost count
of the times that, um...
It's been... I've been blessed
just to be here
and walk this thing out
with you. And, um...
I needed this.
I needed godly men
to challenge me,
to keep me accountable,
to study the Word,
and to pray for me and with me,
and now I want to do this
for someone else.
JAMES: Yes.
Again, thank you.
Gentlemen, The Forge
needs to expand.
Not by addition.
It must be by multiplication.
Groups like this
must spring up everywhere.
ALL: Yes.
Most churches
are trying to win converts,
but not enough
are effectively discipling them.
- Yes.
- ALL: Yes.
- We must go serve them.
The world doesn't need
more lukewarm church goers.
Jesus said
in the great commission,
"Go out into all the world
and make disciples."
ALL: Yes.
JOSHUA: We need more believers
who are whole-heartedly
following Jesus.
That's what
the world needs to see.
ALL: Yes.
JOSHUA: We have
to go after them...
ALL: Yes.
...because whoever wants
the next generation the most
will get them.
This culture is aggressively
chasing after their hearts
and their minds
with a view of morality,
purpose, truth
that's continually redefined.
But God has given us the truth,
His Word.
- The anchor that we hold on to.
- ALL: Yes.
JOSHUA: So even as I pray
for Isaiah,
I pray for you,
that you not be one in a million
- but one of a million.
- ALL: Yes.
JOSHUA: So I say,
let's go where they are!
In the schools,
in the ballfields,
in the marketplaces.
Wherever they hang out,
we must be there,
and we must find them.
Let's do what Jesus did.
Let's go love 'em
with the truth.
- Let's take them Jesus.
- ALL: Yes.
Who's with me?
WOMAN: Yeah,
let's plan to meet Friday.
So I'll see you guys
Friday night? Okay.
- Oh, my gosh. I'm so sorry.
- Excuse me.
Uh... Hey,
it's... Abigail, right?
And you're Isaiah.
Yeah. CHUCKLES Good memory.
- You go to school here?
- Yeah. I just started.
But you know, I'm still learning
my way around campus. So...
BOTH CHUCKLE
Yeah. You... You a junior?
Sophomore. Interior design.
- Oh, nice.
- You?
Business. I hope.
LAUGHS Right.
Well, um, hey, just so you know,
you really made an impact
on my dad.
- Oh, yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
He's brought you up
a few times now.
Well... Well, you know, I, um...
I really appreciate him for
taking the time to talk with me,
so, you know, I might have
to drop by, say hello sometime.
But not to get coffee.
BOTH CHUCKLE
I mean, I just, I don't know.
Just never got into it,
you know.
I mainly drink energy drinks.
It's cool. I get it.
But coffee is better for you.
And there's actually a really
good shop here on campus.
Well, you know,
I might have to try that out.
But I may need some suggestions.
Just saying.
Okay. Well,
where are you headed now?
Glad you asked. Uh...
I'm looking for...
Here it is. Mitchell building?
- I could show you.
- That'd be great.
- Hey, coffee on me.
- Sounds good.
So, why business?
\an8UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING