Hey, Audrey, welcome back!
Let me guess, on your
way to teach a class?
Only way to start the day.
Tell Justin I said hi.
Step touch.
Up for two.
Twist.
Left.
Up for two.
Twist.
Right foot, go.
Darlene, nice!
Carl, shoulders down, remember?
Maria, you're killing it.
Come on, finish strong.
One more time. Strong
arms everybody.
Last four, here we go.
Four, three, two, one, whoo!
Yay!
You guys are so good.
Ah, it feels so good to be home.
Thank you so much.
We really missed
you, around here.
My water aerobics class just
isn't cutting it these days.
I missed you too,
Maria. Good to see you.
How long are you in town for?
Oh, it's up in the
air at the moment.
I hope you're
not going back to New York
after what happened.
I mean, we're just so happy
to have you back here.
Thanks, Darlene.
I have to go back to the bakery
but can you give your dad these?
I made sugar plum cookies.
His favorite. I'll
make sure he gets them.
Thanks, guys. Thanks
for coming. Bye.
Oh, let me get that, hon.
I need to grab some more
napkins anyway. You're the best.
You look hot.
Oh, my gosh, I missed you!
What? I thought you weren't
coming until next week.
Oh, slight change of plans.
I got in late last night.
Oh, God. Why am
I not surprised
that the first thing
you'd do is teach a class,
and the second thing is
say hi to your best friend.
You know me, I'm always late.
Come on, I want you to try
this new gingerbread latte
I've been working on.
Mm, yes, please.
Oh, yeah. It's Christmas
in a cup, baby.
So, tell me. What
happened with Bradley?
We decided to take a break.
Wow. Are you okay?
Yes. No. I don't know.
We just needed time apart.
Wow!
Literally Christmas in a cup.
I'm so proud of you.
You made your dream a
reality opening this place.
I feel the same about
all you did in New York.
Yeah, the difference
is I failed.
Which, by the way,
does everyone in town
know my New York gym
ran out of business
or just Darlene?
You know how fast the
news spreads in Mistletoe.
I mean, I think most people knew
that Jim was gonna propose
to me long before I did.
It's because I was too
excited to keep it a secret.
Jim! Audrey!
Oh, get in here,
I missed your hug.
Oh! I don't know if
you heard the news
but you are looking at the newest
member of the Mistletoe City Council.
Shablammy. Okay!
You know, honey, you don't
have to wear that all the time.
Oh, she's jealous of my bling.
Congratulations.
I didn't even know
you were running.
Yeah, there's a lot of stuff
that we have to catch up on.
Are you pregnant?
Oh... No. We... we wish.
Yeah, we haven't had time. Right
now we've been consumed with, um...
finding a new location
for Mistletoe Coffee Co.
Why? This is the
perfect place.
The town is closing
the rec center.
Permanently.
How did I not know about this?
I had to wait and
tell you in person.
Yeah, that's why we
kept it on the DL.
Town budget was slashed
and the first thing
on the hit list,
parks and recreation.
I know what this
place means to you.
This is horrible.
And at tomorrow's
council meeting
we're hearing a presentation
from some big ski resort company
that wants to buy
up all the land.
Does anyone have any good news?
Any?
Well, you can still teach
in the fitness studio.
Until... well, the
padlocks go up.
Thank you.
The place still smells the same,
peppermint and pine.
Ah, well it's much brighter
now that you're here.
I still can't
believe we have you
for more than three
days this Christmas.
Dad? Yeah.
Why didn't you tell me the
rec center was closing?
You know what, you'd had so
much disappointment in New York,
I just didn't wanna
ruin your homecoming.
I guess I just always
thought it would be there.
You know, part of me taking
a big risk in New York
was knowing that Mom's studio
was always an option.Mm.
Well, I did fight very hard
to get them to cut the budget,
you know, anywhere else.
And I just didn't
have the numbers.
Oh... yeah.
I've got to deliver
these Christmas ornaments
to Carl's Tavern for
Saturday night trivia.
You know what, Dad, I'll just
take these on my way home.
Really? Yeah.
Oh, that'd be
great. Thank you.
Oh, I forgot...
Darlene made you a box of
her sugar plum cookies.
Your favorite.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, that's very sweet of her.
You guys see a
lot of each other?
No, uh...
No, I mean, I sort
of barely know her.
I see her around,
on the council.
Can I give you a hand
with these boxes?
Dad, I'm a professional fitness
instructor. Yeah.
I think I can carry some boxes.
Ahh! See ya
later. See ya.
Oh!
- Merry Christmas!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, gosh.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Are you okay?
Why are you
carrying around a box of dirt?
It's not dirt, it's poinsettias.
Did you not see me?
"Poinsett-ia." "Poinsett-ia."
No, I did see you.
I was looking at my phone.
I think it's you
that didn't see me
'cause you're carrying
this tower of junk.
It's not junk. It's
Christmas decorations.
Well...
Potato, potato.
Well, junk implies that
it's useless or trash
and these are items
that bring people joy
and trust me, we all need
a little joy right now.
Oh... Oh, what's this?
Let me guess...
Overpriced artificial holly.
Careful, this is mistletoe.
Not to be messed with.
Overly-passionate about
Christmas decor, noted.
You know, I'm sorry
I bumped into you
but, uh, a little
advice... Mm-hmm?
This town is called
Mistletoe for a reason.
Ah.We're a Christmas oasis.
If you don't like the
holiday I'd hit the road.
Whoa, whoa. Hit the road?
Does Santa know that
you talk like that?
I never told you I
don't like the holidays.
In fact, I love it.
I applaud the commercial
genius that is Christmas.
The best parts of
Christmas are priceless.
Now why does that
sound familiar?
It's a commercial.
I have to go.
Far away from you.
Merry Christmas!
Hey.
I know. I know
we said no calls.
I just wanted to make
sure you got in okay.
I did, thanks.
Good. Listen, you, uh...
you tell your dad I
say hi, all right?
Bradley, being on a break means
I don't tell my dad you say hi.
Right, that makes sense.
Are we sure about this?
I feel like we might
be overreacting.
Well, what's the
proper way to react
when your boyfriend wants
to put things on hold?
No, no. I never said
let's put us on hold.
I just felt like getting engaged
right now was... reckless.
Reckless?
We always said we wanted to
be engaged by this Christmas
and then you suddenly
changed your mind.
That was before we
lost the gym. I...
I'm sorry. I didn't
call to fight, okay?
I... I just really
miss you. I miss us.
I miss that, too.
But I really feel
like being apart...
taking this time is the
right reset we both need.
Yeah. If you say so.
Good night, Bradley.
Bye, Audrey.
You look
exactly the same.
Look at this.
I got nostalgic while
decorating last night.
Oh.
Look at us in our little tutus.
Didn't we insist on rainbow
frill for, like, four years?
Your mom joked we'd be
going to prom in them.
Mm-hmm. Oh, gosh.
I keep thinking what she'd
say about this place closing.
Yeah. This place means
so much to so many.
Though not everyone can say
they had their first kiss here.
I totally forgot!
Dante Fitzpatrick
after dance class.
I... I think you were the first
and last girl he ever kissed.
Oh, gosh.
Wait a minute, what are
you doing here so early?
I didn't think you had
a class this morning.
Somebody booked a
private session.
I put a link up on my stories
saying I'd be back at home
teaching, filled right up.
You sound surprised.
Oh, let's just say
I have a little PTSD
from the lack of attendance
at the New York City gym.
Hm. Well, here, you're
appreciated and loved.
Thanks, Lisa.
Good morning! Are
you here for your...
You?
You're my private session?
Man, this is a small town.
I had no idea that
you worked here.
You see, when I'm on
the road traveling,
I never wanna miss a workout.
Our inn has no gym, so
Darlene down at the bakery,
she said the very best instructor
she's ever had is back in town.
She signed me up. I'm
assuming that's you.
Yep. That's me.
Wow. Modest, too.
So what are we looking at here?
Some weights? Some plates?
These are terrible by the way.
Dance.
No, no. Darlene said you
were a fitness instructor.
I am. I teach
dance-based fitness.
My routines involve a lot
of cardio and coordination.
Ew... like dance for fitness?
Trust me, it gets intense.
I do cross-fit.
Some side shuffle's
not gonna cut it.
We'll see.Okay.
Ooh. Christmas music?
Starting November 1st,
it's the only thing I play.
You ready? Okay.
It's a simple routine.
You start on the right
foot, single, single.
Double on the
right, left, right,
and a double on the left.
You want me to do that?
Well, you do cross-fit, right?
Surely this will be easy.
Six, seven, eight!
Single! Single!
Double!
Single, single,
double kick right!
A kick, kick, kick! Kick,
kick, out and right!
Right leg for
four, three, two...
Left, four, three,
two, step touch.
And a-one and a-two and
a-three and a-four and a twist.
And a-one, two,
three, whoo! Whoo...
Okay. I think that's
enough for today.
You hear that? That is the sweet
sound of no more Christmas music.
Well, you sure picked the
wrong town to vacation in
if you don't like Christmas.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm, uh...
I'm not on vacation. This
is strictly business for me.
Wait, Darlene said
you're back in town.
What does she mean by that?
Oh, I grew up in Mistletoe
and then, after college, came
back here and taught classes.
But it was always my dream
to open a gym in New York
so for the last couple
years that's what I did.
Oh, so you're basically
home for the holidays then.
Well, something like that.
You know, my private sessions
are for more advanced levels.
You might do better in
one of my group classes.
Okay, I'll think about that.
You really got my heart rate up.
Nice grip.
Mm.
Bye.Bye.
I know. We'll
talk.
Welcome everyone, welcome.
Uh, Darlene, I believe you
wanted to kick things off.
I... I just wanted
to remind everyone
that the last ever rec center Christmas
party will be on Christmas Eve.
Everyone is invited.
Good drinks, great music.
Thank you, Darlene.
You'd better believe
I'll be there.
So I know the closing
of the rec center
has been hard on all of us.
I just wanna remind
everybody that this meeting
is to hear ideas about what
should happen to the building
and of course, that
includes Mount Mistletoe.
Uh... the final vote
will be on December 23rd.
And that is just before the council
adjourns for the Christmas holidays.
You again?
Okay, this is coming
close to stalking.
A tad presumptuous,
don't you think?
Thinking I came
here just for you.
What are you doing here then?
Well, isn't the
whole town invited?
Everyone who lives in Mistletoe.
Don't you technically
live in New York?
"Don't you
technically live in New York?"
First, the council recognizes
Griffin Weston from Skyridge Resorts.
That's my cue.
Watch my jacket.
He's the resort guy?
Do you know him?
He was my private
session this morning.
Conveniently didn't
mention why he was in town.
Mistletoe is such a
charming little town.
A Christmas oasis,
if you will.
Imagine a place where you
can eat the best food,
drink the best wine
and get the most relaxing
massage of your life.
And at this place, imagine
a ski slope so smooth,
so serene, that
as you're flying,
the wind's blowing by you,
you have to ask yourself,
"Am I actually flying?"
That place is called
Skyridge Resort.
People can't be buying this.
And that dream could
become a reality in Mistletoe.
Jackie, right?
Do you ski?
I love to ski.
Takes one to snow one.
Powder to the people.
Oh, wow. Can you help me?
Where is the closest
hill to here?
An hour away.
An hour away. Not anymore.
Not anymore.
It is hard that
your rec center is closing.
But you have to ask yourself,
do you want this place
to just sit here empty,
unloved, unappreciated.
And the worst case scenario,
a big box store comes
in and just
makes themselves at home
right here in your little town.
So you can have that or
this in your backyard.
Skyridge.
No way are they bulldozing
our beautiful center
for those fake cobblestone walkways
and paint-by-numbers hotels.
We might not have a choice.
Not in this town.
Not at Christmas.
I'll stop him. One
way or another.
I don't know, maybe the
dentist on Main Street
would rent us the back
half of his building?
Isn't coffee not
great for teeth?
Oh... mutually
beneficial business then?
Which reminds me.
Tonight, bottle of wine?
Finally some free time?
Hey... Oh, shoot.
I forgot I volunteered for the library
toy drive tonight. Tomorrow then.
Oh, no, wait, no, wait, we
can't. That's trivia night.
Hmm.
When did our lives get so crazy?
Pretty much the second
we decided to start trying
for a baby. Mm.
Good morning.
Three extra shots of espresso
in my gingerbread latte, please.
Also, a blueberry scone.
You stopped ordering the ones with
the gross lemon zest in them, right?
Yes, after your fifth rant,
I switched up my order.
Good. I need sugar and
caffeine. I was up all night.
Then why do you look so upbeat?
I figured it out.
How we save the rec center.
I was up studying
the town's budgets.
Technically, we
only need $80,000
to keep this place
open for another year.
That buys us time to find
a more permanent solution.
Only? That is a lot of money.
So we raise the money.
Well, they're voting
on it December 23rd.
That's, like, in two weeks.
I know it seems impossible,
but if I can figure out a way
for people to donate the money
then the town won't
have to sell the land
to that awful resort guy.
Oh, I hate that guy.
What are
you doing here?
Grabbing myself a cup of
coffee on my way to class.
Black, no room, please.
Oh, you sure you don't wanna try
one of our gingerbread
lattes? They're really good.
Sounds a little too...
Christmassy?
Sugary. But... but,
yeah, that, too.
What do you mean "picking
up a coffee before class"?
Well, my "fitness instructor"
said that I should stick
to group lessons, so...
I also hear that
Darlene might be there
and I may need her vote.
Oh. Well, you'll be
"wasting your breath."
She knows what a
resort like yours
can do to a town like ours.
Improve it?
Ruin it.
Oh, look at the time. I
should probably get going.
Don't wanna be late, get
on my teacher's bad side.
Thank you.
Delicious.
Jimmy? Lise? For the Gram?
Thanks so much.
I can't stand that guy.
I don't know, seems kinda cool.
I really like the
scarf that he's got...
Oh, yeah, no, I get it.
We don't like that guy.
No, Jim.
You forgot your scone!
Mount Mistletoe has
perfect untapped terrain
for prime skiing. Look it.
Yeah.Yeah.
Not much of a skier.Oh.
I, on the other
hand, love to shred.
Is that right? Yeah.
Snowboarding. You
look like you shred.
So here's what
you're gonna like.
Right there is a terrain
park on the bottom.
Hey, oh, Carl, didn't
you break your arm
three times snowboarding?
Well, it was four, but
it was totally worth it.
Oh, that is the spirit.
Nothing is gonna
keep you down, is it?
Black diamond for you.
And come to think...
And I think it's time we
start warming up for class.
Okay, everybody,
let's get going.
The black diamond, is there
a lot of trees going down?
Yeah, but they're spaced
out and it's fluffy snow.
Hey, everybody.
So, as you can see,
Mr. Resort has decided to
join us for class today.
Most people
call me Griffin. Hi, everybody.
Thank you for the introduction.
I can't wait to dance
in the Christmas
capital of the world.
Oh, you're a big fan
of Christmas, huh?
The biggest.
Oh, tell me, what's your
favorite part about Christmas?
Well, it's... I'd have to go
with the joy that it brings.
That's a little vague.
Can you be more specific?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Music. How about... The music.
- The music?
- Yeah.
Oh, well what's your
favorite Christmas carol?
Ooh, I have to pick just one?
I'd say, The Twelve
Days Of Christmas.
Oh, I love that one, too.
Oh, remind me, what did they
bring on the second day?
Oh, that's, um...
Turtles.
Turtles? Yeah. Turtles... No?
Doves, doves.Swans.
Swans?
Turtle... turtle
swans. Turtle swans?
Yeah. Okay, everybody,
let's pick up the pace.
You're kidding.
So you melt the butter first?
Yes. That's what
gives it the texture.
No. I had no idea.
You're really
this interested in baking?
Well, mostly the eating, but
you gotta start somewhere.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, excuse me.
I gotta take this. We
will talk baking later.
Anytime.
Okay. Bye, Darlene. Ciao.
Hello?
So, talk to me, Griffin.
When can we expect
to break ground?
Soon. Very soon.
That's not very specific.
Should I be worried?
When have I ever
let you down, Dad?
Town council votes
on the 23rd December.
That still gives
us a couple weeks
to make sure they
don't choose to do
anything else with the property.
Expect any opposition?
Nothing I can't handle.
That's my boy, chip
off the old block.
Keep me updated, will you?
Okay. Well, talk to you soon.
If you follow Main Street
all the way to its end,
you'll find the beating
heart of our community.
Originally built as the
town founder's home,
it was converted into a
recreation center in 1954.
Is this... is this
your audition tape
for the History Channel?
We're encouraging people to
donate to save the center.
Wait, you're straight up just
asking people for money in a video?
Do you need
something? No, sorry.
Don't mind me, I'm just,
uh, grabbing some photos,
so our marketing team can
hit the ground running.
You have a little
something there.
Thank you. Just ignore
him and keep going.
Okay.Okay.
Not only can you find
an array of classes
like foreign languages,
ceramics, painting,
but also an art gallery,
and of course, my favorite,
a dance and fitness studio.
Wait, Lisa, do you think
that I should talk about
the donate page before I mention
everything that we offer?
Yeah, probably.
Otherwise, it just looks like you're making
a fan video for a building, and that's...
Wait, why are you doing this
video here and not the rec center?
Because... We're gonna edit
that in with Audrey talking.
Mm.
Okay, let's go again.Yeah.
This time, say the donate
now page at the top.
Okay. Okay.Yeah.
Wait a sec, did you say
"donate now"? No, no, no, no.
They give the money back
if you don't hit your goal.
We're meeting our goal.
Okay. How's your frame?
You wanna make sure you
get the whole shot in
so that way that we can really
emphasize the ski resort,
and people can see the
full potential of it, yeah.
Lisa, I'm done.
We're moving inside
the rec center.
Let's go.
Don't stay up too
late, sweetheart.
You know the old saying.
A watched donation
site never boils
or, you know,
something like that.
I have to figure out a way to reach
more people if this is gonna work.
Everything I've read
online says that
the first two hours after a post
goes up are the most important.
But at this rate
it's gonna take me a
decade to save the center.
Well, it's a lot of money to
be raised in a short time.
Maybe I'm
fooling myself.
If I couldn't save my gym,
how can I save the center?
It's just everything I thought
my life would be by now
hasn't happened.
I thought I at
least could do this.
Well, you know what
your mom would say.
She'd say if everything's not going
exactly the way you want it to,
there's usually something
better around the corner.
Good night.
You picked the perfect tree.
And don't forget,
sign up on the donation page
to help save the rec center.
Bradley. Hi.
Are you ready for
some amazing news?
I think so?
I just had a meeting
with Susan Price.
The head of New York
Solis Fitness Clubs?
Yes. She took one
of our classes
back in the day if you remember,
when we first opened, and,
she liked what she saw.
Audrey, she wants to
hire the both of us
to teach at her Solis
Fitness Club in Soho.
You're kidding.
No. She loves our energy.
We'd fit right into
their structure.
She even wants us to
start in the new year.
Can you believe it?
You and I working for one of
the biggest fitness empires
in the world.
That's amazing.
We wouldn't have much
freedom with what we taught.
Um, yeah, you're right.
But the truth is, you know,
boutique fitness clubs
are not exactly
thriving right now
and we had to learn
that the hard way.
So this... this is our
shot at getting back on top
and making it in
New York, together.
Can I think about it?
Absolutely. Yeah.
Maybe we should let her
know soon, though, right?
Totally.
Uh, I have to go.
Can I call you later?
Audrey. Maybe...
maybe this is the
reset we both need.
Need a hand?
Uh, no. Thanks, Darlene.
I got it, I got it.
Oh, okay.
Okay. Carl's best candy
cane martinis, woo-hoo!
Sorry we're late.
Oh, no worries at all.
Oh, we wish that was why,
and we were going to,
but, uh... well, Jim.
Uh, I may or may not have
set off the smoke alarm
trying to surprise Lisa with a
romantic dinner.Oh...
The point is, we're
gonna need some food.
Food. I'll get us
some cheese fries.
Thank you.
Oh! Oh!
Wow. It's a really good
thing that wasn't hot cider.
You've got to be kidding me.
You're here for
Mistletoe trivia night?
Yeah, I'm on Fred
and Margot's team.
Maureen. Fred and
Maureen. You sure?
You realize this is trivia
about the town of Mistletoe?
Something you know
nothing about.
Yeah. Nothing!
Yeah. That's why I'm
on the best team.
It's a strategy.
Are you worried?
You know I think you'll
probably do okay.
You're from here.
You have an open
tab, though, right?
Hey, Carl? Can we get another
one of these on her tab?
Thank you. It's almost gone.
I'm thirsty.
Oh... Do you have a shirt?
Do you have another...
Please. There you go.
Thanks C-Town.
Can you believe him?
So, I guess no
cheese fries then.
Who's ready
to use their brains?
Yeah!
Welcome, everyone,
welcome to Mistletoe's
monthly trivia night.
Whoo!
Please write your
answers legibly.
We don't want another
Santa Fanta debacle.
Here we go.
What year did the
town of Mistletoe
eliminate the sales
tax on Christmas trees?
1931 is the correct answer.
Okay,
folks, here we go.
We're coming down to
it, next question.
Phoradendron is the most
common species of mistletoe.
Name two of the other
1,300 species.
Okay, okay.
You know he's trying to get
them to vote for the resort.
Okay, I know dwarf is one kind
but what's another kind? Yeah.
What could they possibly be laughing
about? Audrey? Audrey? Audrey?
Oh. Uh, uh, uh, uh... desert.
Let's see 'em.
When did they even have
time to write all those?
We cannot let him win!
And so it looks like
it's coming down to...
We Noel It All...
Yes! Yes!
And Too Cool For Yule.
Yeah!
Come on! Come on!
And it is coming down
to the final question,
which is...
What tradition... oh, and this was started
by my wife, uh, Hailey Parker, by the way.
Thank you, Hailey.
What tradition used
to be incorporated
into the school Christmas
recital every year?
No way they know this, Fred
and Maureen don't have kids!
Kickline wins it!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
We Noel It All are the winners!
We won! We won!
That's it! What's it?
That's how we save the
center! A town-wide kickline.
We could get people to sign
up and pledge per kick.
Imagine, a huge kickline
going down Main Street.
It'll be so visually
stunning no one could ignore it.
I love it.
Count me in.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Sign up for the Kickline
Kick-a-thon right here!
Come and get it!
Thank you. See you there.
Oh, kickline...
like the Rockettes?
Yes. And all the money we raise will
be going to save the rec center.
I'm so in.
I've been taking ceramic
classes there since I was four.
Aw, well, here.
Invite your friends.
Get them to sign
up, too.Definitely.
Bye.
Hi. Kickline Kick-a-thon.
Now remember, baking is
both, an art and a science.
Hello.Huh.
Hey, Audrey. You're
just in time.
We're making
some, uh, Christmas rolls
which apparently are
just cinnamon rolls
with red and green
food coloring on them.
Right? And a dash
of peppermint.
Griffin bakes.Yep.
Well, he was sweet
enough to offer to help
since tomorrow's
Mistletoe Christmas Market
usually involves a large order.
How sweet of him.
I'm sure there's no
hidden motive whatsoever.
My vote? Trust me,
I am well-aware.
But he volunteered
and I need as much
help as I can get.
Oh, well, I'll help, too, then.
Uh, not that much help. I
think we've probably got it.
I'm here. Might as well.
Okay, sure.
I'll just grab an
apron. Oh, got one!
Here.
Now this recipe was handed
down to me by my mother.
Aw.
Oh, so she was a baker, too?
Oh, yes, just not
professionally.
Although, neither was
I until 10 years ago.
You're kidding me. I would've thought
you'd been doing this your whole life.
I used to be a lawyer.
Really? Mm-hmm.
Oh, shoot. I'm gonna
get some more flour.
Okay. Thanks, Darlene.
You're not gonna get her vote
so you can stop
whatever... this is.
Well, think of all
the resort guests
who get to enjoy
Darlene's delights.
Oh, so you're telling
me that your resort
wouldn't have a bunch
of chain restaurants
that everyone would
go to instead?
People deserve to
have options, Audrey.
Tell that to all
the local businesses
that are at the
Mistletoe Marketplace.
Right. What's
that again?
The small fair at the rec center
where the local businesses
come to promote their
Christmastime items.
That could be
really informative.
Oh, no. I'm coming.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're not invited.
I'm coming. No!
I'll be there. No!
Ah, this...
Okay. This is way too painful.
Well, I don't know,
it's like, broken.
Let me show you how
you do it. Ugh, gosh.
Go in these... in the lines.
What?
You have something on your nose.
Flour.
Oh.So do you.
Well look, now we, um...
At least we have
something in common.
Hello?
I've got some good news for you.
Oh?
Peter is retiring.
Really? Yeah.
Something about wanting
to spend more time
with his family or something
so I told the board I had
the perfect replacement.
What?
Me?
Of course, you're my
son. This is your legacy.
You land that Montana resort
and you'll be the next
chief operating officer
of Skyridge Resorts.
Um...
Right.
Do I sense some hesitation?
No. I mean, recently, there's
been a little bit of pushback
from the community, but...
nothing I can't handle.
It's nothing to worry about.
I should hope not. The
next COO of Skyridge
can handle a few disgruntled
townies.
That's right.
I gotta jump on this
call. Talk later?
All right, thanks, Dad.
Oh, hey...
Looking good,
sweetheart. Thanks, Dad.
Morning.
No.
No, no, no, no, no!
What are you doing?
I'm setting up my booth.
Spoke to the council, turns out
all you gotta do is pay a fee
and then anyone can set
one of these things up.
And look at this. They chose to
put us right next to each other.
Why do you need a booth?
Well, so people can
learn some information
about Skyridge Resorts.
Look, then the community
can get to know us a little
better. What do you think of this?
Look at that!
The Mistletoe Christmas Market
is to promote
businesses in Mistletoe.
You're not a business
in Mistletoe!
Right, I know. Not yet.
Is it too big? I think
it's a little too big.
Kickline Fundraiser!
A few kicks each and
we save the rec center!
Jim. Yeah?
Will you watch my
booth for a second?
Sure. Why?
Somebody's
gotta stop him.
Okay.
Hey.
Griffin. Hi.
Talk later. Audrey. Hi.
Brochure? Oh, no.
Um, actually, I wanted to see
if you wanted to
grab a cup of coffee.
Black, no sugar.
Just how you like it.
Yeah. You're kidding.
No, come on. Let's go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. I know what you're doing.
You don't wanna
get coffee with me.
You want me to leave this little
Christmas market, don't you?
And I know what you're up to.
You're trying to
razzle-dazzle this town
into thinking what you want
instead of what we want.
You mean what you
want. "Razzle-dazzle."
All right. Enlighten me.
Fine.
Look. This booth over
here with the snow-globes,
it's our bookshop.
They do weekly
story-time for kids.
And you know Carl from class.
Hello,
Carl.
He's the fourth Carl in his
family to own this tavern.
Any boy born in our
family gets the name.
And some girls, too.
Carla. Carlita.
And this is Abe's Auto Shop.
He can fix anything,
not just cars.
Wow. This is great.
All this information for
little conversation starters
when I wanna promote the resort.
Thank you. Thank you for that.
No.
I'm trying to tell you that
each of these establishments
are run by people.
Unique individuals that your
corporate resort would hurt.
You mean help, right?
This town cannot afford
to even keep the
recreation center open.
Yet you have this
beautiful location
that would just attract
tons and tons of people
and it would boost the economy.
I saw the list of
amenities your resort has.
Restaurants. There
goes Carl's Tavern.
Shopping. Goodbye
Main Street boutiques.
And it's a domino effect.
One corporate
resort comes to town
and the rest are sure to follow.
What is it that you have
against big companies?
Nothing.
They just don't belong here.
Can you honestly tell me
that none of these people
would lose their businesses
because of your resort?
Oh, Audrey, have you
met my grandson Elvis?
Hi. Hi, Elvis,
you're adorable.
Do you want one?
He got it.
Mistletoe Toss is open.
Dare I ask what a
Mistletoe Toss is?
It's exactly what
it sounds like.
What color do you
want? No, I'm good.
I don't wanna throw a parasitic
plant at a peppermint...
Griffin.Yep.
Mistletoe tradition.Mm.
You must try.
Come on, it's fun.Okay.
Go, Team Audrey. Thanks, Dad.
What, you scared?
Scared?
Well, you said you worked out
and then my class
kicked your butt,
so I'm guessing that
you're a little nervous
to lose at the Mistletoe Toss
in front of all these people.
Okay, fine. I'll
play you. Let's go.
Are you sure? I'm
practically pro.
What, at this?
How about this?
If I win... Yeah.
You take down your resort
propaganda routine.
Okay. Okay.
And if I win,
which I will, then,
hmm, what am I gonna do? Oh!
I am not giving up the kickline.
You have to have dinner with me.
What? Why?
I think maybe we got
off on the wrong foot.
We could have a
productive conversation
and I could share
with you all the merit
of the Skyridge Resort.
You're not gonna change my mind.
But since I know I'm gonna win,
okay, sure,
let's do it.
Ladies first.
Oh, I thought you
said you were pro.
Warming
up, Griffin. All right.
Okay, maybe I'm just
warming up, too.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Let's see what you got.Mm-hmm.
Yes!
Okay, that's luck.
That is luck.
Skill. Skill, skill,
skill. That is luck.
All right, here
we go. This is...
Oh!
Now that was luck.
No, that was skill.
All right, what you
got.
Might as well start taking
your booth down now.
How about you get ready to
choose what you want for dinner
'cause this is going
right on. Look at that.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
What've you got?
Ooh!
I am so sorry but if I make this
I win the entire thing,
the Mistletoe Toss?
You won't.Okay.
Oh, yeah!
Game, set and match.
That was a fluke.
I thought you were a pro?
Just a question. Do
you like Italian?
Because Carl's Tavern has
a really nice Bolognese.
Yeah, I don't eat meat anymore.
No?
A date?
It's not a date, it's dinner.
Alone, together.
I'm sure I could get out of it.
Why?
It could be fun, and you
and Bradley are on a break.
But he's the enemy.
Pretty cute enemy.
Trust me, it's the last thing
I have to think about right now.
Hmm.
What do you have to
think about right now?
The Solis job? Bradley?
Right now, it's the kickline.
We have a lot of sign-ups,
we just need a lot
more kick pledges.
You should definitely
take it online.
I would love a blueberry scone,
as long as there's
no lemon zest in it,
'cause that is disgusting.
See, Lisa? I'm
not the only one.
Right? Totally overpowers
the simplicity of the scone.
I've been saying that for years.
She really has.
What do you mean take it online?
The kickline is already
connected to a "Donate Now" page.
Well, since you're asking,
Mistletoe is only so big, right?
Mm.
So, if you livestream the event,
then you reach a larger audience
and interest in this thing
just goes up and up and up.
And if you open it up,
then people
everywhere can donate
to your little line kicky thing.
Kickline.
That... yeah, that.
Ooh!
There
we go. See ya tonight.
See ya tonight... Tonight?
Wait! We never decided
on a day for dinner.
Tonight!
See? He's never
doing something
out of the kindness
of his own heart.
Helping Darlene bake,
taking me to dinner,
there's always a hidden motive.
Still, he did inspire a pretty
good idea. Meh...
And until two seconds
ago I thought you were
the only person who hated
lemon zest in their scones.
Everyone hates lemon
zest in their scones.
It's like fruitcake.
Everybody hates fruitcake.
Okay, so, the first link is for
everyone anywhere to watch the kickline.
And then this link is
connected to the donate page
so people can pledge per kick.
Crazy.
Bradley did all this tech
stuff for the gym in New York,
but today, I figured
out I can do it too.
I like seeing you so determined.
Thanks, Dad.
It feels good to be
hopeful again.Yeah.
You expecting anybody?
Tell him I'm not home.
Yeah, she's... Oh,
she's not here.
A poinsettia? Funny.
Pretty sure it's
"poinsett-ia."
And I was... I'm
going more for sweet,
but funny, I'll... I'll
take funny from you.
I know what you're doing. You're
trying to be all charming and sweet.
So you do think I'm
charming and sweet.
You want my dad's vote.
You've got Fred and
Maureen in the bag.
Jackie is a wild card.
Jim still believes
there's a better solution.
And Darlene, hmm,
you just don't know.
So you're trying to secure
me to get all of them.
Wow. That is an exhausting way
to look at somebody who just
wants to invite you to dinner.
Am I wrong?
Listen. My objective is
this, to better this town.
My objective tonight
is to have dinner.
Preferably with you
right next to me
and prove to you that I'm not some
evil corporate mustache twirler.
Right?
She would love to go.
Dad.
It's dinner. It's
not eternity.
Good luck.
It's just dinner.
So why fitness? Why fitness?
Thanks, Carl. CARL: Enjoy.
Thanks, Carl.
My mom.
She taught me that it is a
privilege to move your body
and we shouldn't
take it for granted.
I've never... I've never
thought of it quite like that.
I just love inspiring
people to want to work out.
Is that why you
moved to New York,
to spread the gospel
of enjoying workouts?
My mom was originally
from New York
so it was always my
dream to go there, too.
You know, if you can
make it there, you can...
Yeah. So can I... Can I ask,
what happened in
New York exactly?
Well, Bradley, uh, my
business partner and I,
we thought that a
neighborhood gym could thrive.
You know, something
small and boutique.
We put all our money into it
and, you know, and then
we just couldn't compete
with the big chains and
it fell apart and...
we fell apart.
Everything fell apart.
So, I take it,
Bradley, then is...
is a little bit more
than a business partner.
Boyfriend. Well,
not currently.
We're on a break.
Okay. Well,
that explains why
you have a grudge
against large companies then,
because they ran you
out of business, right?
I don't have a grudge.Oh.
Solis Fitness Center has
offered us jobs in the new year
and I'm seriously
considering accepting.
So you're considering
working for a large
corporation, right?
Yet you're actively
trying to stop me,
a large corporation. No,
not at all the same thing.
Oh, please explain.
I'm not
trying to stop you.
Okay, I am.
I am. I'm trying to stop you.
But it's because I'm trying
to save the rec center.
You just happen to be the person
that wants to tear it all down.
Otherwise we'd be
friends, though, right?
Mm, I don't know
if I'd go that far.
I can't be friends with
somebody who says poinsett-ia.
It's poinsettia.
Really? You can't name five?
I don't think I could
actually name one.
Oh! You know what?
My friend... Okay.
Had a cat. No, goldfish.Good.
Girl... Victoria.
No, Victor. Victor.
No! Victor? Yeah.
Oh, my God. Vixen!
Oh, close enough.
Vixen. Oh, this is real.
What's... What's
real? The whole...
The whole Christmas is
all about making money,
the Scrooge routine.
I hate to break it to you
but them are the facts.
Yes, but you're
missing the point.
What's the point?
The reason for it all.
Christmas is... it's
about a feeling.
It's... it's something that
you can't put into words.
My... my mom was
really into Christmas.
Like, we're talking
Mistletoe level.
Yeah. I think if she
was still around,
you know, maybe things
would be different.
I'd look at Christmas
a bit differently.
Maybe that's why my dad
doesn't wanna celebrate with me,
is 'cause it's too hard for him.
What does your dad do?
Um, he's in real estate.
He, uh... he owns
Skyridge Resorts.
Your dad owns Skyridge? Mm-hmm.
Skyridge is a family business?
Yep. Sure is.
It's sort of like Carl's Tavern,
you know, we'll just fit right
in. Oh, just like Carl's Tavern.
Carl's Tavern is not trying
to take over the world.
Neither are we.
I mean, I do have a shot at COO
if I make this
deal come together.
You know, it'd also make
my dad really happy, so...
Well, what about you,
would that make you happy?
Why wouldn't it?
Well, you know, when
you were little...
what did you dream about?
Is COO your New York?
Um...
No. It was just my
assumed... path for me.
Paths can change.
I don't know who that is.
Bradley!
Surprise.Hi.
I saw your post this morning
and I just wanted to come
and help the kickline.
So I took about three different
flights but I made it.
Ah, hi.
Oh, come in.
The place looks
absolutely great.
Bradley, Griffin.
Griffin, Bradley.
Pleasure.
Hey.Hi.
What's with the
giant poinsettia?
Oh, it's a long story.
Actually,
you know, I'll tell it.
It's "poinsett-ia."
I was, uh... I bumped into
Audrey and she kinda dumped...
she kinda dumped it on me.
You did what now?
Don't worry about it.Okay.
I should probably go. All
right, I'm gonna go. Okay.
Good to meet you. You, too.
Thanks for the cookies.
Who was that guy?
Bradley's here?
I thought you guys broke up
because he wouldn't propose.
No. We're on a break.
Oh. Uh, is that
different or...
Apparently, he saw my
post about the kickline
and said he wanted
to be a part of it.
He said he knew it
was important to me.
Well that's kinda sweet, right?
Very. But I don't know.
It's nice to have the help.
It's just, it felt good
doing something on my own.
Jim, what's with the scarf?
Hmm?
The... Oh, the...
Griff wears a scarf, so...
I guess Griff's making an
impression on everybody.
Oh, my God, that reminds me.
How was the date?
It wasn't a date.
It was dinner.
And?
And, all things considered,
if I had to say...
one way or the other at
the end of the night...
It was nice.
But nothing changes
the fact that he wants
to rip this place apart and
build a mega super-resort.
Oh, Jim, don't
give me that look.
Told you so.
It means nothing!
Thank you. Oh!
Oh, shoot. Oh,
shoot. I'm so sorry.
It's me. You know,
I wasn't looking.
No, no. I was
looking down at my papers.
Here's your card.
Yes. Thank you.
Oh. Okay. You.You.
Grant, right?
No, uh, close.
It's, uh, Griffin.
Griffin.
Barry?
Close, actually. It's Bradley.
Bradley, that's right.Right.
Yeah.
So... So... so.
You are here to destroy
Audrey's rec center.
I wouldn't word it that
way at all, actually. No?
No, I'm here to turn this
land into something useful
that'll benefit Mistletoe
for years to come.
So, gotta go.Sure.
Before... Before you go... Okay.
Just one... one little thing.
Audrey's mom taught
there before she died.
You know, that's why the
place means so much to her.
Yep. I... I know. I know.
The place means a lot, I got it.
And Audrey means a lot to me.
Good. Okay, I'm gonna go.
I should probably go.Yeah.
Don't wanna be late for,
uh... For class.Sure.
Class. Audrey's class? Yeah.
What do you know, I'm
headed there, too.
No way.Yeah. Amazing.
That is great. I know.
Okay, well, after you.
No, please, I
insist. After you.
No, no, no. No, no,
age before beauty.
All right, there you go.Great.
No. Actually, you
know what? No.
Oh, come on! No.
Left side!
Out and in!
Right hip!
Step touch!
Box step!
One more time!
Step touch!
Box step!
And ready, finish!
Whoo!
Okay. Great job, everybody.
Thank you, thank you!
This is different than New York.
You have to order
the cheese fries.
I can't, I'm trying to do
this clean eating week.
You know how it is. Clean
eating? It's Christmas.
Christmas calories don't count.
Right.Uh-huh.
Hmm. I've missed you.
I still can't
believe you're here.
A kickline sounded fun
and I already have some
pledges from some followers.
What?
Thank you, that's awesome.
So, have you given
it any more thought?
I'll call Solis right now
and tell them we're in.
I haven't decided
anything just yet.
Audrey, we... we need
to give them an answer.
It's not a package deal.
You could take the
job without me.
Maybe I don't wanna
do it without you.
It's just that they want me to
teach their classes their way.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, you... you remember
what you first said to me
when we met at that fitness
conference four years ago?
The greatest gift we have
as fitness instructors
is to inspire as many
people as possible.
This is how you do that.
I can't believe
you remember that.
So, there's no one here.
Let's say we close early?
It's like you read
my mind.Mm-hmm.
Oh, good, you're
still open. Hey.
Uh-huh.
Whew. The usual?
No. Actually, I wanna go on
a little bit of an adventure.
Gotta work tonight, so
how about you whip me up
one of those gingerbread lattes
that Audrey's just been
going on and on about?
Yeah. Hmm.
Christmas spirit finally
rubbing off on you.
Yeah.
Something like that.
So you know, the vote, uh,
for the city council's
just in a few days.
Any idea, Jim, which
way you're leaning?
Uh, look, I like you, Griff.
Do you mind if I call you Griff?
Griff? No one
ever has, but sure.
Oh, that's surprising.
Seems natural.
Anyway, uh, as of right now
there is nowhere else in
Mistletoe for the Coffee Co.
Now, I've gotta wait and
see if we can save it.
I mean, you understand, right?
I understand.
You know, maybe there's a way
for the coffee shop
to be at my resort.
But I thought the Skyridge
Resorts had a direct deal
with the, uh,
Buckstar coffee chain.
They do, but it doesn't
have to stay that way.
Mm. Wow, that tastes like
liquid fruitcake, but not gross.
Don't tell Audrey
but she's right.
I'll tell her.
Yeah. Hey, Jimbo,
love the scarf on you.
No.
Loves it.Yeah.
Hi. Sorry, guys. Hey!
Hi.
I thought we could
use this instead.
It's a much better lens.
Oh, my gosh, thank you so much.
You're welcome. So nice of you.
I'll take this.
Whoa, wow.Whoa.
Are you hoping someone
in particular comes?
What?
You and that Griffin guy.
Is there something going
on between you two?
Bradley, I barely know the guy.
And he's trying to
take away the thing
that means the most
to me in this world.
What do you think?
Okay.
Today is about this.
What about tomorrow?
What?
Well, what if
tomorrow was about us?
A second first date.
I'd like that. Yeah.
Great.Okay.
I'll, uh... I'll go
help with more cameras.
Thank you.
Yeah. Dad, hey, thanks
for calling me back.
I just wanna float
something by you.
Shoot.
Okay. One of the things that
makes Mistletoe so great
is the community of
small businesses, right?
They're all unique and some
of them are even legacy.
Okay.
One of the things we're getting
a little bit of pushback on
is some of the things we're
offering are in conflict
and they're... they're worried
that they'll strain some
of the local businesses.
Ah, that's par for the course.
Places usually learn to adapt.
Okay. What if we tailored
the Skyridge Mistletoe Resort
just a little bit differently?
You know, not so much the
cookie-cutter approach.
Ugh. If it ain't
broke, don't fix it.
That's business 101.
Be honest son, are you worried
you won't get the votes?
No. No, no, no.
I'll get... I'll get the
votes, it's...
All right, just... Just
forget I called. All right?
Thanks, Dad.
Okay, T-minus two
minutes! Places, everyone!
Room for one more?
This is the last place
I thought you would be.
Well, I mean, you know how
good I've gotten at dancing.
You think I'd miss
an opportunity
to kick my legs up in the
air over and over again?
No way, Jose.
To save the very
thing you wanna take.
Well, it's great
publicity, right?
Sure. Or was it possibly the
gingerbread latte you had last night?
Maybe.Mm-hmm.
I'm glad you're here.
Come on, get in line.
All right. Let's line kick.Go.
Is this thing on?
Okay, thank you so much.
First and foremost, I just
wanna say thank you again
for coming to the Mistletoe
Kickline Fundraiser!
Thanks to all of you, we are
about to break the record
for the longest
Christmas kickline
and save the rec center
while we're at it.
Whoo!
Okay, so, I'm gonna
start the music.
That way you can hear the beat
and then I'll kick you in.
Okay.
Are we ready?
Five, six, seven, eight!
Step, kick! Step, kick!
Whoo!
Step kick! Step left!
Step right! Step left!
Whoo! Keep going!
Keep up, everybody!
Whoo!
That's right, Mistletoe!
Keep going! Almost there!
Here we go! Last four.
Three, two, one and pose!
Good job, ladies
and gentlemen! We did it!
The longest Christmas
kickline in Mistletoe history!
Whoo!
That was incredible.
Oh, my God, thank you.
You did it! That
was amazing.
Yeah! Thank you. My
gosh, that was so crazy!
Bradley, Bradley...
Jim needs your help
ending the feed.
I'm worried people are
gonna be seeing him stretch.
Ooh, on it.
I would call that a
success. Seriously,
pledges were coming
in left and right.
I have a really, really
good feeling about this.
Yeah?
Uh-oh. What?
You like Griffin.
No. Come on.
The endorphins got
you all mixed up.
Oh.
Bradley's right there.
Seriously.
Nothing's going on, nothing.
Stop it.
Look at Jim!
Jimbo,
what is he doing?
Darlene, CBS Morningshas
mentioned the kickline.
The video went viral. Look
how many views it has.
And donations are
still pouring in,
we only need 20 grand more.
Look at me go.
This is wonderful,
Audrey. Well done.
Round of gingerbread
lattes on the house.
Yes! Whoo! Whoo!
Whoa, whoa. What
are we celebrating?
Well, not to brag, but
numbers are looking good.
Really? Okay.
Let me see this. Look
at the comments, too.
Let me see.
"That looks like fun.
I'd like to try that.
"I hear she's a
fitness instructor.
"I'd take her class."
Look at that. Wow.
This is really good, good
publicity for you, too.
You getting nervous
about the vote tomorrow?
No. Look it, you still
got a ways to go.
Hey, people are still
donating. And it's Christmas!
This is the time for miracles.
I have never met anybody who
sees the world the way you do.
No matter what happens here,
I hope you realize just
how truly amazing you are.
Gingerbread lattes
for everybody!
Oh, wow. Oh, yay. Okay.
Whoo. Oh, me, too? Wow.
Cheers. Cheers.
Griffin.Cheers.
Cheers.Thanks.
Oh, well, look at you.
What are you all dressed up for?
Bradley's taking me on
a second first date.
Oh, so the break is over?
I'm not sure yet.Huh.
Dad, I know that look.
Uh, hey, no judgment.
Um, I just want you
to be with someone
who inspires you, and,
you know, sees you.
Funny. That's what
I want for you, too.
Darlene, Dad.
She clearly likes you.
She's kind, beautiful...
You seem to avoid her
at every chance you get.
What's going on? Do
you not like her?
I do like her.
So ask her out.
You know, your mother
was the love of my life.
Twenty-five wonderful years.
Losing her was the
most painful thing
I have ever experienced
and quite frankly, I'm not
sure I can handle that again.
Dad, I would hate it if
you missed out on love
because you were scared.
You're the bravest man I know.
Ah.
You deserve to be happy.
Don't worry about me, please.
Mom would want you to be happy.
That's Bradley.
You deserve to be happy, too.
That was delicious.Yeah.
I wish I could've taken you
somewhere nicer
for dinner, but...
Carl's Tavern is nice.
Well, soon we'll have all
our restaurant options
back at our fingertips, right?
Remember that sustainable
sushi restaurant?
That just opened right
across the street from Solis.
Oh, spicy tuna...
Bradley.
What if I didn't take
the job at Solis?
And do what instead, freelance?
Stayed here.
I really think I'm
gonna save the center
and these last few
weeks teaching here,
just feels right.
Stay in Mistletoe permanently,
I... I thought you
wanted more than this?
I haven't decided yet, I...
Just being back with
my dad and friends,
I forgot how much I love it.
Audrey, you're meant for
bigger things than Mistletoe.
I know it, you know it.
Just come back to
New York with me.
I, uh...
I should've done
this a long time ago.
I love you, Audrey Parker.
I know. It's a lot
to spring on you
and I don't want you to feel
pressured to answer right now.
Just... just hold
on to it, okay?
Hmm. Wow.
It's, um... Wow.
I know. What did you say?
Nothing yet.
What are you going to say?
I don't know. A part
of me wants to say yes.
It's what we always planned.
I know Bradley. I know
what being with him is.
With this job, things
could be really solid.
Solid. Not the most
romantic word in the world.
You just have to figure out
what it is that you
want in your life.
Is it to marry Bradley
and work for Solis?
Or is it something else?
Solis could put me on the
map. Relaunch my career.
Bradley and I could
be great together.
But...
I just feel like there's
this force or part of me
that's pulling in the
complete opposite direction.
Does that direction start with
a "G" and end with a "riffin"?
Any more donations come in?
Still short, and the
vote is in a few hours.
We could all vote no
and buy us more time.
Maybe.
The last I checked,
Jackie still hasn't
made up her mind yet.
Good.
Maybe we can find some loans or
state subsidies or something.
This can't be it.
I can't have failed
at this, too.
Do you know why your
kickline video went viral?
Because everyone loved
it. They loved you.
And no matter what happens,
I am so proud of you.
I always will be.
Thank you.
All right,
settle down, everyone.
We're officially calling
this meeting to order
and tonight's
meeting is to vote on
whether to approve
the council's decision
to sell the rec center
property to Skyridge Resorts.
Dad? Is it okay if
I say something?
Yes, absolutely.
The floor recognizes
Audrey Parker.
I know some of you heard
that the fundraiser
didn't quite hit our goal.
But we came close.
And I still believe
that there is a way
to raise the rest of the money.
So I'm asking the council,
for the sake of those who
gave what they could, please,
please vote no,
on selling the center
to Skyridge Resorts.
Give us more time.
Even if the rec center stays
empty, at least there's hope.
And isn't that what
Christmas is all about?
Thank you.
Uh, does anyone
have anything else?
I thought I'd be
hearing from you.
The floor recognizes
Griffin Weston.
Thank you.
Listen, I understand
you're hesitant to say goodbye
to something so meaningful.
But I promise you,
Skyridge Resorts
will do everything that we can
to make sure that this
town prospers and grows.
Starting by raising our offer
on the property by $1 million.
Just think
of what that'll
do for this town.
Better schools.
Better roads.
Selling us this land will mean
you won't have to
slash your budgets.
Thank you. Thank
you for your time.
Anyone else?
Then on the matter of
the Mistletoe rec center property
sale to Skyridge Resorts,
we will now take a vote.
Fred?
Aye.
Maureen?
Darlene?
Nay.
Jim?
Bob?
Aye.
And I'm a nay.
Three ayes, three nays.
That leaves Jackie.
Aye.
The ayes have it.
I'm so sorry.
I need some air.
I know you probably
hate me right now.
But I wanted to
ask you something.
Dumping money on the
problem at the last minute.
Dirty tactic.
I don't hate you.
I hate the company you work for.
That's fair.
What did you wanna ask?
Okay, if I...
If I wasn't me...
Rather, wasn't the one
that took the rec
center from you.
Do you think...
Okay, let's say we bumped
into each other at a bar.
A juice bar.
And I... I told you that
I just loved your smile.
And I really wanted
to get to know you.
And I'd never met
anyone like you.
Do you think we
might've hit it off?
Depends.
In this hypothetical,
do you insult my
Christmas decorations?
No.No?
Mm-mm.
Then, yeah.
Yeah, I think we would.
I, um... I should go.
I... I... I didn't know.
What? Wait.
No, it's okay, it's okay. You
don't owe me any explanation.
You... you deserve
to be happy.
I'm just so happy for you.
You are so much like your mom.
I heard you get up. I
figured you'd be here.
I couldn't sleep, Dad.
Yeah, me neither.
Did you hear they cancelled
the Christmas party?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it sucks. Come on, here.
How you holding up?
I'll be okay.
I just need to decide
what my next step is.
You know what?
It was about a month after your
mom got the studio up and running
and I asked her
if she missed it.
You know, the city and the
excitement and the lights.
And you know what she said?
She said I found
something better.
You?
Uh, she was talking
about freedom.
You know, she could do what
she wanted when she wanted.
New York was no longer
a dream for her.
I don't think life's
paths are ever straight.
They twist, they turn,
but I do think the best ones
take you to unexpected places.
Dad?
What are you doing here?
I had to come and congratulate
my new COO in person.
Well done, Griffin.
You know, that extra
million that you put on top,
that was smart.
Right out of my own playbook.
Do you know the surveyors
will be here on Monday?
Oh that's, um...
that's... that's good.
Great. Why don't we go out,
have a nice meal to celebrate.
They've got places to eat
around here, don't they?
Yeah, they have a good
gingerbread pancake
down at Carl's Tavern,
so we'll go there.
Gingerbread pancakes. Okay.
They are
all named Carl, on that wall.
That's certainly
quaint, isn't it?
Here you are.
Thank you.
Enjoy.Yeah.
Buddy of yours?
Yeah, we do a fitness
class together.
Pretty much everybody
here is your buddy.
You know this is good.
Yeah. Isn't it?
Tastes like Christmas.
Sure, I guess so.
Listen. Griffin,
there's this space
that's opening up
in the Poconos.
I want you there Thursday.
Dad, tell me something.
What is your favorite
thing about Christmas?
What?
Come on. We never
talk about this stuff.
Just, humor me.
Okay, well...
I guess when I was little,
I got this authentic
toy train set.
And every year, I looked
forward to getting a new part
to add to the track.
I never knew that. That...
that explains a lot.
Well, your mother was better
at that sentimental
holiday stuff.
Dad. Mm?
I don't wanna be COO.
What are they putting
in these pancakes?
Dad, listen to me, listen.
I have a plan.
But I need you to have
an open mind for this.
Hey. I got your message.
Why do you have to make five dozen
Christmas rolls in two hours?
You do know the party's
cancelled, right?
Not anymore.
Haven't you heard?
It is back on, all
thanks to Griffin. What?
Darlene,
hey. It's Griffin.
I know the rec center
Christmas party of yours
got cancelled after
yesterday's vote
but I can't let that happen.
So, party's back on.
I'll make sure it
all comes together.
I would love some of those
Christmas rolls if you have time.
Why is he doing this?
It's best not to question
a Christmas miracle.
Come on! Okay.
Dad.
I can see it.
See what?
What you saw in this place.
You're not disappointed
in our new arrangement?
No, no, no. If anything,
I'm, uh, I'm proud.
Thank you, Dad.
I love you.
I love you, Griffin.
So, where is she?
Who?
The one that clearly
inspired all of this.
No, it's not... It's
not like that. It's...
Ah, say no more.
Hey.Hi.
Griffin, don't give up.
Thank you, Dad.
Uh, excuse me, everyone,
just for a moment.
If I could just
have your attention.
It'll just take a second.
First of all...
I just wanted to,
um, thank you all
for... for coming on
such short notice.
I know how much this
party meant to you
and I wanted to make sure...
that I... that I made
it happen for you.
Um, but that's not
the only reason
that I brought you here.
I, um, I have some good news.
At least I hope it's good news.
I'm happy to announce
that... that the...
Mistletoe Skyridge will
integrate the rec center
and all of its offerings
into our new design.
And, uh, you know, I think
what's really beautiful,
is the space will be
tailored to Mistletonians
and everybody else
who lives here.
Merry Christmas to you and
long live the rec center!
Yes!
Oh, if I wasn't
clean eating right now,
I would devour one of
those Christmas rolls.
They look delicious, right?
You're missing out.
Hey, I found this great
listing, I gotta show you.
It's a loft in midtown,
so close to Solis.
It is perfect.
I'm sorry, Bradley,
I... I can't do it.
Can't do what?
Move back to New York.
I belong here.
What about our dreams?
This is my dream.
I'm going to stay in Mistletoe
and livestream classes.
Do things my way.
And us?
I'll always care about you.
I'll miss you.
Did I just see Bradley leave?
I ended it.
And?
It feels right.
You know what, often the hardest
things are the most worthwhile.
Come on.
Thanks, Dad.
I'm proud of you, sweetheart.
Dad, why don't you
take your own advice?
Darlene, Dad.
Oh... Talk to her.
Um, I don't know how
to do that anymore.
Go ask her to dance.Uh...
Go.All right.
Go!
Can I cut in,
please? Thank you.
You look very handsome
tonight, Edgar.
Thank you, Darlene.
You look...
You look absolutely beautiful.
Uh, do you think that,
uh, in the very
near future that...
you could have dinner...
with me?
What took you so long?
I'd love to.
Oh.
Ah, imagine all the tourists
that will come to ski
but stay for
Mistletoe Coffee Co.
I would say that this news is
the best Christmas present ever.
I don't know, I think I have
something that might top it.
Oh, sweetie, I thought we said
we weren't gonna do
presents until tomorrow.
Just open it.Okay.
Wait. Wait, are... you're...
is this... we're...
I mean you, mainly, but we're...
Yes.
Wow. Uh, let's
name him Griffin.
What? Joke. I'm
joking. It's a joke.
Who knew Griffin Weston could
throw a Christmas party?
Well,
I had some help
and it's just all about
capturing a feeling.
Oh.
You look stunning.
Not so bad yourself.
So, was all that true?
About saving the rec center
and keeping it as is?
Every word of it.
Yeah, we're gonna find a way
to build it into
the whole system.
I'm
shocked. Elated.
Just... shocked.
It's all because of you.
You inspired me to
follow my own path.
You showed me how
special this town was,
how special
Christmas was, how...
how special you are.
Now, I know you're engaged...
I'm not engaged.
I know you saw me with the ring,
and then, we were talking and...
I just needed you to know that.
So you two...
Are over. Over.
Really? Yeah.
That's great.
I mean... I'm sorry.
I mean, "Oh, no."
Are you okay?
Stop.
You know, it turns out,
you're pretty inspiring, too.
Really? Is that so?
Well, your whole
livestream idea,
it helped me figure
out my new path.
And I'll be able to
teach all my classes
right here in Mistletoe.
To reach anyone, anywhere.
Funny thing about that
is I'm staying here, too.
You're looking at the new
operations manager of the resort.
Oh.
I have to stay here to make sure
that my vision becomes a reality.
So we'll both be
here... together.
Yeah.Hmm.
Well, would
you look at that!
Mistletoe.
Someone once told me it's
not to be messed with.