Surprise!
(CHUCKLES)
Not yet, Olaf.
Surprise!
(WOMEN GASP)
WOMEN: Not yet, Olaf.
Surprise!
(GASPS)
(SIGHS) Not yet, Olaf.
Whoa!
Hello!
Surprise!
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES) Olaf! Not yet!
ELSA: Anna's right.
Our surprise holiday party
doesn't start
until after
the Jule bell rings.
Sorry, the suspense
is tearing me apart.
Thank you!
(CHUCKLES)
I'm excited too, Olaf.
This is Arendelle's
first Christmas in forever.
The first of many to come.
Elsa, look!
They're arriving!
♪ Look at everyone
♪ They don't realize
(GASPS) What?
♪ We planned a party
as a big surprise
♪ Soon the ballroom will echo
With sounds of cheer
♪ As we ring in
the season this year
♪ This is overdue
♪ Gotta look our best
Ooh!
♪ I've never been
so nicely dressed
♪ We'll be hosting
and toasting
♪ The whole night through
♪ As we ring in
the season with you
♪ It's the first Christmas
in forever
♪ Since we opened up
the gate
♪ And it's the first Christmas
I remember to date
♪ And it's already
worth the wait
(CROWD CHEERING)
♪ Look at all the joy
♪ All the joy
♪ And it's everywhere
♪ Everywhere
♪ I feel the Christmas spirit
in the air
♪ Feel the spirit
♪ And the party will start
At the strike of noon
♪ And we'll ring
in the season so soon
OLAF: Hey!
It's Kristoff and Sven!
(GASPS) And the Jule bell!
Why am I so excited
about that?
Olaf,
the Jule bell signals
the start of the holidays
in Arendelle.
Ooh!
♪ And it's almost time
to ring the bell
♪ We'll hear it chime
through Arendelle
♪ It's finally here
and it's happening fast
♪ We'll make up for all
We have missed in the past
♪ It's time to celebrate
♪ As we ring in the season
♪ At last ♪
(TOLLING)
Let the holidays begin!
(CHEERING)
Okay, now!
(CHUCKLES) Surprise!
(GASPS)
OLAF: Uh-oh.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
Going so soon?
The Jule bell rang.
I must get home
for my family's
holiday tradition...
rolling the lefse.
Um...
Ours is putting out porridge
for the Tomte.
We're making traditional
bordstabelbakkels!
And I'm gonna filet
the krumsakringlekakke!
That's a thing, right?
Oh, Mr. and Mrs. Olsen?
You're welcome to join us
in the castle if you'd like.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
But Olga and I
should be getting home
to knit socks
for our grandchildren.
It's our tradition.
(LAUGHS) Yes.
And we wouldn't
want to intrude
on your family traditions.
(SIGHS)
Oh, so the surprise
is everyone left.
Hey, I say it's their loss.
Who needs
a big party anyway?
Kristoff?
I've got just the thing
to cheer you up:
my favorite traditional
troll tradition.
Care to join in?
Uh, yeah!
Okay, it starts
with a gathering song,
"The Ballad of Flemmingrad."
I love ballads!
♪ Every December
we all gather round
♪ To pay our respects
To a troll so renowned
♪ In remembrance
of the friend we had
♪ A jolly old soul
we called Flemmingrad
Tempo!
♪ We all dig deep down
And we uproot the past
♪ We shove up its nostrils
A fistful of grass
Nostrils?
♪ We shape his likeness
Bless his soul
(SHRIEKS)
Whoa, gross.
♪ Oh Flemmy
The fungus troll ♪
Now, you lick his forehead
and make a wish.
(LICKS) Who's next?
Elsa, you're up.
(GAGS)
Come on.
Tastes like lichen.
You're a princess.
You don't have to settle.
Okay. Not so much
a royal activity.
I get it.
But wait until you taste
my traditional Flemmy stew.
It may smell like wet fur,
but it's a real
crowd pleaser.
Oh, thanks.
We're good.
Big breakfast.
(CHUCKLES)
(OLAF EXCLAIMS)
(CHUCKLES) I can't wait!
ELSA: For what, Olaf?
For your family tradition.
What is it?
Tell me, tell me,
tell me!
Do we have
any traditions, Elsa?
Do you remember?
Well, I remember...
♪ It was long ago
♪ They would ring the bell
♪ We could hear it chime
through Arendelle
♪ I remember the way
that I felt back then
♪ We would ring in
the season
the season ♪
But the Jule bell was
for the kingdom.
What about us?
After the gates were closed,
we were never together.
(SIGHS)
Elsa?
ELSA: I'm sorry, Anna.
It's my fault we don't have
a family tradition.
Wait, Elsa...
(SIGHS)
(OLAF WHIMPER)
(GASPS)
Sven! Anna and Elsa
don't have a family tradition.
(WHIMPERS)
I know it's sad...
but I have a solution!
We'll go and find
the best tradition
Anna and Elsa
have ever seen...
and bring it back
to the castle!
Are you with me?
Ow!
Let's go
find their tradition!
House number one.
Wow, festive.
WOMAN: Coming!
Good afternoon.
I am Olaf, and...
Hey, Olaf!
Please let me finish,
and I like warm hugs.
This is my associate, Sven.
We're going door to door
looking for
family traditions.
Tell us yours,
and we'll decide if
it's special enough.
Oh! We make
candy canes together.
Ooh!
(CHUCKLES)
Sugar rush!
You're supposed to eat it.
Eat my new nose?
Why would I do that?
Because it's that time
of year!
Hmm.
It's that time of year!
(CLEARS THROAT)
♪ Happy, merry, holly, jolly
Season's greetings here
♪ I'm wondering
what your family does
♪ At that time of year
♪ Love and joy
and peace on earth
♪ And tidings of good cheer
♪ Do you
have tradition things
♪ For that time of year?
♪ Well, we hang up
boughs of evergreen
♪ On every single doorway
♪ Bake a giant cookie
In the wavy shape of Norway
♪ Go from door
to door to door
Wassailing with our choir!
♪ Hang up
all your giant socks
Above an open fire
That sounds safe.
♪ So happy, merry,
yuletide carol
♪ Faithful friends are deer
♪ Thanks for sharing
what you do
♪ At that time of year
(CLOCK CHIMES)
(GASPS) We better get
a move on
if we're gonna hit
every house in the kingdom.
(NEIGHS)
♪ Jolly, merry, happy, holly
On a midnight clear
♪ I'm here to ask you
what you do
♪ At that time of year
♪ Hi, shalom, happy solstice
Fancy chandelier
♪ I'm looking
for tradition stuff
♪ For that time of year
♪ Well, we make
our decorations
♪ Out of flotsam and jetsam
♪ Bake a yummy fruitcake
♪ And you can't leave
till you get some
That went right through me.
♪ Buy each other presents
♪ And then hide them
very nimbly
♪ Wait up for a chubby man
To shimmy down your chimney
Breaking and entering:
okay on Christmas.
♪ Oh, happy,
merry mule-tied barrels
♪ Faithful, gladsome cheer
♪ And thanks for sharing
what you do
♪ At that time of year
Thank you.
♪ We knit scarves
and sweaters
♪ And we wear
our matching mittens
♪ Don't forget
the jammies
♪ That I knitted
for my kittens
♪ Eight nights in a row
♪ We light menorahs
on our mantels
You cut down a tree...
and then you dress
its corpse with candles.
(KIDS WHIMPER)
I love it!
♪ Anna and Elsa
♪ Will have all that
they need
♪ I'll fill my sleigh here
♪ With the help of my steed
♪ It'll be the best
time of year
♪ It's up to you
♪ Up to me
Me, me
♪ Up to...
♪ Mew
♪ Oh, happy, merry,
Mele Kaliki
♪ Holly, jolly, happy tappy
♪ Chubby man
will soon appear
♪ And faithful friends
are tiny deer
♪ And festive tidings
midnight clear, and...
Can I leave
this fruitcake here?
♪ At that time of year ♪
(MEWS)
Last house, Sven.
Something tells me this will
be the best tradition yet!
Yoo-hoo.
Hello.
And what does your family do
at that time of year?
(CHUCKLES) Oh!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Enjoying the Christmas sweats,
inquisitive magic snowman?
Oh, yeah!
Nothin' like
taking your coals off
once in a while.
You know what I mean?
My troubles
are just melting away.
In retrospect,
the holiday sweats
are for those
not made of snow.
(SPLUTTERS)
Oh, I feel so refreshed!
Am I glowing?
(GRUNTS) Here's a sauna
for your friends.
Thank you,
Mr. Wandering Oaken.
Oh, one last thing.
Would it be possible to get
one of those
awkwardly revealing...
yet tastefully
traditional towels
your family is
so fond of wearing?
Take mine, yeah?
(DOOR CLOSES)
OLAF: Still warm.
♪ Dashing through the snow
♪ With traditions
in our sleigh
♪ Back to the castle we go
To save this holiday
♪ Ho, ho, ho
♪ Our plan has zero flaws
I see nothing going wrong ♪
(SHRIEKS)
Whew! Crisis averted.
(WHISTLING)
Oh, look, another reindeer
going the opposite direction.
Hi!
Wow, we're making
really good time!
(GASPS)
Hey! The fire's out.
(EXPLODES)
Oh, darn it.
(SIGHS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Anna, I owe you
an apology for earlier.
Anna?
(CLATTERS)
(GASPS)
Hi, Elsa!
(SIGHS) Anna!
What are you doing up here?
Looking for traditions.
Ooh! (CHUCKLES)
And what are you wearing?
My old Viking helmet...
and this was
my sorceress cloak.
Dragon feet!
(MIMICS GROWLING)
(LAUGHS)
I found them
in my old trunk.
What's in yours?
Oh, mostly gloves.
Right. Rows and rows
of satin gloves.
Oh.
Yep. Welcome to my world.
Wait. Who's this little guy?
Oh! Sir Jorgenbjorgen!
He was a really good listener.
Anna, how are we going to
find any traditions up here?
(BELL JINGLES SOFTLY)
Unless...
What's that?
Look inside.
(GASPS)
OLAF: Okay, Sven...
I'm not gonna sugarcoat it.
This is a bit of a setback.
Ooh!
Maybe this is salvageable.
No, definitely not.
Oh, parts of this
are still good, I think.
Oh, no,
this is unsafe now.
(GASPS) Hey, the fruitcake!
These things
are indestructible!
I'll just take this seemingly
harmless shortcut here...
and meet you back
at the castle, okay?
(WOLVES HOWLING)
OLAF: Oh, puppies!
(WOLVES GROWLING)
Down, boy.
Ah! I'm just
gonna go now!
(OLAF SCREAMING)
Hey!
MAN: Whoa!
WOMAN: No!
Oh, Sven!
The Flemmy stew is ready!
Anna and Elsa
are gonna love this.
(GRUNTING)
"Oh, Kristoff,
you're so thoughtful.
"Now where's my bowl?"
Hey, simmer down, buddy.
Here you go.
Whoa, what are you...
Oh! Of course!
"Needs more carrots!"
Can't get enough of 'em,
can ya?
(CHUCKLING)
(MIMICS WOLF HOWLING)
(GROWLING)
Uh...
Oh, no!
Olaf's lost in the forest?
And being chased
by hungry wolves?
Yeah. Obviously.
Ring the bell.
Gather everyone!
Come on, Sven!
Make yourself useful.
Olaf needs our help.
(BELL RINGING)
(WOLVES HOWLING)
(PANTING)
Okay.
Please,
I know you're hungry...
but I need
at least one tradition
for my best friends.
The fate of the world
depends on it!
(SCREAMS)
(SIGHS AND GASPS)
Yes! Yes, I did it!
A tradition is saved!
(HAWK SHRIEKS)
Well, I guess hawks need
traditions too.
(SIGHS)
♪ Happy, merry,
holly, jolly
♪ Tidings of good cheer
(SNIFFLES)
♪ I never meant
to let them down
♪ At that time of year ♪
(SIGHS)
Maybe I should just
stay lost.
(WHIMPERS)
(WIND HOWLING)
(INAUDIBLE)
TEENAGER: Olaf!
MAN: Olaf, where are you?
KID: Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
Any sign of him?
No.
(SIGHS)
Olaf?
Olaf? Where are you?
OLAF: He's not here.
(ANNA GASPS)
Oh.
Hmm. I wonder
where he went.
OLAF: Well, he probably
went on a mission
to find traditions
for Anna and Elsa.
Oh. And did he find any?
OLAF: He did...
but then they caught fire
and fell off a cliff.
And then
they caught fire again.
And then a hawk took them.
(SIGHS)
I'm sorry.
You still don't have
a tradition.
But we do, Olaf.
Look.
(GASPS) Wait...
is that...
ELSA: Anna made these
years ago.
When we first made you.
"Hi, I'm Olaf."
You were the one
who brought us together...
and kept us connected
when we were apart.
ANNA: Every Christmas...
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
I made Elsa a gift.
ELSA: All those
long years alone...
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
we had you to remind us
of our childhood.
ANNA: Of how much
we still loved each other.
ELSA: It's you, Olaf.
You are our tradition.
Me?
Surprise!
Aw!
♪ Sure, it's nice
to open a gift
♪ That's tied up
with a perfect bow
♪ But the greatest
present of all
♪ Was given to me long ago
♪ It's something
I would never trade
Olaf!
♪ It's the family
that we've made
We were worried
about you!
♪ 'Cause when
we're together
♪ I have everything
on my list
♪ And when we're together
♪ I have all I wished
♪ All around
the Christmas tree
♪ There'll be dreams
coming true
♪ But when we're together
♪ Then my favorite gift
is you
(GIGGLING)
♪ I would travel
miles and miles
♪ And I would follow
any star
♪ I'd go almost any place
♪ If it's any place
you are
♪ 'Cause when
we're together
♪ When we're together
♪ I'll forever
feel at home
♪ And when we're together
♪ When we're together
♪ We'll be safe and warm
♪ Safe and warm
♪ Doesn't matter where we are
If you're there with me
♪ 'Cause when we're together
♪ That's my favorite
place to be
♪ To be
♪ 'Cause when
we're together
♪ It's a holiday
every night
♪ And when we're together
♪ Then the season's bright
♪ Season's bright
♪ I don't need
the bells to ring
♪ I don't need the bells
♪ I'll know when it's here
♪ 'Cause when
we're together
♪ I could stay forever
♪ And when we're together
♪ It's my favorite
♪ Time of year ♪
Well, I think Arendelle
has a new tradition.
Thank you, Olaf.
(HAWK SHRIEKS)
Ooh!
OLAF: (GASPS) The fruitcake!
It's a Christmas miracle!
(JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING)