Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Whoa!
I'm okay.
Truck 416,
what's your location?
Just passing through a sleepy little
town called Adventure Bay. Over.
Oh!
That's cold, that's cold!
Oh, ooh, ooh!
I got blue slushie
in my skivvies!
Cold, cold, cold!
Ahhh! Look out, little guy!
No, no, no, no, no!
Whoa!
Hang in there! Oh, no!
Oh, no! No!
No, no, no!
Hello! Down there!
Oh, my.
That's not good.
That's not
good at all.
Good morning there, friend!
Looks like you're in a particularly
precarious predicament.
Call the police!
Call the fire department!
Call everybody!
You're in Adventure Bay.
Here, we call
the PAW Patrol!
You're gonna call the who?
♪ PAW Patrol, PAW Patrol
♪ We'll be there
on the double
♪ Whenever there's a problem
♪ Round Adventure Bay
♪ Ryder and his team of pups
♪ Will come and save the day
♪ Marshall, Rubble, Chase
♪ Rocky, Zuma, Skye
♪ Yeah, they're on the way
♪ PAW Patrol, PAW Patrol
♪ Whenever you're in trouble
♪ We'll be there
on the double
♪ No job's too big,
no pup's too small
♪ PAW Patrol,
we're on a roll!
♪ So here we go
PAW Patrol
♪ Whoa-oh-oh
♪ PAW Patrol
♪ Whoa-oh-oh-oh
♪ PAW Patrol ♪
All
right, pups, here we go.
Let's work together
out there.
Rocky, I need you to shut down
the bridge and control traffic.
Arf! Flares!
Zuma, I need you to keep
that waterway clear.
Nobody under the bridge.
You got it, Ryder!
Waterway secure!
Chase, it's all
up to you.
Use the winch in your pup pack to get
the driver and bring him to safety!
Chase is on the case!
Arf!
Grappling hook!
Sir, don't be alarmed.
I'm coming down!
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank
you, the rescue team is here!
A dog?
Actually, sir,
I'm a puppy.
A baby dog?
That's even worse!
You're in shock, so I'm not
going to take that personally.
Now, let's get you
out of here.
No way! I'm waiting
right here for a real rescue.
Ahhh!
I changed my mind,
I'll go with you!
Ryder! These cables aren't
going to hold much longer!
Let's go, Chase.
Get him out of there!
We're coming out!
Oh! Oh!
Don't panic.
I need you to stay calm.
No deal!
I'm freaking out!
Then you're really
not going to like this!
Ahhh!
We're not going to make it.
We're not going to make it!
Ah!
You can open
your eyes now.
Oh, we made it.
Great work,
PAW Patrol!
Everybody
get back!
The truck's leaking gas!
Oh, come on,
that's not gas.
That's the stuff I've been
hauling from coast to coast.
That is pure
Canadian maple syrup!
Okay, time to
clean up this mess.
Deploy waffles, pancakes,
and French toast!
It's okay, little guy,
you're safe.
You can
come out now.
Let's get you
back to your family.
There you go.
Great work, pups.
Another perfect rescue.
♪ I woke up this morning
And I took a look outside
♪ And I was like
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah ♪
Oh! Um...
Hey. Excuse me?
You dropped something.
I'm done with it.
Buzz off, wiener dog.
"Wiener dog"?
Maybe you should just pick that
up and put it in the trash!
Yeah? Or what?
Or I'm going to pick you up
and put you in the trash.
Hey, I don't want no trouble.
I'm pickin' up the trash,
I'm pickin' up the trash.
Thank you. We've all got
to take pride in our city.
Don't ever forget that.
This is the D train...
This is my stop.
It's been a slice.
I'm going to turn my life around.
I really am.
♪ I've got
a real good feeling
Hey, Liberty!
♪ I've got a real
good feeling
♪ That we're doing
something right ♪
It's election day
in Adventure City.
I'm Marty Muckraker,
reporting live from City Square.
In a surprising twist,
the leading candidate
has dropped out of the race,
leaving only one name
on the ticket.
Mayor Humdinger,
who has just won by default.
Mayor Humdinger.
Ugh!
Just saying it
makes my skin crawl.
No dogs.
By order of the new mayor.
- Excuse me?
- Yeah, you heard him.
No dogs.
He's more of a cat person.
Now beat it!
If those are the rules,
those are the rules.
You gentlemen
have a wonderful day.
Ha-ha!
Did you see that?
You gotta show these
dogs you're the alpha.
You're not the alpha.
I'm the alpha!
- No, I'm the alpha!
I'm the
alpha!
Right this
way, ma'am.
- I'm the alpha!
- No. I'm the alpha!
- Thanks for the lift!
- Happy to help.
Excuse me, coming through,
make way,
pardon me, underfoot.
Please welcome
to the stage,
a man who needs
no introduction.
He's literally the greatest
human being on the planet.
He's... Me!
♪ I am the champion ♪
Thank you, thank you.
- Really?
- Yeah...
I want to start off
by thanking
each and every one of you
for choosing me
to be your new mayor.
You were the only
name on the ballot!
You could only vote for one name
anyway, so what does it matter?
I won this election
fair and square.
Well, maybe not fair,
but who's keeping track?
You know, they call this place
Adventure City,
but what's so adventure-y
about it?
The truth is, it's boring.
Libraries? Boring!
Museums? Boring!
Cute little dog parks?
Aw.
Ugh! Definitely boring!
But don't worry.
I'm going to put the adventure
back in Adventure City!
When I'm done with this place,
you won't even recognize it.
PAW Patrol.
What's your emergency?
What? You answer
your own calls?
Oh, my goodness,
I didn't even think I was gonna...
Oh!
I can't believe
I'm looking at the PAW Patrol!
I am such a big fan!
This is off the leash!
Is there something
we can help you with?
Yes, yes, yes!
My name is Liberty,
and I'm calling from Adventure City.
Something terrible
has happened.
Humdinger was just
elected mayor.
Humdinger?
He's the worst mayor
in the history of mayors!
And that's
being generous.
You're telling me,
this guy's a disaster!
He's going to destroy
the whole city.
Please, we need your help.
Come quickly!
Adventure City's in trouble.
Come on, pups,
pack your things.
No city's too big,
no pup's too small!
Yeah!
What's wrong, Chase?
I'm not going.
We have to go.
They need us.
I'm never going back to
Adventure City!
Chase...
What's got his leash in a knot?
Chase has a history
with Adventure City.
He has a lot of tough memories
from that place.
He was abandoned there
as a pup.
The city was so big,
and he was so small.
It was a hard life.
The city can be a scary place
when you're all alone.
- Is that where you found him?
- That's right.
And I brought him back here
to Adventure Bay.
Chase?
Let's talk
about this.
I don't want to go back to
Adventure City.
I know it was tough,
but that was a long time ago.
I'm afraid
if I go back there,
everyone will see I'm still
that scared little puppy,
and not the hero
they think I am.
I promise it will be nothing
like it was when you were little.
Everything will be fine.
Come on, Chase.
Those people need our help.
We're the PAW Patrol,
this is what we do.
Trust me.
Okay. I trust you.
Now, can I get a yelp?
Come on. You can do
better than that.
Attaboy!
Let's get to work.
Skye, Chase, Rocky,
Marshall, Zuma...
Rubble!
It's not my fault!
I couldn't decide what to bring.
So I brought everything!
Get there, come on.
Come on, come on!
See? It fits!
PAW Patrol is on a roll!
Road trip!
♪ Hop in my ride
Don't you know
♪ We got the sun Always
shining Wherever we go
♪ Don't need no map
We just roll
♪ Let the vibe give direction
Take control
♪ When it's good
When it's bad
♪ Yeah, you got me
♪ And when I turn around
- Hi!
♪ You got a way to make
a problem disappear
♪ Up to the clouds
Bye!
♪ I'm spinning around
♪ And now you know why
♪ 'Cause no one in this world
Can make me feel loved
♪ In the way that you do now
♪ No, no one in this world
can make me come down
♪ When I'm in such a good mood now
♪ Yeah
♪ Good mood
♪ Good mood ♪
Wake up, pups,
we're here!
Oh, wow!
- Check it out!
- Cool!
- No way!
- It's amazing!
This place is so much
bigger than Adventure Bay.
You okay, Chase?
It's a lot bigger
than I remember.
It's like they super-sized it!
Ugh! Rain!
Does it always rain
in this lousy city?
Okay, which one of you
eggheads is in charge?
- Hello!
- Gah!
I'm the lead egghead.
Kendra Wilson.
Hmm.
I've got a fireworks
celebration tonight
and they're going to cancel
it because of the rain.
I hear you have a weather
machine that sucks up clouds.
Is that true?
You're looking at it.
It's a free-floating
gyroscopically balanced
remote-controlled weather
containment and analysis apparatus.
What? I don't understand
a word you just said.
Well...
We call it the Cloud Catcher.
It flies around
and sucks up clouds,
then brings them back to the
lab so we can study them.
Excellent,
excellent.
Well, kitties, it looks like our
bad weather problem is solved.
I want all those pesky rain clouds
sucked up by the end of the day.
Oh! I'm sorry
if I wasn't clear.
The Cloud Catcher is for
studying clouds,
not for changing
the weather.
And I'm sorry
if I wasn't clear.
Suck up those clouds or I'm
closing this university forever!
Well...
I guess we could try using
it to clear the rain clouds.
- Just for tonight.
- Wonderful!
That's what I call
scientific consensus!
Oh!
My top hat!
Here you go, boss.
That's incredible!
We'll have the sky
clear by sundown.
Ugh! I've got a bad
feeling about this.
I'll hang on to this remote!
People are going to
love these fireworks,
and more importantly,
they're going to love me!
All right, pups,
keep an eye out for the new headquarters.
- We're almost there.
- Yeah!
- Cool!
- I can't wait!
- Where is it?
- There are so many buildings!
I wonder
which one it is.
Whoa!
Oh.
Yeah.
Couldn't have missed that.
Whoa!
Welcome to our new
Adventure City headquarters.
- Whoa!
- Wow!
Awesome!
Now that's a view!
Whoa!
How can we afford
this place?
Officially licensed
PAW Patrol merchandise.
This stuff sells
like hot cakes!
We've got everything we need
at our fingertips.
Ahhh!
- Marshall!
Next time, warn me before you
stick a building up my nose!
This is
so cool!
It's so high-tech!
And check this out.
There's even a new and
improved pup treat dispenser.
What? It's a
beautiful thing.
Last but not least,
this is our mission prep area.
Everybody's got
their own cubby.
Oh, Oh, Oh!
I want that one!
No, Rubble, don't!
No, cubby belongs to...
Skye!
...Skye.
Oops.
It's not important how it looks,
it's how it makes you feel.
I think you guys are going to
have to cut me out of this thing.
Actually, I'm good.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I've gathered you here tonight
for a very important reason.
To celebrate me!
Prepare to be blown away
by the most breathtaking fireworks
display you've ever seen!
Time to light up the sky!
Yeesh! This is less
than spectacular.
You, ponytail man!
Why are you taking so long
between fireworks?
I'm building
momentum, man.
I have a whole routine
mapped out in my head.
Nobody's got time for your
self-indulgent,
hippy-dippy art project.
They want spectacle!
Rock and roll, man!
Yay!
They're all for me!
Ahhh!
Oh, boy!
Whoa!
Oh! Wow!
How often do you get to see
fireworks this close?
My top hat!
- Here you go, boss!
- Ahhh!
This is why
dogs hate fireworks!
Whoa...
I'm no expert,
but aren't fireworks supposed
to explode in the sky?
Let's see what's going on!
It looks like Mayor
Humdinger's fireworks display
has turned into
a fireworks disaster.
We've got to stop those fireworks
before they burn down the city.
Time to suit up!
Whoa!
Thanks, robot arm!
PAW Patrol, ready for action,
Ryder sir!
Whoa!
This is your new car.
Wow!
Awesome!
So cool!
I could get used to this.
You better hang on
to your hat.
Chase!
Ready for launch in five...
Four... Three... Two... One.
Go!
♪ PAW Patrol
♪ Go, go, go, go, go
♪ Go, PAW Patrol
Marshall. Go!
♪ Go, go, go, go, go
Skye.
Ready for launch!
♪ PAW Patrol
Skye is go for launch.
Go!
Whoa! That's got a kick to it!
♪ PAW Patrol ♪
PAW Patrol
is on a roll...
Are you kidding me?
Come on!
This is ridiculous!
Green means go!
Green does still
mean go, right?
You're taking Main Street
at rush hour?
No wonder
you're stuck in traffic!
I'm Liberty.
We spoke on the phone.
So nice to finally
meet you in person.
Ryder.
What your team needs
is a pup like me.
I know the city
like the back of my paw.
Uptown, downtown,
crosstown, midtown.
24-7, 365, I'll get you
where you need to be!
Well, we could use a hand
getting out of this traffic jam.
That's what I'm talking about.
My first assignment!
- Get out of the way! Move!
- Okay!
Move!
You've got to know
how to talk to people.
Now go!
Excuse me.
Pardon me!
Coming through!
Have a nice day!
Turn here!
Left!
Right, then right again,
right away!
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoo-hoo!
Ha-ha! You see that?
I'm like a furry GPS!
Ahhh! Turn left!
Whoa!
You have reached
your destination.
Now we know what happens when
you give Humdinger fireworks!
The PAW Patrol?
What are they doing
in Adventure City?
Chase, set up a perimeter.
Chase is on the case!
PAW Patrol!
Arf! Shields!
Marshall, Rocky,
put out those fireworks!
Let's kick the tires
and fight some fires!
Mr. Mayor, we've got
to get you out of here.
I can't believe the PAW
Patrol crashed my party.
- Yes, sir.
- I can't stand those dogs!
Everyone knows
you're a cat person.
- I can't stand them!
- Yes, sir.
Hey, wait up!
Time to fight some fireworks!
We're gonna need more water!
Arf! Water cannon!
Yes! Now that's what
I'm talking about.
- Nice work, Marshall!
- Thank you.
Rocky, you're up!
Okay, I got it from here!
And crush 'em!
Whoa! Whoa!
Ride 'em, cowboy!
Look at him go!
Perimeter secure!
Ryder, we've got people trapped
on the balcony! I'm going in.
Copy that.
Arf! Eject!
Arf! Parachute!
Everything's going to be fine.
I'm going
to get you out of here.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Ryder, help!
Marshall! Chase needs help!
I'm on it!
Stand back!
Get away from the edge!
Help me get him down!
- Careful.
- Help me get him off.
It's okay, buddy.
I've got you.
- Say cheese!
- Cheese!
Hey! Hey! Anyone want
a picture with me?
I'm kind of like an honorary
member of the PAW Patrol.
You should have
seen me out there.
I was like, "Turn left, turn
right, turn left, turn right..."
It was amazing!
You look okay.
How do you feel?
I can't believe I forgot
to disconnect my parachute.
It's Air Rescue 101.
Well, that's why
we're a team.
Everyone pulled together,
and things worked out okay.
But what if
they didn't?
What if something happened to those
people and it was all my fault?
Guardians. Heroes.
Cute little dogs
in adorable outfits.
Whatever you call them,
the PAW Patrol were here
to save the city
from Mayor Humdinger's
disastrous fireworks debacle.
As a professional journalist,
it's important that I remain unbiased.
That being said...
Oh, yikes!
An embarrassing start
for Mayor Humdinger,
but an incredible debut for the
PAW Patrol in Adventure City!
PAW Patrol? PAW Patrol?
I'm sick and tired of
hearing about the PAW Patrol!
I came to Adventure City
to get away from them
and make a name for myself.
Now they're all over the TV
stealing my headlines!
Butch! Ruben! Get in here!
Oh!
Sorry, sir.
I want the PAW Patrol
off the streets now!
Find them, catch them,
and lock them away.
- Yes, sir.
- Right away, sir.
The PAW Patrol have humiliated
me for the last time!
Sorry, did you
say something?
What? No, no!
I was just having
a private moment!
Now get out of here!
♪ Just a jump away
from where you wanna go
♪ But you're too afraid
of doing it alone
♪ So getting halfway there
is all you've ever known
♪ I've been down that road ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Hold your head up
♪ You'll find your way home
♪ You won't get
what you give sometimes
♪ But when the dust all settles
♪ And the smoke
all clears up
♪ It's pieces of yourself
you're gonna find
♪ Maybe that's the use
in trying
♪ It's pieces of yourself
you're gonna find
♪ Maybe that's the use
in trying ♪
Liberty!
I hear that sound,
and I know it's you.
"Eee-ooo-eee-ooo-eee-ooo!"
I know, I know, I've got
to get my wagon fixed.
So, how's the fruit
business, Tony?
Well, it would be better if I
wasn't always giving you free fruit.
Hey, you hear about that
fireworks fiasco last night?
I didn't just hear about
it, I was there.
Honestly, Tony,
it was the best night of my life.
For a few hours, it was like I was
a real member of the PAW Patrol.
Imagine that, huh?
"The newest member of
the PAW Patrol, Liberty!"
Yeah, right, I wish.
I heard that new mayor is
monkeying with the subway now.
You better stay off
those trains, kiddo.
- Stick to your wagon.
- Thanks for the tip, Tony.
Hey, Liberty.
Take one for the road!
Thank you!
Another perfect day
in Adventure City.
Enjoy that sunbeam, kitties.
Mr. Mayor!
The Cloud Catcher's hygrometer
is overloading the capacity
of its pressurized internal
containment chamber!
What? Do I look like
a scientist to you?
We need to bring down
the Cloud Catcher now!
And ruin this
beautiful weather?
The Cloud Catcher wasn't
designed to run non-stop.
Nonsense!
As long as I'm mayor,
the sun will always shine
on Adventure City.
Now get her out of here.
Get out of here!
What are you doin'? I'm the one who
tells people to get out of here.
No, you're not.
I'm in charge!
- No, I'm in charge!
- I'm in charge!
I'm in charge!
Citizens of Adventure City!
As your new, and already
favorite, mayor,
I proudly present
the next step in my plan
to put the adventure
in Adventure City.
The Humdinger Hyperloop!
The kookiest, swoopiest,
loop-de-loopiest subway
the world has ever seen!
Mmm-mmm. I am not
riding that thing.
Mr. Mayor,
Mr. Mayor!
Have you considered the possibility
that this is the single dumbest idea
that anyone
has ever had ever?
I'm an unqualified
elected official.
What's the worst
that could happen?
Look, here comes
the express train now.
Throw the switch, kitties!
Whee!
Ooh! That is not good.
Butch, get the car.
Ruben, get the kitties.
Time for me to vamoose!
PAW Patrol,
what's your emergency?
Help! Help us!
Mayor Humdinger stuck a loop-de-loop
in the middle of the subway track,
and now, we're hanging on
for dear life!
This is a new low for
subway service in this city,
and that is
saying something!
Hang tight!
We're on our way!
Okay, pups.
We've got to rescue the
passengers on that train
before the whole thing
comes crashing down.
Let's move!
PAW Patrol is on a roll!
Yeah!
Marty Muckraker reporting live from
Mayor Humdinger's latest disaster.
In a surprising twist
that surprised nobody,
the shoddily built
upside-down subway
turned out to be
a steaming hot pile of,
dare I say, poop.
Look, Mom,
the PAW Patrol!
I can't believe Humdinger
thought this was a good idea.
The subway's wild enough
without a stinkin' loop-de-loop!
Hey, Liberty!
Reporting for duty.
Unofficially, of course.
You know, like an honorary member.
Rocky, I need you
to stabilize that loop.
Rubble, see if you can
lock it into place
with some
quick-dry cement.
We're on it!
Skye, I need you to
secure that loop from the air.
Let's take to the sky!
Don't worry, Ryder, I've got
crowd control under control.
Stand back!
Give us some space!
PAW Patrol at work!
I'm an honorary member
at the moment,
but my authority
should still be respected.
Arf! Hydraulic arms!
Gotcha!
- Hey, look!
- It's Skye!
Time for a little more power.
Arf! Afterburners!
Okay, Rubble, let 'er rip!
Rubble on the double!
The track is secure!
Yeah, Rubble!
Nice work, Rubble!
Chase, we've got to
rescue those people.
Are you up for it?
Chase is on the case.
Hang on!
You're going to be okay.
Arf! Zipline!
Chase! Chase! Chase!
How are you
holding up, Chase?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
I can do this!
- Chase! Chase!
- You can do it, Chase!
I can do this.
Chase! Chase!
I can...
Chase?
Chase, do you copy?
Ryder, we've got a problem.
What's going on?
It's Chase.
Something's wrong.
He's just standing there.
Chase is in trouble.
Skye, bring him down.
Marshall, get your ladder up
to the train.
I'm on it!
I think I can
reach them from here.
Arf! Ladder!
Please exit the
train and proceed down the ladder.
This should speed things up.
Arf! Ladder slide!
Here goes nothing!
Whoo-hoo!
Nice work, Marshall!
Chase?
I'm coming out to get you.
What's wrong?
Tell me what happened.
I don't know.
I just froze.
It's okay. Everyone's safe.
Let's get you down.
Okay, that's all of them.
Good job, pups.
Chase...
I don't know
what happened.
I'm just glad
you're okay.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's my fault.
I thought you'd be
okay in Adventure City,
but it's still
too much for you.
I'll be fine.
I just need to...
You're not fine.
You need to take a break.
We'll take care of the
rescues for a while.
What? No!
That's not fair.
I'm sorry, Chase.
I know it's hard,
but it's the way it's got to be.
I didn't even want to
come to Adventure City!
I trusted you.
You said everything would be
fine, but it's not!
What kind of leader gives up on
someone the second things get hard?
Chase...
Chase, wait!
Oh-ho!
What do we
have here?
Looks like we got one of them
PAW Patrols all on his own.
Get the net.
Chase? Chase!
- Come on, Chase.
- Chase?
Chase!
Hey, buddy,
where are you?
Where'd you go, bud? Chase!
- Oh, no.
- Where did he go?
I was right
behind him.
I turned the corner
and he was gone.
He just disappeared.
- What are we going to do?
- I don't know.
There's no way for us to track him
if he's not wearing his pup tag.
We might not have
a tracking collar,
but the city has eyes,
and the city has ears.
Somebody had
to see something.
Okay.
Where do we start?
We need to pound
the pavement.
I'll get my jackhammer!
No, not like that.
"Pound the pavement" means we're
gonna need to talk to everyone.
Ask questions.
Leave no
stone unturned.
Then I'll get the stone turning
attachment for my dozer.
Can someone please
explain it to him?
Out of the way!
Learn to drive!
Someone should take away
his license.
Stop this vehicle right now!
I'm a police dog
and you're under arrest!
Oh, no!
You hear that, Butch?
We're under arrest.
Hey, why do you get
to wear the hat?
'Cause I took
it from him!
Well, I'm taking it
from you!
- Give me that back, it's my hat! My hat!
- No, it's my hat!
Hey, hands on
the wheel!
Ahhh!
So unprofessional!
Quit squirming!
Put me down!
Let me go!
Welcome to your
new home.
What is this place?
It's Fuzzy Buddies
Obedience School!
- Isn't it awesome?
- What?
We're gonna learn
so many new tricks,
like sit, and roll over,
and, uh, sit.
Ugh, Barney, how many times
do I have to tell you?
It's not
an obedience school anymore.
Mayor Humdinger's goons
took over this place
and turned it into a jail.
Old Humdinger's
not exactly a dog lover.
He's more of a cat person.
He's rounding up all
the dogs in the city,
and locking us
in here.
That's terrible.
Never let your
guard down in here.
There's one guy you
gotta watch out for.
He'll sneak up behind you
when you least expect it.
There he is!
Don't worry, guys,
I'll protect you!
Leave my friends alone! Ow!
He got away!
I gotta get
out of here.
So what's your
story, kid?
I don't even
know anymore.
I thought I was a member
of the PAW Patrol.
But now I feel like they're
better off without me.
What makes you say
a thing like that?
I keep messing up
and letting everyone down.
I can't even,
with all this negativity.
Just ignore her.
She's all bark and no bite.
Now pick yourself
a doghouse.
You're gonna be
here awhile.
Come on, in here!
Liberty!
Que gusto verte!
How's life treating
you these days?
Carmen, I got
no time for chitchat.
We're in a jam
and we need your help.
Have you seen
this dog?
No, I haven't
seen him.
If you want, you can put
his picture up on the wall.
Whoa...
Lots of dogs
going missing lately.
I'm keeping
my eyes open
but it's like
they just disappear.
How long has this
been happening?
It started
a couple days ago.
Now, half my customers
are missing a dog.
This can't be a coincidence.
Somebody's got to be
taking them.
Dog-napping?
Who would do that?
Humdinger!
It's got to be him.
He hates dogs
more than anything.
But where is he
taking them?
I think I know
how we can find out.
- How?
- I'm a dog.
I'm also kind of an honorary
member of the PAW Patrol,
so I'll be
the bait.
I get captured,
you tail me,
and boom, we find out
where he's taking them.
That might actually work.
We just need to figure out how
to get Humdinger's attention.
Leave that to me.
Marty Muckraker here,
bringing you an exclusive interview
with recently disgraced
Mayor Humdinger.
Thanks, Marty.
After today's
little subway snafu,
I just wanted to assure
the public
there will be no more
embarrassing mishaps.
Ahhh!
Put a cork in it,
windbag!
Somebody get this filthy dog away from me!
Gotcha!
Oh, no!
Please! Let me go!
Don't take me to exactly the same
place you took the other dogs,
in this white van,
license plate number YVP 8624!
You, with the pants
on your head,
- get me a new pair of pants.
- Right away, sir!
When my new pants arrive,
we'll take this interview
from the top.
Um... Mr. Mayor,
we're live.
Ahhh!
If this goes viral,
I'm canceling the Internet!
Get back here!
I'm gonna get you!
Was this one easier to catch,
or are we getting better at this?
Oh-ho-ho! We're definitely
getting better at this.
Chase? Chase?
Anybody here seen a German Shepherd
about yay high, always saying,
"Chase is on the case"?
Liberty?
Hey, buddy!
I came to bust you
out of here.
Puh-lease.
This scrawny little purse pup
is going to pull a jailbreak?
You talk a lot of trash for a dog
who looks like a toilet brush.
Hmph!
Come on, Chase,
get up.
You shouldn't have
come after me.
Now we're both
stuck in here.
Of course
I came after you.
I might just be one small pup,
all alone in the big city,
but I can still
make a difference.
I can still be a hero,
just like you.
- I'm no hero.
- Yeah, right.
And I'm a purebred
show dog with papers.
Oh... You're serious.
I used to think I was a hero,
but it turns out I'm just scared.
So? Who cares
if you're scared?
Heroes get scared
all the time.
- They do?
- Of course they do.
But even though they're scared,
they push through and keep going.
That's what
makes them heroes.
While you chew over that
knowledge I just dropped,
I'm gonna get us outta here.
We're stuck
in here, Liberty.
That door is always locked,
and it's the only way out.
Well, there's one thing
I forgot to mention.
I brought backup!
- Rubble!
- On the double!
♪ Three, two, one, go ♪
Yeah!
Chase!
- What's going on in here?
Get 'em!
Charge!
I'm gonna get ya!
Yes, we're free!
All right, pups, let's roll.
Chase,
you ride with me.
- Whoa!
- You cool back there, Liberty?
I'm doing
great! Ahhh!
Come on, you bucket of bolts,
don't quit on me now!
Chase and I have
to make a stop.
We'll meet you back
at headquarters.
Aye aye, Ryder, sir!
See you there.
Where are we going?
There's something
I need to show you.
Do you remember
this place?
This is where
I found you.
Why would you
bring me here?
I know this place reminds you
of the worst time in your life.
But there's more
to it than that.
It's also
a great place.
I remember the first
time I saw you.
You were a tiny little pup,
all alone in the big city.
I know. You saw me
and took pity on me.
Not at all.
What I saw was a brave,
heroic pup.
Even though you were too small
to look after yourself,
and you were up against
all those scary things,
you got back up
and kept going.
I didn't adopt you
because I felt sorry for you.
I chose you because you were
the bravest pup I'd ever seen.
I know Adventure City
has been tough for you,
but I also know that deep down
you were born to be a hero.
So, what do you say?
Wanna go to work?
Ready for action,
Ryder sir.
Here you go, boss.
Let's make history.
- Mayor Humdinger!
- Ahhh!
Don't sneak up
on me like that.
The Cloud Catcher's
precipometer has short-circuited
and the barometric pressure has
dropped below 87 kilopascals!
What? I never know
what you're talking about.
Dumb it down for me!
We've got to bring down the Cloud
Catcher, it's gonna blow!
Hogwash! Give me that.
What are you doing?
Hmm!
There's a free-floating
meteorological
weather containment
system overhead,
and the anemometer readings
are off the charts!
What?
We're all in grave danger.
In danger of having the time
of our lives!
Thank you, Kendra,
for that lovely introduction.
You're making a big mistake!
Ladies and gentlemen,
members of the press,
and most importantly
influencers with over
10,000 followers,
we are gathered here today
for the grand opening
of Humdinger Heights!
I took the tallest skyscraper
in Adventure City
and stuck a brand-new tower
on top,
turning it into the tallest
building in the world!
And I've put my office right
at the top.
Now you'll have
to look up to me,
and I'll always
look down on you.
#Humdinger!
Oh, no!
Marty Muckraker reporting live
with a correction to this
morning's weather forecast.
Instead of clear blue skies
and gentle breeze,
it will now be pitch-black
skies and hurricane-force winds.
Whoa!
This just in.
I've been lying about my hair!
Yikes, that's
looking gnarly.
Ahhh! Ahhh!
- Rubble!
- What?
Lightning is frightening!
PAW Patrol.
What's your emergency?
What's the emergency?
The mesoscale convective system is
causing exponential thermal lift
and catastrophic downbursts
at over 190 knots!
What?
It's a super
bad storm.
Come on,
guys, keep up.
Finally, somebody gets me!
This is not a regular storm.
It's being caused by
a weather-control device
that's unleashing weeks' worth
of bad weather all at once!
Take cover.
We're on our way.
Chase...
Ready for launch. Go!
Marshall. Go!
Rubble. Go!
Rocky. Go!
Whoo-hoo!
Zuma. Go!
Go get 'em, pups!
You know, Liberty,
I've been thinking.
You're kind of like an honorary
member of the PAW Patrol, right?
I suppose you could say that.
I mean, your words,
not mine.
But to be an official member,
you'd need a faster vehicle, right?
I know, I know,
my ride's a rusty old
wagon with a wonky wheel
that goes
"eee-ooo-eee-ooo-eee-ooo."
You don't have to rub it in.
Is that...
It's yours.
Okay, Liberty, play it
cool, play it cool.
Ahhh! This is amazing! It's the greatest
thing I've ever seen in my life!
I've never been so happy!
It's like my whole life has been
building towards this moment!
All my dreams have come true!
It's so amazing!
Looking good,
Liberty.
Liberty!
Ready for launch.
The voice
said my name!
I can't believe
this is really happening!
Five...
Four... Three...
Wait, I'm not sure
I'm ready for this.
- Two...
- You might want to hang on.
One... Go!
♪ That's my girl
♪ What you waiting for
Whoo-hoo!
♪ That's my girl ♪
- Yeah, Liberty!
- Nice wheels!
Welcome to the team!
I can't wait to do that again!
Okay, team, we've got no idea
what we're heading into.
We're going to have
to improvise.
♪ That's my girl
♪ That's my girl ♪
Closing in
on Humdinger Heights!
Ugh!
Things are getting
pretty hairy out here!
Rocky, Marshall, Rubble,
get those people inside!
Zuma, Liberty, make sure
the streets are clear.
Aye aye, Ryder!
- Incoming!
- Look out!
Arf! Net!
Nice catch!
You can count on me, Ryder.
The Cloud Catcher
has gone critical.
There's no way
to bring it down!
- We'll see about that.
- Be careful up there.
Don't worry about me.
I can handle
a little turbulence.
Zuma, this is Liberty.
Streets are empty, everyone's safe.
Copy that.
Good job, Liberty!
- Help!
- Hold on!
There's a car
in the water.
I'm diving in!
♪ Everybody needs
somebody sometimes
Arf! Submarine!
♪ Everybody needs
somebody sometimes
- Help!
I'm right behind you, Zuma!
Copy that!
I'm in your raft,
headed downstream.
I'm closing in
on the car.
Gotcha!
Arf! Zuma suit!
♪ Now we just rollin'
♪ Yeah, we keep it goin'
It's the PAW Patrol!
Everybody say cheese!
- Cheese!
- Hi!
Now is not the time for selfies!
♪ Everybody needs
somebody sometimes ♪
Okay, the rescue raft
is in position!
Ryder, this is Zuma!
The family is safe
and we're headed to dry land.
Good job, pups!
You have to get out of the
street right now! It's not safe!
The mayor is up there!
I'll get Humdinger.
You get her to safety.
- Everybody inside!
- This way!
Follow me!
Ahhh!
Everybody, stay away
from the windows!
Hey! That's my hair!
Where did you find it?
The hair found me.
It was my destiny.
Well,
it's my signature look!
Buy your own hair!
Cloud Catcher, dead ahead!
This is gonna get bumpy.
It's okay, kitties,
we'll just hunker down
and ride out the storm.
- Mayor Humdinger?
- Yes? How can I help you?
Ryder? What are you doing here?
This tower isn't safe.
We've got to get you out of here.
Oh, no, the power's out.
That means the elevator's dead.
We have to go now.
Nice try! I'm not going
anywhere with you.
Ah! Oh! Ahhh!
My top hat!
Okay, fine.
I'll go with you.
But I want to make it very
clear, this is not a rescue.
It's... Uh,
an "assisted exit."
You can call it
whatever you want,
as long as you get in the
elevator now!
I'll release the cables
manually from above.
Once I've lowered you down safely,
I'll rappel down the elevator shaft.
Hmpf. Show off.
Even though we've had our personal
differences over the years,
I take no pleasure
in doing this.
Doing what?
Ahhh!
Actually, that's
pretty satisfying.
One one thousand, two one thousand,
three one thousand, four one thousand,
five one thousand.
Oh, uh...
Nothing to worry about,
everything's fine.
Okay, pups, Humdinger's out!
I'm coming down.
Nice job, Ryder!
See you on the ground.
Whoa!
That's not good.
That's very not good!
Ahhh! Oh!
Whoa!
Ryder!
Arf! Shields!
Arf! Motorcycle!
Suction tires!
I'm coming, Ryder!
Ryder? Ryder?
Where are you?
Ryder! I can see
your light. Hang on!
I can do this.
I can do this!
Arf! Grappling hook!
Oh, no!
Disconnect pup pack.
Ryder...
I chose you because you
were the bravest pup I'd ever seen.
Ryder!
Ryder?
Chase!
I can't believe you found me!
You can always
count on me, Ryder.
Come on, we gotta
get out of here!
I can't.
I'm stuck.
On three, pull as hard as you can.
One, two, three!
Come on!
It won't budge.
One more try.
You did it!
We did it.
I told you
you were a hero.
Now come on.
Let's get out of here.
Just a little bit further.
Whoa.
Oh, great. Lightning.
Arf! Net!
Target acquired.
Fire!
Got it!
Whoa!
Don't got it!
Warning. Warning. Warning.
Come on, baby, turn it around!
Okay, Cloud Catcher...
Catch this!
Eject!
What's that?
Whoo-hoo!
- Yay, Skye!
- Awesome!
Whoa!
Good job, Skye!
That was
totally awesome!
You're definitely
my favorite pup.
I hope Ryder got insurance
on my 'copter.
That'll buff
right out.
- He's okay!
- All right!
Yeah!
Okay, okay.
Give him some air.
How do you feel?
Covered in drool.
I can't help it,
I'm a bulldog.
My tongue is too big
for my mouth!
See?
You did good, pups.
Time for me
to get out of here!
Hey! Mayor Humdinger!
You are under arrest
for gross negligence,
public endangerment,
and dog-napping!
You can't arrest me,
I'm the mayor!
- He's getting away!
- Arf! Mini-drone!
Ahhh!
Hey, hey, hey!
Put me down!
Nobody makes a fool of Mayor
Humdinger five times in the same day!
Ahhh!
Well, this is humiliating.
Here you go, boss.
That's better.
Adventure City
is our home.
It's up to all of us
to take care of it.
But once in a while,
a group of heroes
go above and beyond
the call of duty.
They look out
for their neighbors
before they look out
for themselves.
And they're so darn cute,
I just want to squeeze 'em!
It is our great honor to present
the key to Adventure City to...
- The PAW Patrol!
Me and the PAW Patrol,
we go way back!
And to think I knew them
before they were famous!
Hey, Rubble,
I got something for you.
I am never taking this off!
I want to take this special
occasion to introduce you
to the newest member
of the PAW Patrol.
Adventure City's very own...
Liberty!
My own pup tag?
Welcome to
the family, Liberty.
I'm official.
Hey, check it out!
I'm officially official!
Official member of the
PAW Patrol right here!
Thank you for this honor.
The PAW Patrol will always
look out for Adventure City.
Remember, if you're ever
in trouble, just yelp for...
Ugh. That's so embarrassing.
I thought I had
this thing on silent.
Ryder! Something big is
going down at the waterfront.
We need the PAW Patrol!
PAW Patrol ready for
action, Ryder sir!
Sorry, folks.
Duty calls.
♪ PAW Patrol, PAW Patrol
♪ We'll be there
on the double
♪ Whenever there's a problem
♪ Round Adventure Bay
♪ Ryder and his team of pups
♪ Will come and save the day
♪ Marshall, Rubble, Chase
♪ Rocky, Zuma, Skye
♪ And Liberty!
♪ You make me dance
Yeah, you do
♪ You got my heart beating
rhythms when you move
♪ Don't need no plans,
feeling loose
♪ Like there's a rainbow
of magic next to you
♪ When it's good
when it's bad
♪ Yeah, you got me
♪ Not alone in this town
'cause you make me feel
♪ Anytime that I call
you'll be ready
♪ Anytime
♪ And when I turn around
♪ I see you there
♪ You got a way to make
a problem disappear
♪ Up to the clouds
♪ I'm spinning round
♪ And now you know why
♪ 'Cause no one in this world
can make me feel loved
♪ In the way that you do now
♪ No, no one in this world
can make me come down
♪ When I'm in such
a good mood now
♪ Whoo-ooh
♪ Good mood
♪ Hop in my ride
don't you know
♪ We got the sun always
shining wherever we go
♪ Don't need no map
we just roll
♪ Let the vibe give direction
take control
♪ When it's good
when it's bad
♪ Yeah, you got me
♪ Not alone in this town
'cause you make me feel
♪ Anytime that I call
you'll be ready
♪ Anytime
♪ And when I turn around
♪ I see you there
♪ You got a way to make
a problem disappear
♪ Up to the clouds
♪ I'm spinning round
♪ And now you know why
♪ 'Cause no one in this world
can make me feel loved
♪ In the way that you do now
♪ No, no one in this world
can make me come down
♪ When I'm in such a good
mood now
♪ Whoo-ooh
♪ Good mood
♪ You make me
have a good mood
♪ Ooh
♪ Yeah
♪ You make me feel, yeah
♪ Ooh, you make me feel good
♪ Whoo-hoo
♪ Good mood
♪ Good mood ♪
♪ PAW Patrol, PAW Patrol
♪ We'll be there
on the double
♪ Wherever there is trouble
♪ Around Adventure Bay
♪ Ryder and his team of pups
♪ Will come and save the day
♪ Me and Ryder ride around
town in Adventure Bay
♪ If somebody needs
some help
♪ Them pups will be there
right away
♪ The captain's coming, come along too
If you got four legs or you got two
♪ Let me hear
the names of the crew
♪ We've got Marshall, Rubble
Chase, Rocky, Zuma, Skye
♪ They're on their way
♪ PAW Patrol, PAW Patrol
♪ Whenever you're in trouble
♪ We'll be there
on the double
♪ If something's going wrong
call the PAW Patrol
♪ You wanna have some fun
♪ Who's gonna save the day
That's the PAW Patrol
♪ We gonna tell them
one more time
♪ We've got Marshall, Rubble
Chase, Rocky, Zuma, Skye
♪ They're on their way
♪ PAW Patrol, PAW Patrol
♪ Whenever you're in trouble
♪ We'll be there on the double
♪ No job is too big
No pup is too small
♪ PAW Patrol, we're on a roll!
♪ PAW Patrol, here we go ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull