I've lived in this city
all my life.
I'm Max.
And I'm the luckiest dog
in New York,
because of her.
That's Katie.
Katie and I...
Well, we have a perfect relationship.
We met a few years ago. And...
Boy, let me tell you,
we got along right away.
You know, it was one of those
relationships where...
Where you just know.
And get this. She was
looking for a roommate,
and so was I!
So, I just moved in
that same day!
Was perfect!
We've been togather ever since.
Katie would do anything for me.
And I'm her lawyer protector.
Our love is...
Our love is, how do I put this?
Our love is stronger than words,
Or shoes.
It's me and Katie.
Kaite and me.
Us against the world.
I wouldn't go so far as
to call us soulmates,
Even though, any sane
person who saw us would.
There's just one little problem.
- Pretty much, everyday!
- Come on, Max!
She leaves!
I'll see you tonight.
Sometime I try stuff
to get her to stay!
Okay, sit.
Spin.
Speak.
Okay, that's a good boy.
But, it never works!
Where is she going?
What could she possibly
be doing?
I miss her so much!
Wow, oh my... oh, she's back!
Forgot my phone!
What took so long?
Why did you...?
Oh, come on!
Uhh!
I miss her so much!
Bye, Gidget! Be a good doggy.
- Hey, Max!
- Hey, Gidget!
Any plans today?
Yes. Big, big
stuff today, Gidget.
I got big plans.
I'm gonna sit here
and I'm gonna wait for
Katie to come back.
Oh, that sounds exciting.
Well, I won't interrupt.
I've got a very busy day, too.
Here you go.
See you later, Chloe.
Bye, Peppi.
So long, Mel.
Bye, Sweet Pea.
See you, Gino.
- Sorry, pal.
- Bye, Mitsy.
I'll miss you, Shelly.
Later, Runty.
Bye, everyone.
Bye.
You be a good boy, Leonard.
Hey, Max!
Hey, Chloe.
Do you ever wonder
where they go during the day?
Do you know what?
I just, I don't really care.
Maybe that's what it's
like for you,
but, Katie and I have
a different relationship.
You know, you're a cat,
so, maybe that's why.
'Cause nobody could
ever love a cat
the way they love a dog,
I'm just saying.
Maybe that's why.
Whatever you need
to tell yourself.
- Hey, Morning, Max!
- Hey, guys.
What's up, Sweet Pea?
Hey, Mel.
Where've you been, man?
Oh! Get this.
Last sunday, my owner feeds me
a small white pill, right?
I start to feel little groggy.
The next thing I know
I wake up, I'm in the sky!
Wait a minute, the sky?
Yeah, there was
suitcases everywhere.
- I'm locked up in a crate!
- Come on!
There's suitcases in the sky?
So, I pass out from fear.
And when I wake up,
I'm in Florida!
Um, this did not happend.
I will never eat a pill
like that again,
unless it's covered in
peanut butter.
Because, I mean come on, right?
It's peanut butter.
- Hey, guys.
- Oh, hey, Norman.
You still looking for
your apartment?
Yeah, going on three weeks, now.
Is this the second
or the third floor?
I don't know any numbers
but, you don't live here.
Oh, damn it.
Well, see you guys later.
You know what? You can do it.
Can't do it.
Buddy, there you are.
Did you find it?
You know I did.
Voila.
- Ball!
Ball! Ball! Ball!
Katie is gonna be so excited.
This is exactly that
what she lost.
I mean, look at it. It's round,
it fits in my mouth.
- Ball!
- Yeah!
Oh!
There is no other ball
in the city like this one ball.
Guarantee, this is the ball.
Hey!
- Katie!
- I'm home, Max.
Hey, Maximillian.
How's your day, buddy?
That's a good boy.
Oh, yes. I'm so excited
to see you too, buddy.
Okay, boy. Calm down.
It's okay. Let's all be calm.
Now, I have some big news.
I know this will take some
getting used to, but...
but, I think it's gonna be
a great thing in the long...
Max. This is, Duke.
He's going to be
your... brother.
No, no. Max. Okay.
It's gonna be alright, Duke.
It's okay.
Oh, see? He likes you.
Yeah. That's it, Duke.
Take a look around.
I know, buddy.
This is a lot to take in, but...
he didn't have a home.
So, you and I are gonna
have to take care of him.
Okay?
Oh my Gosh!
Duke, found our lost ball.
What a great team
we're gonna be.
Love you, Maxi.
Love you, Duke.
Sleep tight, boys.
Psst!
Pssst!
Hey! Little guy!
This place is so great.
Uh-huh.
By the way that is...
That is one gorgeous bed.
Yeah, that's okay.
Maybe we could share.
You know, one night
you get the bed,
the next night I do.
- That kind of thing.
- Yo, this bed is mine.
You? You get an old blanket.
That suits you.
You're an old blanket
kind of a dog.
Oh, wow. You are a stubborn.
Hey, I got it.
I'm stubborn, too.
- But, we gotta learn to get along.
- Wait, what are you...?
How about we can both
fit in this bed,
if we really trying on
squeeze in there.
No, wait.
Perfect. This is comfy, right?
No, it is not.
I'm comfy.
Duke is just ruining our lives.
He's ruin... It's an emergency
that you get rid of this dog.
He stool my...
And he's scary,
and he's threatening,
and he's the death
of all good things.
Oh! You little cutie pie!
We'll play tomorrow buddy, okay?
Okay, sleep well.
Are you trying to get rid of me?
Before I answer that...
I'd like to know
how much you heard.
So, that's how it's gonna be, huh?
Oh man! You're making me angry.
And when I get angry,
I do this...
And I don't want to do that.
I need this place.
And if it's gonna
come down to you or me?
It's gonna be me!
Ahh!
Morning, Max!
Max! Max! What are you doing?
Hi, it's me. Hi!
Chloe!
Chloe, Chloe!
I got a bad situation.
Katie brought home
a new dog from the pound!
She said, he's my brother.
I don't want a brother.
And I don't, I don't even
have a bed, now.
I'm sleeping on the floor,
like a dog.
Why would Katie do this to me?
Because, she's a dog person, Max.
And dog people do wierd,
inexplicable things, like...
they get dogs instead of cats.
Okay, please
don't start now, Chloe.
That is not helping.
Max, come on!
I'm your friend, okay?
And as your friend,
I gotta be honest with you,
I don't care about you
or your problems.
But, if you don't do
something about this guy.
And soon,
your perfect little life
with your dump human...
is gonna be over.
- Forever.
- Forever?
Foreve, yeah.
That's what I just...
Why is this mouse
on my paw still?
Ahh.
Look, if you really want to
get your turf back,
you're gonna have to star
acting like the alpha dog.
Right, alpha dog. I can do that.
- Okay! Okay!
- Please, don't go.
This time, really don't go.
Okay, I'm running late.
I gotta go.
Wait, wait! No!
Stay, stay for the trick.
Spin. I'm doing spin.
You guys be good.
I'll see you later.
- Wait. No, no. Wait, look.
- Okay, Max.
Oh!
Listen, Duke.
I'm not sure if you're aware,
but, one of those food bowls
technically, it's reserved for...
I know, maybe you didn't
read the names, but...
That's my bowl.
Um.
I know, that's... Hey!
I mean, I was just thinking...
I don't know, maybe we could
institute some ground rules.
I just thought that if...
Or... Or not. I, I don't,
I don't need a bowl.
Here again?
- Rodent!
- Whoa, whoa. No, no!
Aah!
Oh!
Dah!
Oh, Duke!
Duke, Katie is not...
Katie is gonna be upset
when she sees that.
Katie is... gonna flip out
when she sees how
you trashed her whole place.
Oh, it's just,
it's just one vase.
Is it, Duke? Is it?
Oh! That's a shame.
- What are you doing?
- Whoa! What am I doing?
Nothing.
I'm, I'm a cute little doggie.
Katie knows I wouldn't do
anything like this!
No, no! Whoa!
Uhh!
This could only be the work
of a dangerous stray...
who hasn't lay down
a foundation of trust.
You're the new dog.
And... Hey, Duke!
Why'd you going do this for?
Argh! I'm gonna...
Whoa! What, bite me?
Rip my face off?
Perfect.
Wait till Katie finds out,
"Oh! Katie, thank Godness
you're here."
"I tried to stop him.
But, he's crazy!"
Uh!
Huh!
Now, sit!
Okay! Okay! Okay!
Lay down.
Argh!
Good boy.
- Hi, Max!
- Hey, Gidget!
Who's your new roommate?
Is it a girl dog, or a boy dog?
Not that I care.
It doesn't matter to me.
Oh, that's nobody, Gidget.
He's just visiting.
Yeah, he, he's gonna
be gone, soon.
- Hey! What's up?
- Oh, Hi!
Your hat is best hat
I ever seen.
Hey!
Uhh, excuse me, genius.
You forgot my leash.
Ohh! Never mind.
Hey, fellas. Who's it... Woah!
Hey, fellas. Who's it... Uhwah!
Hey! Fellas! Huweeh!
- Oh! Say, Duke?
- Yes?
Be a good lad and
bring me a stick, won't you?
It would please me to
chew on a stick just now.
You heard me. Fetch.
Argh!
Na, na, na. Not that one.
That one doesn't please me.
Find a really good one, Duke.
Yeah, that's it.
Argh.
Hey, Max! Boy!
Oh, wow! There are a ton of
sticks over here, Max!
You should come over
and look at them.
Yeah, I want to make sure
I grab the right one.
Well, that's very...
That's very thoughtful.
Look at all these sticks!
Ha!
Whoa! Help! Help!
Hey, did you hear that?
Butterfly!
- Butterfly! Butterfly!
- Oh, butterfly! Let's get it!
Wha... What's...
Ahh! Whoa! Ahhh!
Oh!
Aww!
Ahh!
Oh! Ahh!
Ahhh!
Ahh! Oh! Oh!
Argh!
Wow! Uhh!
Hel.. Hel.. Help Help, Help!
- So long.
- Don't leave me here.
Didn't have to be this way, Max.
- Wait!
- No heart feelings.
Duke, Please!
- Boy, what's going on here?
- Mind your own business...
Oh my Gosh!
What happened to you?
Oh, I had a fight, alright?
With a big stupid dog. He lost.
Oh! You're heading into a dangerous
territory there, kitty cat!
I'd watch your tone, sunshine.
Know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna catch you
into a string,
pull you up, and then I bet
you run for hours,
in a game that only I understand.
Oh. Very nice.
I'll take that!
Huh?
Oh!
Oh! Huh! Whoo-hoo!
You want to start
with me, little raisin?
Okay, get your umbrellas out, kitties.
Because, here they come...
The thunder! And the lightning!
Right down on your face.
Gosh, there are a lot
of you up there.
I'm talking about thunder
and lightning,
and it's coming down on all
of your collected faces.
Attack on, three, two...
Ahhhh!
Ohh!
I just remember,
I gotta be somewhere!
Ha-ha! That...
Haha, ha! That guy, huh?
Am I right?
Okay, I'm just... You know what?
I'm just gonna...
It's no offense, but... Bye!
Ohh!
Whoaa!
Ahh! Whoa! Whoa!
Ahhhh!
Uhh!
Uh-huh!
Whoa! Ahhh!
Ahhh! Ahhhh!
Huh?
Ha!
He-Huh!
Hey!
Hey, you little...
Whoaa!
Whoaa! Ohh!
Ahh! Uh!
Blah!
Duke?
- You came back?
- Run!
Whoa! Ahhh!
Wow!
It's the Po-Po! Scram!
Hay!
Huh! Ah! Whoah!
Wait!
Two, four, six, eight. Mmmm.
- See you tomorrow, Germo!
- You know it.
Ten... Ah, okay.
Right.
Uh-Huh.
- Did you see that?
- Yeah, I saw it.
Throw it with your arm,
you lazy weirdo.
I would not fetch that.
I'm old school.
Ahh!
Humph! Thanks a lot, Duke.
I don't like to use this phrase,
because it is offensive to our kind,
but you're a bad dog.
Katie is not gonna like this.
I, I can't go to the pound!
What? What's wrong with you?
Well, Katie just...
She just got me out
of the pound.
And if I go back...
Back it's the end of
the life for me.
La pasión de la pasión.
Ha! Yes! Mmmm.
Why? Why?!
What's the matter, Maria?
Maria, your face!
It worths a thousand souls.
What's wrong?
I have come face-to-face
with a worst thing in the world!
What? Oh, tell me, Maria.
Tell me now!
I can not bear another moment
without knowing!
Loneliness.
Huh!
- But, Maria. You can not be lonely.
- Ha! Max. Max!
Max! Huh?
Hey! I see you, squirrel!
This is not your area!
We marked that tree!
Don't you trying hide.
I can see you... Ahh!
What was that? How dare you?
- Hey, guys! Where's Max?
- Hey! No!
Nobody likes you, squirrels!
- No! Aww!
- Ahh!
Guys, seriously. Where is Max?
Calm down, girl. He's right...
Huh! He's gone.
All is fine!
I heard him screaming after
he disappeared into those bushes!
Max is gone?
This is bad. This is so bad.
Maria, if he's your true love.
You must go to him.
Save him. Save him!
Yes! Yes! Save my true love!
Run! Come on! Go!
I'm coming, Max!
Aahhh!
Aaahh!
Hi, Chloe. If anyone ask,
I'm on my way to the roof
to look for, Max.
Okay, Bye-bye.
Whoa! You see that?
Yeah, give me a second.
Aww! Hey, there cute little bunny.
What are you doing
in the middle of the road?
Aahhh!
Bunny!
Huh?
Hey, what's going on?
What the...?
- Save yourself!
- Shut it, human.
Let's dow this now! Now! Now!
Wait up!
Get off me, pig!
Ooh! Ouch!
Get off!
Whoo-ooh! Aah!
Whoah!
- What's happening?
- I don't know!
Ripper? Ripper, where you at?
Let's go, Ripper.
I'm bustin' you outta here.
The revolution has begun!
Librated forever!
Domesticated never!
Yeah!
Ouch!
Who's driving this thing?
Whoo-hoo!
Aaahhh!
Ah!
Ha-ha! Huh!
Ooh!
Let's go. Let's go! Let's go!
- Who are you, guys?
- Huh?
Who are we?
Who are we?!
We are The Flushed Pets.
Thrown away by our owners,
and now we're out for revenge!
It's like a club but with
biting and scratching.
Ta.. Take us with you.
I don't think so, pets.
Yeah, you got the stench of
domestication all over you.
You chose your side.
And now you're gonna burn.
No! Stop! Who you calling pets?
I ain't no pets.
You got it all wrong.
We're just like you, guys.
We hate humans.
- Oh, yeah! That's right.
- Hate them.
Oh, man. Don't get me started
on people. Am I right, Duke?
Yeah, That's why
we burned our collars, man!
- We burned 'em to the ground.
- It killed our owners.
Yeah... Wait a minute.
That's too far, maybe?
No, they dig it.
- Yes, we whacked 'em.
- Yeah, that's right.
Bang! Bang! With our own paws.
I had a dime
for every owner I kill.
- Oh, yeah.
- I had a dime...
'Cause I just killed the one.
Whoo-ooh!
Oh, you're cold-blooded.
Oh man, you remind me
my boy, Ricky.
He died, tho. R.I.P, Ricky.
You know what truth is?
The struggle could use
some more muscle.
Alright, look.
I'll tell you what.
We bust the both
of you outta here,
but understand this,
from now on you work for me.
- That's fine.
- Sounds like a fun challenge.
Aah! Oh!
Alright, guys. Let's do this.
Aaah!
- To the sewers!
- The sewers?
What are you waiting for?
I'm not playin'.
I said, to the sewers!
Long live the revolution, suckers!
I can do it.
Max!
Max! Max!
Max! Max! Max!
Where are you, Max?
Looks like you could
use a little help.
Who said that?
Over here!
In this dark and forbidding shed.
Uh... Hello?
I can see from miles.
If you let me out,
I'll find your friend.
Wow! Really!
Aww! You're so sweet!
You're sweet, too.
Ooh! Thanks stranger.
But not so sweet, there's also
a salty, gainly thing going on.
Yeah, that's me.
Come on, let's get you
outta that shed.
Yeah, that's it. Just step over
the pile of bones.
Pile of bones. Okay, well do.
I sure hope Max is safe.
You're a very thoughtful food.
Food? I didn't say that.
I said friend.
I meant food, Fri... Friend.
You know what I meant.
I'm sure lucky I found you...
Uh...
Tiberius.
And yes, this is a very good
thing for you.
This whole meeting me thing.
Take off my hood.
Ha!
Aahh!
Aaahhh!
Ow! The chain!
Oh, you tried to eat me!
I'm sorry!
You should be sorry!
You deserve to be locked up!
You're a bad, bad bird!
I can't help it!
I was born with killer instincts!
That is just no excuse!
You're right, even for a predator
I'm selfish.
I'm selfish predator.
It's no wonder
I have no friends. Nobody.
I... I... This is hopeless. I...
Oh, don't.
There is no need to cry.
I'm sorry that I yalled
at you before.
Please take off the chain.
This time I'll help you,
I promise.
Tiberius, this is gonna sound
completely horrible, but um...
I don't fully trust you.
Oh! No, no, but...
I guess everyone deserves
a second chance,
And you are just a lonely
old bird,
And you do have weird manners,
because you live in
a weird shed on a roof.
So, I'll tell you what,
if you find Max...
I'll be your best friend!
Best friend?
You and me?
Whoo-ooh!
Awww!
Yaah!
Yes! That sounds nice.
Let's do this.
Okay.
So, what does this Max look like?
Brown and white,
he's a short hair,
roguishly handsome,
he's got a sparkle in his eye.
He sounds dreamy.
Ohh! You have no idea.
I mean, what! Whatever!
Shut up. Pfff!
If my owner comes,
put on the hood
and pretend to be me.
Okay, thank you!
Ugh! The smell is disgusting...
ly good!
This is also great.
We love it here.
Huh!
What's the password?
Password?
Look, look at me.
I am your leader.
The leader does not
decide the password.
The leader makes up
the password, idiots!
Everybody, I'm making up
a new password, right now.
The new password, is don't ask
the leader for the password!
Follow me.
Welcome to The Underbelly, brothers.
Home of the flushed pets.
Brothers and sisters,
as you see, I've return from
the surface with two new recruits.
These guys are owner killers.
Yay!
Hey! Hey! Settle it down!
Guys! I want you to tell 'em
how you did it.
Go ahead, tell 'em the whole story
about how you took out your owner.
Don't leave out nothing.
We love gory detail here.
- Oh yeah!
- Tell us!
- Right.
- So, tell 'em, Max.
Okay, okay. So...
- I was like...
- Well, we were like...
- Take that, stupid owner.
- Yeah.
So, that's...
That who you're dealing with.
Hey, that's story bored me
to death.
Boring!
Give us detail.
Okay. Max?
Okay, Well... Uh...
So, there's this...
There's this thing in the kitchen.
Yeah, table.
- It's like flat...
- Toaster.
And then, round on
just the end of it.
A spoon?
- Yes, a spoon!
- Exactly.
You can't hurt someone
with a spoon.
You scoop with a spoon.
How many people wanna know
how to kill somebody with a spoon?
- I do!
- Oh yeah!
Okay. Well, we use a spoon...
Hit the button on this machine...
- Right, right.
- On the counter.
- And it's go those...
- The... You know...
- Those blades.
- It's got blades!
Was it a blender? Whaoh!
You blending somebody?
He's talk about the blender, guys.
Oh, please!
Tell me it was a blender.
Hey, buddy.
I don't ask what it's call,
- We just kill with it.
- But, it was a blender.
Wow! Do ya'll hear this?
You know who's like this?
Ricky! Rest in peace.
Ricky was the only
soldier I had...
that was ready to kill
humans on sight.
Everybody else need a pet talk.
Not these two brothers.
Whoa-hoo! Yay!
See, all of us have suffered
at the hands of man.
I mean, take me for instance.
I was a magician's rabbit
for kids parties.
But then, bunny tricks
went out of style.
So, what did my owner do?
My owner went and left
magic behind,
And made me disappear...
From his life!
Uh-huh.
I lived in a tattoo parlor.
The trainees used to practice
on me.
Until they ran outta space!
I mean, yes.
Human say they love us,
But then, they turn around
and throw us out like garbage.
Ain't that right, Seamonkeys?
Hey! It's not our fault
we don't look like the ad.
Yeah.
Alright, you guys are joining
The Brotherhood.
It's initiation time.
- What?
- I'm sorry, what time?
Summon the Viper!
Is this Viper poisonous?
Because I should warning you
I'm very allergic to poison!
Ouch! Ah!
Alright, show her.
Huh! Max's collar! Where is he?
Wha... Wha...
What happened to him?
Oi, I ain't say nothing.
You're gonna tell us where Max is,
and you're gonna tell us now!
Is this supposed to scare me?
I'm a cat.
- I'll end on my feet.
- Does it always happen?
'Cause your head looks like
it's taken a lot of landings.
Do you want me to catch you?
'Cause I'll catch you this way,
and let you look like a waffle.
Okay, he's too stupid to talk
and too ugly to eat.
Aahhh!
I'm done playing nice!
Where is Max?!
- Oh!
- Tell me!
What? Aw!
I ju... I can't... Aww!
Let me finish... Aww! Help me!
Don't look at him, look at me!
Nobody can help you!
Where is Max?!
Okay! Okay! He's in the sewers.
He got taken.
Please, have mercy!
Adorable buffy dog.
Huh!
Snake bite! Snake bite!
Snake bite!
Aww!
As proof of your allegiance,
You're now receve the bite
of a one fang...
half-blind Viper,
fueled by a diet of
anti human rage!
Who wants to go first?
Uh... Yeah.
Hey, here's the thing, tho.
- I mean, It's...
- Tiny dog.
Can I call you, tiny dog?
It fits you. Let's admit that.
Mate, look.
Between you and the fat dog?
I like you the best.
Oh, thank you.
Tiny dog is gonna fo first.
Everybody, T.D is going first.
No, no, no!
Tiny dog does not wannago first,
take the fat dog.
Aww! Aahh!
- No, no, no! Stop!
- Snake bite! Snake bite!
Snake bite! Snake bite!
No, no, no, no!
What are you doing,
initiating a couple of domestics?
Domestics?
Yeah, we just dumped
those two in the alley,
Slashed two of their collars.
No, no, no.
That.. That's not true.
You said, you burned your collars.
Well, burned, lost,
had 'em stolen by a cat.
It's all just word.
Really? Isn't it?
You don't deserve to be
marked by a Viper.
- Oh, wow!
- We'll just show ourselves out.
You deserve to be eaten
by the Viper.
Het those leash lovers!
Aahhh!
Hold on!
Go get 'em, Duke!
Whoa!
Uhh. Fellas, that was an accident.
You squished the sacred Viper?
He's a flapjack! Oh, Viper.
Viper, you in a better place.
You and Ricky.
You ain't never did
nothing to nobody.
Well, you bit a lot of people, Viper.
So technically, you might
actually deserve this.
This might be something
that was long overdue.
But...
It shouldn't came like this.
Not on my watch.
Get 'em!
Whoah!
Come on!
Aw! Wait on, Duke!
We're sorry.
Can this be over, now?
We've got a problem!
We have so many problems.
Which one do you mean it,
this moment?
Stop running, dummies!
Stop it, right there!
- Hold your breathe!
- Hold my breathe?
This is my least favorite party
this holding so far.
Friends. I'm afraid that I have
some terrible news.
The squirrels are gonna
take over the world!
I knew it!
I always said, squirrels are little
shifty, little guys.
No! We're not doing
this squirrel thing, right now.
That's not... No!
Max is missing!
He's out there, somewhere.
Lost, scared, so, so handsome.
We've got to find him
and bring him home!
But, the outside world is loud
and scary... Whoa!
Is that a hawk?
This is my friend, Tiberius.
He's going to help us.
He's not going to eat us.
We've already been over it.
Come on, Gidget.
We go out there without a leash?
We'll get caught by a net.
Or something worse.
Yeah, like a hawk!
We're wasting time!
Max needs us!
Come on, girl. Max doesn't even
know you're alive.
Well, I don't care. I love him,
I love him with all my heart.
And, I'm gonna go look for Max
no matter who's with me.
So...
Who's with me?
Alright. Fine, fine.
Oh, come on, guys.
I can't believe you.
When I got my claws
caught in the curtains,
Who pulled me down?
Max, did!
Buddy, Mile!
When you were fixed,
Who told you to sit
the comfortable way?
- Max, did.
- Max, did!
Max, did! He did it!
And, when that random cat
tried to eat Sweet Pea,
Who saved him?
It wasn't a random cat,
it was you!
The identity of the random cat
is not the point,
We're talking about
who saved him?
Max, did!
We gotta sive him.
We gotta go save Max!
Yeah! Let's go save Max!
Uhh... Which one is Max, again?
- Hmmm.
- Tiberius!
No! Bad, bad bird!
Nice little guy.
I like this, bird.
Crazy bird.
Aahhh!
Ohh!
Come on, we gotta get to shore.
I only do the doggie paddle.
And I don't know it well.
Swim, tiny dog. Swim!
Aww!
Duke!
Help!
Max, grab the ring!
I ca... I can't!
Keep it up, Max! You're doing...
Well, you're not...
You're not doing great.
But, you're not drowning,
and that's something.
Ah! Aww!
You're almost there!
Whoah!
Huh!
Ahh!
Uh!
- Thanks, Duke.
- No problem.
Finally, we're going home.
Uh... Isn't home that way?
Uhh! Seriously?
They're going to Brooklyn.
They say, everyone's
going to Brooklyn these days.
It's makin' a real comeback.
I'm not talking about hipster
real estate trends.
I'm talking about vengeance, Tattoo!
Death is coming to Brooklyn.
And it's got buck teeth,
and a cottontail!
Let's go.
Weee!
- Hey, how are you?
- Hi, how are you?
Enchanté.
Chuck! Chuck! Chuck!
Chuck! Chuck!
Yay!!
What is this creepy joint?
This is Pops place.
His owner is never home
so, it's kind of a hotspot.
Pops knows everyone in this city.
If he agrees to help us.
Max is as good as found.
- Cool!
- Oh, fabulous.
- Tell me you got that.
- Oh, have yes I did.
- What's up, Peanut?
- Hey, Buddy.
- You see Pops around here?
- Yeah, he's over there.
Hey, Pops.
- Mushroom and sweet potatos.
- Pops!
Owee! Guys! Who's that? What?
Oh! Hey, Buddy.
How you've been, old timer?
Paralysed.
Great. Listen mr. Pops.
Our friend Max was taken.
Last we heard,
he was lost in the sewers.
Buddy said that maybe
you could help us?
No, I do know a guy
in the sewers, but...
I... I don't go out anymore.
Uh. What a waste of time.
Who said that?
Oh! I said it.
By the way, I meant no offence.
I just...
Have you seen yourself?
Welldy, well, well, well.
Looky what we apparently
have here!
Me see would like
to have a look see.
Myron, brows!
Oh, no.
Oh, yes. Me like what me see.
Well, what me can see,
it's only an an attractive blur.
Little lady, this is my city.
I'll find your friend.
Alright, party is over.
Myron, vacuum!
So, where are you from,
my fuzzy angel?
Dude, I'm a cat.
Well, nobody is perfect.
I'm so hungry.
Oh man, would you
look at that sandwich!
Alright, time to work the gift.
No, no, no!
Argh!
Okay. This... This...
This will be fine. We're fine.
We can find our way home.
We're descended from
the mighty wolf.
We've raw primal instincts...
that are mere moments away
from kicking in...
And leading us home.
I can not wait! Here it comes...
- Anything?
- No.
Wait! Aw! I...
Argh! No!
I don't know, Duke.
Maybe the legend of dogs
coming from wolves is just wrong.
I mean like, maybe one puppy
asks his mom,
"Where did we come from?"
and the mom said, "Woof"!
And the kid was like,
"Oh, wolves"!
And she's like, "Yeah, fine".
- Sausage!
- Huh?
Do you smell that?
- Oh, man. It is!
- Sausage!
Well then,
what are we waiting for?
We're coming for you, baby!
Lower the ramp, dummy!
Who are they?
This is Puffball, Squashface,
Wiener Dog,
Yellow Bird, Eagle Eye,
Guinea Pig Joe!
And of course
my girlfriend, Ronda!
Ah! 100% percent wrong.
Good enough.
Come on, let's go!
Move it or lose it.
Every bird instinct I have says,
"Don't follow a dog on wheels".
Um... Mr. Pops. Sir...
Shouldn't we be
heading to the sewers?
Now, if we take the human road,
getting there is gonna
take days.
You may have lot of time,
but for me, every breath
is a cliffhanger!
So, we gotta take
the secret route.
Okay! The secret route was death.
- Well, that's that, I guess.
- Come on!
Get down here.
Sweet Pea.
Keep moving.
Oh, no!
Stop it! Look away!
Come on, I don't have all day.
Come on, slowpokes.
What is that smell?
It's poo-poo
with a dash of caca.
Scent is getting stronger.
Aww!
Oh, man!
Duke, let's eat!
Oh, yes!
Oh, smells so good!
Oh, yeah!
- Sausages!
Come on, boys!
Holy Schnitzel!
"We go together,."
"Like rama lamma lamma
ka dinga da dinga dong."
"Remembered forever,
"As shoobop sha wadda
wadda yippity boom de boom".
"Chang chang
changitty chang shoobop."
"That's the way it should be."
"Wha-oohh, yeah!"
"We're for each other,
"Like a wop ba-ba lu-bop
and wop bam boom".
"Just like my brother is,
"Sha-na-na-na-na-na
yippity dip de doom".
"Chang chang
chanitty chang sha-bop".
"We'll always be together,."
"Wha-oohh, yeah!"
"We'll always be together".
"We'll always..."
You get in a wierd pipe, man.
Alright, now these guys are
a bit testy.
So, just let me do the talking.
Hey, you cry baby!
Where is the Viper at?
Don't you worry, Viper!
You will not be forgotten!
You will be avenged, Viper!
And if you don't believe me,
You can look at my battle plans.
It's all laid out, right here!
Boss. I can't tell thogh what it is.
Well, you have to really
look at it to understand it.
Like, that's you guys
right here. And...
See, that's Brooklyn.
That's where we go get 'em dogs.
Bam! Bam!
That ball of fluff's got
a screw loose. Let's get at 'em.
But, you get it.
You see what I'm sayin'.
Bottom line is, I'm coming
right to you, Tiny Dog.
And that big fat brown dog,
he gonna get it, too.
Tiny Dog?
There're lots of tiny dogs
in the city!
I mean, you're a tiny dog, okay?
So, let's just go.
He also said, big fat brown dog.
Like Max's new roommate.
Not necessarily.
Whoo! Max! Max! Max! Max! Max!
You are gonna get it!
Ahh! That's kinda hard
to hard to dispute.
Hey! You stay away from...
Wait, what? You know, Tiny Dog?
He's my friend!
And some might say my boyfriend!
Uhh... Nobody says that.
I can't beleive you know, Tiny Dog.
Oh man, that's cool!
It's such a small world.
That's the funny thing about it.
- Get 'em!
- Scatter!
Not good.
See you guys, later.
Oh my God!
Everybody, run!
Derick, you idiot!
Did they all get away?
Hewo! That was a close one.
Oh, nuts!
Yes! We got one.
Oh, good for you, guys!
- Yay!
- Ya-hey!
Oh yes, Tiny Dog!
We got your friend!
Advantage me!
Uh-oh!
Just ignore
what just happend, okay?
Yes!
You know what?
I mean, this maybe
the sausage talking...
But, you're okay.
Right back at you, man!
You know, when I met you
I was all like...
"Oh! I don't know if I like him".
But, now that I know you,
I'm like...
"I like him".
You know, I saw this place.
From the outside. Many times!
And I know what treasures
are weighted within these walls.
I would've broke down that door
a long time ago, I tell you.
What are you talking about?
My old owner and I
used to live arond here.
Duke! Man, wait!
Did you used to have an owner?
Well, It was...
It was a long time ago.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Yes, you do. Come on.
I don't know.
But, you know what?
He was so cool.
Yeah?
Yeah. He was the best.
Man, we had fun!
We play fetch!
We go for walks.
We take naps.
We're both big nappers.
I got out one night,
chasing a butterfly or a car.
By the time, I'd caught up
with it and ate it!
Probably a butterfly, then.
I realized I was so far away
from my home.
I couldn't find it.
Few days later, I was picked up
by animal control.
I had a great thing going, but...
I had it go and mess it up.
Duke, we gotta go to your house!
Na!
You know, your owner
is gonna relieved!
Really?
Yeah, but...
But, he never came for me.
Maybe he...
Maybe he didn't like me.
Hey, of course he liked you.
He was your owner!
I mean, he's probably worried sick.
I don't know.
Well, I do know and we're going.
Your owner is gonna freak.
I'm freaking out just thinking about it!
Okay. Let's do it.
Here they are.
Alright, doggie, come on.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Where you think
you're going?
Come back here, you dogs!
Aahhh!
That rabbit. He has crazy eyes.
There ain't no curing
was wrong with that thing!
Gidget, here's an idea,
Maybe there's a dog in
the neighborhood that looks like Max.
Start hanging out with him,
after a while you'll think it's him,
you'll be done.
We're not just giving up!
We're dedicated, we're loyal,
We're easly the greatest
pet ever,
We're dogs!
- Cat.
- Hawk.
Well, Congratulations,
today you're dogs
whether you like it or not.
Sweet!
Now, let's find Max
before that rabbit does.
Right! We're dogs!
Yep! They were here.
Excellent.
We're closing in.
This is a groundbreaking
evil behavior, people.
Groundbreaking.
Light pop just now
from my brain.
The bunny has an idea.
Okay. So, how do I look?
You look great.
How do I smell?
Like a dog, Duke. Relax, man.
There it is!
Well, go on up.
Go scratch that door.
Remember that sausage factory?
That was fun, huh?
Are you stalling?
No, why do you think that?
Let's have a walk talk
about why you think I'm stalling.
Duke, you have nothing
to be nervous about.
You're owner is gonna be
thrilled to see you.
Okay.
Huh! That car's new!
Can I help you?
No, we're good, thanks.
You're not good. You look dirty.
And I'm gonna have to ask you
to get off my lawn
before I get... Um...
You know, what you have.
This is my lawn!
Duke, maybe we shoyld go.
And, why...
Why would Fred get a cat?
He hates cats.
It's one of things
I love about him.
Fred? The old guy?
He... Um...
He died.
Duke, maybe I made a mistake
saying we should come here.
Let... Let's go.
You're a lair.
Max, cats lie all the time.
Don't faff for it!
Who are they?
Hey! This is my home! Go away!
Duke! It's time to go.
Duke, let's go, come on!
This isn't your home anymore.
Why did you bring me here, Max?
Wait a minute. This is my fault?
You know, I was trying
to help you!
You were trying
to get rid of me!
Yeah, you know what, Duke?
I don't need this.
Um... See you later.
Whoa! Whoa!
Come on, settle down!
Go home, Max!
Hey! Help me out here!
Hold on, I'm coming!
Let's move!
Finally get you, big fella.
Whoa! Come on!
This is it for you!
Duke!
Tiny Dog!
Oh! Are you kidding me?
You thought this was over, Tiny Dog?
Jab! Jab! Jab!
Body blow! Body blow!
- Karate chop to your neck!
- Would you...
Would you get off me?
Tattoo!
No, no, no, no!
Oh, T.D. This kills me to say,
But, we gotta join forces, man!
We make a great team, Tiny Dog!
Well, mainly I'm doing
all the hard work.
But you're helping.
Yes, yes. Fine.
Just keep your eyes on the road.
You're driving like an animal!
What was that?
Oh, that was a pothole.
You're hitting things on purpose?
You know, you know me, too L.T.D.
Always keeping me in check.
Do you see the van?
Yeah, I see it.
We're about to hit it.
Relax Snowball, I got you.
There he is!
He's got Snowball!
Look, fellas.
This is not what it looks like.
Shhh you!
You are gonna eat the boss!
No, no, no. Snowball and I
are the same side, now!
Can you tell 'em, Snowball?
Tell them!
That raccoon is lying.
He's not the president.
Uh... I... I...
I...
Come on, now.
Gidget!
Go, Max!
Right! Okay, I gotta go.
Thank you! Thank you!
Stay down!
Duke, hang on!
Whoa! Whoah!
- Duke!
- Max! Max!
Oh! Okay, get the keys!
- Right!
- Hurry!
Come on! Come on!
I got 'em!
Max!
Remember me!
I feel heroic and handsome!
A ittle wet, but
I still look good! I look good!
Are you... Are you okay?
I'm good. I'm good.
Thanks for coming
to save me, Max.
Yay!
Max! Oh-hoh! Max!
You need a lift?
Yes, we need a lift!
Let's go, Tattoo!
Taxi!
Whoa!!
Hey! Hey! Uh, Gidget! Wait up!
- Oh! Hi, Max!
- Yeah, hi. Um..
Play it cool!
Yeah, I have...
I, I, I... I just wanted to...
Look.
Have you ever lived across
from someone your whole life...
But, you... But, you don't really
appreciate them until...
I don't know, until...
They're beating up a dozens
of animals on the Brooklyn bridge.
I guess, what I'm tryning
to say is...
If you ever wanna...
Okay.
Oh, great! You're in love.
How gross for everyone.
Now, move it!
- Good bye! See you later, Max!
- Good bye.
Does anyone know where we are?
- Bye, Max!
- Bye, Gidget.
- Okay, Bye-bye!
- See you, guys!
Man, I feel sorry for them.
Gotta run home to thier owners!
Not us!
Now, is back to our primary mission!
The downfall of the human race!
It is on, humans!
It is on!
Mommy! Can I have a bunny?
And a pig, and a crocodile
and a lizard?
Uh-oh!
Yay! Bunny!
Jab! Jab! Jab!
Body blow! Body blow!
Break away move!
Uh... What's going on?
What's she doing?
Bunny, I'm gonna love you
forever and ever, and ever!
Aww! Bunny!
Here you go.
Duke, This's the best part
of the day!
- Oh, is that her?
- Na, no. That's... Wait...
Yeah, she... That's her.
That's her!
- Katie!
There they are!
Max and Duke. Duke and Max.
Aww! My boys!
So, how'd it go? Great, right?
I... Uhh...
So, maybe a few box.
But, I knew this is gonna work out.
So...
Who's hungry?
Welcome home, Duke.
Thanks, Max.
Come on, man! Hurry it up!
Okay! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Welcome, my dogs!
Oh, you guys look weird!
Hurry up! Come on in!
You siad it was a costume party!
Why do you listen to me?
I'm home Leonard.
Were you a good boy, Leonard?
Alright, party is over!