(FAIRIES CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY)
(ALL LAUGHING)
If I could reach the top of the world
Be all I am
It'd be so beautiful
If only I could be brave
and I could be strong
I would know where I belong
(LAUGHING)
If only
I wanna feel free to be who I am
What I'm about is more than I've been
Ready to show the world who I am
Oh!
A little bit of sun.
Oh, look!
Hey, Zarina!
Oh.
Out of pixie dust again, sug?
(CHUCKLING) You know me, Rosetta.
I could give you some tips
on conserving your supply.
I may just take you up on that, Dessa.
A Dust Keeper Fairy
who's always out of pixie dust.
Ironic, isn't it?
Right there. Nice. Okay.
Rinse time!
Time to dry!
Hey, Z! Wings okay?
Just enjoying a stroll. But thanks, Fawn.
Nice wind, Vidia.
-Thanks. What's a "stroll"?
-(CHIRPING)
(LAUGHING)
Oh, no!
So I could be who I am
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm closer to where I'm meant to be
If I try I know that I can get there
I'm not gonna stop 'cause I believe
-(BLOWS)
-(FAIRY BLOWING CONCH)
That there's so much more to me
So much more
(GRUNTING)
I wanna feel free to be who I am
What I'm about is more than I've been
Ready to show the world who I am
Started it out, but I'm holding in
Find my own place to stay
So I can be who I am
Uh...
We put the dust in the bags
and they stay there, right?
And yet, we sprinkle dust
on top of something,
and it floats.
(ALL GASP)
Well, that's just how pixie dust works.
Well, yes, I know,
but "Why?" is the question.
Know what I mean?
Not even a little?
Never once had the thought?
FAIRY GARY: Good morning,
-Dust Keepers!
-Oh!
DUST KEEPER FAIRIES:
Good morning, Fairy Gary!
All right, let's see.
On blue dust duty today we have, uh...
-What were we on?
-"Y."
Ah! Yes. Yvette.
Yvette is out for the day, Fairy Gary.
Dust-Keeper elbow flared up again.
(GASPS) That's fantastic!
I mean, poor, poor Yvette.
Well, um, that brings us to...
"Z."
(SIGHS)
Zarina, you're up!
Uh-oh.
Can you believe it?
I mean, one day early.
It's so exciting!
Uh... Six clicks to the right.
Yes, thank you.
-Wow.
-Careful, now!
After last time,
I'm sure I don't have to remind you
just how potent and powerful...
-No touching, I promise.
-Attagirl!
All right, then. Exactly 26 specks.
But why 26?
-And here we go.
-Why not 25?
What would happen
if we put in, say, 27?
-We put in 26.
-But why?
Ah, Zarina, you're the most
inquisitive fairy I've ever known.
Correction, it's a tie.
Let's just say, you're the Tinker Bell
of Dust Keepers.
But why do you say it
like it's a bad thing?
Because we don't work
with twigs and acorn caps.
We work with pixie dust.
It's our lifeblood.
There's no room for error.
(LAUGHS)
Blue dust.
One of nature's mightiest multipliers.
It takes the golden dust
from a trickle to a roar.
No matter how many times
I see it, just... Wow!
Indeed.
Okay, but if there's blue dust,
why can't there be other colors?
Because there aren't.
And maybe those other colors
do other things.
What if there was, I don't know, purple?
(GASPS)
What if there's pink?
(LAUGHS)
The day someone finds pink pixie dust
is the day I trade in my kilt for trousers.
Well, what if we don't find it?
What if we make it?
Listen carefully, Zarina.
We do not tamper with pixie dust.
It is far too powerful.
But if we don't,
we'll never fully understand
what it's capable of.
That is not our job.
We're Dust Keepers.
We nurture the dust, maintain it,
measure it, package it,
and distribute it.
A beautiful tradition, day in, day out,
-passed from one generation...
-(BLOWS)
-...to the next, to the next, to the next.
-Oh!
(GASPS)
(ZARINA GASPS)
-Oh! Ahh!
-Oh, no!
-Fairy Gary!
-(GROANS)
-Are you okay?
-(GRUNTS)
Technically, I didn't touch it this time.
The cap?
Let me be absolutely clear, Zarina.
Dust Keepers are forbidden
to tamper with pixie dust.
Hmm.
No result.
No result. No result.
No result. Ugh!
Huh?
Hmm.
Two parts sunflower seed,
a dash of moonflower.
(GASPING)
Huh.
(GASPS)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(LAUGHING)
It worked!
Oh! Hey, Zarina!
-What brings you...
-Tinker Bell...
-...here?
-Remember how you were
the first one to use lost things,
and everyone thought
you were kind of crazy?
I believe Fairy Mary called them "junk."
Exactly! But now, even she uses them
and tinkering is better than ever.
Well, that's nice of...
And remember how you crossed
the Winter border
when you knew it wasn't allowed,
but you just had to anyway?
I like to think it was more of a grey area.
-Good. Now, keep that in mind.
-Whoa!
TINKER BELL: You...
You're bending light.
You're bending light?
But you're not a Light Fairy.
You're a Dust Keeper.
Amazing, right?
Uh, but, how?
Whoa!
You found orange pixie dust?
No, Tink. I made orange pixie dust.
That's never been done before.
Exactly! I knew you'd understand.
Now, I can finally figure out
everything pixie dust is capable of.
Oh, what does Fairy Gary
think about all this?
Uh...
-He doesn't exactly know.
-What?
ZARINA: He doesn't really think
we should tamper with pixie dust.
-Do you mind stirring?
-Uh, okay.
I guess he thinks it's just too powerful.
-Oh! You can't stop.
-Oh! Uh...
(CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY)
Is that blue dust?
You're doing this with blue dust?
Yes, and it just takes the tiniest bit.
Can you believe it?
-Back up a little.
-Uh...
ZARINA: Huh.
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
-Wow.
-ZARINA: Purple pixie dust.
(GASPS) Wind!
Purple equals fast-flying talent!
Huh. (GASPS)
-Uh...
-(GIGGLES)
-Garden talent next!
-Uh...
-Zarina?
-Pink pixie dust...
Maybe you should, you know,
slow down a bit.
Five pieces of petal
for every three drops of extract.
-Uh, should it be bubbling like that?
-Mmm-hmm.
Two? This time you're adding two?
Uh-huh.
(BOTH YELP)
Zarina! Are you okay?
Tinker Fairy Gary some trousers,
because I just made pink pixie dust.
Zarina, this seems kind of dangerous.
Do you know what this means, Tink?
I've finally found my "lost things."
Dust-keeping will change forever!
Zarina, I really think you should stop!
What? (YELPS)
(GASPS)
(RUMBLING)
(BOTH GASP)
Oh, no! No, no, no, no, no.
-(ALL GASPING)
-MALE FAIRY: Whoa! Look out!
(GASPS)
(YELPS)
(SCREAMING)
Huh?
(GASPING)
Oh, no!
No! (GRUNTING)
Ow! Oh!
Oh, no!
Whoa!
(FAIRY GARY GRUNTING)
(SIGHS)
(COUGHING)
(SIGHING)
Huh?
No...
Hmm?
(PANTING)
CLARION: Oh!
How did this happen?
(PANTING)
-(ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
-Oh, no!
What happened?
-Tink, are you okay?
-Oh, my.
-Yeah.
-Who grew these?
(FAIRY GARY CLEARING THROAT)
I'm so sorry. I'll help rebuild the depot.
I'll come in early, I'll stay late!
You were told not
to tamper with pixie dust.
I think it's best
if you don't come in at all.
What are you saying?
You are no longer a Dust Keeper.
It's simply too dangerous.
We'll start rebuilding in the morning,
Queen Clarion.
(SIGHS)
FAIRY ANNOUNCER:
Welcome one, welcome all
to the Four Seasons Festival!
Tonight, every talent
from every season will gather together
to celebrate all the realms
of Pixie Hollow.
Wow! Can you believe it?
Everyone in Pixie Hollow is here!
It's so great to have
the Winter Fairies join us.
I'll say it is.
(SIGHS)
It's enough to give you the vapors.
(TINKER BELL GRUNTING)
Tinker Bell, don't you Tinkers
ever stop tinkering?
Can't seem to get this latch to open!
(SIGHS) It had better not stick like that
-for our grand finale.
-(BUGLE BLOWING)
-(GASPS) Is it starting?
-No, that's just Clank.
(EXCLAIMING IN APPROVAL)
(LAUGHS)
-The thing is pretty loud, eh, Bobble?
-(LAUGHS)
Indeed, my bugling buddy.
Sure makes me thirsty, though.
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
BOTH: It's starting!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(GASPS) Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
Bobble...
Oh, no! Already?
Hold these!
But the show just started!
-CLANK: Ask them to wait!
-(LAUGHING)
-(ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
-Hey, guys, I can't see!
Oh! It's Periwinkle!
-Beautiful.
-Oh, look at that.
Hi, Peri!
(GIGGLES)
That's my sister.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
All right!
-(ALL CHEERING)
-Oh, wow!
-Yeah!
-Yay!
Go, fairies!
Ro, did you do those?
That wasn't in rehearsal.
ROSETTA: Wasn't me.
I never work with poppies.
The pollen makes me sleepy.
Wait. Is that...
Zarina?
-Zarina?
-Hmm.
She's back?
What's with that wild hair?
(ALL CHEERING)
Oh, look at those flowers!
BOBBLE: Ooh!
Spring must be next! (CHUCKLES)
That's my favorite.
Oh, I hope Clanky doesn't miss it.
-(BLOWING)
-Oh!
(ALL GASP)
-AUDIENCE: Wow! Oh!
-Huh?
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Oh, lovely! Oh!
-Guys, guys! We gotta hide!
-ALL: Oh!
Now, now, now!
They've really outdone
themselves this year.
(SIGHS)
(YAWNS) What a show.
(YAWNING)
(BLOWING)
(ALL SNORING)
(SCOFFS)
(GASPS) Whoo!
Excuse me. Sorry.
Yes, me again. Coming through.
No, no, don't get up.
Oh, sorry, I should have flown.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you, Bobble.
(EXHALES) What did I miss?
(SNORING)
(BUGLE BLOWING)
Wake up!
Please! Anyone?
-FAIRIES: Clank, help us! Down here!
-(GASPS)
TINKER BELL: Clank!
-In here! In the box!
-Oh! Oh, oh...
-Ms. Bell?
-TINKER BELL: Help, we're stuck.
Right. How does it open?
TINKER BELL: Push the button!
-(ALL SIGH IN RELIEF)
-Thank you so much.
You've got to see this.
(ALL GASP)
Oh, no.
(ALL SNORING)
-Are they...
-No. Goodness, no.
(SIGHS)
ROSETTA: They're in a deep sleep.
For how long?
ROSETTA: At least a couple of days.
Why would Zarina do this?
Clank, did you see her?
No, no.
(GASPS) Yes, yes,
I saw her flying towards the dust depot.
(GASPS)
The blue pixie dust.
Ooh, this is bad.
Uh, yeah.
Without it, the tree
can't make pixie dust.
(STAMMERING)
And if the tree can't make pixie dust...
We can't fly.
Oh! Can't... Can't fly...
-Deep breaths.
-Can't fly...
-Okay. Okay.
-That's it. Deep breaths.
(INHALING DEEPLY)
What could she want it for?
I don't know. But we have to find her.
Clank, stay here
and watch over everyone.
I'm on it.
Especially the Winter Fairies.
Make sure they get
a steady stream of snow.
Right!
(EXHALES)
Right.
The blue dust has a strong glow.
If we can just spot it...
(GASPS) There!
Whoa, she's moving fast!
-(SCREECHES)
-(FAIRIES GASP)
FAWN: Oh, sorry!
Where is all this fog coming from?
It's mist. We must be
getting near the coast.
TINKER BELL:
(GASPS) We're losing her!
Over there!
(ALL GASP)
-ROSETTA: Oh, my!
-(PIRATES LAUGHING)
TINKER BELL: Oh, no.
(STAMMERING) It's...
Pirates.
Great, now there's pirates.
Maybe they're nice pirates.
Right.
They must have captured her,
forced her to take the dust.
Well, we have to rescue her.
(STAMMERING) But they're...
Deep breaths. Deep (INHALES) breaths.
-Okay.
-Hmm.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(PIRATES LAUGHING)
-JAMES: Magnificent!
-Quite right.
-A fine haul.
-(PIRATES LAUGHING)
PORT: We got their blue dust!
STARBOARD:
Well, it's not theirs anymore.
PORT: It is theirs no longer.
STARBOARD:
I just said that, you daft potato muncher.
-(GASPS)
-PORT: Potato...
They're holding her
in the bottom of the boat.
STARBOARD: You've got a right
wee brain, you know that?
PORT: Still smart enough
-to know we got their dust!
-(SHUDDERS)
Let me just say that your plan
worked perfectly, Captain.
(ALL LAUGHING)
-"Captain"?
-(ALL GASP)
Here's to perfect plans.
Aye! Perfect!
Guess she doesn't need rescuing.
But now the hair makes sense.
What do we do now?
Let's just get the dust
and get out of here.
A little bit of pillage,
a little bit of plunder.
BOTH: Oh!
(YELPING)
(GASPS)
Fairies!
-Ahh!
-(GRUNTING)
Get her! Get her!
PIRATES: Whoa!
(GRUNTING)
Got it.
-Here!
-PORT: She's getting away!
JAMES: They took the blue dust!
(GRUNTING)
Captain!
Give me back that dust!
Zarina, why are you doing this?
-(GRUNTING)
-ROSETTA: Fawn!
If you give it to me, I'll give you quarter.
Quarter? I think we need all of it.
"Quarter" means mercy!
-(GRUNTS)
-Ooh.
This dust belongs to Pixie Hollow.
You had your chance.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL GROAN)
-SILVERMIST: Wake up.
-(GROANS)
-Tink, wake up.
-(GASPS)
(GROANS)
What happened?
The last thing I remember
was Zarina throwing that dust at us.
Your dress.
I know. Um...
-(GASPS)
-(FAWN GROANING)
Is everyone all right?
I guess so.
(GASPS) I'm not. Look at my outfit!
Orange is not my color.
-She's right.
-(WHIMPERS)
Listen, we have to get out of here
and go after Zarina.
Silvermist, can you part the...
(ALL YELPING)
Shut it off! Shut it off!
I didn't do anything. I just...
ALL: (YELPING) Tink!
Tink, could you stop
not doing anything?
It's okay, I got this.
Whoa! (GROANS)
TINKER BELL:
Silvermist, are you okay?
Whoa!
(GROANS)
That's weird. Here, let me help you.
(ALL GASPING)
It's so bright!
-Bright!
-IRIDESSA: Fawn, I can't see!
(SCREAMS)
-What did you do?
-IRIDESSA: I don't know.
Ew, ew, ew, ew.
Get them off. Get them off! Get them off!
Get them off!
TINKER BELL: Wait a minute.
Do you realize what this means?
Oh, my gosh!
Zarina switched our heads!
TINKER BELL: No. No, no, no.
She switched our talents.
-Excuse me?
-What?
I must be a Water Fairy now.
Oh, so, that's why your dress is blue.
And I guess you're a Fast-Flying Fairy.
I'm a... I'm a Light Fairy.
Ow.
IRIDESSA: Garden Fairy!
ROSETTA: Oh.
(SIGHS)
Looks like I'm an Animal Fairy now. Huh.
Lucky me.
No, no, no, it can't be.
-(LAUGHS) You're a...
-Don't say it.
Tinker Bell, take these things
back right now!
(CHUCKLING) Okay.
(SIGHS)
-Tinker.
-(GROWLS)
Guys, come on,
we gotta get out of here.
Well, you're the Water Fairy.
Part the waters.
Um, use both hands this time.
(GRUNTING)
Well, you don't see that every day.
You guys better hurry! I can't hold it!
(GRUNTS) Sil!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Oops!
(ALL GROANING)
-(COUGHING)
-SILVERMIST: Guys, are you...
-(GRUNTS)
-(IRIDESSA WHIMPERING)
...okay?
Yeah.
Guys, I think I broke something.
(YELPS)
Whoa!
Uh...
Nice, little, harmless,
sharp-toothed, hungry croco...
(BOTH GASP)
...dile.
Fawn!
It's okay. When babies are born,
they imprint on the first thing they see.
Uh, guys, sorry to interrupt
whatever that is,
but the pirate ship is gone.
-What?
-Oh, no.
VIDIA: Sil, Fast Flyer, check it out.
Oh, yeah.
(STAMMERING)
Where is she?
(SILVERMIST SCREAMING)
You guys, I saw it, up the coast!
Let's go!
(SILVERMIST STAMMERING)
Oh, right, you can't fly.
-Wet wings.
-(CLICKS TONGUE)
Still, there's got to be a way to... Ah!
Excuse me, Ro.
Hmm. Structurally sound enough.
Strength-to-weight ratio seems good.
If I had some rope...
(GASPS) Oh!
You're thinking like a Tinker.
(GROWLING)
Okay, fine.
Get me some vines.
Not a problem.
(EXCLAIMING)
IRIDESSA: Will these do?
Okay, ready?
Wait for me!
(GRUNTING)
Sorry. Gotta...
Can I please have that?
-Oh! (GRUNTS)
-VIDIA: Go!
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
There's the pirate ship!
You can slow down now!
Easy for you to say. (SCREAMS)
-Hold on!
-(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL GROANING)
ROSETTA:
Well, at least our wings are dry.
Yeah.
YANG: (LAUGHS)
Twenty-one gun salute to the captain!
OPPENHEIMER: Right, 21.
(PIRATES LAUGHING)
BONITO: Nice boom!
PORT: Oh, yes! Nice!
ALL: Ohh!
(PIRATES LAUGHING)
Music to my ear!
BONITO: That's right!
STARBOARD: Encore!
PORT: Beautiful!
Yes, yes, yes!
(EXPLOSION)
Cease fire!
What? Cease fire?
(STAMMERING) What for?
That was only seven.
I say 21.
(BLOWS)
Right! (CHUCKLES)
Twenty-one, obviously,
on the metric system, which is fine.
Come on,
we've got to find that dust.
(CLEARS THROAT)
If I may, good sirs, I believe
the proper acknowledgement
would be a toast.
(LAUGHS) A toast it is!
Now, there is a good cabin boy.
BONITO: A beautiful suggestion.
-STARBOARD: Quite thirsty, myself.
-Uh-uh!
If it pleases the captain.
You tell those scurvy scallywags that...
(BELL TINKLING)
What did she say?
She said, it does!
(PIRATES CHEERING)
What is better
than a good mug of grog?
Two mugs!
Your tea, Captain. Earl Grey, hot.
Please, sir, may I have some more?
JAMES: To our cunning captain.
Okay, you gotta love the boots.
Just one year ago, we'd lost everything.
Our ship turned adrift, and then
(CHUCKLES)
-we found her.
-(BELL TINKLES)
(LAUGHING)
Exactly. We needed a captain.
And when we humbly asked
if she could make us fly...
She didn't stop there.
No! She did one better, she did.
Better indeed!
Soon, she's going to
make the whole ship fly!
PIRATES: To flying!
(ALL GASP)
Fly?
First the Tower of London, arr!
The guards won't know what hit it
We'll swoop right down
and take the crown
And the Crown Jewels with it
And when we fly to Paris
Oh, the treasures I'll be grabbin'
The Mona Lisa will look lovely
Hanging in me cabin
PIRATES: Hey-ho
Imagine the places that we'll go
No one can stop us
When we're so
High in the stratosphere!
PIRATES: Hey-ho
We'll be the freighter that plunders
Every one of the world's
seven wonders
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a frigate that flies?
No one can fight a frigate that flies
Next we'll roam to Rome, me lads
And here's what I'll be stealin'
I'll rob the Sistine Chapel
Of the Sistine Chapel's ceilin'
And for all the folks in Egypt
It will be a dismal day
They'll be crying for their mummies
When we take their mummies away!
PIRATES: Hey-ho
Imagine the places that we'll go
No can stop us when we're so high!
They will all cower in fear
Hey-ho, from Delhi to Rio to Venice
There's no city that we will not menace
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a frigate that flies?
No one can fight a frigate that flies
-Oh, how high we will be!
-We will be
'Cause the blue fairy dust
Surely packs a mighty wallop
Only takes a dollop
-Soon it will set us free
-We'll be free
From the chains of gravity
Then we'll hoist up the sail
And we'll set course for the sun
'Cause when you've got wings
No wicked deed cannot be done
And we owe it all
To our great and glorious captain
Although, now that you mention it,
why are we taking orders
from some fairy, anyway?
-(ALL GASP)
-(SWORD UNSHEATHES)
(GASPS) Heh, heh, heh...
Two, three, four!
Hey-ho,
imagine the places that we'll go
No one can stop us when we're so high
-Givin' a pirate cheer
-PIRATES: Arr!
Hey-ho, we'll be
the freighter that plunders
Every one of the world's
seven wonders
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a frigate that flies?
Hey-ho, there's not a town or a county
That will not yield its bounty up
When our ship draws near
Hey-ho, there's not a city or village
That we will not plunder or pillage
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a frigate that flies?
And every nation will give a donation
When they see us sail the skies
In a frigate that flies!
Hey!
(ALL LAUGHING)
ALL: Ah!
(SEAGULLS CAWING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(FAIRIES GASPING)
-Whoa.
-Tink.
(ALL GASP)
IRIDESSA: It looks like...
The Pixie Dust Tree back home.
Zarina must have grown it.
So, that's how they're going to fly.
She's going to make pixie dust.
Ahoy, you biscuit-eating bilge rats!
Prepare to dock starboard!
-PIRATES: Docking starboard!
-(BELL TINKLING)
Captain says, raise the sails
and step lively!
PIRATES: Raise the sails!
Heave!
Bring her around, Mr. Yang!
(GRUNTING) Bringing her around!
-Let go anchor!
-JAMES: Let go anchor!
-Get out all lines!
-JAMES: Get out all lines!
PIRATES: Casting lines!
(LAUGHING)
STARBOARD: Come on, get moving.
PORT: Are you talking to me?
JAMES: Captain says, restock the ship.
We set sail at dawn.
Yes, Captain. Load ship, right away.
PORT: Hey, watch where
you're swinging that thing!
YANG: (LAUGHS) Work faster, now!
That's it!
Come on.
(GRUNTING)
Locked.
PORT: Come on, you lubber,
get on with it.
Someone's coming!
-Pirate!
-(GASPS)
Hide!
-(MOUSE SQUEAKS)
-(ALL GASP)
(FAIRIES WHIMPERING)
(WHISPERS) Animal Fairy, you're up.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Excuse me, mouse. Uh...
Mr. Mouse. (CHUCKLES)
Would you mind terribly moving on?
We need this space to do a little hiding.
-(SQUEAKING)
-Oh!
(CHUCKLES)
Much obliged.
Bye-bye!
Aw, what a cute little mouse.
-It was a rat.
-(GASPS)
Ew!
JAMES: Hey, shoo, rat!
(SQUEAKING)
Uh, permission to enter, Captain.
This is our chance.
Now!
(ALL GASP)
No!
I had Oppenheimer
make you your favorite.
The dust.
I know how much you like
a little something sweet while you work.
(BELL TINKLING)
Well, you're quite welcome.
Hmm? Oh, uh...
Uh, yes, of course. Sorry.
Ah, right, second drawer.
(CHUCKLES)
Look at that.
It sparkles like a thousand sapphires.
(SIGHS)
You're quite the little genius.
It's hard to believe the other fairies
didn't appreciate your talent.
(GROANING)
-Sil?
-She looks seasick.
(RETCHES) This never happened
when I was a Water Fairy.
JAMES:
You know, I remember when I couldn't
-understand a single jingle.
-VIDIA: Oh, no!
Huh?
(SILVERMIST VOMITING)
I'm fine.
(SNIFFING)
-ROSETTA: Fawn!
-(GASPS)
(BOTH GASP)
-Sorry!
-What are you doing?
-What Dess does.
-That's not what I do.
Well, stop it!
You shouldn't take light so lightly.
(GASPS)
-What?
-What, what? What?
(CHUCKLING NERVOUSLY)
No, nothing, nothing!
Ooh.
(GASPS)
It's still so hard to believe
that this blue dust can make flying dust.
Yes, but only if you...
-(BELL TINKLING)
-Ah!
So, the secret is the infusion
of the blue dust directly into the tree.
-(GROANS)
-Sil, you okay?
Start throwing out the line.
All right, Tink, open the drawer
as much as you can.
JAMES: So, once the golden
dust has been produced...
Sil, hold the line.
JAMES: ...the sluice will coat the ship
with the perfect amount,
and at that point, we take to the skies!
Very impressive, Captain.
(GRUNTS)
JAMES: No pirate I know could
have imagined such a scheme.
-(BOTH GRUNTING)
-Whoa!
Ahh!
-Oh.
-Vidia!
You've turned out to be quite
the pint-sized prodigy,
if I may say.
It's been an adventure and an honor.
Your sword, Captain.
Hmm.
(ALL GASP)
(ALL EXCLAIM)
Y'all okay?
Yeah. They're headed for the tree.
Come on!
Whoa! What is up with your...
Hey, hey, we should catch up with Tink.
Shh.
STARBOARD:
All right, just give me the strap.
YANG: That's it, hold it in place.
JAMES:
Right, watch the angle of the flume.
Too much pitch, and she'll overflow.
STARBOARD: Aye aye, Captain!
JAMES:
Make sure the seams are sealed.
Captain doesn't want
to lose a single grain
of that precious dust.
STARBOARD: Oh, that golden dust.
(IRIDESSA WHIMPERS)
FAIRIES: Dess! Quiet!
Sorry. I barely touched it.
Well, don't touch it at all.
-Just hover.
-Yeah, hover.
All right, all right.
As soon as she's gone,
we'll grab the dust and get out of here.
Maybe we should try and talk to her.
Yeah, because that worked out
so well back at the waterfall.
(SIGHS)
(BUZZING)
Hey, shoo.
(GRUNTS) Hey!
Shoo, shoo!
-(BUZZING)
-Hey, hey, hey...
Go, go, go!
Oh, no. No!
No, no, no, no, no!
Stop growing. Stop growing.
Please, branch, no!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(WHIMPERS)
(LAUGHING)
We got you!
Did you really think
by switching our talents,
you could beat us?
(CHUCKLES) Looks that way.
-(WHISTLES)
-OPPENHEIMER: Got them!
-(ALL GASPING)
-TINKER BELL: Zarina!
Well done. Got them all
in one swell foop, I did.
Zarina, don't do this.
Come back with us. Come back home.
(LAUGHING)
I'll never go back to Pixie Hollow.
You don't belong here.
This is exactly where I belong, Tink.
We appreciate what she can do.
We treasure it, actually.
-(SNAP FINGERS)
-(OPPENHEIMER LAUGHING)
Put them below,
and keep your eye on them.
Oh, right. Maybe I'll use, uh, this one?
While you still have it. (LAUGHING)
Captain, are you all right?
(BELL TINKLES)
Captain says, back to work, gentlemen.
YANG: All righty, mates, you heard him.
(LAUGHING)
OPPENHEIMER: And, right.
Perfect fit.
Welcome to your new cabin.
-(ALARM RINGING)
-Oh.
Me stock is ready.
(GRUNTING)
(SINGING)
Oh, well, now, look at that.
(SNIFFS) Oh, lovely.
Oh, that is good eating right there.
Isn't it, Mum? "Yes, it is, darling."
Oh, let me see.
What shall I make tonight?
Well, I've still got some lard
and some old cabbage.
Okay, we need a plan.
Here we go.
(RUMBLING)
(BOTH GASPING)
-Whoa!
-Mmm.
-Ah!
-JAMES: Oh!
It worked!
-Yes, she did it!
-YANG: It worked! (LAUGHS)
-It's working!
-Pixie dust!
-Look at it! Amazing!
-(ALL CHEERING)
We're going to fly!
(LAUGHS) From a trickle to a roar.
BONITO: Fly like a happy bird!
Cold gruel, with a little bit of sawdust.
A dash of rodent, sauteed of course.
Some carrots? No.
Hey, where you think
you're going, little fella?
(LAUGHING)
Now is our chance. Go, go, go, go!
-Come on, all together.
-(FAIRIES QUARRELLING)
IRIDESSA: I'm going as fast as I can!
Oh, not today, my darlings.
Would you be kind enough
to hold this for me?
Perfect.
Anybody else got an idea?
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Absolutely astonishing.
Just imagine, flying like a bird.
(CHUCKLES)
Of course, you do that all the time.
What's it like? How do you even steer?
It's pretty simple, actually. Lean left.
Lean right, fly right.
(STAMMERING)
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
This is... (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Are you afraid?
Hmm?
Afraid? (CHUCKLES)
Lead on, Captain.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, I'm doing it.
I'm...
I'm flying!
(BOTH GASPING)
-Look out, mates!
-(ALL EXCLAIMING)
-Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-STARBOARD: Look at him go.
What's so funny? Whoa! Whoa, whoa...
You can't fly like that.
Put your legs together.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(YELLING)
Whoo! (LAUGHING)
Oh!
Oh. (LAUGHING)
Just try to keep up.
(JAMES PANTING)
(LAUGHING)
Whoo-hoo!
-Whoo.
-(BELL TINKLING)
Aye aye, Captain!
STARBOARD: The lad is flying!
(PIRATES LAUGHING)
It works! It really works.
And pretty soon, we'll have enough dust
to make the whole ship fly.
-Right, Zarina?
-(BELL TINKLES)
And as long as we have the blue dust,
we'll never run out of flying dust.
-Right again?
-Right again, James.
(GASPS)
Well, then, we won't need you anymore.
(GRUNTS)
(JAMES LAUGHING)
-Our plan worked perfectly.
-(PIRATES LAUGHING)
Fairies are such gullible creatures.
-Aren't they, lads?
-(PIRATES CHEER)
No match for an Eton education
such as mine.
STARBOARD:
He's a smart one, isn't he?
The power of the pixie dust
is finally ours.
(ALL CHEERING)
We've had enough kissing up
to that pint-sized prima donna.
No quarter for her.
Let's make her walk a tiny little plank.
STARBOARD: Yes, tiny!
PORT: A tiny plank!
She can fly, you cretins.
ALL: Oh!
YANG: You know, he's right.
That is why he is the captain.
She'd just fly away. I get it.
(LAUGHS) Mi capitn.
PORT:
What if we tie her wings together?
(LAUGHS)
There's no stopping us.
We'll plunder every port
in all the seven seas.
(PIRATES CHEERING)
Prepare to get under way,
you scurvy scallywags.
We've got a ship to fly.
(ALL CHEERING)
Ha. And as for you,
you'll make a fine little nightlight.
(GRUNTS)
-(GASPS)
-(LAUGHING)
Swoggle me eyes.
-Now, there's a sight.
-(BELL TINKLES)
Oh, don't feel foolish.
I was just too clever for you. That's all.
Ah! Yes.
Now, you see, my little fairy,
navigating the Never Seas is one thing.
But to chart a course for the sky,
not only do you need
longitude and latitude,
but you also need altitude.
-(BELL TINKLING)
-Hmm. Oh...
Now, let's not be a sore loser.
(LAUGHS)
Once we're past the second star,
the world will be my oyster.
And I don't even like oysters.
(LAUGHS)
We'll be in and out of every port so fast,
they won't even know what hit them.
(GRUNTS)
No, no, no.
Nice try, but it's fairy-proof.
Brilliant, right?
(LAUGHING)
-(CLOCK TICKING)
-(GROANS)
Oppenheimer!
That ticking is driving me mad!
Right. It's just a clock, you know.
-Well, not to worry.
-(BELLS TINKLING)
Pretty soon, we'll be flying so high
it'll make these high seas
look downright low!
-Crazy.
-Like we have a choice.
Come on, guys,
we're gonna get out of this.
Well, we wouldn't even be in it
if our new Garden Fairy
didn't grow branches willy-nilly!
You're not saying this is my fault.
-Hmm. If the flower fits.
-(GASPS)
How can I cook
with all that infernal jingle-jangling?
There's only one thing to do.
(GRUNTING)
Oh, much better. Don't you think, Mum?
None of it would've happened
if you would have come over
to help me with the bee!
Are you saying this is my fault?
Well, if the rose fits.
-(GASPS)
-Let's not point fingers. It's Zarina's fault.
-Guys? Guys?
-Right, what about her?
IRIDESSA: Yeah, let's talk about that.
Guys, look!
(SNIFFING)
(LAUGHS) Great. Just what I need.
(COOING)
Uh-uh-uh. Bad crocodile. Bad croc.
-(WHINES)
-I am not your mother!
Wait. Rosetta,
he can get us out of here.
You're right.
Good. Good crocodile. Come here.
Come here, crocky.
Come to Mama.
Shh! Quiet.
Okay. Now, pull us off the table.
Come here. Come to Mama.
-That's right, sugar.
-(ALL EXCLAIMING)
What is going on here? (GASPS)
A stowaway, is it?
Oh, no!
Oh, no, you don't. (GRUNTS)
Hello.
Hurry! Hurry!
-Gotcha!
-FAIRIES: Rosetta!
-A little extra flavor.
-(GROWLING)
(SCREAMS)
Ooh! (LAUGHING)
Good job, crocky.
You are such a good little boy.
Yes, you are.
What a good little
widdle snuggle wuggums.
That's his mama.
Okay, enough. Let's get out of here.
Wait, Vidia.
We can't just race out there.
They'll see us.
Hmm.
(GRUNTS)
JAMES: Make ready to sail!
STARBOARD: Aye aye, Captain!
I love the life of a pirate.
-(SQUEAKING)
-(GASPS)
But I hate rats.
STARBOARD: Move it, Port.
PORT: I'll move it in me own good time.
Huh, see anything?
Nope. All clear up here.
Well, it's not clear down here. It stinks!
I know, isn't it great?
-Smells just like skunk.
-Huh.
Spoken like a true Animal Fairy.
I wish.
All right, you guys.
Remember, right arm, left foot. Got it?
FAIRIES: Aye aye.
Sil, I'm right, you're left.
-SILVERMIST: Right.
-No, left.
-I mean, left.
-What?
-And you're right.
-(SCOFFS) Let's go.
Aye aye!
(FAIRIES GROAN)
SILVERMIST: Big pole.
FAIRIES: Back, back, back.
VIDIA: Forward, forward, forward.
Hey, you swabs, work faster!
Hey!
Oppenheimer!
Don't forget the kippers. (LAUGHING)
And you, back to work.
Ah, muy bien.
Ah, we're gonna fly, mate!
We're gonna fly!
ROSETTA: It's a do-si-do.
FAWN: I can't dance!
(LAUGHING)
(ALL GASP)
VIDIA: Uh-oh.
Look out!
-(ALL GASP)
-VIDIA: Fly!
PORT: Would you watch
where I'm going?
FAWN: Go, go!
(BOTH GROAN)
Come on!
-Hurry up!
-Okay.
We got it!
JAMES: Return that blue dust!
-Or your friend is done for.
-(GASPS)
JAMES: That's right.
Captain Zarina
has been relieved of duty.
Ha.
You truly are a talented fairy.
(GRUNTS)
Prepare to cast off!
Weigh anchor and get ready to fly,
me hearties!
Casting off!
It's working!
I can't believe my eye!
YANG: Weigh anchor!
-(LAUGHING)
-BONITO: We're flying!
PIRATES: We're flying!
OPPENHEIMER: It's perfect.
We can fly!
OPPENHEIMER:
Oh, my! Up, up and away!
(PIRATES LAUGHING)
STARBOARD:
Shiver me timbers, we're flying!
-Bon voyage, little captain.
-(SCREAMING)
-No!
-(FAIRIES GASP)
(ALL GRUNTING)
-Come on, hurry!
-(ALL STRAINING)
Hurry!
(ZARINA COUGHING)
Help! Please!
Help! (GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
Help me!
(GASPS)
-Here, I'll dry you off.
-(ALL PANTING)
(PIRATES LAUGHING)
JAMES: We're flying!
Are you okay?
You saved me.
Why?
Let's just say,
we're offering you quarter.
I'm so sorry.
(ZARINA SIGHS)
They're headed for the second star.
If they make it past
we'll never find them.
The blue dust will be gone forever.
Then let's stop them
before they get there.
Captain.
Port, Starboard, get up the mizzen
and raise the royal.
BOTH: Aye aye, Captain!
Raising the royal!
More pixie dust!
(JAMES LAUGHING)
Who's in the mood to plunder?
You guys turn the ship around.
-I'm getting back that blue dust.
-Right.
Look alive, men!
The second star, dead ahead.
-Nothing but smooth sailing.
-(THUDDING)
Huh?
ALL: Yeah!
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
Fairies! Fairies!
-It's the fairies!
-(LAUGHS)
She's back? Well, get them off my ship.
-Gladly.
-(PIRATES LAUGHING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(LAUGHS) It's actually
quite amusing.
Stand your ground, men!
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHING)
-Yang, the helm!
-(LAUGHING)
Aye aye, Captain!
Ladies, until we meet again.
(LAUGHING)
-Great.
-Ha.
You dare to fight the captain, do you?
Only until I get that dust.
(LAUGHING)
Well, this should be fun.
(GRUNTING)
Come here, you little cuties.
-Okay, this isn't working.
-(GASPS)
Fawn, the spyglass!
Brilliant!
(LAUGHS)
-(GRUNTS)
-(SCREAMS)
BONITO: You tiny thing.
(SCREAMING)
-No!
-(WATER SPLASHING)
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
(STAMMERS) Man overboard!
(GASPS) I did it!
Stop them, you imbeciles.
They're six-inch fairies!
Fawn, the wheel!
(GROANING)
Sil, whirlwind!
(YANG CONTINUES GROANING)
Take that! Whoa, whoa...
Blast it. The second star!
They turned the ship around!
-Yup, we sure did.
-(GRUNTS)
Get this ship back on course!
Aye aye, Captain! (GRUNTING)
-Now!
-(GRUNTS)
(EXCLAIMS)
Why you...
Bull's-eye!
(GRUNTING)
No fair! Come back here!
Fairies, fairies, nothing but fairies!
Stop moving so fast.
Ha-ha! Just one more, pirate.
Jingle-jingle. Ha!
(GASPS)
Uh-oh! (GROANS)
-Nice work.
-Just thinking like a Tinker.
No, no, no! Take that, you little...
-Oh, my!
-(ROARS)
Avast, crocky! Charge!
OPPENHEIMER: No!
Get it away, get it away,
get it away, get it away!
Yeah, that's it.
Don't make me use my teaspoon.
Oh, no. Oh, no, you don't, you little...
-Oh! You ate my mummy's clock?
-(CLOCK TICKING)
What was wrong with the spatula?
(LAUGHING) Sic him!
(SCREAMING)
(WATER SPLASHING)
Oh! (LAUGHING)
That's my crocky.
There's nothing I revel quite as much
-as a worthy opponent.
-(GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
(GROANS)
You're stronger than you look.
-(GRUNTING)
-(FAIRIES STRAINING)
Hey, need some help?
IRIDESSA: Anchor's away!
Grow some seaweed, sunflower.
PIRATES: Whoa!
Ahh! (GROWLS)
(CHUCKLES)
Now, that's some seaweed!
I've had just about
enough of this.
(GRUNTING)
Ha!
(ALL CHEERING)
(ALL GASP)
(FAIRIES GROAN)
-(GASPS)
-You, too!
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
STARBOARD:
You're not going anywhere.
(LAUGHING)
These ought to fetch a hefty price, eh?
(FAIRIES WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTING)
Back on course.
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTING)
(YANG LAUGHS)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
Give me that dust!
No!
(PIRATES YELPING)
(PIRATES SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
The dust! Not my dust!
No!
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
I got the dust.
TINKER BELL: Oh, you're okay.
ROSETTA: Oh, thank goodness.
(STRAINING)
Let's get you out of there.
-(LAUGHING)
-(GASPS)
Lean right,
fly right.
-(ALL GASP)
-I'll take that!
Now, where was I?
Ah, yes. The second star.
-(GROANING)
-(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS) You simply don't give up.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
Well, I guess I'm stronger than I look.
(STRAINING)
The second star.
(GRUNTING)
-(GROANS)
-(GRUNTS)
Oh...
(GASPS) Zarina!
You fought well, little fairy.
But it's over.
The dust is mine.
The ship is mine.
Your adventure has come to an end.
(BELL TINKLES)
Oh, go ahead, take it.
What's one speck between friends?
No, really, I think you should have it all!
-(ZARINA LAUGHING)
-Huh?
From a trickle to a roar.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS) Whoa!
(FAIRIES GASP)
SILVERMIST: We're free!
(SCREAMING)
Look at him go!
He's very fast.
Yeah, you think?
(SCREAMING)
Is it time to get that blue dust back?
Watch this.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
Can't fly without dust.
Blast!
(PIRATES YELPING)
Goodbye, James.
JAMES: Curse you, fairies!
Curse you!
Tiny she-devils they are, really.
-(CLOCK TICKING)
-Huh?
(GROANING)
(PIRATES LAUGHING)
Oh, no, no, no! (GROANS)
I am not a codfish! (GROANING)
I'm a pirate!
-All right.
-(FAIRIES LAUGHING)
You got the dust!
-We did it!
-(ALL CHEERING)
We can go home!
Oh, I'm gonna soak in a nice,
hot milkweed bath.
Get the smell of pirates off me.
SILVERMIST:
That was what I was thinking.
-VIDIA: You said it, Ro.
-(ALL GIGGLING)
Here, please,
take this back to Pixie Hollow.
TINKER BELL: Uh, Zarina,
we didn't just come for the dust.
-(LAUGHS JOYFULLY)
-FAIRIES: Oh!
Um, Ro? There's something
you should know.
It's about your hair.
(ROSETTA SCREAMING)
First, I lose my talent,
then I become a mother.
I do-si-doed in a stinky shoe,
and now, my hair?
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Well, you don't know who you are
Sky is the limit
And I just wanna flow
Free as a spirit on a journey of hope
VIDIA: Hang on, guys!
Cut the strings and let me go
I'm weightless, I'm weightless
Millions of balloons
tethered to the ground
Hey! There it is.
Home.
-(GRUNTING)
-(FAIRIES SNORING)
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
And...now!
(EXHALES)
(SILVERMIST CHUCKLES)
(AUDIENCE SNORING)
(ALL YAWNING)
(PANTING)
(LAUGHING)
(ALL GASP)
(ALL YAWNING)
(GASPS) Bobble!
(CLANK LAUGHING)
You're awake!
(LAUGHING)
(ALL GASPING)
This is the best show yet!
Uh, girls?
Queen Clarion,
we got the blue dust back.
Which I didn't know was missing.
We also got Zarina.
-(GASPS)
-FAIRY GARY: Zarina!
(LAUGHING)
-Oh, you're home!
-(CHUCKLING)
Yeah. And from now on, I promise...
You know, Zarina's
pretty much mastered
that pixie dust thing of hers.
Yeah, she even grew a pixie dust tree.
Now, we've got an extra.
(GASPS)
Does this talent of yours have a name?
"Alchemy."
Pixie dust alchemy.
You should really see her in action.
-Oh, you definitely should.
-Very impressive.
Hmm.
Well, we do have an audience.
(GASPS)
(BUZZING)
(AUDIENCE CHATTERING
EXCITEDLY)
AUDIENCE: Oh!
-(CHEERING)
-(BLOWING BUGLE)
AUDIENCE: Wow!
Thanks.
Well, how's my hair?
It's good!
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
Yeah!
AUDIENCE: Oh!
(CHUCKLES)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
Whoo-hoo!
(ALL GASP)
(ALL CHEERING)
All right!
Gorgeous.
If I could reach the top of the world
Be all I am
It'd be so beautiful
If only I could be brave
and I could be strong
I would know where I belong
(ALL CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
If only
I wanna feel free to be who I am
What I'm about is more than I've been
Ready to show the world who I am
Start letting out, what I'm holding in
And find my own place to stay
I can be who I am
(VOCALIZING)
I'm closer to what I'm meant to be
If I try I know that I can get there
I'm not gonna stop 'cause I believe
That there's so much more to me
SMEE: Man in the water!
Oh, dear.
Oh, my.
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
That's a very nice hook.
(GRUNTS)
Just give me a hand.
I wanna feel free to be who I am
What I am about is more than I've been
Ready to show the world who I am
Started it out, but I am holding in
Find my own place to stay
So I can be who I am
(VOCALIZING)
I can be who I am
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
First the Tower of London, arr!
The guards won't know what hit it
We'll swoop right down
and take the crown
And the Crown Jewels with it
And when we fly to Paris
Oh, the treasures I'll be grabbin'
The Mona Lisa will look lovely
Hanging in me cabin
Hey-ho
Imagine the places that we'll go
No one can stop us
When we're so
High in the stratosphere!
Hey-ho
We'll be the freighter that plunders
Every one of the world's
seven wonders
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a frigate that flies?
No one can fight a frigate that flies
Next we'll roam to Rome, me lads
And here's what I'll be stealin'
I'll rob the Sistine Chapel
Of the Sistine Chapel's ceilin'
And for all the folks in Egypt
It will be a dismal day
They'll be crying for their mummies
When we take their mummies away!
Hey-ho
Imagine the places that we'll go
No can stop us when we're so high!
They will all cower in fear
Hey-ho, from Delhi to Rio to Venice
There's no city that we will not menace
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a frigate that flies?
No one can fight a frigate that flies
-Oh, how high we will be!
-We will be
'Cause the blue fairy dust
Surely packs a mighty wallop
Only takes a dollop
-Soon it will set us free
-We'll be free
From the chains of gravity
Then we'll hoist up the sail
And we'll set course for the sun
'Cause when you've got wings
No wicked deed cannot be done
And we owe it all
To our great and glorious captain
YANG: Two, three, four!
Hey-ho,
imagine the places that we'll go
No one can stop us when we're so high
-Givin' a pirate cheer
-Arr!
Hey-ho, we'll be
the freighter that plunders
Every one of the world's
seven wonders
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a frigate that flies?
Hey-ho, there's not a town or a county
That will not yield its bounty up
When our ship draws near
Hey-ho, there's not a city or village
That we will not plunder or pillage
When we're up in the skies
For who can fight a frigate that flies?
And every nation will give a donation
When they see us sail the skies
In a frigate that flies!
Hey!