Okay, time to eat.
Let's see... Open the app.
I'm gonna get a double
pepperoni pizza,
order of breadsticks,
and, well, lasagna, yeah.
New item alert? Jalapeño
breadstick quick bites.
It might be nice to have
something in the salad family.
And do I want dessert?
I'm gonna be naughty,
butterscotch budino.
Okay, I'm gonna have five.
Delivery?
Goes without saying.
Now, please.
All right, that ought to
hold me 'til breakfast.
Hey! Wait, are you guys
early or am I late?
No matter. I have got a
real treat for you today.
No, not a treat for you.
Okay.
Anyway, about that treat.
Can I just say, you will
not be disappointed?
It's a story about me that
no one's ever heard before,
featuring someone in my
life you've never met.
I don't know about you,
but color me intrigued.
Yeah, drone delivery.
Welcome to the future.
You know, to really
understand everything,
I'm gonna have to take you
back to where it all began.
Don't want anything to take away
from the flavor of the cheese.
And like every great
story, it all started...
on a dark and stormy night.
Wait here, Junior.
I'll be right back.
Open wide, Jake.
Hi there, little buddy! Hi!
I'm so full.
You hungry, little guy?
You want a little more?
You are a hungry little guy.
That was a quick dinner,
Signore Jon.
You must have been very hungry.
Can I bring you anything else?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Some... lasagna?
- Si, lasagna for one.
- Yeah.
You know what, no.
- Make it family-style.
- Very good.
- To go, please, Vito.
- Okay, everybody!
- What? Where'd he go?
- You all know this one!
Hey!
Stand up and sing.
Join with us!
No! Hey! Oh, no, I'm dancing.
Excuse me, pardon me.
I hate this. What? Hey! Oh, no.
Jon! Takeout for Jon!
Your takeout is ready,
- Signore Jon.
- Yes.
One famiglia style
lasagna, to go.
- You eat alone too much, Jon.
- Yeah.
You should get on
the dating apps.
- There's Bumble, Tinder...
- I'm good, thanks.
Gluten-Free Singles...
- Hot Sauce Passions.
- No, I could never...
And you should spend serious money
on premium memberships.
Bye!
Hey!
Well, that was an
interesting dinner...
that you had.
Well, I guess... this
is where we say goodbye.
You're really cute
but I can't have pets
in my apartment.
So, I'll see you around.
Okay? Go on.
No. No, don't cry, don't cry.
No, no, no!
No. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
You don't have a home, do you?
And that's how I adopted Jon.
So, I moved Jon out
of his apartment...
to this nice little two-bed,
two-bath in the suburbs.
As soon as he understood
the ground rules,
well, let's just say...
we were living the dream.
And once we were settled in,
I even let Jon get a pet.
Odie became my
most trusted ally.
He was kind, gentle...
and most importantly,
my unpaid intern.
Yeah, as you can see,
life here is pretty
near perfect.
Well, yeah, except for...
Time to go to the vet!
We're gonna need the big scale!
Does she need to announce
it to the whole office?
No! Please, no!
It's so hot, it's really hurting!
And that's why we should
go from Sunday to Tuesday.
Okay. Where were we?
Wakey, wakey, eggs and
bakey. Good morning!
What? Where'd you
get that chair?
I think I was meant
to be here tonight
because I was meant to meet you.
- I think we were meant to be.
- That's what I meant to say.
You had me at the word, meant.
We're gonna ride like the wind!
Faster! Harder! More insane!
Odie?
Yeah, can you put
this back to normal?
There you go, just
let the pepperoni's
healing powers work its magic.
You saw nothing.
Up until that moment,
my life was a perfect soufflé.
Little did I know it was
all about to collapse.
Imagine yourself drifting away
on a sea of tranquility.
There are no pets to bother you,
distract you or max
out your credit card
by excessively placing
online food orders.
Yeah... Sorry...
What? Who said that?
Odie, Odie? Odie!
It's time for our
midnight snack.
Thank you, good sir,
your kindness will be rewarded.
What are we feeling
like today? French?
Italian? Chinese?
Cupcakes? Chinese it is.
Odie, shape everything
from the bottom two shelves
into a dumpling.
- Late night snackin'.
- Not good for digestion!
Odie, I'm dreamin' again.
Slap me across the face.
Nope. Still dreamin'.
I must be really
deep in this one.
What do you guys...
You want money?
I don't have any money, okay?
Who carries cash anymore?
I've got Jon's credit card
number memorized...
5-5-5-2-3-8-5-7-5-5-2-1.
Did you write that down?
- Expiration code is 5-5-5.
- The cat is out of the bag!
I really hope this
kidnapping plan works
or she'll put us down...
with her insults and
cutting observations.
I think this is a case
of mistaken identity.
You must be looking for another
gorgeous, lovable
kitty cat, right?
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, where're you going?
No, no, come back, come back!
Odie? I'll handle this.
All right, you guys.
I'm giving you to
the count of three
to get back here
and let us down.
One, two, three!
Four, five...
I am not kidding here!
Three hundred and eight,
309, 300...
Yeah, they're not comin'.
It's over.
Am I dead?
Are you an angel?
Please, take me.
I am ready to go to that...
to that all-you-can-eat
buffet in the sky.
What? Listen,
I'm going to swing you out,
cut your ropes and drop you
safely to that landing below.
Wait, what?
That seems a tad risky.
Is there another plan
that doesn't involve
cutting a rope over
a 40-foot drop?
No time. We gotta get outta
here before they come back.
We need to go.
Come on, Junior!
Wait here, Junior.
I'll be right back.
- You!
- Hey! Junior.
Who is he?
This is Vic. My father.
Look, Junior, I know
how you might be upset.
Upset?
Why would I be upset?
You only abandoned me
in an alley as a kitten.
I'm probably just overreacting!
Oh, no, not her.
- Okay, follow me, Junior.
- No, no, no.
You lost the privilege
of telling me
what to do a long time ago.
- Hello, Vic.
- Dang it!
Scare cam! You should've
seen your faces!
Okay, boys, show me!
Hello, Vic.
Dang...
Post that ASAP!
What? Hey, Jinx!
I haven't seen you since...
Well, no hard feelings
though, right?
I don't think so.
I'm a hugger!
Part of me wants
to be mad at her
for kidnapping us, but
you gotta love her energy.
Where are my manners?
Chop-chop, gentlemen!
Look alive!
Perfection.
You know, I was so delighted
that you accepted my
invitation here tonight.
Well, throwing us
in a burlap sack
wasn't exactly an Evite.
Vic, you're so quiet.
Are you feline sad?
Cat got your tongue?
Would you prefer a mew-mosa?
Excuse me, how do you
two know each other?
- Let me handle this, Junior.
- Don't Junior me.
You may call me Garfield,
Mr. Garfield, or G-Money.
Okay, whatever, no G-Money.
Anyway, can somebody please
tell me what is going on?
We really don't
need to get into...
I'll take this one.
What?
I'm from a small
town outside London
that you've probably
never heard of.
I scratched and clawed my
way through hard times...
to come here with one dream.
I wanted to be seen.
I wanted to matter.
But I was a failure.
The winner!
And then I met Vic and his crew.
They were outcasts,
losers, thugs.
We didn't have much,
but we had each other.
We became a real family.
Vic and family? I know
where this is goin'.
Excuse me,
garçon, when might
we expect appetizers?
- Perhaps an amuse-bouche?
- And then one night...
We were about to make
our biggest score.
Enough milk to
last us for weeks.
Vic!
Jinx, I tried to
come back for you.
You have to know that.
- Yes, you get an A for effort.
- So, what happened next?
Imagine Alcatraz...
but smellier.
It was cold. And lonely.
And stinky. So very stinky.
I can't overstate that enough.
But it gave me purpose.
I needed to get out.
I just needed help.
So, your purpose
was to escape jail
and get involved with charities?
No. My purpose was...
revenge.
I see, I went
the other way with it.
I'm kidding.
Another cat would
be bent on revenge,
but I'm...
How would you put it?
Evolved, compassionate,
- and incredibly self-actualized.
- Bingo!
I had such trouble finding him
and when I discovered
you were his son,
I had no choice but to
kidnap you to lure him here.
No, listen, I totally get it.
It's all part of bein'
associated with Vic.
So, what do you need from
him to make this right?
I simply want him to pay back
the quart of milk
I lost that night
- and we'll call it even.
- I can do that.
What he can't do
is raise a child.
- Just one quart.
- Done.
For every day
I was in the pound.
- What now?
- Nice twist. Well played.
How long were you
in the pound again?
Four years, seven
months and two days.
That long?
All right, I'm gonna
do the math here
in my brain. The way
you do that is...
Odie?
1,675 quarts of milk.
Exactly right, Odie.
We both came up with it
at the exact same time.
Where am I gonna
find that much milk?
Well, I suggest you
go back to the place
you double-crossed me.
- Lactose Farms.
- Well, good luck, Vic!
I'll leave you two to
work out the fine print.
We'll just see
ourselves out. Odie?
No.
You're all going to do this.
What? Wait, why me?
He's the one who abandoned you.
Yes, but this is more
than a one-cat job.
Yeah, but I'm sure
Vic has a whole crew
of low-life cat
burglars he could ask.
I'm sure he does.
But if I'm being
completely honest,
seeing how miserable
you make one another
brings me endless satisfaction.
Well, thank you
for your honesty.
And if I don't go?
You can stay and have a
playdate with Roland and Nolan.
Okay, boys... go play!
Ma'am, I think this
is an opportunity
to take a deep,
cleansing breath...
and repeat your anger
management mantra.
Anyone else have any objections?
Nope, I'm good. Thanks
for the opportunity.
Excellent! Now, you
boys have 72 hours.
Or else...
I can't believe
this is happening!
I don't see you for
years and when I do,
you pull me into
a life of crime!
I had this reunion playing
differently in my head too.
Well, that's the
difference between us,
because I never wanted
to see you again!
Now, I totally
understand your anger.
But if you give me
a chance to explain
you'll see I'm not the
bad guy you think I am.
A good guy doesn't leave
his kid in an alley!
- It wasn't like that.
- It was exactly like that!
No, it wasn't.
- Let me tell you what, Junior...
- No, no!
I don't wanna hear it!
This whole thing with Jinx?
This is your mess, not mine.
Come on, Odie.
Can't let you do that.
We'll be watching you.
Like a hawk.
Is today a Monday?
Because it feels an
awful lot like a Monday.
It's Thursday.
- Not to me, it's not!
- Look, I know this isn't ideal,
but we have to do this.
So, let's just try and make
- the best of our time together.
- Our time together?
What are you talkin' about?
Once we get this milk,
I want you out of my life.
Forever!
All right, just relax.
Lactose Farms ain't nothing
but a sleepy little
mom-and-pop dairy.
This will be a
quick grab and go.
You'll be back home
before you know it.
So, how do we even
get to Lactose Farms?
It's way out in the country.
You ever jumped a train?
I've never jumped.
Look, if jumpin' a train
is too hard, just say it.
- How hard could it be?
- Exactly!
This is gonna be fun.
Garfield?
Odie? Hello?
Garfield, how many
times have I told you
to close the
refrigerator door?
Wait, there's food on the floor.
He's never left food
on the floor. Garfield?
Garfield? Garfield? Garfield?
Our best shot at jumping
on the train is here.
Hold on a sec. I'm just
taking in the wind speed,
the direction of the sun,
and various angles.
Yes, I say we jump the
train from right here.
Didn't I just say that?
I've seen it on television
a million times.
- We'll need a 100 feet of rope.
- Uh-huh, rope. Yeah, okay.
- Great idea.
- Yep.
We'll throw the rope
over that branch
- right there.
- Over the branch. Got it.
Can you follow me? All right.
And then timing it just right,
we swing over as
the train passes by
and land on top of the car.
- Boom!
- Or, we can do this!
Odie, jump, boy!
Part of me wants to help him.
No. This is how he learns.
I don't know,
it's kind of pricey.
How does it handle?
I'll take it!
See? I told you this
was gonna be fun.
You and I have different
definitions of fun.
- Hello?
- Finally! Hello!
You've reached Find My Pet.
If your pet is lost,
we're here to help.
Hi, yes! Great, okay.
My orange tabby and my dog
are both missing and
I need your help.
Please listen carefully
as our menu options
have changed.
- Okay.
- If you'd like to hear
this call in Spanish...
- oprima número dos.
- What?
For Pig Latin,
ess-pray even-say.
For gibberish...
Come on. What do I press
to talk to a real person?
Your call is very
important to us.
There are 1,346
people ahead of you.
What?
Garfield, where are you?
Okay, Vic, you gotta
figure this out.
Jinx can't be trusted
and you gotta keep Junior safe!
You just gotta figure out a way
- to get him outta this.
- Tell me, is it a bur? It hurts.
You pulled my hair.
Is it a gnat?
Is it a bug? A bug?
Odie, Odie!
Okay.
You know what, Junior?
- This is gonna be good for you.
- What'll be good for me?
What we're doing.
We're about to steal
a truck full of milk
from a dairy to pay
back a deranged cat.
What part of that is
going to be good for me?
All of it!
You can't even imagine
the life lessons
you're gonna learn.
Oh, yeah? Name one.
Well, for starters,
you already know
how to get on a moving train.
I found it funny.
All I'm sayin' is that
to break into a dairy,
it's going to take
a few skills...
I'm guessing a
rounded, mush-filled,
overly pampered
indoor cat like you...
doesn't have,
so we need to toughen you up.
Toughen me up?
Hey, I know tough, Vic.
You've obviously never
been in an Olive Garden
that's run out of breadsticks.
Anyway, I'm never
gonna need those skills
- you're talking about.
- But you'll have them.
I'm never gonna
break into a dairy
or anything else, ever again.
You are missing the point.
You're going to
learn to improvise,
think on your feet,
develop moves
that'll come in handy out
there in the real world!
I wouldn't be in
the real world
if it wasn't for you!
True. You'd still be hanging
upside down in the mall.
- No, I would be asleep at home!
- Missing out on life altogether.
Look, I'm just a dad trying
to teach his son some skills.
No, no, no. You can't
make up for five years
- of not being around.
- Yes, I can.
- No, you can't.
- I think I can.
- In fact, you can't.
- Yes, I can!
- You really can't!
- With your attitude, I can.
Okay, whatever, Dad.
Great lesson.
I'm done talking to you.
You do not know me,
you don't know the
first thing about me.
I am not pampered. I'm not
anything you think I am!
Okay. I'm just gonna say
that blanket is
not the best idea.
Fantastic, thank you.
I'll take it from here.
Get them off! Get them off!
Get them off me!
What are you doin'?
- What did you do?
- Cedar chips.
Spiders hate 'em. See?
Another life skill learned.
I...
I think the words you're
looking for are...
Thank you, Pops.
No, the word
I'm looking for is...
- Here's our stop!
- Really? Where?
Odie, you think
he'd see that coming.
Cheese!
- Take your picture.
- Yeah!
Yeah!
Here you go!
Quaint. Just a simple
little grab and go.
Okay. Okay, so they've
done a few upgrades
since I was last here.
Why being so dramatic?
All we have to do is
climb the fence...
Wait. Is that Otto?
- Who?
- Otto!
Of Otto and Ethel.
No clue who you're
talkin' about.
He's one of the mascots
of Lactose Farms.
See?
On the side of the barn?
I'll bet he knows how
to get into that place.
Leave him alone.
Seems to be in a period of
meditation... or depression.
Yes, he does.
This calls for tact,
sensitivity, and diplomacy.
Yeah? And where are we
supposed to get that?
I have it. In spades.
Watch! Maybe you'll
learn somethin'.
Excuse me, you're Otto, right?
I'm Garfield.
- A pleasure.
- Go away.
I just wanted to
say I am a huge fan.
I have eaten everything
that has a picture
of your face on it.
I'm not that guy anymore.
I even loved that recalled
provolone from a few years back.
- Junior, no.
- Yeah.
Anyways, here's the thing.
Me and my crew back there,
we're in a bit of a bind.
Got ourselves in a situation.
Long story short,
we could use your help.
You're a fan, huh?
- Yes! Big time.
- Then sing the jingle.
Well, I don't really
sing on command.
I'm not a circus animal.
- Sing it.
- Really?
- Lactose Farms, Lactose Farms
We've got milks, butters,
creams and cheeses
- More spirit.
- Much as you want
- As much as it pleases...
- Livelier!
Come and take a look
and see what we got
'Cause what we got
is a whole lotta lot
Tasty goodness is our
motto brought to you
By Ethel and Otto!
What was that for?
I hate that jingle.
You could've just
told me to stop.
Let's go.
Kids are waiting.
Odie, come back!
Leave him alone!
He might punch you!
Was that Ethel?
A few years back,
Old Man Lactose was
forced out of business.
The corporation that took over
separated me from my Ethel.
- Ethel!
- You are my day!
You are my night!
I was put out to pasture.
She was put on display
as part of the tour.
I tried to get in there
to break Ethel free...
but they stop me every time.
Now, I only see her six
seconds, twice a day.
We feel you, Otto.
Come on, let's go, Junior.
We'll find another
way to break in there.
What could you possibly
want from that place?
You know, a couple
quarts of milk.
Couple thousand quarts.
Good luck.
We'll take any helpful
hints you have.
Pass.
I'm telling you, it's a
life-or-death situation.
Then I hope you've
notified your next of kin.
What if we can get Ethel out?
Or get you a commemorative pin?
Where are we gonna find
a commemorative pin?
Now, pay attention.
Here's the perimeter
of the plant.
And here are the two
places you need to go.
First, the truck with
your milk is back here.
And this delicate
buttercup is my Ethel.
My North Star, and
reason for living
is being kept by those
barbarians in a petting zoo.
Located here.
This cricket represents
the electrical room...
this snail, the
refrigeration room...
this toadstool is
the loading dock
where you'll find the
keys to the trucks.
Wait, what's the pinecone?
The pinecone is the
cheese and butter room.
- Cheese is my love language.
- Now, for this briefing,
I've done a quick reading
of your personalities
and have chosen tokens
to represent each of you.
You are the majestic bullfrog.
Yeah, that feels right.
You are the curious
and clever chipmunk.
- And you...
- Wait for it...
are roadkill.
What? No, I get it.
That's a good one, Otto!
Giving your new best
friend roadkill.
Seriously, though,
what's my real token?
That is your real token.
Now, if you have any
chance of succeeding...
Wait, can I... Excuse me,
can I switch to something living?
- Like the snail or the cricket?
- You should've spoken up sooner.
At this point, it would be
too confusing to switch.
Sooner? But you just told me
this five seconds ago.
- Come on, Roadkill, focus.
- Really?
You give Vic the
majestic bullfrog.
You give Odie the curious
and clever chipmunk...
and then you give me,
your new bff, roadkill?
I mean, it feels
disrespectful, not gonna lie.
What makes you think he's dead?
My eyes. I have
eyes and can see.
It's a possum. They're
masters at playing dead.
Well then, little
Daniel Day-Possum here
should do Shakespeare
in the Park!
Things aren't always
what they seem.
You're right. But in
this case, they are.
What's the big deal?
Possums play dead.
Do they, Otto?
Do they play dead?
Do possums play possum,
is that what they do?
Yes. Possums are very clever.
Yeah, I'm sure he was
until the day
he ate a pick-up truck!
Just ignore him.
Please, continue.
I'll just put this
back where you had it.
The straightest line
to the loading dock
is through the snail here,
then the cricket, there,
cut through the toadstool
and onto the rock.
Each of these rooms
have their own set
- of unique challenges.
- Well, why can't we just go
straight through the pinecone?
You don't want to go
through the pinecone.
Looks like the straightest
shot is through the pinecone.
You like walking with
those feet, do you?
You a fan of unimaginable
pain and misery?
Then go through the pinecone.
Stay away from the
pinecone. Got it.
Once you're inside
the facility...
You will enter the
electrical room.
There you will
locate the air vent.
Pop the grate and climb up.
Then, you'll crawl through a
maze of vents and drop down...
to the refrigeration room.
Next, you will need
to hurl your body
over a 30-foot drop
to a series of hand rungs.
You'll propel yourselves
hand-over-hand...
and drop down directly
into a loading dock.
From there, you'll locate
the keys to the milk truck.
Drive that truck to the
west pasture of the complex,
cut the lock on the gate.
And find the closest
thing we have
to an angel here on earth.
You'll escort my sweet
Ethel onto the truck
and drive her to freedom.
It's going to take mad skills
to get that milk, and
free my dear, sweet Ethel.
Clearly, this one is
qualified for the mission.
But, I have some serious
doubts here about all of...
- this.
- He's pointing to you, Roadkill.
Let's get to work.
Stupid roadkill.
Hey! I'm workin' here!
Definitely a Monday.
Your call is fairly
important to us.
If you've lost a cat,
please press one.
- If your cat is orange...
- Yeah.
Please press two.
This doesn't really
accomplish anything...
but gives you the false sense
that we're engaged with you.
All right, gentlemen,
I've made a list of skills...
that you'll need
to master in order
to break into Lactose Farms.
Number one,
develop lightning-fast reflexes.
You tell Garfield
there's a plate of pasta
on the other side of that wall
and you will see
lightning reflexes.
Yeah, no, no, no. Depends
what kind of pasta.
This pebble represents
danger you may encounter.
You need to grab it,
before it grabs you.
It grabs me?
Snatch the pebble from my hand.
Too slow!
What was that for?
Being able to grab
the pebble could be
the difference between
life and death.
All right,
let me try that again.
Got it!
Now what was that for?
It's never just
about the pebble.
Come on, Junior,
everyone knows that.
Your head's got to be on
a swivel at all times.
Gotta be ready for anything.
I was ready.
He changed the game.
Sounds like someone's
making excuses!
And what was that about
being ready for anything?
You were distracting me!
Might I suggest putting
your head on a swivel?
You should have
seen that coming.
Toes on the line!
Guard your grill!
Cover your stomach!
There are surprises
around every corner
at Lactose Farms.
You need to stay alert!
Too slow! A baby could
have seen that coming!
Too slow! Too slow!
Too slow!
You'll never make it
through Lactose Farms
if you can't survive
this training!
Are you for real?
What kinda dairy is this?
The kind of dairy that
requires teamwork to survive!
Danger could be
anywhere, gentlemen!
You've got to be
ready to outrun it.
Here comes the pain!
- Left, right, left, right.
- You're confusing me!
I think I'm gonna need rehab.
If this is going to work,
these two have to
be on the same page.
I'm out of ideas.
You got any?
Can't believe I'm out
in the middle of nowhere
getting beaten up
against my will
by a former celebrity steer.
Odie? Will you tell my son
to please stop whining?
Odie, can you tell Vic
that I collapsed
on this tree first
and that he needs
to find another one?
Odie, can you tell my son
that I will gladly
find another one
when I get the feeling
back in my legs?
Odie, can you tell my father
that he wouldn't
be lying in pain
if he led a better life
and didn't create
problems for himself?
Could you please inform my son
that he should focus on
fixing his own issues?
Odie? What?
Odie? What'd you do?
After all I've
let you do for me.
What is this?
Hey, watch it!
What's the problem, Vic?
Is this bothering you?
No. In fact, I don't
mind it at all!
I don't mind it either.
I could watch this all day.
- Stop pulling.
- I'm not, you're pulling!
If I was pulling,
you would know it!
Why does everything you do
always end up hurting me?
Hurt you?
All I ever did was
try to help you.
You sure? 'Cause every
time you're around,
it ends up with me in pain.
Odie! These ropes are
not funny anymore!
Maybe, if you were a little
more open to seeing me,
things might be
better between us.
You do remember you were the one
who left me in an alley, right?
You don't know what
you're talkin' about.
Then please, enlighten me.
This is about to get real.
That's right. You're
normally never around
to actually defend yourself.
No back door to slink
out of this time.
First, you abandon me,
then years later,
you pull me into
a life of crime.
Well, classic Father of
the Year stuff, Dad.
You know, why would I ever think
that seeing you
could be anything
other than a train wreck?
I did not leave
you in that alley!
You did!
You told me you'd come
right back. You never did!
No. That is not what happened.
Please! You were probably
on the run from someone
- like Jinx and I was in the way.
- No.
No, that night...
That night was different.
Hey! Shoo, shoo!
Get outta here!
Wait here, Junior.
I'll be right back.
Hey, get outta here.
Hey, how you doing? Yeah.
I had to shoo a cat.
Yeah, yeah, diggin'
in the trash. Yeah.
So, what'cha up to now, huh?
Still takin' it easy?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, no, you're kiddin'.
Really? Yeah, yeah.
It's been raining here for
a while now. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah! I'll see you then.
Okay, bye.
I never knew.
I know, how could you?
Why didn't you
ever come visit me?
I did.
Million times I...
came to knock on your door
and I'd see what a great
life you had with Jon.
So, I just...
thought it was better
if I kept my distance.
I sense a positive breakthrough
in your relationship.
Am I wrong?
Good. After an
extensive evaluation,
I have concluded
that you two are,
in fact,
ready to move forward
- with this mission.
- We are?
- How is that even possible?
- Mathematically, it isn't.
But given your present
levels of incompetence
and overall lack
of basic skills,
I have determined
it would take roughly...
seventeen years to get you both
properly ready for this job.
And since we have...
less than 48 hours,
you've passed.
Congratulations.
She's really losin' it.
Yes, what is it?
They're ready to rob the dairy.
Perfect.
Everything is going to plan.
Now, it's time to make a call.
Excuse me, you keep that
thing in your folds?
That is so disgusting.
You. You dial the number
and put me on speaker!
Hello?
- Hello? Lactose Farms?
- How may I help you?
It's come to my attention
that there'll be
an attempt to rob
one of your dairy
trucks tomorrow.
It's not important who I am
or how I came to know this.
Just think of me as
a concerned citizen
intent on fulfilling my
civic responsibility
as well as...
Chief?
- We may have a situation.
- Well, okay then.
Let's go have a look-see.
This is the third
time they've called.
It just sounds like some
cat prank callin' us.
If it were a dog barking,
I'd be on board for a prank.
Them dogs are born for
mischief, they just are.
Not cats. Oh, no.
Cats mean business.
I repeat, there
will be an attempt
to make off with one of
your milk trucks tomorrow.
I suggest you take
appropriate measures
to prevent this brazen
thievery from occurring.
Okay, I'm done.
Hang up the phone.
Ha, ha. What an
evil genius I am.
Well, then, still seem
like a prank to ya?
- That last part did a little.
- What's our next move, Chief?
Our next move is for me
to go back to my office
and formulate an ingenious plan.
And you go get my car waxed.
Well, well, well,
would you look at that,
Margie Malone?
We're having company tomorrow.
I guess I better take
out my finest china
to serve a heapin' plate
of justice.
What are those for?
For us to communicate
once you're inside...
the belly of the beast.
Okay. Don't we need something
more like radio headsets?
Indoor cat. These are better.
It just feels like
Bluetooth would be better.
These are better than Bluetooth.
These are better than Bluetooth?
They're equal.
And I don't have to
pay for the brand.
Gold Eagle to Chipmunk.
Do you copy?
Of course, you can hear him.
He's standing three
feet away from you.
I see you sprung
for the binoculars.
Now, we just need to find...
a way in.
Anyone ever told
you that you take
a lot of dramatic
pauses when you speak?
Yes.
Hey, wait up!
- Look at that!
- Bingo.
Hello, everyone! And
welcome to the one
and only Lactose Farms!
If you will all
gather around me,
we'll begin our tour
and head into the
heart of the farm.
I know you're here.
I can feel it. Show yourself.
Today you will
discover the answers
to all of your dairy questions,
including the most asked
dairy question of all time,
are curds the whey?
Bullfrog, Chipmunk,
Roadkill, do you copy?
Are you kidding me?
They actually work?
You should take
this to Shark Tank.
Now, remember, the only
way to get the keys
to the milk truck and
free Ethel undetected
is by sticking to the
path I mapped out for you.
If you deviate from that path,
you will trigger security
and all bets are off.
Understood?
All right, look alive.
The electrical access door
should be coming up
on your left.
Okay, this way!
Hey, hey, look!
There it is!
Okay, we're in.
Continue through and
locate the air vent
at the end of the hallway.
That will take you to
the refrigeration room.
Factory workers, your
15-minute break begins now.
Your feet need a deep rinse.
- What's the hold up, Junior?
- How do you get through this?
- You're bigger than me.
- Am I?
- Yes!
- Well, the vent doesn't agree.
- Try sucking in your gut.
- I am.
Try sucking in your
butt and your gut.
Bullfrog, what's happening now?
We fell out of a vent...
into a room that looks like
- it's full of heavy machinery.
- Son of a cud.
You're in the pinecone.
Jiminy Davis!
The perp is a cat!
And this one looks like
it could eat us out of business.
Vic, Vic! Look, there's
the loading dock.
- No! Junior! Don't move.
- What? Why?
We're in the middle
of the pinecone!
Otto told us to stay
out of the pinecone.
Stop. There's no pinecone.
Otto's a bit of a worrywart.
I can walk to the
loading dock from here.
No...
Junior!
Cheddar.
Probably one of my top
26 favorite cheeses.
What do you think happens
when that gets to zero?
Bullfrog, what's happening now?
Roadkill got carried
away into the pinecone!
Listen to me.
You have to carry on
with the mission.
Get to the loading dock
before the workers
return from their break
or you'll miss your only
chance to get that truck.
No, no, no. No, no, no!
Shred sequence initiated.
Odie! Thanks, buddy,
but I'm pretty full
from the cheddar.
Jump off.
Yeah, yeah, good idea.
Good. He's safe.
Hang on.
Wait. Where am I going?
Fondue. Fondue!
Junior.
Hot, hot, hot! Hot!
Junior!
That was too close even for me.
Thanks.
I couldn't let you
have all the fun.
- Workers...
- What?
Your break ends in five minutes.
Okay, Otto, we're
in the loading dock.
Where are the keys?
They should be hanging on
a pegboard on the far wall.
What do you mean
we have a problem?
- Pegboard's empty!
- Empty?
Now would you look at this?
Three misguided stray pets
trying to steal a truck o' milk.
Never a dull moment at this
dairy, is there, Margie?
Well, you're looking
for these, aren't ya?
Well, here you go then.
So, how's this gonna
play out, fellas?
The easy way or the hard way?
And just so you know,
I'm up for either.
- Follow my lead.
- What?
Who's next then?
Otto, a security guard
has the truck keys!
Crazy eyes? Tragic
sense of fashion?
Yeah. How did you know?
Marge Malone.
- Ethel!
- Otto!
She's not just my nemesis,
she's also my enemy.
Love to hear about it,
but right now,
- what do we do?
- Get those keys.
I'll create a distraction
so you can get out of there.
Come here, you!
Did you see that?
That's indoor cat style!
No, no, no.
You're not getting away. I've
already called the pound.
Your days of thievery end today.
Attempted perimeter breach.
Otto.
- Junior, sorry about this.
- Sorry? For what?
Vic?
What are you doing?
Vic! Don't you go.
Vic!
Please!
Send security to
the loading dock.
Otto!
You do not want to
try me today, mister.
Get him!
Welcome back... Victor.
Hey, Jinx.
Why are you here? I was
bringing this to you.
Were you? Really?
Yeah, of course I was. That's
what we agreed to, right?
- So, you and me square now?
- Not quite.
There's still the matter
of those five years
I lost because of you.
What? But I thought
this settled that.
It was never about the milk.
It was about you getting caught
trying to steal it and
being sent to the pound
like I was.
You see, Vic,
I needed you to suffer
like I did.
I see.
And I'm guessing
you have an idea
about how that should happen.
As a matter of fact, I do.
I can't believe he did that.
He ran out, and
he left me. Again.
I thought he'd changed,
but it was...
it was a lie.
All of it.
How could I have been so stupid?
Come on, kid.
Don't beat yourself up.
Vic, man, we've all
been burned by Vic.
Yeah, that's right.
Burned every cat I know.
Yeah, the one thing about
Vic you can count on
- is that you can't count on him.
- Tell me about it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'll tell you about it.
Long story short, we all
used to run in a pack
until we had to kick
him out the crew.
Like I said, couldn't
count on him.
Sounds about right.
He'd leave in the
middle of a job
just to go see his kid.
Yeah, he said he wanted
to check up on him.
Make sure he was doing okay.
But get this,
he'd never actually visit.
He'd just sit across the street
from his kid's house
in a giant oak tree.
- That never happened.
- He'd watch that kid eat...
- and eat and eat...
- and eat...
- He put a notch in the bark...
- and eat, and eat, and eat.
- Every time he was there.
- Yeah. Sure, he did.
He'd go every Sunday night,
rain or shine.
Said that it was his kid's...
family dinner night.
Okay, hate to tell you guys...
I guarantee that never happened.
Okay?
You all fell for another one
of Vic's lies. We all have.
Because that's
what he does best.
Odie? Odie!
How did you get out?
- Quick, pick the lock on my cage.
- Garfield, there you are!
Jon!
Take me away from all this.
You can't imagine what
I've been through.
- You want this one too?
- Yes, I do.
- I was hung upside down.
- You sure he's yours?
He didn't have a tag.
- I jumped a train.
- Yeah. He has a tag.
I have a collar and a tag?
How long have I had those?
Okay. I'm just gonna
need you to hold.
I will not hold!
I am done holding!
The Jon who was on hold is dead.
Do you understand?
That's right.
I'm back, baby!
I was just talking
about you, wasn't I?
I've missed you too.
Pooky!
I have a lot to tell you.
You're never gonna believe it.
Crazy stuff happened.
I slept outside, twice!
I know. Me.
And I got you this
commemorative pin.
Dinner time!
Talk later.
Say when.
Never, Jon. Bury me in cheese.
I have two more in the freezer.
Let me know when you want 'em.
I'm gonna go check on dessert.
I apologize in advance.
The eating you're about
to see will not be pretty
and if you have young children,
this would be a good time
for them to leave the room.
He'd just sit across the
street from his kid's house
in a giant oak tree.
I know, I know.
We're coming back.
I just need to check
something out first.
He put a notch in the bark...
every time he was there.
He left a notch.
Yeah, right.
He was here.
He saw me grow up.
Wow, that really stings.
I don't know why
I didn't think it would.
Give me a second.
Vic loves us!
Me first, of course,
but then you too!
But me, a lot, and first!
Wait, but if he loves me, us,
why would he let me, us,
get captured at the dairy?
Unless, he wanted
- us to get captured!
- Hey!
- Yes!
- Hey, watch it!
He knew that Jinx wasn't
gonna let him off the hook.
But if we got caught,
we'd get sent to the pound
and Jon would come to get us!
Don't you see, Odie?
- He was trying to save us!
- Losers!
We have to go save my dad.
And here's your
favorite dessert,
Mount Candy-toa!
Guys?
Come on!
What is this?
Half a star for Mamma Leoni's?
She's a monster.
She's gonna tie him up...
take him on a train...
She's going to throw him
off the Mile High Bridge!
We're gonna need help.
Who can we call?
You've got a lot
of waxy buildup.
What's your Q-tip routine?
You're right, you're right.
We can deal with
that situation later.
Hello? Hello?
Is anyone there? Hello?
Get off the line.
This acorn is for
emergency use only.
Otto! Otto, please, listen.
I wanna make good on
our original deal,
but I need a favor first.
Otto, are you still there or
are you taking a dramatic pause?
I'm listening.
You know, Vic,
you only have yourself
to blame for this.
Right. Look,
there's got to be some way
for me to make this right.
I mean, I know we can
think of somethin'.
There is, and you will.
So, once I get on the train...
I untie Vic and we jump off
right as the train
gets to the bridge.
Correct. Chipmunk will
be waiting for you.
Confirm your status, Chipmunk.
If you don't jump right as
the train gets to the bridge,
you'll miss the net.
Got it. It's getting close.
Have you considered throwing
a rope over a branch
and just swinging onto
the passing train instead?
You watch too much TV.
I've never watched TV.
Well, this way is much
better than your rope idea.
Better than the versatile,
reliable rope?
Look, I've studied the science.
I know what I'm doing.
And you think you can battle
these villains on your own?
Oh yeah. I have a plan.
Odie?
Make the order.
Now get ready to fling me
in the direction of
that moving train.
Get ready.
If I don't make it back...
tell my story. Now!
Roadkill! You're too high!
You're gonna miss it!
No, no, this is how you do it!
It's called the
ricochet approach!
It won't be long now.
I can't tell you
how excited I am
for what's about to happen next.
Dad! I'm here to rescue you!
No, no, no, Junior!
- Get outta here!
- I'm gonna untie you,
and we're gonna
jump off the train!
- No! Just leave me and go!
- I didn't come this far...
just to turn around,
let me untie you!
You're ruining everything!
Quick, this way!
You half-wit! Get them!
The bridge is comin' up!
We gotta get to the caboose now!
- What? Why?
- Just follow my lead!
Oi, kitty cat!
Did you expect to take
us on all by yourself?
No. I brought takeout.
I never understood
the purpose of salad
until this exact moment!
Go, go! Now!
Get after him!
Yeah, in case you
were wonderin',
I do my own stunts.
Me...
and Tom Cruise.
Junior!
Stop him!
Now that's amazing!
I can't feel my tongue.
Roadkill!
Are you at the caboose,
ready to jump?
Dad! Dad!
Jump, Junior! I'll catch you!
What do we do now?
We do this!
See ya, everyone.
The net's too tight!
Roadkill, the net is too tight!
I heard!
Hello again, welcome back!
Now, where were we?
No, no! Don't throw
them over just yet.
No!
I want to find the perfect place
for them to make
the biggest splat.
Hey, hey! Junior!
Junior, Junior.
Get ready! Almost there!
I'm sorry my rescue
didn't work out.
No, you gave me another chance.
That's all that matters.
Now, now! Drop them now!
What are you waiting for?
Their love for one
another indicates that
despite their
current circumstance,
they are at peace.
- Because they are together.
- So?
If the point of your
revenge was to hurt them,
it has done the opposite.
It's actually textbook irony!
And we're no longer
comfortable with your plan.
You two are still
as weak as you were
when I found you
sniveling in the pound.
No one will adopt us.
I never grew into my folds.
I hide behind them because
I'm socially awkward.
Please, somebody love me
even though I can't sit still
for more than ten seconds
and have the attention
span of a bloody goldfish!
We did everything
you ever asked of us.
I even spoke with
this ridiculous accent
to make you feel more at home.
But no more!
I'm New York, loud and proud!
I love myself the way I am
and I'm a big, brave, boy, baby!
And I've been working
on my attention span.
Is that a hot air balloon?
You two...
are...
worthless!
Might I just say as someone
else with a zaftig figure,
you have a beautiful body, sir.
Oh, dear!
Rope. Versatile. Reliable.
There's something
about your cadence
that really throws me,
but thank you.
Tossing me off the train?
Did not see that coming.
Well, when you live in the wild,
you gotta keep your
head on a swivel.
Right.
It's basic Outdoor Cat 101.
And that had bird poop on it.
Hey. You good, Roadkill?
Not quite.
There's one last
thing to take care of.
Cut to...
It was a dark and foggy night.
The air was damp and
heavier than a broken heart.
On nights like this,
you can't swing a cat
without hittin' shady characters
makin' shady deals
all over town.
But this night was going
to be different.
Justice was about to be served.
With a helping of
retribution on the side.
Is that... the package?
It is.
Then we have a deal.
No one will come
looking for her?
Nope. I did what you said.
I burned her paperwork.
And then shredded it
and burned it some more.
It's like she never existed.
Except for the image of her face
on millions of dairy products.
This...
never happened.
Agreed.
Save it, Cat Fancy.
I know you planned the
milk truck heist...
and then tried to throw those
innocent cats off a train
to cover it up.
The boys told me everything.
Otto!
You are my day.
You are my night.
Well, this is us.
Right. You're home.
- Hey, listen, I'm sorry.
- I just want to say I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
For misjudging you.
Well. Thanks.
Well, I just wanted to
apologize to you for...
Everything bad that happened
to us the last three days?
You know, you had your hand in
a few bad decisions
back there too, but...
yeah, I'm sorry for
dragging you into my world.
This is where you belong,
here with Jon and...
What's your name again?
Odor?
- So, yeah, I should go.
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean, unless...
you'd want to come in?
Nah. No, no. I don't
think that would work.
- You know, I'm an outdoor cat.
- Right. Sure. Sure.
- No, I just... I figured that...
- No, no, no, I get it.
But, you know what?
I got this thing on the other
side of town I gotta go do so...
No. I'm very busy too. Yeah.
See you around then?
You know where to find me.
In the kitchen.
Well, take care.
And remember,
stay out of the pinecone.
What? You heard him.
It's for the best.
You're back?
What is going on? Are you okay?
I was so worried!
You know, I was gonna add
more locks to the door,
you know, try to keep you in,
but then I thought, well,
what if they wanted
to be outdoor pets?
Do you wanna be free-range?
I really missed you guys.
And I gotta say...
it's great to be together again,
the whole entire family.
You have no idea what the
last few days have been like.
Phone calls, and hold times
and tears. And more tears.
Don't give me that,
I asked him to stay.
He wanted to leave!
You heard him,
he said he had to...
Well, I...
- A family should consist...
- Fine. I'll be right back!
Wait, wait, what?
Am I using trigger words
that I'm not aware of?
So, you coming in or do we have
to bring food up there to you?
I'll come to you.
I just need to finish
something up here.
You know, those notches
show how much you love me.
Is that what you
think they mean?
Yeah.
Nah, I was just counting how
many slices of lasagna you ate.
My medium is cuisine...
my colors are flavors...
my palette is my palate...
if you will.
Dinner is served!
Wow, son, I didn't know
you could cook.
Yes, pasta is my paint, and...
the dinner plate my canvas.
That's where that went.
I've had worse.
Thank you, Garfield.
Is he gonna be coming
around for dinner often?
Yeah, he's family.
What?
Why do I have a takeout bill
for 6,000 drone deliveries?