They're outside.
We're losing power in
the containment chamber!
- You hear that?
- Something's close.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
My heart is pounding.
Get down, get down.
Cubone!
Uh... a Cubone?
We're not catching
you a Pokémon, are we?
- What?
- Tell me you didn't plan this, Jack.
- I'm sor... are you serious?
- Jack, tell me you didn't plan this.
How dare you! Okay...
Of course not! Come on!
Okay maybe.
There was a full moon last night,
and my mom heard it crying it's eyes out,
cause she can't... and was having
a nightmare so
she brought me a glass of warm milk.
Dude, I thought you wanted to, you know,
hang out and relive the good old days
- Like when we were kids.
- I do! But just look at it.
That is the perfect Pokémon for you.
Jack I'm not looking for a Pokémon.
I've told you this.
I've thought long
and hard about this, okay?
Water type is not right for you.
Neither is fire type.
- But Cubone is...
- Lonely.
Exactly!
Okay thank you, Jack.
Thank you for that.
Are there any other emotional
truth bombs you wanna drop on me?
Maybe later, but right now,
the truth is in my hands.
- Just give me the ball.
- Yes! Yes!
Okay, remember catching a
Pokémon is not about skill.
- So you can do this.
- Good pep talk!
Okay, it has to
choose you too, so...
Make it wanna be
your partner, yeah.
Hey, Cubone.
What's up buddy?
You know, not everyone can...
pull off wearing the skull
of their dead relative,
but, you know, you sure can.
Okay he didn't like that.
He did not like that.
- Jack.
- Throw it.
- Throw the ball.
- Like a man.
I did it!
Still got it.
The light's not green.
It still hasn't turned green yet,
Jack that's bad right?
Run!
- He didn't choose me!
- Run!
- He didn't choose me, Jack!
- I do see that!
I'm not his choice.
Cubone!
That was one angry Cubone.
He reminded me a lot of my mom.
So um, I don't know if this
is gonna sound corny or whatever.
Just say it Jack.
I'm too tired to be angry.
- I'm worried about you.
- This again?
Okay listen, everyone we know has
left town and now I'm leaving too.
Yeah but that's okay, you gotta do what's
best for you with the time that you got.
That's what I'm doing.
You know I'm crushing it at work.
Gonna get that promotion real soon.
What's the promotion
for an insurance appraiser?
Senior insurance appraiser?
No actually that's two
steps up above where I'm at.
You are gonna make me throw up.
That's not a real thing.
Oh, I finally have service.
Wait, five voicemails?
I don't have five voicemails.
Maybe it's an insurance emergency?
Who is it?
Um, it's the Rhyme City
police department.
There was an accident.
Please don't.
All you hear is please do it.
Thank you... thank you.
You have a very generous tongue.
Does this Lickitung
belong to anyone?
Anybody? No?
Thank you for
traveling with us.
Please sit back and watch this short informational
video welcoming you to Rhyme City.
Throughout history,
Pokémon have been
part of our world.
Early humans used to catch
them and train them
to use their unique
powers for the common good.
This relationship evolved
into what we now refer to as
Pokémon Battles.
One man changed all of this.
Howard Clifford.
Founder and chairman
of Clifford Industries.
Diagnosed with a rare,
degenerative disease,
he resigned from his corporation
and searched the world for a cure.
And turned out that the
cure I was looking for,
was for me to evolve
into a better version of myself
And I discovered how to do that
through a partnership with Pokémon.
And he wanted to
share that discovery
with the world.
This is what inspired Howard
Clifford to build Rhyme City.
A place where humans and Pokémon
can live side by side.
Unlike other regions, where
Pokémon live in the wild,
here we live
and work together.
No battles. No trainers.
No Pokéballs.
A stronger, more harmonious world.
For all our citizens,
welcome to Rhyme City.
Fighting fires wouldn't be the
same without their Squirtle partners.
Squirtle. Squirtle.
- Hi, Tim.
- Lieutenant Yoshida.
Your dad was the
best of the best.
He was a legend in this precinct.
Thank you, thank you,
for saying that.
It was a terrible tragedy
losing him and his partner.
- His partner?
- His Pokémon.
Oh... I didn't...
I'm sorry, is yours mad at me?
- Snubbull?
- Yeah.
He may look grumpy on the outside,
but I assure you he is
adorable on the inside.
If you don't mind me asking,
how come you don't have a Pokémon?
I thought I remember Harry saying you
wanted to be a Pokémon trainer
- When you were young.
- Yeah, that didn't really work out.
I work in insurance now.
I understand.
But Tim, please don't put
this all on yourself.
No one should go through
this type of thing alone.
- If you are anything like your dad...
- I'm not.
I was just really raised
by my grandmother.
Do you have the spare keys for his apartment?
I should go wrap things up there.
Of course, of course.
- Here's his address.
- Awesome.
- I can take you over if you want.
- No, no. I'm all good.
Thank you so much.
Tim...
This job, it demands a lot.
But you were on his mind every day.
He loved you more than
anything else in the world.
Uh, it was nice to
meet you, lieutenant.
- Excuse me.
- Treecko...
- Tree!
- Okay...
Psyduck?
Psyduck.
Are you trying to rob me,
or just annoy me?
- Psyduck.
- He's with me.
- We need to talk.
- We do?
I've been waiting to see
who would open up that mailbox.
You just walked in
into quite the story.
Stories like this spread fear.
And they are afraid of fear.
But I don't fear, fear.
I walk the walk, and I talk the
talk, and I'm willing to do
whatever it takes get the honest
scoop and that's the hard truth.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Lucy Stevens.
Reporter for CNM.
Oh... you seem kinda young for that.
I work for the CNM Blog,
making Pokémon lists all day, okay?
- Top 10 cutest Pokémon.
- Yeah my grandma loves those.
Yeah newsflash: they're all cute!
Such a waste of time for someone
with my nose for a story.
No, no, not now, Psyduck.
I'm working a source...
Okay... I'll get... uh...
I'm gonna need you to
go on record and tell
me everything you know
about Harry Goodman.
- Wait, what?
- Harry was onto something big.
Real big.
And then all of the sudden, his
car crashes over a bridge, I think not.
Something's rotten and I'm
gonna get to the bottom of it.
- Hey look, I barely
know the guy,
- I haven't seen him in years.
- Where is your Pokémon partner?
I don't have one, why is
everyone keep asking me that?
- Loner, probably hiding something.
- Psyduck!
- Okay I'm gonna go.
- Hey!
I may only be an unpaid intern,
but I can smell a story,
and I'm going to find it.
Okay, you do that.
- Come on Psyduck, let's go.
- Psyduck.
- Who is it?
- Hello?
It's me, Snakes. I got the stuff.
Leave it on the doorstep,
and get the hell outta here.
Alright, Johnny.
But what about my money?
Still with the old
detective movies?
What the...
What... is this stuff?
"Dear Tim, I can do better
if you give me a chance.
I will always have a
place for you to stay."
Your father will pick
you up at the station.
I'm not going.
- What?
- I don't wanna go...
I wanna stay with
you and grandma.
Oh man.
This is the most
important day of my life.
I know, Tim.
But your mother had to see
the doctor, it couldn't wait.
Is someone there?
Hello?
Ouch... that's a sprain...
Okay, okay, okay.
Whoever you are...
I know how to use this.
- It's a Pikachu?
- Oh... jeez.
Hey, little guy,
how did you get in here?
I know you can't understand me,
but put down the stapler,
or I will electrocute you.
Did you just talk?
Woah, did you just understand me?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
That is heavy eye contact right there.
You heard me.
- No, no, no.
- Yes you did! Oh my god! This is amazing.
- Stop, stop, stop it!
- You do understand me!
I've been so lonely.
- I'm gonna throw up.
- No, kid, I need your help.
- I'm in serious trouble I need you to listen.
- I'm gonna throw up. I'm gonna throw up.
- No, no, no.
- Excuse me, Aipom.
We're having a private
conversation here please.
- Stop talking, you're hallucinating.
- You're a hallucination.
You, out! Shoo! Go!
I'll tread lightly there, chief.
That, that Aipom don't look right.
Get off!
Get up, kid.
He's coming back around!
Okay, here's what you wanna do.
Okay, you wanna bite him,
you wanna scream,
we are playing charades,
we are not playing charades,
Okay, I'm gonna get a knife.
- Not the knife.
- Okay bad idea with the knife, I'll find something else.
Eat this!
You are so welcome.
He's just a hungry little guy.
Come on kid, let's move!
To the roof!
Brilliant idea, you hold
the door, I'll go get help!
- What?
- Help!
Oh my god, help!
Oh shit.
Help! Help!
Oh my god help!
Oh he is being eaten alive!
A man is dying!
No one's coming,
people are so insensitive!
Uh oh, put your pants back on,
and run like the wind.
They seem to be more attracted
to your increasing nudeness!
Okay.
Alright we're jumping down here.
- No, no! I'm not going into the trash chute.
- Good call,
let me know how it goes with
the super crazy Pokémon.
You died a hero.
- Way to stick the landing, kid.
- Leave me alone!
Oh, looks like someone's
back in a good mood.
Run! Ravage Aipoms!
Look out!
Run! Go, go, go, go!
They...
I think pants are gonna
do you a lot of good right now.
Shoo! Go!
You know, I've pictured you as a,
as a bit of a briefs guy, but those are nice.
Me, I don't wear underwear.
You know, I'm not modest.
Excuse me, excuse me,
hi, sorry,
You can hear him, right?
You can hear him talking?
Pika-Pika.
Oh, yeah, Pika-Pika-Pika,
he's adorable.
You're adorable.
They can't understand me, kid.
It's me, it's that stuff
that I put up my nose.
No, not like that, it was
a gas, I was breathing gas.
Accidentally, accidentally...
unless you want charming law to give
you one way ticket to hoosegow. Let's move.
- No one else can hear him?
- This is a first for me too, kid.
I tried to talk to the all the time
all they hear is "Pika-Pika".
Pet me, or kiss me,
stick a finger in me.
- It's really gross.
- Anyone? No one else can hear him?
Can you hear him talking?
Can you hear him saying words?
What are you not getting here, kid?
You are the only one who can hear me.
- It's like destiny.
- It's not destiny.
- Then why were you in that apartment?
- It's my father's place.
That's why I was there.
Why where you there?
You're Harry's son?
How do you know his name?
You're Harry Pokémon's partner?
You want a coffee?
'Cause I could use a coffee.
Yeah, let's get a coffee.
Yeah, come on.
So there I was,
in the middle of nowhere,
with a bad case of the forgetsies.
The only clue to my past, is Harry's
name and address inside this hat.
So, I made my way to the apartment
and that's when I've found you.
Jiggaly... puff... jiggaly...
- I don't know, maybe I've got too deep.
- Deep in what?
You know, mix up with the
wrong crowd, that kind of thing.
Happens to the best of us.
The deads pile up,
the walls close in.
Right becomes wrong,
wrong becomes wrong.
- Wait, who are you calling?
- No one.
Yeah, yeah, no that's sounds great, that
sounds great. This menu looks really nice.
Wait, I'm confused, are you
hearing other voices besides mine?
All I wanna know is, why
do I understand you?
Can't help you there, kid. Like I said
I have amnesia. I can't remember a darn thing.
Okay so you are a talking Pikachu,
with no memories, who's addicted to caffeine.
I can stop wherever I want.
These are just choices.
Another round, extra shot.
- Like is night. Thank you sweety.
- Ludicolo!
Look, I'm a great detective,
but I can't solve my own mystery
if I have no memory.
- Then how do you even know you are a detective?
- Well that, I can feel that in my jellys.
- What is that, what is that?
- It's the jellys, it's that thing, you know you feel it.
When you really believe in something
despite everyone telling you you're wrong.
Which is why I need to find Harry.
He's the key to my past.
- Ludicolo!
- Thanks doll.
I've got some bad news
for you, 'cause uh...
Harry's dead.
What? No.
No, no, no, Harry ain't dead.
No, Harry is dead.
You're wrong, sorry.
I saw on the police report
that he's dead.
- Just 'cause the cop say he's dead...
- I mean he's legally dead.
Really?
Did they find a body?
Well I didn't think so.
And by the way, did that report
also said that I'm dead?
'Cause if I'm still alive and kicking
that means Harry is out there too.
Case closed.
But still open!
- Until I solve it.
- Okay, I'll bite, solve what?
Oh I'm glad you are gonna bite.
Alright, here it is:
Harry faked his own death.
Or, somebody else
faked Harry's death.
Or, Harry faked
somebody else's death.
- That last one, doesn't work at all.
- No, no it doesn't.
But the first two does, real contenders.
- No, uh, I'm gonna go, we're done here, this is...
- No we are not done here...
Wait, wait, wait a minute,
where are you going?
- Hold up a second, we're gonna need each other.
- No, we don't.
I don't need a Pokémon.
Period. Got it?
And what about a world-class detective.
Because if you wanna find your pops,
I'm your best bet.
I think a world-class detective
oughta have already figured out by now
that I'm not here
to find my father.
I'm here, to say goodbye.
Hey, hey, there's no one
to say goodbye to.
Look, you can talk to humans,
I can talk to Pokémon.
We can talk to each other.
This doesn't happen, kid.
It has to mean something.
- Can you...
- It's magic, that brought us together.
And that magic is called: Hope.
Hope that Harry is still alive.
Ooh, you feel it.
You feel it in your jellys, don't you?
There's nothing in my jellys.
We are gonna do this.
You and me.
I can't believ...
I will meet you here
tomorrow morning.
Great.
- Where are you going?
- To my apartment.
What do you mean "your apartment"?
- What? Alright you can sleep on the couch.
- No I'm not gonna sleep on the couch.
Well, then you can sleep on the stove.
- Be a dear, would you get the door for me?
- What am I doing?
I just invited someone
to my apartment!
I never do this, I'm not
that kind of Pokémon.
Dust everywhere,
no fingerprints.
Don't add up.
- What is going on in here?
- I'm searching the joint. Looking for clues to my past.
- Is this your room?
- No.
- Does Harry have other children?
He wanted me to live
here when I was a kid,
so he made it look like
my childhood room.
Should we talking about the fact
that your childhood bed is a Pikachu bed?
- It's a coincidence.
- I'm sorry, can you speak up?
I can't hear you.
I've never been so flattered
and creeped out at the same time.
- Are you gonna make me into a lampshade?
- Oh I might.
Hang on, hang on, hang on,
all these Pokémon cards
and the battle posters,
There's a connection, isn't there?
- You love Pokémon.
- No.
- Yeah, yeah you do.
- That was a long time ago...
before my father moved to the city
and spent more time with
Pokémon than his own son.
Um, yeah, blaming your dad.
Okay, look, what about this:
This picture is all over the apartment
she's obviously connected to Harry,
she might know me.
She could be a lead.
No, she's not.
That's my mom.
She passed away when I was eleven.
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't...
I didn't realize.
Tomorrow morning I'm gonna take you
to Yoshida so we can get some answers.
- Argh, my clues!
- What is all this?!
Hard work, that's what this is!
And by the way...
we can't go to the cops,
not until we know who we can trust.
- So put my clues back in order, would 'cha?
- These are not clues. This is the work of a serial killer.
- Were almost clues.
- What does that even mean?
I'm trying to jog my memory, retrace my steps,
it helps me to see it all laid out.
That's how I found this...
This, is what a French man
would call Caliente Fiesta.
- Not French.
- Smell my finger.
- I will never smell your finger.
- Coward.
The point is that I smelled this "R" stuff
on those Aipom when they attacked us yesterday.
- "R"?
- Bingo! La Cucaracha.
So I'm thinking, Harry
caught a break in the case,
forcing shadowing kingpins
send down hired goons
to deliver the big hush hush...
We need to retrace Harry's steps,
either solve the case ourselves,
or get far enough along
that this A number one bad guy
has to reveal himself
or herself!
- You need to stop doing that.
- So what is the way in?
The answer is in this room.
This isn't a room,
this is a fire hazard.
Is just junk, and papers... and...
Newspapers.
What you got, kid?
I literally just met someone,
she was a junior reporter at CNM.
She was doing a story on Harry.
I think she knows more than she let on.
The smart ones always do.
We gotta go down to
her work and press her.
- That's a metaphor.
- Yeah I know what a metaphor is.
I was drinking that.
I was also drinking...
Just step anywhere,
it's only my life's work.
No, no.
- We're not doing that.
- Fine, I'll walk.
I'm trying to get in a
100,000 steps this hour.
Hello I'm Roger Clifford, president
of CNM and chairman of Clifford Enterprises.
And I'm Howard Clifford,
the visionary icon behind Rhyme City.
Together, in the spirit of harmony,
we're throwing the largest
parade that Rhyme City has ever seen.
- You won't wanna miss it.
- So at the weekend,
- we invite the people...
- and the Pokémon to be there.
A celebration of the harmony
between humans and Pokémon.
And, cut!
- Oh I think that went rather well.
- Oh shut up, dad.
- He seems nice.
- Roger, please.
This is supposed to be
our gift to the citizens.
Visionary icon, really?
Was "Savior of the world" taken?
It was your people who
wrote the promo, son.
Oh is there an unabridged version
where you cure cancer?
Oh that's right, turn your back
on me, like you always did.
- Ditto!
- By the way, no one likes your Pokémon.
There she is.
I can see why you
were so excited.
Okay... I was not...
- that excited.
- Mr. Clifford... Mr. Clifford...
Mr. Clifford, I may have
a story for you.
I've heard rumors of
Pokémon attacking people
- But there's been no mainstream coverage...
- I'm sorry...
we're not a tabloid, which
means that we don't report
on rumors, gossip,
or hearsay.
It's not news if it can't be verified.
You want a story? Find a source.
Oh and pro tip...
a reasonable sense of fashion.
Here she comes, here she comes,
try to look deep.
What are you doing here?
Hey, again.
Uh, yeah I know this seems weird,
but I actually needed to ask you something.
Now is not really a good time.
Yeah, I saw that.
I'm sorry.
Sorry. It's piping hot.
You found yourself a Pokémon partner.
- Not exactly, no.
- Oh he's cute.
Yeah she's trying to work me kid,
but trust me, I can oh...
sweet mother of Arceus,
that feels so good.
- So... listen.
- Oh my god... oh.
What happened?
I've found something
on Harry's desk.
- Nearly choked me to death, and...
- No, not here.
In my office.
In her office.
We're going to her office.
This is great.
This isn't her office, it's a
coffin with pencils.
- Psyduck?
- Yeah that's right, I can talk to the kid
and he can talk to me.
We're gifted.
You didn't tell me that
she has a Psyduck.
This things explodes
when they are stressed.
Hey, hey, keep calm duck.
Serenity now, serenity now.
- No.
- Okay.
- Okay, here it is.
- You got it?
Where'd you find these?
Word on the street is that
Harry had an informer near the docks.
I went there to snoop around.
And that's where I found the vial.
But the docks can be dangerous.
It's not the sort of place
you wanna visit alone at night.
I'm actually pretty good
at being alone at night.
Nope, that did not land right at all.
It's not... it's not what
I meant to say... um
- It's okay.
- I'm just gonna...
We should go soon.
Yeah, yeah, we should go.
Good god,
have you ever talked
to a women before?
Psyduck...
Yes I've talked to women before,
and no I don't need your help.
It was during the birth canal or...?
You know what you need? A shoulder
saddle. I bet someone makes one.
Okay, there are other ways for you
to get around. This is humiliating.
Every step for you is a thousand for me,
and my lungs are the size of grapes.
We need to get some ground rules
if this partnership's gonna work.
- You are not my partner.
- Mentor, Sensei, Master,
whatever you wanna call it,
I'm fine with all of those.
And what if it wasn't the gas?
What if it's hereditary, uh?
What if Harry could understand
your annoying voice too?
You don't need to talk to us
for us to understand.
We can feel what you are saying.
You have to be open to the experience.
Try it some time.
Yeah I'd rather not.
I've got my plate full talking to you.
- What is that?
- Silent, but deadly.
Apologies, my tummy's bad
from all the coffee.
No, ew, get off!
I meant that.
Oh that...
It's a Mr. Mime, they're the worst.
Silent, but annoying.
Does he recognize you?
I think he recognizes you.
Well I was Harry's partner,
so I would've been with him.
- Oh, Harry's informant is a Pokémon!
Get him!
- He's barely moving.
- Don't tell him that.
Oh, he's on a bike.
Come on, he thinks he's getting away. Quick
get in front of him. Cut him off, you can make it.
Stop!
Oh no he's going down hard, Tim.
Should've worn a helmet.
- I hope he makes it.
- Come on, this is ridiculous.
I'm good cop, you are bad cop.
- We're not cops.
- Grow some berries.
You're bigger and tougher looking
than I am, stand up straight.
Listen up, we got ways to
make you talk, or mime.
So tell us what we wanna know...
why was Harry Goodman here and
what did it had to do with the "R"?
Pipe.
Yes, a can.
Shoving, pushing...
The problem is that I push people
away and I hate them for leaving.
He is saying you can "shove it".
What? I can shove it?
Okay that's it. No, we are switching roles.
I'm bad cop, you're good cop.
- No, we are not cops.
- Oh good god, that's a very hard wall.
Oh yeah, Mr. Mime has the abilities
to make invisible walls.
Oh yes I know, I happen to be
a Pokémon too, remember?
Look, Harry figured
this guy out somehow.
I think the trick is,
getting inside his head.
I have an idea.
What are you doing?
What's this? Oh there's a door there?
I didn't... probably because it's invisible.
Oh yeah, I'm in your space now, right?
You don't like this so much, do you?
What are you doing?
That's a jug.
- No, you're pouring.
- Salt. It's a salt shaker, you're cooking.
Real cooking is by following your
heart not a recipe!
- What are you talking about?
- Gas...
You're pouring gasoline!
Oh, that went dark fast, I like this,
I like this very much.
Alright, alright.
Okay, you wanna play that game?
I'm gonna play that game.
You think that's funny?
You think that's funny huh?
I'm gonna be laughing soon.
Who's laughing now? Huh?
Oh I smell what you are stepping in.
That's right Mr. Mime,
you are about to be Mr. Melt
unless you start talking.
Cards, cards,
playing cards, poker...
No I think he is talking
about the "R".
Someone was handing out "R".
Use your body words, where?
Circle, house, Moon house, Moon, House.
Stop with the games, say it! Just
say it! Talk you stupid mime.
Okay... just... relax.
Round, round house,
the source of the "R" came from
the round house.
Yeah nice work kid, maybe there's
a little detective in you after all.
Critical hit!
Additional damage!
I didn't know they had
Pokémon battles in Rhyme City.
You're not supposed to.
Gengar uses Dark Ball.
Come on, let's take a look around.
Okay kid, so here's what we know:
Harry traces the "R" here
and frequents this joint, 'cause someone
here knows something about something.
We just need to find this
someone and the something.
Hey, hey, where's that Pikachu's
partner? Don't go!
I think that someone just found us.
Wow, I'd like to see this
guy's internet search history.
- Who are you?
- Let's see where this goes.
- Tell him you're my new partner.
- I'm his new partner.
Well, that Pikachu's thunderbolt
almost wrecked my prized Charizard
last time he was here.
His scar's still fresh.
All I hear are consonants and
all I see are nipples.
And you know what?
He ruined my coat man, look at this.
- I'm so sorry.
- Forget the coat, where's his shirt?
This... this is my place!
And nobody comes into my place
and does that to my Pokémon
- What are you looking at?
- Or to my coat.
Right, the coat.
The coat...
What are you doing?
Classic stare down kid,
the first one to blink, loses.
- Now stop distracting me.
- Uh, look,
I just wanna know why his old
partner was here, that's all.
Gengar wins.
Ready for the next battle.
And I want a rematch.
You give me my rematch
and I'll tell you everything
you want to know. What I know.
Tell him he's on, amigo.
- Okay.
- A new battle's upholding!
Pikachu versus Charizard.
Rematch!
Here, hold my hat.
- I'm 'bout to rock this place.
- Okay.
Just doing some light stretching,
you never want to go on these things tight.
We are going to win this time okay?
What are you doing?
What is your plan of attack?
I don't operate according to plans, kid.
I deal with things in the moment.
Okay, here we go.
Now obviously,
I've dealt with these putz before,
so I'll just do it again.
Give me my hat back!
That thing just chugged a year's
worth of that "R" stuff.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. It's like you said okay?
You did it before.
You just gotta use your powers.
You can use Quick Attack,
Discharge or Electro Ball
but, I think Volt Tackle
is your best move,
- so let's start with that.
- First of all,
when did you learn how
to be a Pokémon trainer?
And secondly, get me the
hell out of here!
Begin!
Look out!
I forgot everything you said.
I forget things, it's what I do,
I have amnesia.
You wanna go for a critical hit,
use Volt Tackle.
Volt Tackle will knock me out,
I'm going for Thunderbolt.
Come on, you got it, you got it!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on...
Hey bud? What are you doing?
I can't do it when
people are watching.
Can everyone just look away please?
It's not working.
I forgot how to use my powers.
But he didn't.
Pikachu, run!
Taken out with one hit!
Hi there, Pikachu. Wanna cry?
You don't wanna do this.
I'm adorable.
Pika-Pika!
Are you crazy?
Get out of there!
I got it, kid!
What are you doing to my baby!
Get out of the way!
Uh oh, that's not good.
- What are you doing...
- Tell me what you know!
The guy you were looking for,
wanted to know the source of "R".
It comes from the doctor,
that's all I know.
Now let me go.
Nice catch, kid.
Let's get out of here.
I've got a plan.
Look it's not gonna work,
Magikarp is the worst.
Magikarp can evolve into Gyarados,
all he needs it's just a little kick.
Water in the hole!
In my head, I saw that differently.
Hey Tim, I don't float.
I told you Magikarp
weren't useless.
You're under arrest.
I thought you couldn't
wait to get home.
Yeah well, my plan's changed
because I found him.
- I'm not following.
- Harry's not dead.
If his Pokémon partner's
still alive, that means he is too.
- That is not proof, son.
- Tell him about the chemical "R".
Give me a minute. Harry's last case
had to do with those underground battles.
That's why I was there.
There's a chemical...
- We ran an investigation...
- Harry figured it out...
- and it is over!
- and got in trouble for it.
Re-open the investigation, he's out there, I can feel it.
- In your jellys, go ahead say it.
- I'm not gonna say that.
I can feel it, lieutenant,
in my bones.
- Not as good.
- Stop.
Oh yeah and I... can understand
Pikachu like... we're perfect.
Tim...
It's very difficult
coping with loss.
- Denial can be a...
- No I'm not in denial!
I'm right, I know it.
He's... he's out there.
I never wanted to show you this,
but I think it's important you see it.
No one could survive
a crash like that.
Not even your dad.
He's gone, Tim.
Should've gotten on that train.
What's that kid?
After my mom died,
my dad and I drifted apart.
He moved here and...
poured himself into his work.
Eventually, he tried to get me
to come live with him but,
I wouldn't go.
How come?
I didn't think he cared.
I guess I just got used to him
not being around and...
I couldn't forgive him for it...
'til I got here, and...
I realized that he did care.
But I didn't know,
'cause I've never gave him the chance.
And now, it's too late.
I really...
I really wish I had
got on that train.
Listen, kid.
I may not have memories
but I know this much:
It wasn't your fault.
Wasn't anybody's fault.
And I'm sure that if
your dad was here,
he would hug you so hard,
your bones would pop...
and he'd tell you he's
sorry for everything.
He'd be damn proud of you, kid.
I haven't been really nice to you.
No you really haven't.
Well...
We still got one mystery to solve.
- What?
- Yours.
Let's find out who
did this to you.
- Get your memory back.
- I'd like that.
I'd like that very much.
Well, that's a bad guy car.
Thank you, Miss Norman.
Yes thank you, Miss Norman.
That would be all.
What a blabbermouth.
Please, come in.
Magnificent creatures, aren't they?
Woah, a Flareon.
Imagine being able to evolve
into the best possible
version of yourself.
That greatness inside you,
just waiting to be awoken.
- Hello, Tim.
- He knows you?
I see you partnered
with Harry's Pikachu.
- And he knows me too.
- You knew Harry?
The case Harry was working on,
- it was for me.
- That's a twist. That's very twisty.
This compound threatens
everything I've built.
He knows about the "R".
How does he know about the "R"?
I hired Harry to trace
it to it's source.
Imagine my shock
when the answer
turned out to be my own son.
I've devoted my life to
perfecting the partnership
between Pokémon and humans.
A partnership where Pokémon
bring out the best in us.
In doing so, I'm
afraid I neglected
my responsibilities as a parent.
Roger resents the Pokémon.
I think he's lived in
my shadow for so long,
he actually wants
to destroy my legacy.
Well there's no such thing
as daddy issues without daddy.
But Mr. Clifford, how could
you let him do that?
Ever since my illness put
me in this chair,
Roger has taken over more
and more of the company.
He controls the board, he also controls
the police and the politicians...
and he owns the press.
Harry is the only one I can trust,
that's why you need to find him.
You haven't heard.
Harry's dead.
Oh no, Tim.
Your father is alive.
Look out, Tim!
Advanced Holographic Imaging.
Since being confined to this chair,
I've invested in ways of
bringing the world to me.
This was recreated from police footage,
it allows us to see
things that they cannot
or don't want us to see.
He's alive.
- Pika...
- It's me,
- I was with Harry in the crash.
- He needs my help.
If Harry is alive,
why didn't they find him?
- What is that?
- Mewtwo.
A man-made abomination.
Created in a
laboratory using DNA
from the fossil remains
of the ancient Mew.
I can't believe it.
If that thing came from Mew,
then we are looking at the most
powerful Pokémon in the world.
That's it! That's
what happened to me.
Mewtwo wiped my memory.
But why?
Wait, wait, wait!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait... where did he take him?
- That's for you to solve now.
Find Mewtwo, and you'll find your father.
Second chances are
special things, kid.
There's a lot we can make better
if we crack this case.
One question though,
where are we going?
I don't know, I'm just going, you gotta
tell me where, you're the detective.
Okay, if Roger Clifford
is the key to all of this,
then we need someone
who has access to him.
And we both know who that is.
- Lover boy.
- Okay, come on, let's not start that again.
- There she is.
- What's with the sunglasses?
Can she see us?
I don't think she can see us.
- Hey, thanks for coming.
- Don't talk to me.
Okay.
- What happens now?
- Just act casual...
but don't look at me.
There's nothing really
casual about this.
Look at this.
I'm sorry.
- That's my fault.
- Sorry... I'm sorry.
- Oh it's working out great, why don't you just have her sit over here?
- You want to just come sit with us?
I should have never encouraged
you, you have no chance.
- I got access to Roger's computer.
- Oh wow, how'd you do that?
- Spilled the cappuccino on his lap.
- It sounds like a waste of coffee.
So I searched through all his records. I
targeted the property rights in the region,
and I cross-checked that with city records
for any Clifford's finance businesses
until I found...
May I present: PCL.
A Pokémon genetic research facility.
- But that's not all.
- She's good.
Last week, PCL had an accident
and had to shutdown their entire facility.
That's the same night
Harry Goodman went missing.
No one knows what happened.
Total media blackout.
What does it all mean?
I don't know.
This is very exciting.
Are you excited?
- Yeah.
- I think he just peed a little.
- So...
- No, no, that's me. That was me.
So, um, there's a cover up.
But...
what are they covering up?
What do you say we go find out?
So let me get this right.
We are forced to listen
to this spa music
so your head doesn't explode
- and kill us all?
- Psyduck.
Your Pikachu, it's so unusual.
- Psyduck?
- Hey you put that down.
- I'm not giving you a massage.
- Psyduck.
I have never known a
Pokémon to wear a hat.
Yeah he's weird.
He's so weird.
Of course I care about
my partner's life.
Fine, fine,
hand it over.
What are you doing?
What?
Nothing, I was actually
wondering who this was.
It's PCL's chief scientist,
Dr. Ann Laurent.
I bet this is the doctor
shirtless was talking about.
She lost her university grant
over a experimentation of Pokémon
because she was trying to
control their minds.
She's essentially a
neurologist for Pokémon.
Maybe this doctor could weigh in
on the long term psychological effects
of being strapped into a
baby seat, next to a bomb.
This is it.
Look at the signs.
It must have been a
really bad accident.
That's what they
want you to believe.
Whoever staged this did an excellent job. Those
signs are the perfect scarecrow for suckers.
- Yeah well, they're working on me.
- Psyduck.
Kid, this dame is looking for danger.
You want to win her over you
gotta lead her straight to it.
Okay, first of all women don't
like to be called dame.
Second, women appreciate
calm, level-headed,
and responsible decision making...
What is she doing?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, Lucy, what are you doing?
I'm cutting the fence
so that we can slip through.
No... wha... where'd you get those?
- Oh don't worry about it.
- After you, sir.
- Psyduck.
- No? Okay I'll go first.
- Whatever is most calming.
- Psyduck.
Psyduck, Psyduck.
It's okay.
You can stay up there.
I have amnesia but,
I'm pretty sure this is the worst
idea anyone has ever had.
What is that?
I'm not sure.
Psyduck!
It's Greninja.
They don't look right.
Test 22: Power Enhancement?
They were experimenting on them.
Why? If Roger Clifford
is behind this,
what's he doing
experimenting on Pokémon?
Torterra garden.
Pokémon Evolution Test 33:
Growth Enhancement.
They look normal-sized to me.
Maybe it hasn't started yet.
It's like they're trying to
manipulate Pokémon evolution.
Is that possible?
I don't know.
I need to document all of this though.
You go ahead,
I'll catch up to you.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
What happened here?
Bad stuff.
Really bad stuff.
Still think this was staged?
Kid, hey, over here.
It says Dr. Laurent station.
Looks like it's still working.
Remote access initiated.
Psyduck.
Looks like most of the
files are corrupted.
Uh oh, not another one of those holograms.
Day 42.
After much trial and error,
we perfected a stable method
to extract Mewtwo's DNA.
It's Mewtwo, no way.
Wait, Mewtwo came from this place?
Day 60, clinical trials
proven successful.
The inhalant results
in confusion
and the total loss
of free will,
which in turn makes
the Pokémon go wild.
We designated this chemical
as serum "R".
They used Mewtwo to make "R".
And they were testing it,
at the battles.
Day 68.
The neural link is operational.
Alert: Condition Red
Alert! Alert!
Alert!
No! No! No!
We're losing power in the
containment chamber!
That must have been
how Mewtwo escaped.
Now we're getting somewhere.
- But what did that thing want with Harry?
- Good question, kid.
I'll try to take us
back to the beginning.
Day 1. The lab is almost
fully operational.
All that remains now is
to capture the most powerful
Pokémon known to mankind:
Mewtwo.
It escaped nearly 20 years ago
from the Kanto region.
Fortunately, our benefactors hired a
specialist to track it down.
Good luck, detective Goodman.
That's why Mewtwo took Harry.
It was revenge for being captured.
This doesn't make any sense!
- Harry would have never been a part of this.
- I wanna believe that kid.
We gotta be honest here, you haven't
seen him in years and I got amnesia,
neither of us can say for sure
what Harry would or wouldn't do.
We gotta get back to the city.
Lucy!
We gotta get back to...
Lucy?
That was not there before, kid.
Ew!
Kid, the fire alarm!
Psyduck!
Come on!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
- Go back.
- Psyduck!
Psyduck. Psyduck.
Get down!
Psyduck!
Run!
Psyduck! Psyduck! Psyduck!
- Psyduck!
- It's okay, it's okay Psyduck! Everything's fine!
He's gonna blow his head, kid.
It's okay, Psyduck.
It's okay!
Psyduck!
This is no time for your
stupid headache.
No, wait, wait.
This is the perfect time
to get a headache.
- Psyduck.
- I hated rubbing your feet!
Psyduck, psyduck!
I'll never forget my hands
for what they did.
Get a splitting headache now,
you neurotic duck!
- Do it! Do it!
- Psyduck!
- Do it!
- Psy... duck.
- Good job, Psyduck.
Where's my hat?
Something's wrong.
This isn't really happening.
Don't worry.
Psyduck psionic waves are
causing hallucinations.
None of this is real.
All of this is real!
Run!
What's happening?
We're falling down!
At this point,
how can you not believe
in climate change?
No!
I've got you.
Tim!
Run!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go!
We made it.
I officially hate this forest.
Tim!
- Lucy!
- Tim! - Psyduck!
Walls are closing in.
We have to do something,
and we gotta do it fast.
- I'm gonna jump for it.
- That's a great fifth option.
- Let's work on the first four.
- You're not gonna make it!
- There's no other choice.
- We have a lot of choices,
only going down is
not one of them.
Come on!
Never thought...
I thought I was gonna...
Eye, eye...
- Eyeball.
Eyeball!
I get it!
I get it now, this
isn't a forest at all!
This is the Torterra Garden!
Pikachu!
He's alright!
- Is he okay?
- I'm in bad shape, kid.
I'm here, partner.
I'm here.
Did you just called
me your partner?
Yeah, of course!
You're my partner.
Oh that's right, I'm your par...
You've got my back.
Buddy!
Pikachu!
No.
Hey, hey, help!
Please!
He's hurt!
He doesn't know what
you're saying.
But he knows what
I'm feeling.
I need to get Pikachu
to a healer Pokémon.
Please.
I'm begging you.
I don't wanna lose him too.
It's okay.
Tim, look.
Okay.
I'll wait you at the car.
You're gonna be okay, partner.
Here?
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Where are you going?
What am I supposed to do?
I've been waiting for you.
Mewtwo.
No, no!
Wait!
Where am I?
You're okay!
Yeah I... somehow I'm fine!
You brought the son to me,
as we agreed.
- What is he talking about?
- I don't know kid, I'm as lost as you are.
Where's my father?
What'd you do with him?
Alert!
We're losing power in the
containment chamber!
You've done well.
Humanity is evil.
I've always believed Pokémon...
No!
Wait, wait, wait.
Pikachu, wait.
Hey, slow down! We
have to talk about this.
You'll have to go on without me.
What? What are you saying?
Roger has Mewtwo.
Mewtwo has my father. We're running
out of time, we have a case to solve.
We already solved mine.
I know who I am.
I'm the guy who betrayed Harry.
You don't know that.
We both saw it. I betrayed your father.
Which means...
- I could betray you too.
- You wouldn't do that.
I don't care what I saw,
I know who you are.
- How do you know?
- Because I...
- I can feel it in my jellys.
- I made that up.
- There's no jellys. There's no me.
- I don't believe that.
- You're better off on your own.
- Come on, Pikachu.
- I need you, please.
- No you have to... you have to stay away, it's for your own good.
No, I'm not letting you go.
You see?
I can't help it, I hurt
the people who need me.
That's who I am.
I'm sorry.
Tim.
Where is he going?
What happened?
Is Pikachu okay?
No, he's not.
Let's go. We gotta get
back to the city.
The tenth anniversary
Rhyme City Pokémon Parade
is set to begin this afternoon.
The whole city is converging on downtown
to watch today's festivities.
I don't know what happened between
you two, but we need to strategize.
Wait, where are you going?
We need to tell the public what
we found! This is breaking news!
No, no, you should break the news, you.
I'm gonna go talk to Howard.
Tim?
How am I supposed to break the news
when the guy that runs the news
is the breaking news?
- Just stay in the car, okay?
- Psyduck.
Mrs McMaster, hi.
It's Lucy Stevens,
- the intern at CNM.
- Could you?
Yeah, um I have a story
that's really important.
And the people need to hear it, and
I was really hoping you could help me tell it.
Lucy, please, take my coffee order.
Latte, extra sugar.
You got it, Cynthia.
Searching far and wide.
Each Pokémon to understand
the power that's inside!
Pokémon!
Gotta catch 'em all.
It's you and me.
I know it's my destiny!
Pokémon!
What is this?
I know this place.
This is the scene of the crash.
What is that?
Greninja stars.
Roger must have sent the
Greninjas to cause the crash, which...
Which means...
Mewtwo was trying to protect us?
Advanced Holographic Imaging.
It allows us to see
things that they cannot
- or don't want us to see.
- Wait...
Howard would've seen
this in his hologram.
Oh no! No, no, no.
Tim!
Howard!
Mr. Clifford.
Your son...
Has Mewtwo here.
- Wait, what?
- Tim.
It's gonna be okay.
Run!
The transfer worked.
My body is in the chair,
but my mind is in Mewtwo.
- Howard?
- Well done, Tim.
You and Harry's Pikachu lead
me straight to Mewtwo.
Mewtwo didn't cause the crash.
All your father had to do
was take the money and walk away.
But he started asking questions.
- I had to stop him.
- You tried to kill him!
I had no choice!
He tracked the "R" to the battles.
Traced it back to Dr. Laurent.
And then he and his Pikachu
helped Mewtwo escape.
So as you can see, we are more
than happy with the turnout today.
So many families...
Thank you so much. Thank you.
That's all for today. Thank you.
Excuse me, please.
Hello.
Hi, hi. I have an interview.
- With the mayor...
- Go on please.
Mr. Mayor, Mr. Mayor! I need
to speak with you please, it's urgent.
- Little late for an interview, don't you think?
- Please.
Before we begin the parade,
I'd like to thank our
benefactor Howard Clifford.
This was never about curing me.
I've found a path forward
for all of us.
Mewtwo has the
power to transfer
the soul of a human
into the body of a Pokémon,
as long as the Pokémon
are in a crazed state.
The "R" gas takes care of that.
The balloons.
The "R" gas is in the balloons.
People of Rhyme City.
I've finally discovered a cure.
Not just for me,
but for all of humanity.
Pokémon can evolve into
better versions of themselves.
And now, so can you.
Humans and Pokémon,
merged into one.
Don't let your Pokémon
breathe the purple gas.
This is Yoshida requesting backup.
All units...
Snubbull, no!
Don't let your Pokémon
breathe the gas.
Come on...
This is Lucy Stevens
reporting a citywide emergency.
Do not let your
Pokémon breathe...
Psyduck!
Psyduck! Psyduck!
Psyduck?
Okay.
Worst parade I've ever seen!
- Psyduck!
- Lucy. Lucy, you're in there?
- Where's Tim?
- Psyduck, Psyduck.
- Howard is Mewtwo?
This really blows my bridge
discovery out of the water.
Alright.
I gotta stop this.
Game on.
Okay, Pikachu.
Your powers are in there somewhere.
Just need a little spark
to get this party started.
Let's do this!
Harry's Pikachu.
You think you can stand
in the way of the future?
I am the future!
He's back!
The neural link.
Roger?
Behind you!
You're a Ditto.
Ditto!
Flank left!
Flank right, right!
Where did you learn how to fly, the ground?
No, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Come on, no, that's not fair.
Okay, for the record,
I have no guilt hitting
a beady-eyed version of the
woman I'm very attracted to.
Uh oh! Now pull up,
don't breathe the gas.
You breathed the gas, didn't you?
Okay.
- Finish him, Ditto!
- Ditto.
No!
No, no, no!
Pikachu!
Tim.
Harry's son is finished.
No.
Tim said Volt Tackle
is my best move.
Let's do this Pokémon Battle
thing right!
No!
Yeah! Give me your hand! Give me your hand!
What kind of a Ditto was that?
That was modified.
Father's genetic experiments.
Ditto!
Ditto...
A feeble effort!
A Pikachu cannot defeat
Mewtwo in battle.
I didn't mean to defeat you.
I just needed to distract you.
No!
What have you done?
Pikachu! No!
- Pikachu!
- Tim!
- Are you okay?
- I'm sorry!
I'm sorry I pushed you away
just when you needed me the most.
I'm just happy you are back.
Partner.
Please tell me you can
fix this mess.
I will undo
what has been done.
Let's never do that again.
Okay?
The strange thing is that
no matter what his flaws,
deep down I blame myself
for not being there for him.
You! You were working
on this story.
Had a lead on it before
anyone else even knew.
- That's correct.
- Good. Alright you're getting on camera!
I want you to give an in-depth report
for CNM tonight, prime time.
And make sure you close with:
"Roger Clifford pledges to undo
all the harm his father caused,
starting with the Pokémon
he experimented on."
I can't believe we did it.
- Psyduck!
- Great work!
Hey calm down.
Stay calm.
I hope we never get
to see each other again.
- Meet me later tonight?
- Cool.
I mean, yeah!
- Come on.
- Psyduck, Psyduck, Psyduck.
Way to go, Tim!
There is one last
thing I must fix.
My father!
The father you have been looking
for has been with you all along.
What's he talking about?
I don't...
You've done well.
Humanity is evil!
But you have shown me...
that not all humans are bad.
Harry Goodman,
your Pikachu offers it's
body to save your mind.
There is a son.
With the son's return,
I can repair the father.
Your memory will be gone,
but your heart will know who you are.
I take this body so
that you might live.
Return with the son!
Hey, kid!
Grams will meet you
when you arrive.
Okay.
See ya.
Hey dad...
Yeah?
You think I can stay
with you for a while?
I'd like that, kid.
Yeah I'd like that very much.
Me too!
- You wanna get a coffee?
- It's the weirdest thing.
It's all I've been thinking about
was having a coffee right now.
I think I'll have
to find a new job.
Oh yeah?
What are you thinking?
- Maybe I could give detective work a try?
- Pika-Pika.
I think he likes that idea.