Andrew!
No!
Thousands gathered
in the Bay Area last night
to honor the victims
of the 2014 attacks.
Part of a wave of memorials and protests
demanding that the secretive...
...monster-hunting coalition
known as Monarch be held accountable.
The recent spike in mass die-offs
in the world's oceans
could be caused by efforts to locate
and track Godzilla,
who hasn't been seen in over five years.
Top brass at the mysterious
Monarch organization
will face another intense grilling
as the government continues
to push for extermination of the Titans.
And rumors persist
that Monarch may be hiding
even more creatures discovered
since the attacks of 2014.
A historic tragedy that changed
the world as we know it forever.
The day the world discovered
that monsters are real.
Shit!
Shit, shit, shit!
- Oh...
- Maddie?
Good morning!
- Good morning, Mom!
- Oh, God!
- Uh...
- Okay.
I made us breakfast.
It's, uh...
eggs, toast, and what was once bacon.
And which do you recommend?
The toast and eggs.
Thank you.
Coffee?
What were you working on?
Um, I was looking at recipes.
For toast?
Dad's been emailing me.
But he looks good.
Healthy.
Have you responded?
Not yet.
Madison, I just
don't want to see you get hurt.
- I know.
- Especially with everything
- that's going on right now.
- Mom, I know.
Listen, I know
things haven't been easy for you.
But we're gonna get through this.
Together.
You sure he's gonna be okay?
He is in the safest place
that he could be right now.
You wanna hear some good news?
I finished it.
Really?
You think it's gonna work?
It's gonna work.
It's gonna be okay.
Dr. Russell,
we need you in Containment.
I'm on my way.
- What the hell happened?
- No idea.
She was sleeping like a baby
until an hour ago, and then, boom.
Her radiation levels
went through the roof.
Almost like something triggered it.
Thanks, Tim. You know,
I can take it from here.
Why don't you get some rest?
No way. Sleep or no sleep,
I'm not missing this.
Containment Team,
move into primary position.
- Sedatives?
- No effect.
This thing wants to be born.
Emergency protocol is in effect.
Ten seconds to biocontainment.
Her time has come.
Meet Titanus mosura.
Or as we like to call her...
Mothra.
Incredible.
Activating containment grid.
- Warning.
- What's happening?
- Something's really wrong here.
Containment systems are failing.
Perimeter alarms are going off,
the whole network's going insane.
What do you mean?
How is that possible?
Emma, I think
someone else is doing this.
Containment Team, stand down.
I repeat, stand down.
You are scaring her.
- No!
- Dr. Russell, I'm sorry.
But you know the protocols.
We have to terminate!
I'll handle this.
Mom! No!
Madison, stay here. It's gonna work.
Stand clear.
It's okay.
Mom!
Maddie, wait!
Maddie!
Get back in here!
Maddie! Go back!
Mom! Let's go!
Mom!
Son of a bitch.
It worked.
Mom?
What we are witnessing here, Senators,
is the return of an ancient
and forgotten super species.
Godzilla, the MUTOs, Kong.
We believe that these "Titans"
and others like them
provide an essential balance
to our world.
And while some may pose a threat,
Monarch is uniquely prepared
to determine
which of these Titans are here
to threaten us
and which of these Titans are here
to protect us.
Thank you for the fifth grade
history lesson, Mr. Coleman.
But we still haven't heard
one good reason
why Monarch shouldn't fall under
militaryjurisdiction.
Or why these creatures
shouldn't be exterminated.
Monarch was tasked
with finding and destroying
these radioactive monsters.
But you either can't or won't tell us
how many there are
or why they're showing up.
So, maybe it's time for the military
to put them down.
Killing them
would be a mistake.
They returned because of us.
It was our atomic testing
that awoke Gojira.
Other creatures like the MUTOs
from strip mining and seismic surveys.
But these are not monsters.
They are animals rising to reclaim
a world that was once theirs.
It almost sounds like
you're protecting them, Dr. Serizawa.
As if you admire them.
I admire all forms of life.
Senators, if we hope to survive,
we must find ways
to coexist with Titans.
With Gojira.
A sort of symbiotic relationship,
if you will.
Like the lion and the mouse.
Or the scorpion and the frog.
So you'd want to make Godzilla our pet?
No.
We will be his.
Uh... No. No, actually.
That's not what Dr. Serizawa meant.
- We have to go.
- No one is implying that we would be...
- Sam, we have to go.
- Godzilla's or anyone's pet.
Dr. Serizawa, Dr. Graham,
this hearing is not adjourned.
Dr. Serizawa, I hope you understand
the consequences
of walking out that door.
Uh, you know what, Senators,
while I confer with my colleagues here,
I'm gonna set you up with a very brief
and pretty fun documentary
on Titan reproduction.
I think this is the one
where the genitals are blurred out.
But if not, you can leave
a comment with my assistant.
The feed cuts out there.
The survivors haven't been able
to give us much more
than what the footage allows.
Only that Emma and Madison
were the only ones taken.
I'm sorry, Mark.
I should've been there for her.
- Who are they?
- We don't know yet.
We believe they were after this.
You didn't.
It's the ORCA.
That's why we think they need Emma.
She believed
that if we could somehow replicate
the biosonar the Titans use
to communicate...
I know what the hell it is.
I helped build the prototype.
Who is he?
Uh, Sam Coleman.
I'm the head of technology.
I joined Monarch,
uh, shortly after you left.
I'm a big fan of your wife's work.
And you.
That just came out so weird, I'm sorry.
Emma and I destroyed the prototype.
And then Emma decided to rebuild it.
After San Francisco, she went home
to Boston, spent years developing it.
She thought it could help...
Would help what? Play God?
No.
Help prevent another attack.
ORCA was a grad school science project.
It was meant to keep whales
away from the shoreline.
Not so you could talk
to your little creatures out there.
Listen to me,
they'll think it's one of them.
You use the wrong frequency
on one of 'em,
and you're gonna be responsible
for 1,000 San Franciscos.
Which is why we need to get it back.
Emma always said
no one knew the ORCA better than you.
It shouldn't even exist.
That may be, Mark.
But it's fallen into the wrong hands.
And right now,
the ORCA is the only thing
keeping Emma and Madison alive.
Mark, we know you're hurting.
But if we find the ORCA,
we'll find your family.
I promise.
When was the last time
you spoke to Emma?
About three years ago.
After San Francisco
we went back home to Boston.
Tried to put the pieces back together.
Emma dealt with it by doubling down
on saving the world
and I started drinking.
I can't tell you how much I hated myself
for letting Maddie see me that way.
Uh, you mind if we cut in here?
It's just, you're gonna wanna see this.
Emma combined the bioacoustics
of different Titans
to create the ORCA's signal.
A sort of baseline frequency
that all the creatures respond to.
Attracting them, repelling them,
even at times calming them down.
It's pretty remarkable actually.
The problem is
we don't know which Titans she combined.
But if you can identify
those frequencies,
we'll be able to track the ORCA
and find Emma and Madison.
Jesus!
How many of these things are there?
Seventeen and counting after Gojira.
Seventeen?
Most of them were discovered
in deep hibernation.
While others, we've contained
at top secret sites around the globe.
Cambodia, Mexico, Skull Island.
We even found one in Wyoming.
They're everywhere.
Why don't you kill 'em?
The government wants to.
But Emma and I believe
some are benevolent.
Don't kid yourself.
Uh... Hey, look at that. We're here.
Castle Bravo, this is Raptor One.
On direct approach.
Raptor One, you are cleared
for assisted descent to pad four.
Sensors set for three meters.
Beginning sub-surface descent.
This is new.
Yeah, we call it Castle Bravo.
Our new flagship facility,
built to track and study Godzilla
on his own turf.
I thought he was missing.
Well, only if you don't know
where to look.
As you know, at approximately 0700 hours
our containment site in China's
Yunnan Rainforest was raided.
The specimen, code name Mothra, escaped.
Only to cocoon itself later
under a nearby waterfall.
While Dr. Emma Russell and
her daughter Madison were taken hostage.
This is the man responsible, Alan Jonah.
A former British army colonel
turned ecoterrorist.
Obsessed with restoring natural order.
And to fund his operations,
he began trafficking
in a new and dangerous market.
Titan DNA.
What the hell is someone gonna do
with a giant worm?
Are you kidding, Martinez?
What can't you do with it?
Pharmaceuticals, bioweapons, food...
Hell, there isn't a country or a company
on the planet
that doesn't wanna get its hands
on one of these suckers.
And remember, this is just a larva.
That's a baby.
After it cocoons,
something else is gonna crawl out.
Something bigger, meaner...
- We don't know that, Rick.
- Oh, yeah?
Just wait for it, Chen.
Our intel indicates that Jonah
wants to capture this specimen.
Alive.
Which means that he and his mercs
won't be far behind.
At 0500, we'll ship out
to launch a joint operation...
I wouldn't bother.
Excuse me?
Sounds like a duck hunt to me.
Uh, Mark, why don't we let
Colonel Foster finish...
A decoy. A diversion.
Look, they've already got Emma
and the ORCA.
Why would they want just this one
when they've got the keys
to your entire magic kingdom
of horrors back here?
I think that they want you
to go after this Mothra,
so they can go after a real prize.
Something bigger.
Right.
Mark, this is not the first specimen
they've captured.
- They know what they are doing.
- That's not just a specimen.
I've got an ex-wife and a daughter
out there, in case you forgot.
No. No one has forgotten that, Mark,
but, uh, to remind you,
you were brought on here to help track
the ORCA, and to advise us...
I advise you to kill these things.
All of 'em.
Especially him.
You wanna make sure these things
don't fall into the wrong hands?
You kill them and the ORCA's useless.
Emma wouldn't have wanted that.
Even to save her life.
Well, it wouldn't be the first time
Emma put all of this before herself
or her family, would it?
Dude hates Titans.
Yeah, well, you would too,
if you were him.
Outpost 32,
this is Raptor Five,
on approach
with reinforcements and supplies.
Requesting permission to land.
Serizawa has all sites on high alert,
so transmitting emergency codes now.
Copy that, Raptor Five.
Codes are good. Nice to have you back.
Go.
It's good to see ya.
- Need a hand with offload?
- No, we're good!
We're gonna put it over
at bay five.
- Follow me!
- Go back up! Hey, hey!
Leave them, let's go!
I'm scared.
I know. Me, too.
Okay.
Let's go.
Eyes straight ahead.
Deep breaths.
Just like we talked about.
Hmm.
Mother of God.
She had nothing to do with this.
Monster Zero.
Any survivors?
No. They tried to launch
an emergency beacon,
but we cut them off in time.
They'll figure it out.
Fire up the drills.
Do you have everything you need?
Good.
Well, let's get started.
Further.
We have a grizzly situation
up here in the attic.
Come on, Andrew. Andrew.
- I've come to eat your horses.
- No, you can't eat my horses...
That's not...
Stop.
Look.
- An intruder! Get her!
- Get her!
- Get her! Get her!
- No, don't get me!
Andrew, Madison! Get her!
- Get her!
- Bear kisses.
Bear kisses!
All personnel,
report to battle stations. Code red.
report to battle stations.
- Code red.
- At least 60 knots.
This is not a drill. All personnel,
report to battle stations.
Code red.
What's happening?
Something's wrong.
He's never been this close before.
- Who's he?
- Who do you think?
He's taking out our observation drones.
Trajectory?
Straight at us!
1,200 meters and closing.
G-Team. Barnes, Martinez, Hendricks,
I want you on those CROWS now!
You heard boss lady! Let's move!
Dr. Stanton.
Do you have his bioacoustics?
Acoustics coming up!
Okay, he's closing. We're at 800 meters!
His movements are erratic.
Heart and breathing elevated.
Yeah, he's definitely not happy
about something.
How are they getting all this?
Emma isolated Godzilla's bioacoustics.
It allows us to track him.
Even to get his vitals.
Circling now, closing in, 200 meters.
Colonel!
All teams in position, weapons hot,
ready to engage on my command.
Come on, come on, come on.
Hold your fire.
We don't know he'll attack.
He will if you keep those guns on him.
Now I want him dead more than anybody,
but unless this is a fight that you know
that you can win,
for God's sake, stand down.
Stand down.
You can't be serious.
I am.
Stand down.
I say again, safe your weapons.
Do not engage.
Listen.
His heart rate, it's slowing.
Open the shields.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Let's bring him in for a beer.
You out of your goddamn mind?
Let him know we're not a threat.
Open the shields.
Do it.
Hey, what's with the light show?
It's an intimidation display.
Like a gorilla pounding his chest.
Consider us very
intimidated.
I don't think it's for us.
What are you doing, dude?
Well, that was interesting.
Jesus!
Can we maybe close the shield now?
Show me his territorial routes.
What? Why?
Because I wanna start a boat tour.
Just show me.
Okay. Coming up.
You care to tell us
what you're looking for?
When an animal leaves
its hunting ground,
it's usually because it's threatened
by something.
Run a course projection.
We gotta go after him.
He's looking for something out there.
It could be the ORCA.
Dr. Stanton, what's your projection?
All paths have him landing
in the same place.
Antarctica.
Good, then.
I mean, let's go!
Let's go find him. Let's...
Wait, what's in Antarctica?
Barnes, contact the Argo.
Yes, ma'am.
The specimen at this site
has been kept entirely off-book.
And since it's a more recent discovery,
our data is limited.
But it seems to be
another apex predator.
Emma called it Monster Zero.
It may have been
a rival alpha to Godzilla.
Battling for dominance
over the other Titans.
Dr. Chen?
I've been scouring
through thousands of years
of myths and legends.
But it's almost as if people were scared
to even write about it.
As if it was meant to be forgotten.
Sorry, I hate to crash a party,
but I got some bad news.
You could just say news.
It's always bad.
We lost Godzilla.
He dropped off the scan near Venezuela.
Dropped off?
I'm telling you, Dr. Brooks was right.
It's a Hollow Earth.
That's how he moves around so fast,
using these underwater tunnels
like wormholes.
- Just like, zippin' around.
- Everyone look sharp.
We're approaching the base.
- They're here.
- Keep 'em busy.
Launch reaction force. Move out!
All right, gents!
Got the green light!
Go! Right there, right there.
Nine o'clock. And cross!
And you, go down!
If Jonah is looking
to extract genetic samples,
they'll be here in the bio labs.
All right, two minutes.
Check your equipment, stand by the door.
Come on, Ash. Make it snappy.
- Detonator ready.
- Let's go.
Come on, Maddie.
Move! Move!
Remember, eyes wide.
We got friendlies in here.
Move to tunnel two.
Stay on overwatch.
Roger that, Chief.
Ambush! Ambush!
Team under fire! 360 ambush!
We're taking heavy losses.
Break right!
Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
We got friendlies!
No!
Mark?
Get down there and help Barnes.
I'm going after him.
Roger that.
Hey, guys. I'm getting an EKG reading.
Emma?
Maddie!
Number one, let's go.
Barnes, this is Foster.
I've got eyes on the target.
Repeat, eyes on the target.
Let 'em go!
- Ash!
- Dad!
- Mark.
- Emma, Madison, let's go.
Dad.
- Let's go. Emma, Maddie, come on.
- Daddy?
Madison, walk to me.
Walk to me now. Come on, honey.
Barnes, I've got two hostages,
one target down.
- Now! Come on, Maddie.
- I do not have a shot.
Repeat, I do not have a shot.
Emma, what are you doing?
Let's go. Come on!
- Dad.
- Maddie.
Dad.
Madison.
What the hell?
I'm sorry.
Run.
Maddie!
Dad!
Move, move!
- Foster!
- Get out of the way!
Hang in there. Jam the doors!
- Let's go!
- Hang on! Move!
Hendricks, on the double!
- I got you, Colonel!
- Get her legs!
We gotta go!
Damn it!
Martinez, Foster, let's go!
Move, move! Now!
Okay, let's go!
No checklist this time.
- Right.
- We're up.
- What is Dad doing here?
- I don't know, honey.
Let's go.
We can't leave him.
What are you waiting for?
Wake it up.
Launch is up ahead!
Let's go! Move it!
Keep going!
Go, go, go!
You gotta be fucking kidding.
Fall back! Fall back!
Get to the chopper!
Go, go, go!
Keep it going!
Come on!
Hurry up, men!
Open fire!
Get in!
We'll do an emergency
vertical take-off at max RPM.
Number two's still spinning up.
Oh, shit.
This is Raptor One to Argo.
Requesting immediate urgent extract.
Again, I say urgent extract.
Griffin, get us the hell out of here!
Madison!
Madison, no!
- You need to let go of it!
- No! No! No!
- Madison!
- Maddie! Let go!
No!
Argo, this is Raptor One.
We've been hit. All systems are down.
Look out!
Everybody, hold on!
Mark!
Everybody, clear out. Let's go!
Go! Go!
- Mark!
- I'm stuck.
Are you all right?
I got it! I got it. Go, go!
Anything on the satellites?
Subs have Godzilla
hauling ass off Argentina.
We lost Monster Zero
in a tropical storm over Brazil.
Scanning the entire Southern Hemisphere.
So far, nothing.
- Then scan the Northern.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know what I saw, Sam.
And I'm telling you,
she pulled that trigger.
All due respect, Colonel, you saw wrong.
Okay? She wouldn't have done it.
Christ, she recruited
pretty much everyone in this room.
Maybe Jonah forced her, right?
Maybe he used Madison as leverage.
No, no. It had to be someone else.
Emma.
It was Emma.
Foster saw it right.
It was her. No one forced her to.
Are you sure?
First, she releases Mothra.
And now Monster Zero.
Anyone else sensing a pattern here?
Yes, and not a good one.
It's as if she is trying
to start a mass awakening.
Well, it's just too bad
that no one tried
to warn you that that was gonna happen.
Hang on, guys. Why the hell
would she want to release them?
And why would she team up with Jonah,
of all people, to do it?
We'll ask her
when we find her.
So, let's keep looking.
Godzilla appears
to be following
the same path as Emma's osprey,
heading north
over South America to here.
Outpost 56 in Isla de Mara, Mexico.
We touch down there in 10 minutes.
What about the people?
I'm sorry?
The people. The people
down there in that village
that don't realize they're gonna be
the special of the day.
We've sent G-Team
to begin an evacuation.
Dr. Serizawa,
we have a call on the emergency channel
from Isla de Mara.
Answer it.
I suppose I should go first.
Where's Madison?
- She's right here with me.
- Dad, are you okay?
Madison, you all right, hon?
Dad...
I'm sorry.
You don't need to be...
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry, Dad.
She's fine, Mark, trust me.
Trust is a little hard
to come by, Dr. Russell.
Especially after what you pulled.
I know.
And I can only imagine
what you're all thinking.
But if there were any other way
to do this, I would.
Do what, Emma?
I'm saving the world.
But by releasing those things?
That doesn't make sense.
As impossible as it seems, it does.
Hear me out, Mark.
After we lost Andrew, I swore his death
would not be in vain.
That I would find an answer. A solution
to why the Titans were rising.
But as I dug deeper, I realized
that they were here for a reason.
And that despite all the years
that we spent trying to stop them,
we never dared to confront the truth.
Which truth?
Humans have been the dominant species
for thousands of years,
and look what's happened.
Overpopulation,
pollution, war.
The mass extinction we feared
has already begun.
And we are the cause.
We are the infection.
But like all living organisms,
the Earth unleashed a fever
to fight this infection.
Its original and rightful rulers,
the Titans.
They are part
of the Earth's natural defense system.
A way to protect the planet,
to maintain its balance.
But if governments are allowed
to contain them, destroy them,
or use them for war,
the human infection
will only continue to spread.
And within our lifetime,
our planet will perish,
and so will we.
Unless we restore balance.
And what's gonna be left,
if you do this?
A dead, charred world,
overrun by monsters?
No, Dr. Stanton, the exact opposite.
Just like how a forest fire
replenishes the soil,
or how a volcano creates new land,
we have seen signs that these creatures
will do the same.
San Francisco, Las Vegas,
wherever the Titans go,
life follows,
triggered by their radiation.
They are the only thing that can reverse
the destruction that we started.
They are the only guarantee
that life will carry on.
But for that to happen,
we must set them free.
You are murdering the world.
No.
Because as difficult as this will be,
I promise humanity will not go extinct.
Using the ORCA,
we will return to a natural order.
A forgotten order, where we coexisted
in balance with the Titans.
The first gods.
This is a dangerous path.
You are meddling with forces
beyond our comprehension.
Gambling with the lives of billions!
And what are you
gambling with, Serizawa?
Monarch is broken.
It's on the verge of being shut down
by a government
whose only objective
is to eradicate the creatures.
And if that happens,
what will our chances be?
You are out of your goddamn mind!
First, you put
our daughter's life in danger
and now you get to decide the fate
of the world. That's rich, Emma!
I couldn't be more sane,
and Madison couldn't be stronger.
After we lost Andrew,
I trained her to survive.
And at least now,
she will have a fighting chance.
A fighting chance?
Why don't you listen to yourself?
It's not all math, Emma.
Some things, you can't control.
And there are some things
that you can't run from.
This won't bring him back to us.
I can only urge you all to take refuge.
Over the last 60 years, Monarch has
prepared bunkers around the world
to save and restart civilization.
I suggest you find them.
That bitch.
How long until this thing lands?
Three minutes.
You might want to rethink that.
Why?
Something's not right. Check this out.
Emma's not at Isla de Mara. I mean,
the signal's too weak to be local.
She's bouncing it off our satellites.
They must be holed up
in one of our old bunkers.
She could be anywhere.
What is that?
Oh, Jesus! She shut down
the containment system.
How much time do we have?
Containment system bypassed.
We're patched in.
- Hmm.
- Ready to broadcast the ORCA.
Doctor?
Mom, don't!
I'm sorry, did a child just tell you
what to do?
Maybe Dad is right.
Maybe this isn't the way.
By all means, Dr. Russell,
let's reconsider our entire plan.
Especially after telling
your friends about it.
Madison, we talked about this.
No, you said you were gonna help people,
that you would let them find shelter...
We don't have time for this!
Did you really think
this was gonna be easy?
Painless? Is that what you told her?
- Leave her out of this.
- Why?
You're the one who pulled her into it.
Madison, tell me, what exactly
did Mommy sell you on?
Some grand utopia?
Man and monster,
living together in blissful harmony?
Sir,
they're attempting to lock us out.
It's now or never.
Emma, you came to me. This is your plan.
We both want to save the planet,
but everything is going to die
if we don't see it through.
Please, at least let them get to safety.
Ma'am, our window's closing.
Mom...
I'm sorry, Madison.
This is bigger than just you and me.
Tell them to slow it down.
Tell them to stand back!
Move! Get out of the way!
Clear, men!
You got a catchy name for this one?
Local legends call it
Rodan, the fire demon.
That's comforting.
Guys?
You remember that tropical storm
where we lost Monster Zero?
It's changing direction,
and, uh, guess where it's headed now.
That's not possible.
No storm moves that fast.
Unless it's not a storm.
- Oh, man!
- We need time to finish the evacuation.
Well, then you'd better hurry,
'cause it's closing in fast.
Serizawa, it's not a coincidence
that Monster Zero thing is headed here.
It's reacting to Big Bird's cries.
That means it's coming
for food, a fight, or...
...something more intimate.
What do you suggest?
All fighters, weapons free.
Oh, I think we got his attention.
Everyone, strap in.
All ships, follow our lead.
No!
Please! Wait!
It's gonna be okay!
Hang on, kid!
No! Mama!
Argo to Gold Squadron.
Let's lure this turkey away
from the mainland
straight to Monster Zero.
ETA two minutes!
Gold Squadron, engage on our six.
Copy. Start the clock.
Bogey. Nine o'clock high!
Duster 223.
Get out of there. He's on your tail.
Get out of there!
Cobra's Raptor is off the team!
ETA to Monster Zero, 60 seconds!
Raptor 37.
Bogey coming up on your six.
I'm losing control here.
I'm losing control!
We lost the squadron!
ETA to Monster Zero, 30 seconds!
Ten seconds!
Dive! Dive!
Jesus, they're killing each other.
Mayday, mayday!
This is Raptor One to Argo.
Argo, do you read?
Copy, Raptor One.
What's your status?
We're screwed, that's what.
And we got kids on board.
We're gonna need
immediate mid-air retrieval.
Lock on to their position, and prepare
the hangar for an emergency landing.
- Hangar doors are unresponsive.
- Manual override?
They're stuck!
- All right, which way to the hangar?
- I can show you.
Anybody else?
I know the way. Come on.
Hope you got a big wrench.
- What's the problem?
- Hydraulics systems are jammed!
I'm trying to jump-start power.
It's not looking good.
It's Admiral Stenz.
- Admiral.
- Dr. Serizawa,
Colonel Foster. I need you
and your forces to immediately disengage
and withdraw to a safe distance.
Admiral, I don't understand.
We have been developing a prototype
for a new weapon. An oxygen destroyer.
Designed to exterminate all life forms
within a two-mile radius.
With any luck, it will kill these things
and this nightmare will finally be over.
Admiral, we must keep
our faith in Gojira.
I'm sorry, Doctor. You had your chance.
The missile is already on its way.
May God have mercy on us all.
He's not lying.
It's coming in hot.
Argo, you gotta get
those bay doors open now!
Have the crash and fire crews ready.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Look out!
Hold on!
Come on, Griff! Come on!
Hit it! Hit it!
That's what
I'm talking about, Griff!
Everybody okay?
Get over
to the back of the hangar.
We're all gonna head this way.
This way. This way.
Thanks for the lift!
Go! Go!
Oh, God!
We're getting out of here.
The military launched a weapon.
It's gonna kill 'em both.
Well, that's not the worst idea.
Ten...
nine...
eight...
seven...
Three, two...
Jesus.
Dr. Stanton, can you locate Gojira?
Yeah. I got something.
His vitals are fading.
Radiation levels plummeting.
Come on, big guy. Fight it.
He's gone.
Looks like you got your wish, Mark.
I thought we were going
to release them gradually.
One at a time.
I'm not the one doing this.
Long live the king.
You're a monster.
Castle Bravo,
this is Containment Team Mosura.
Do you read? Over.
- Castle Bravo, this is Containment Team.
- Anything?
Dr. Brooks.
We've lost contact with the Argo,
Castle Bravo
and the other containment sites.
Angkor Wat, Skull Island,
Stone Mountain.
All the Titans, they're escaping.
Repeat, this may be our last comm.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's him.
He's the one doing this.
They're responding to his call.
Oh, God!
Where's Dr. Ling?
She's outside.
Dr. Ling!
We've lost contact with Monarch.
Dr. Ling?
- Madison, wait!
- Get away from me!
Look, I know things haven't gone exactly
according to plan, but I can fix this.
According to plan?
You said that you were gonna be careful.
That you'd release them one at a time,
that you would restore balance!
They were gonna take over Monarch
and kill the Titans.
I didn't have a choice.
Bullshit!
You said we were doing this for Andrew.
Do you really think
he would've wanted this?
Exactly.
Madison!
Any luck?
No.
Whatever Emma used to create
the ORCA signal, I've never heard it.
How are you doing?
How's that?
"Myth is our compass."
It's something my mom used to say.
She believed our stories
about monsters and dragons
could help us find the Titans
and restore our connection to nature.
Wait, your mother?
You're second-generation Monarch?
Third.
It runs in the family.
That's incredible.
I don't suppose your family has any tips
on slaying dragons, do they?
Slaying dragons is a Western concept.
In the East, they are sacred.
Divine creatures who brought
wisdom, strength...
even redemption.
This oxygen destroyer,
why wasn't Monster Zero affected?
I mean, I'm no scientist,
but I think it has something to do
with his goddamn head growing back.
Well, I've never seen anything like it.
It violates everything we know
about the natural order.
Unless he's not part
of the natural order.
What do you mean?
I was able to piece this together.
Well, he looks vaguely familiar.
It tells of a great dragon
who fell from the stars.
A Hydra whose storm swallowed
both men and gods alike.
What, you mean an alien?
Yes.
He's not part of our natural order.
And he's not meant to be here.
A false king.
An invasive species.
That could explain how he's creating
these massive storms
and the effect he's having
on the other Titans.
It's almost like he's reshaping
the planet to his own liking.
These legends, what did they call him?
Ghidorah. "The one who is many."
- Ghi-what?
- She's saying it's like gonorrhea.
- Huh?
- Ghidorah!
Dr. Serizawa,
we're approaching Castle Bravo...
but there's something you should see.
I'm guessing
you weren't expecting these guys.
Moscow, London, Washington, D.C.,
all under attack.
On every continent,
the Titans are triggering
earthquakes, wildfires, tsunamis
and disasters we don't even
have names for yet.
Now as before, we have been trying
to lure the creatures
with nuclear materials,
but they are not taking
the bait this time.
Their behavior has become random.
Erratic.
And with our forces
spread desperately thin
and these things
roaming the globe unimpeded
we are running out of options...
and time.
Excuse me, do you have something to add?
Yeah. You're wrong.
Their behavior is not random or erratic.
If I may, sir.
As amazing as this sounds,
they're moving like a pack.
They're hunting.
All packs, from wolves to killer whales,
they all respond directly to an alpha.
And this Ghidorah is the new alpha.
And all the other creatures
are just doing his bidding.
They're an extension of him.
We stop him, we stop them all.
Is there another creature
that might stand a chance against him?
No.
Ghidorah and Gojira's rivalry
was ancient and unique.
Right, so we killed our best shot
at beating this thing?
Jonah, you don't get it.
This changes everything.
With Godzilla gone,
Monster Zero isn't using the Titans
to restore the planet.
He is using them to destroy it.
This isn't coexistence.
This is extinction.
Listen, while you
were sitting comfortably
in some laboratory,
we've been fighting for decades
in one dirty war after another.
I've seen human nature firsthand,
and I'm here to tell you
that it doesn't get any better.
It just gets worse.
So, I'm sorry that Monster Zero
isn't exactly what we were expecting.
But we opened Pandora's Box
and there's no closing it now.
- Maybe there is.
- Oh, don't be stupid.
You broadcast again,
and you will expose us all.
These creatures communicate
like whales, okay?
They can hear sonar
for thousands of miles,
so let's send a team.
Let's broadcast the ORCA from Fenway.
It's just a few miles from here.
I could use the stadium to amplify
a signal that might stop these attacks.
The city's already being evacuated,
so it'll be safe.
And then what?
And then I'll figure out
what the hell Monster Zero
really is and try to stop it.
Before Monarch finds us?
I'm sure all your friends will be
very happy to see you again.
We can'tjust sit here.
All right?
This isn't the world that we wanted.
I seem to remember
you telling me
that the world always belonged to them.
Well, maybe it is time we give it back.
Mark!
Mark, wait.
What are you doing?
I can't just sit down there.
I gotta do something.
Like what?
- Like go find my daughter.
- How?
Where are you gonna go?
She's the only thing I got left, Sam.
I wasn't there for her.
I'm not gonna let that happen again.
Good luck.
Beautiful.
Mothra.
Queen of the Monsters.
Are you recording this, Stanton?
I record everything now.
Everything.
It's like a song.
I bet there's only one thing
that can understand this.
Godzilla.
Yeah, I got it.
Picking up a reply. Bringing it up.
He's still alive.
So, her and Godzilla...
They got a thing going on?
That's kind of messed up, right?
Symbiotic relationships
between two different species
aren't all that uncommon.
Can you track him?
No. Signal's too weak.
But maybe she can.
How many nukes do you have?
Why?
We could help him.
This category six hurricane over D.C.
is where King Ghidorah is nesting.
Working with all four branches
of the military,
this will be a joint operation
to lure it away from the mainland,
so that we can continue evacuations
long enough
for our submersible team
to complete its mission.
So this plan is what you would call
a "long shot," right?
What do those nerds think they're gonna
do down there with a bunch of nukes?
You ain't hear 'em, Griffin?
They wanna bring Godzilla
back from the dead.
We'll be out of range
while you're down there,
but a squadron will stay behind
to keep an eye out for you.
- Appreciate it.
- All righty, Bowman,
let's take her down.
Dive the ship.
Make depth 150.
Good luck.
Thanks, Sam. We'll need it.
What time is it?
Time to get a new watch.
Andrew's favorite joke.
You never took that watch out of your
pocket without him asking that question.
You told me five years ago,
I'd be trying to save the thing
that took my son,
that would be the only way
to save the family I have left, I'd...
Sometimes...
the only way to heal our wounds
is to make peace
with the demons who created them.
You really believe that?
Don't you?
Isn't that why you are here?
There are some things
beyond our understanding, Mark.
We must accept them and learn from them
because these moments of crisis
are also potential moments of faith.
A time
when we either come together
or fall apart.
Nature always has a way
of balancing itself.
The only question is...
what part will we play?
Did you just make that up?
No.
I read it in a fortune cookie once.
A really long fortune cookie.
- Status of the ship?
- Some sort of vortex, Captain.
It's dragging us.
1,600 feet till impact.
800 feet.
Emergency blow! 200 feet!
One hundred!
Twenty-five!
Brace for impact!
Argo, this is USS Brody
en route to evacuation perimeter.
Weapons hot.
Ready to engage Titans on your command.
Jesus.
It's like the whole sky's alive.
That's because it is.
Here we go.
Status report.
Can't fix our position. GPS is down.
But inertial says we're
600 miles from departure.
That can't be.
I knew it, man!
The vortex was a tunnel
into the Hollow Earth.
It's a subterranean tunnel system
that connects the entire planet.
It doesn't matter. I knew I was right.
I told you, Chen!
Shut up, Rick.
One second emergency blow forward.
Doctor?
Launch probes.
Range 1,000 meters.
Camera good.
Holding range. Steady.
Jesus.
Pan right.
Looks Egyptian.
- Or Roman.
- No, this is something different.
This is way older.
Oh, my.
All of the legends...
the stories...
they are true.
They really were the first gods.
If only the earth and stones
could speak,
the stories they could tell us.
Dr. Stanton,
any sign of Gojira?
Yeah, the probe is picking up
a radioactive blob
just past that ridge.
Set a course.
Attention, please.
Martial law has now been instated
by order of the President.
The greater Boston area is now
under control of the US Military.
All citizens to report to the nearest
evacuation center
for immediate transport.
I repeat, all citizens are to report
to the nearest evacuation...
Massive storms and
other disasters triggered by the Titans
have forced millions
to flee major cities.
And with D. C. hit hard
by a category six hurricane
that has left the capital
completely flooded,
this is the single greatest disaster
in human history.
The grim search continues,
as people around the world
sift through the debris of leveled homes
in the hope of finding
missing loved ones.
And though this sight is heartbreaking,
it is unfortunately nothing unique.
Cities around the globe have fallen
under the wake of what many are calling
"The Rise of the Titans."
I think we should stop.
Why?
'Cause I still wanna have kids
one day.
Preferably without flippers.
All stop.
Hover the ship.
Whoa.
We got O2, CO2, and methane.
It looks like there's
some sort of air pocket in there.
- My God.
- Zilla.
- And good night, Gracie.
- Pull up the last frame.
- Yup.
- There.
The source of the radiation.
That's why he returned here.
He's feeding...
regenerating.
This is his home.
This is how he's survived for so long.
Always adapting, evolving.
- It's incredible.
- So...
dude's got this covered.
Right? He just needs a little nap.
No.
This process could take years.
We have to proceed as planned.
Hang on.
We're gonna launch a nuclear torpedo
in order to revive a giant monster.
Okay, this is not like
we're just jump-starting a car.
We have another complication.
Our weapons systems were damaged
during the crash.
- We can't launch.
- Can it be repaired?
I'm afraid not.
Okay.
What if we go inside, set a timer,
and blow up the warhead manually?
No way. If the heat doesn't fry you,
the radiation will.
I'll go.
What the hell does that mean?
- There must be another way.
- There's no time for debate.
I'll go.
Argo, we are red on ammo
and low on fuel.
We can't take much more of this!
Copy, copy.
Just hold them off as long as you can.
Colonel, take a look at this.
All the Titans have stopped.
What the hell has gotten into them now?
It does appear as if
the attacks have ceased
for the time being
with the creatures going
from destructive to docile
within minutes.
Now, no one is sure how or why,
but this seems to be happening
simultaneously around the world.
What's going on?
The ORCA.
What?
I wonder who could have done this.
Maddie?
Maddie.
First contact, you're gonna
start losing your long-range vision.
When you surface,
your motor skills
are gonna start to fade,
but I put a helioxed mixture in the tank
which should help you
stay stable a little longer.
It was an honor, man.
Thank you.
My notes.
Are you sure?
He fought for us, died for us.
He's not only proof
that coexistence is possible...
he is the key to it.
Take care of them, Mark.
Bowman, take us out, fast.
Aye, Captain.
He's clear.
You all right?
Bowman, send a distress message
to the Argo.
Aye, Captain.
See anything?
Nobody move!
Are you okay?
I know how to find 'em.
I know how to find 'em!
Let's make him proud
and not screw this up.
- How did he, uh...
- By saving us.
Sam, what've we got going on?
We think Emma activated the ORCA
somewhere near Boston.
That's why Ghidorah and Godzilla
are both headed that way now.
But we haven't been able to pinpoint
the exact location
without the missing piece
of the ORCA signal.
I've got the missing piece.
It's Godzilla, right?
- I know we already tried.
- It's not Godzilla.
- It's us.
- What do you mean "us"?
Emma combined the bioacoustics
of Godzilla with a human.
That's how she made
the signal for the ORCA.
The creatures just think
it's another apex predator.
Well, that makes sense.
I mean, we are a bunch of
horny murderous carnivores.
Yeah, that's real poetic. Now what?
We track it, we find it,
and we get my daughter back.
What about Moe, Larry,
and Curly over here?
Godzilla will bring balance.
Oh, I get it.
A little Serizawa let-'em-fight action.
I used to love it when he said that.
No. This time, we join the fight.
What do you think you're doing?
I don't have time
to argue about this, Jonah.
- I'm getting Maddie back.
- Not with my men, you're not.
Emma, you said this was about
the greater good.
That the planet deserved a clean slate.
But now you're prepared
to put all our lives in danger
because your little girl is missing.
- The ORCA is with...
- The ORCA no longer matters.
Man does not control the laws of nature.
And neither do you.
I already lost one child...
I'm not losing another.
I have to fix this.
Let her go.
We have everything we need.
Oh, shit!
Okay, we've zeroed in
on the last ping from the ORCA.
Fenway Park, dead ahead.
We'll lay cover fire
to keep Ghidorah distracted.
Copy that.
Colonel, all squadrons
are locked on target.
For Serizawa.
Is it just me
or has he been working out?
Are you kidding me?
- Serizawa's got that lizard juiced!
- Damn right.
Oh, boy. Godzilla's radiation levels
are going through the roof.
We got about 12 minutes
before he goes thermonuclear.
What do you mean?
I'm sayin' in about 12 minutes
it's gonna be a bad day
to be a Red Sox fan.
Okay, guys,
you need to find the ORCA,
get Madison,
and get the hell out of there.
Whatever Serizawa did to Godzilla
worked a little too well.
'Cause he's about to explode
like an atom bomb.
Roger that. Prepare for landing.
Go, go, go!
Spread out!
Flank left!
On me!
Eyes up!
You two, over there!
Madison!
I got something! Over here.
Come check this out!
Are you all right?
I found the ORCA, sir,
it looks pretty banged up!
No sign of your daughter.
She's not here!
We gotta get out of here!
Let's go!
Get in!
Incoming!
- Get in!
- Griffin, you all right?
Martinez, let's get her up.
- Where's Madison?
- I don't know. I thought she was there!
Well, she's not there!
Take it easy!
- Get that side.
- Okay, okay.
Look out!
I hope you're as good at finding her
as you are losing her.
I didn't lose her, she ran away.
- Well, gee, I wonder why!
- I can't blame that kid.
If I had these two for parents,
I'd have run away from home, too.
What did you just say?
"If I had the two of you for parents,
I'd run away from home, too."
Home.
Godzilla's radiation's
reaching critical mass.
Six minutes until he blows.
Order all remaining craft to retreat!
Maddie!
Madison!
Emma!
Maddie!
Martinez!
We got it. On three.
One, two, three...
Lift together.
Oh, my baby.
Is she breathing?
Mark, is she breathing?
Maddie.
Mom.
- Dad.
- Shh.
- Mom.
- We're here.
Roger that.
Osprey's coming in two minutes.
- We gotta work fast.
- To do what?
You sure about this?
It's the only way to save him.
We fix it, get on the osprey
and draw that thing away from Godzilla.
Buy him time to get back on his feet.
Mark, you've seen
what that thing can do.
I know. It'll be tight,
but we have to take that chance.
Are you good to go?
- Yes.
- All right. One, two...
three.
That's it. That's it!
Come on, Griff. We got you.
Come on, Emma. Let's go.
Okay. Take her. Take her!
I still have to activate it.
- What?
- I'm right behind you. Go!
Let's go, let's go!
Mom!
Come on, Maddie!
Go, go, go!
You got any pain anywhere
besides your leg?
- We gotta lift off, now!
- Wait!
Emma, let's go! Come on!
Mom!
Mom.
I love you.
No.
- No!
- Emma!
Mom!
No.
Long live... the king.
Jesus.
Good thing he's on our side.
For now.
Look.
It's a brave new world, my friend.
Such things as this...
become much more valuable
since the rise of the king.
My men, they don't ask for much.
Can't fish here anymore.
Everything's dead.
We'll take it.