You'll float, too!
I saw all of us.
All of us were there.
Back in the cistern.
But we were older.
We were our parents' ages.
Am I still handsome as an adult?
You grow into your looks.
What the fuck does that mean?
What about me?
Like now...
but taller.
Swear it.
Swear if It isn't dead...
if It ever comes back...
we'll come back, too.
Memory...
it's a funny thing.
People want to believe they are
what they choose to remember.
The good stuff.
The moments.
The places.
The people we all hold on to.
But sometimes...
...sometimes...
we are what we wish we could forget.
Okay, kids.
Get ready.
Go!
Who's it gonna be? First one to pop
their balloon's a winner!
It could be anyone!
We got a real barn burner here, folks.
Come on. Come on.
It's getting close.
Who's gonna catch the leader, huh?
Who's gonna be the big winner tonight?
- Oh, yeah!
- Whoo!
Winner, winner, chicken dinner.
- Thank you.
- Wow.
You really showed 'em, huh?
I did. I...
Yeah.
Hey, girl, do you want this?
Thanks for letting me win.
Yeah.
- What'd you get, Vicky?
- Aw. Such a gentleman.
Look at that!
Here is your consolation prize.
Look at that.
Never been a fan of the beaver...
but, um, look at this hat.
I mean...
Thank you.
So, we need to talk logistics.
Ooh. How romantic.
Romantic?
What's so fucking romantic, huh?
Hey.
Your mommas ever teach you boys
to respond to someone...
when they ask you a fucking question?
Come on, Adrian.
You got a problem, faggot?
I don't, but Meg Ryan called.
She wants her wig back.
All right. All right.
Come on.
Come on, Adrian.
Stuff like that is why
I have to leave this shithole town.
Small minds.
They have small dicks.
I'm being serious.
We belong elsewhere.
Hey, look,
if you end up hating New York...
we can always move back here.
I just want to be with you.
I don't care. New York, Derry, whatever.
You have to say that.
I don't have to say anything.
Take off that fucking hat.
- Oh, God.
- Come on, let's go.
Wouldn't want to give people
the impression...
we allow a bunch of fucking fairies
like you in this town.
Yeah, he was born here, asshole.
- All right, let's go.
- No. You know what?
I'll take off the hat for you.
But why leave it there?
Anything else you would like me
to take off for you tonight?
Any special requests, ladies?
Fucker!
Let him go!
What's that?
- Stop.
- I don't think you'll be needing that.
- Leave him alone!
- Hit him.
He's got asthma, fucker!
Come on!
Fuck him up!
Come on, kick him!
- Come on, kick the shit out of him.
- Adrian!
I still hate your fucking hair.
Adrian!
Get the fuck off him!
Look what you did to his fucking face!
Hey! Hey! Help me get him up.
Adrian.
Help me get this fucking punk up
right now.
Give me the hat, Chris.
It's fucking mine!
I said, give me the fucking hat!
Adrian!
You like that?
Welcome to Derry, motherfucker.
No! Adrian!
No!
Let's get the fuck out of here.
- Let's go!
- No!
Adrian!
Help!
Help me!
Somebody!
Somebody fucking help me!
Adrian.
No!
Adrian!
We all float down here!
Thing is...
sometimes what we wish was forgotten...
what we tried to leave in the past...
...won't stay there.
Units, please respond.
I'm getting reports of a body
found dismembered.
Come back.
Was that "dismembered"?
That's affirmative.
Scene is near the south entrance
of the festival grounds.
Copy that. En route.
- Any directive for TC?
- That's affirmative.
Chief said to tape off
the Derry Street Bridge.
Sometimes, it comes back for you.
Ah.
Mr. Denbrough? They need you on set.
Good?
We're just going to go this way.
- I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
- No, don't!
Hey! Clear the door!
Oh, come on.
You've never seen Indiana Jones?
Watch your back.
Hey, hey. You a crewmember?
I'm the writer.
Your husband's here.
Hey! Do you have the pages?
Everyone, clear the crane.
My friend, a film needs an ending.
- You do know that, right?
- Oh, yeah.
You said that you needed another day
to finish the pages...
and we're shooting this thing.
It's tonight.
That's, like, 17 hours...
Everybody, calm down, okay?
I'm calm.
I want you to be happy with the movie.
You understand? I'm on your side.
That's great.
'Cause in my book, the ending...
Is terrible.
All due respect,
people loved your book. Loved.
They hated the ending.
You said you liked the ending.
That was a lie.
- We gotta do better, okay?
- Yeah.
Audra, you have my notes.
Would you...
Okay, thank you very much.
Take me back to one, please.
Bye.
You have his notes?
He's not wrong.
You hate my endings, too?
Not all your endings.
But this...
- Okay.
- Just...
What? Do you want me
to keep lying to you...
- just because I'm your wife?
- You're my wife?
No. No. But, you know, what?
You've been blowing smoke up my ass
for eight years?
I guess I thought you were someone else.
I have not been blowing
smoke up your ass.
Everybody wants a happy ending.
Everybody wants closure.
But that's not the way life works out.
I think what Peter wants
and what the studio wants...
The studio?
When'd you become a company man?
Jesus, you're an artist.
Come on. What's wrong with just doing it
the way it's written?
The way I wanted.
What's wrong with being the woman
I want you to be?
Fuck you, Bill.
On the page. The part, I mean. Not you.
Hello?
Bill Denbrough? It's Mike.
Mike who?
Mike Hanlon.
From Derry.
You need to come home.
Eddie, I keep
telling you not to scare me like this.
- And you never listen to me.
- All right. Myra, please. Not now.
You shouldn't be out there.
Eddie, it's not safe to drive
when the roads are slick like this.
Sweetheart, it stopped raining, like,
three hours ago.
All right? Everything is gonna be fine.
Hey, dickhead!
Flow of traffic mean anything to you?
What if you hydroplane?
I'm not gonna hydroplane.
It is my job to assess risk.
So, please trust me when I tell you...
that, statistically speaking, I am much
more likely to get into an accident...
because I am talking to you
on the phone!
All right? I have to go.
I will talk to you soon. Goodbye.
Edward Kaspbrak speaking.
You didn't say, "Okay, bye,
I love you," like you usually do.
Listen to me. I can't!
I'm going to be late to this...
...meeting.
Say "I love you," Eddie.
Okay, I love you, Mommy.
What?
Myra.
Bye.
Hello? Who's this?
It's me. Mike.
Mike who?
Eddie! You okay?
Yeah, I'm pretty good.
Dude, what the fuck?
You were fine, like, five seconds ago.
Who was it? Who called? Huh?
Rich? Rich? Talk to me.
You're on in two minutes.
You good?
'Cause you look not good.
- I'm fine.
- You're fine? Okay.
And we're walking. We're walking.
Sixty seconds.
Even faster. All right.
Can you get him
a bottle of water, maybe?
- Bourbon.
- Bourbon. Sure, sure.
And a mint.
It is showtime.
I don't think I can do this.
- It's what you do. You kill.
- That was fast.
You're a killer.
Okay. We are good to go, and...
Hey! Where we going? Where we going?
This way. Attaboy.
Okay.
All right. How do I look?
Your hands are shaking, Rich.
Shit.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Richie Tozier!
All right. How are we doing tonight?
So, my girlfriend caught me masturbating
to her friend's Facebook page.
And, uh, so now I'm in
Masturbators Anonymous.
And I stand up at the first meeting...
and I say,
"My name is Richie Trashmouth."
- Trashmouth.
- Shut up, Richie.
- Fucking perv.
Pussy!
Trashmouth. Uh...
Forgot the joke.
You suck!
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen,
for letting us present to you today.
Now, this will include
over a million square feet...
of commercial and residential space.
State-of-the-art office towers.
What I'm really looking for
is to understand...
how we create
even more retail opportunities.
If we put in walls here
and all along here...
Lose them.
With all due respect, Mr. Hanscom...
Ben, please.
And with all due respect to you...
I'm getting claustrophobic
just looking at this model. Aren't you?
Look. Throw up more walls,
it's gonna feel like a prison.
You know what people want to do
in prison?
Get out. Right?
This should be a place
that brings people together.
A meeting ground.
A clubhouse.
And if, while people are there...
Excuse me for one second.
- Hello?
- Ben?
It's Mike Hanlon. From Derry.
Should I just book it?
You're sure you can get away from work?
It's summer, why not?
Okay, we are Buenos Aires-bound.
Stanley Uris speaking.
It's Mike.
I'm sorry?
Mike Hanlon.
From Derry.
Mike.
God, sorry. Yes, hi.
I don't know why I didn't, um...
How long's it been?
A long time.
27 years.
It's come back, hasn't it?
That's why you're calling me?
It's starting again, Stan.
Bad things are happening.
Did you call the others?
I mean, what if they don't come?
We made a promise, remember?
How soon can you get here?
Um...
Yeah, I would need to do a few things...
Tomorrow.
We don't have much time.
I'll text you everything you need.
I'll see you soon, Stan the Man.
Do you swear?
I swear, Bill.
You made a promise, Beverly.
I'm so sorry, Mike.
I don't even really remember.
Haven't you ever wondered...
why you can't seem to remember
the things most people should...
about where they're from,
about who they are...
why you have that scar on your hand?
No one else remembered, either.
Eddie, Ben, Stan, Richie...
Bill.
You have to come back.
You all do.
When?
Whoa. Are you okay? What's going on?
It's the middle of the night.
You're packing?
I didn't want to wake you, honey.
I know this week's been
really exhausting.
I just got a phone call
from an old friend from Derry.
I have to go back there.
It's really hard to explain why.
It's okay.
You don't have to
explain yourself to me. Relax.
I trust you.
Thank you.
I just don't understand
why you'd lie to me.
I heard you.
You said the name Mike.
Yes, my friend.
See, there was a group of us
back then...
and we all made a promise to each other
when we were kids.
You know trust is everything
in a relationship.
You know it's everything to me, right?
I know. This isn't...
What? Like the last time?
I never cheated on you.
You're a bad fucking liar, Bev.
You're not going anywhere, okay?
I want you to stay right here...
and you're gonna show me
what it is you're gonna do with Mike.
Okay?
You're hurting me, honey.
No one else is gonna love you like me.
You know that, right?
I'm sorry.
- Don't make this fucking harder!
- Don't.
You're nothing without me!
You know that, right?
Tell me I'm wrong!
Jesus Christ.
Boys.
Little prick's got balls,
I'll give him that.
Far enough, Bowers!
I'm not done yet.
I'm not done. I'm not fucking done.
- On your knees.
- I can't. No!
I gotta kill them all!
Fuck, fuck!
Fucking kill them all!
Stop it!
- Cuff this sorry sack of shit!
- Fuck you!
Fuck you!
Henry Bowers,
I am placing you under arrest...
for the murder of Oscar Bowers.
Do you understand, dipshit?
You have the right to an attorney.
You have the right to remain silent.
Bowers!
Bowers, calm the fuck down!
Someone needs a little extra
clozapine today, don't they?
Stay in your fucking room.
Hockstetter.
My knife.
- Whoa.
- Careful.
This way.
Thanks a lot.
- Hey.
- Oh...
- Mike, you look good. Oh.
- Bill.
Hey. How you doing?
Bill.
I didn't know if any of you would...
- I mean, after all this time...
- Yeah.
But of course you came.
You know, an oath is an oath.
Losers...
gotta stick together, right?
The Losers.
You remember that. That's good.
What else do you remember?
I am allergic to soy,
anything that has egg in it, gluten...
and if I eat a cashew,
I could realistically die.
Holy shit.
Is there a password or something?
I'm sorry.
The new kid.
Ben?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's been so long.
Stay cool, Ben from soc class.
You, too, Beverly.
Hang tough,
new kid on the block.
Wow.
You two look amazing.
What the fuck happened to me?
- What's going on, man?
- Hey, man.
- It's Richie. Hi.
- Yeah. It's Ben.
- Hi.
- Hey.
This meeting of the Losers' Club
has officially begun.
Look at these guys.
Ben.
So, wait, Eddie, you got married?
Yeah, why's that
so fucking funny, dickwad?
What? To, like, a woman?
Fuck you, bro.
Fuck you!
What about you, Trashmouth?
You married?
There's no way Richie's married.
No, I got married.
- Richie, I don't believe it.
- When?
- Did you not hear this?
- No.
- You didn't know I got married?
Yeah, no. Me and your mom
are very, very happy right now.
Yeah, very happy.
He totally fell for it!
Fuck you.
She's very sweet. Sometimes, she'll put
her arm around me...
and she'll whisper to me, she'll go...
We all get it.
My mom was a great, big, fat person.
Hilarious. Hysterical.
Yeah, it's a nice watch.
Wait, let's talk about the elephant
not in the room...
Ben.
What the fuck, man?
Okay, okay.
Obviously, I lost a few pounds.
- Lost a few pounds?
- Yeah, no shit, you lost a few pounds.
You're hot!
That's true.
No, you're like every Brazilian soccer
player wrapped up into one person.
Leave him alone.
You're embarrassing him.
Okay, okay, all right. Please, come on.
Is Stanley coming or what?
Someone save me.
Stan.
Stan, uh...
Stan Uris. Stan Urine.
Stanley Urine.
No, no, he's a fucking pussy.
He's not gonna show.
Why would Stanley save you, anyway?
Was I not the one who basically
performed surgery on you...
- after Bowers cut you up?
- Yes!
Holy shit! That's right.
Please tell me you ended up
becoming a doctor, Eds.
No, I ended up becoming
a risk analyst.
Oh, that sounds
really interesting.
What does that entail?
Yeah, so I work
for a big insurance firm and...
Fuck you, dude. Fuck you.
Was this job invented before fun?
- Oh, that's so not funny.
- It is funny.
What the fuck are you laughing at?
I propose a toast...
to the Losers.
Let's take our shirts off
and kiss!
- Oh, here we go.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Like, Rogan-Marsh,
half my wife's closet Rogan-Marsh?
That's huge.
That's our line.
Me and my husband, Tom.
How long have you been married?
Hey, we saw your movie...
- by the way.
- You did?
- Oh, my God! It was so good.
- Oh, my God.
It was so scary.
And the ending sucked?
Yeah, it did. I'm sorry.
That's all right.
What?
Nothing. This is just weird.
Yeah.
Just all this, all these memories...
people that I don't even
remember forgetting.
I mean, it's weird, right?
Now that we're all here...
everything just comes back
faster and faster.
I mean, all of it.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, when Mike called me,
I threw up.
Isn't that weird?
Like, I got nervous.
I got, like, sick and I threw up.
I feel fine now. I feel very relieved
to be here with you guys.
Why is everybody looking at me
like this?
When Mike called me, I crashed my car.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Shit, man, I hear you.
I mean, my heart was literally
pounding right out of my chest.
- I thought it was only me.
- It was like pure...
Fear.
It's fear. What you felt.
Why did we all feel like that, Mike?
You remember something we don't,
don't you, Mike?
Something happens to you
when you leave this town.
The farther away,
the hazier it all gets.
But me, I never left.
So, yeah.
I remember.
I remember all of it.
Pennywise.
Oh, the fucking clown.
- Oh, shit.
- Pennywise.
Mike, you said you wanted our help
with something.
What was that?
There's an echo here in Derry
that bounces back every 27 years.
What are you talking about?
Hold on. Listen, listen.
We thought we stopped It back then.
We thought It was done, but...
Mike.
A week ago, a man,
Adrian Mellon, slaughtered.
A girl, Lisa Albrecht, the other night,
went missing.
All right.
There've already been others
and there will be more.
I don't want to hear
about this shit.
- More death. More pain.
- Calm down.
Let's get another drink.
Let him explain. Let him explain.
Explain it to us, Mike.
That echo...
we might have changed It...
just like It changed us.
But we didn't stop It.
Because It just bounced back.
We made an oath.
That's why I brought you back.
That's why you're here.
To finish It.
For good.
Well, that shit got dark fast.
Thanks, Mike.
My fortune cookie just says "Could."
They don't know how to do
fortune cookies here.
Mine just says "Guess."
You wanna throw that over here?
What you got, Mikey?
Wait, what?
This is what I'm talking about.
"Guess. Cut. Not. Could. It."
It's a message.
No, "Guess it could not cut."
Why would it guess it could not cut?
- Cut what?
- "Guess it could not cut."
"It" goes in front. There.
"It could not guess."
- It couldn't guess.
- "Could it..."
No. "Could it not cut."
When it says "It,"
is it talking about It?
- Yeah. All right.
- Is that what it means? Is "It" It?
Where does this go?
- That's what I'm talking about.
- It... It could...
I don't know
what it fucking means!
You fuck with the fortune cookies, Mike?
No.
Let him speak, man.
This is not me.
This is what It does.
I need my fucking inhaler!
What is wrong with you, man?
Why'd you call us?
- This is so not funny!
- This is not fucking funny!
- Beverly?
- This is so not funny.
Why does it say Stanley?
Someone else fucking answer me!
Holy shit.
What the fuck is that, man?
Oh, my God.
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Shit.
Hey!
That fortune cookie's looking at me!
Shit!
I don't want to be here.
I can't fucking do this.
I wanna go home!
I don't wanna be here!
Holy shit!
Hey! God damn it.
Eddie!
Fuck!
It's not real!
This isn't real!
It's not real! It's not real!
Is everything all right?
Yeah. Could we get the check?
That's what Pennywise does, right?
He fucks with us.
So, Stanley's probably fine.
Hey, Mike. Do you have Stan's number?
Yeah.
Hey, Richie.
How'd you know my name?
The fun's just beginning.
Right?
What he said, is it...
Listen. You think this is funny?
All right?
Think this is some sort of game, huh?
Well, fuck you, all right?
Rich, be careful, dude.
Fuck you! I'm not afraid of you!
"The fun's just beginning."
The line from your act, dude.
I'm a fan.
- Are those your parents?
- Yeah.
You want a picture?
- You okay, Dean? Come on.
- I think I'm good.
Okay, cool.
He's a good kid.
Jesus, Richie. You don't remember a line
from your own show?
I don't write my own material.
I fucking knew it!
Hello, Mrs. Uris.
My name's Beverly Marsh.
I apologize for calling,
but I'm an old friend of your husband's.
You lied to us. That's not okay.
Yeah, first words out of your mouth
should have been like...
"Hey, man. You want to come to Derry
and get murdered?"
'Cause then I would have said no.
Guys.
Fucking entrapment, man.
Oh...
He passed.
When did it happen?
Yesterday.
It was horrible, the way he died.
His wrists.
- In the bathtub.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
We're all very sorry, Patty.
Thank you.
Stanley.
Pennywise knew. He knew before we did.
We have to stop him.
I have a plan.
I got a plan.
Getting the fuck out of Dodge...
before this ends worse
than one of Bill's books.
Who's with me?
We made a promise to each other.
Let's un-make the promise.
Richie, other people are gonna die.
Other people die every day, man!
We don't owe this town shit!
Plus, I just remembered I grew up here,
like, two hours ago.
So, I'm fucking leaving. Fuck this.
I'm sorry, man, I'm with Richie.
- Eds, please.
- Listen.
What? We stay, we die, that's it?
I'm gonna go back to the inn,
I'm gonna pack up my shit...
and I'm gonna drive to my home.
I'm sorry, man. Good luck.
No, Eddie. Please.
Please, Eddie!
Eddie, wait!
You okay?
I'm gonna head back
to the Town House, too.
- Are you coming?
- Yeah.
You should have told us, Mikey.
Bill. Please, man.
I'm begging you. Please.
Just listen to me, man. Please.
What are you gonna say?
What could you possibly say that
would make any kind of a difference?
They're all gone.
Come on. Let me show you something.
One thing. And if you want to leave,
you can leave.
Just let me show you this first. Please.
Lapskew!
What kind of name is that, huh?
My mom swings better than you!
How many times do I have to...
She doesn't even play baseball!
You suck!
Mommy, how much longer?
Victoria, we came to watch the game.
We're gonna watch the game.
Hello, Vicky.
Isn't that what your friends call you?
Vicky?
How did I know that?
I guess I must be
your friend, too.
If you're my friend,
why are you hiding in the dark?
You're not my friend.
You're scary.
Why are you crying?
People always make fun
'cause of the way I look.
I thought if you couldn't see my face...
then maybe you'd want to be my friend.
Oh. Never mind.
Oh, silly old Pennywise,
you'll never have no friends.
People make fun of me, too.
They do?
'Cause of this.
Well, isn't that silly?
That little thing?
Why, I can blow that thing right away.
You could?
Oh, yes!
One poof and it'd be gone!
You would have to get close enough
to see my face.
I don't know, Vicky.
No, it's okay. I won't make fun.
I promise.
Promise, promise?
Well, okie-dokie!
Just come on in a little closer
and we'll blow it away
on the count of three!
One...
two...
You're supposed to say three.
Holy fuck.
Boo!
Fuck yeah!
Hey, Hockstetter.
Let's go!
Let's get our shit
and get the fuck out of here.
Did you leave your stuff here?
No, my stuff's still in the car.
- Tell me.
- Tell you what?
Whatever it is you're afraid
to tell me right now.
Bev. Bev.
Back at the Jade when you were
on the phone with Stanley's...
Stop.
She told you that she found him
in the bathtub...
but, Bev, I saw you.
I heard it. You said it first.
Whatever you guys are talking about...
let's make it happen faster, all right?
We gotta go.
Eduardo, ándale! Let's go!
There's something you're not telling us.
You knew how Stanley died.
You knew.
Wait, what?
I can't do this.
She knew how Stanley was going to die,
is that what she just said?
You can't just walk away from this.
How did you know
where he killed himself?
Bev.
Talk to me.
Just talk to me.
Like we used to.
Come on, how did you know?
Because I saw it.
I've seen all of us die.
Okay, I just got to grab my toiletry bag
and then we can go.
What'd I miss?
The library?
Mmm-hmm.
Wow.
Didn't this place used to be bigger?
Yo!
Mike, where are you going?
Mike, you live... live here?
Yeah. Make yourself at home.
- You want some water?
- Yeah, sure.
You see, memory's the thing.
It's the key.
It's the key to everything.
If It really does
want us back here...
don't you think
the smartest thing we can do
is just get the hell out of Derry?
No, no, no. It does want us back.
Of course It does!
- But It doesn't know I know what I know.
- What do you know?
How to kill the shit out of It!
I've read every book.
I've talked to every person
in this godforsaken town,
everybody that would talk to me, anyway,
and that's not a long list.
But it wasn't enough.
I had to know how this all started.
How It started.
And It started...
here.
Whoa.
- What am I looking at, Mike?
- It's an artifact.
Early 18th century Shokopiwah.
How'd you get it?
I found it, in the...
No, no, they gave it to me.
I stole it.
You stole it?
- From Native Americans?
- Uh...
- It's complicated.
- Yeah, it is.
They helped me on my journey.
So beautiful.
They showed me things. A vision.
Ow.
Holy fuck.
I feel kind of funky.
Hot.
Am I sweating?
I need you to see
what they showed me, Bill.
They live outside of Derry.
Beyond It's reach.
They moved there many years ago.
Their holy man...
their holy of holies...
he took me in.
Fed me their sacred Maturin.
I started to... to react.
All living things
must abide by the laws...
of the shape they inhabit.
While I sat there,
looking out over the valley...
I saw It arrive.
I knew that one day,
I would have to make you all see.
Mike...
did you put something in my drink?
It's a root.
- You drugged me?
- No, it's a root with properties.
It's just a micro-dose
of what the Shokopiwah gave me...
Why would you do that?
...to open my eyes.
I don't feel real good.
I need you to look...
and you'll see.
I don't feel good.
Open your eyes.
They showed me the past.
Showed me the way It appeared to them.
They showed me their pain.
They showed me how to stop It!
It's over.
It's over. You're okay.
You're okay. Did you see it?
The ritual?
The Ritual of Chüd?
I knew you would see it.
I saw the whole fucking thing, Mike.
That's how we kill It.
How are we going to do it?
Everybody already said no.
But with you...
they'll listen.
This won't work without all of us.
Okay. So, what do you mean
that you've seen us all die?
Yeah, 'cause I gotta be honest.
That's a fucked-up thing
to just drop on somebody.
Every night since Derry...
I've been having these nightmares.
People in pain. People dying.
People...
So, you have nightmares.
I have nightmares.
People, they have nightmares.
But that doesn't mean
that your visions are true.
I've watched every single one of us...
You've seen
every single one of us what?
At the place that Stanley wound up.
That's how we end.
Okay, how come the rest of us
aren't seeing that shit?
I mean, what makes her so different?
The Deadlights.
She was the only one of us
that got caught
in the Deadlights that day.
We were all touched by It.
Changed.
Deep down. Like an infection.
Or a virus.
A virus. You understand.
Slowly growing.
That virus, it's been growing
for 27 years.
This whole time, metastasizing.
- It just got to Stan first, because...
- He was the weakest.
Jesus Christ, Rich.
Just saying what everyone else
is thinking, man.
I mean, Rich, come on.
What Beverly sees, it will come to pass.
It's what'll happen
to all of us, eventually...
unless we stop It.
How the hell are we supposed to do that?
The Ritual of Chüd.
The Shokopiwah.
The first ones who fought It,
they have a saying.
"All living things must abide
by the laws of the shape they inhabit."
A tribal ritual?
Are you fucking kidding me, man?
All right, there's gotta be another way.
Okay? This thing comes back,
what, every 27 years?
Let's just kick the can down the road
and do it then.
Wait, we'll be 70 years old, asshole.
It doesn't work that way.
None of us make it another 20 years...
and the way it happens...
So, if we don't beat It
this cycle, then...
We die.
Horribly.
Yeah, I don't need the "horribly" part.
I didn't say it. She said it.
Not me.
All right, guys. Look.
I've seen
what he's talking about...
and it's all true.
It's the only way.
If we want this ritual to work...
We have to remember.
Remember what?
It's better if I show you.
We don't have much time.
This cycle will end soon.
And once it does...
We're fucked.
The Barrens.
This is where we came.
After the rock fight.
The clubhouse.
You built that for us.
Yeah, the hatch has got to be
around here someplace.
You did. I do remember that!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
You okay?
- What?
- Nothing, it's just...
You haven't changed.
It's a good thing.
You know what? I actually think
the door was more like...
around...
Found it.
I'm okay!
Come down!
What the dick is this?
How'd you build it?
When did you build it?
Here and there, I guess.
It was already dug out from something,
so I just had to reinforce the walls...
and get some wood for the roof door...
and that's pretty much it.
Pretty good for my first time, huh?
Now, that's a cool feature.
What happens when you put your hand
on the other pillar, professor?
Okay, you see, this is exactly
why there are safety codes...
why we have permits.
This place is a death trap.
You understand that?
Well, it's a work in progress.
Okay, Eddie?
Just so you know, I get hurt,
you are liable.
And, also, what is this?
The switch of an iron maiden?
That's a flashlight.
What is that, a horse hitch?
When do you have horses down...
Oh, this is cool.
That was like, three dollars,
so be careful with that, please.
I have one of these.
Hey, Stan, you see this?
Yeah, okay, can you maybe not?
Maybe not what? Yeah, yeah, hold on.
Maybe not what?
Be awesome and have fun and celebrate
the magic of the paddle-ball?
Wow.
Oh, good going, fucknut.
You broke his thing.
- I broke it?
- Yeah, you broke it with your face.
What?
I'm not putting
my fucking hand down there.
Oh, man. That's so cool.
Oh, my God.
How do we all not remember
that this was here?
Hey, Losers.
Time to float.
- Ah.
- Fuck, Richie.
- Dude!
- Remember when he used to say that shit?
And he'd do that little dance.
Am I the only one
who remembers this shit?
Are you gonna be like this
the entire time we're home?
All right. Just trying to add
some levity to this shit.
I'll go fuck myself.
It smells so fucking
terrible in here.
Hey, you guys?
This says, "Stan.
For the use of Losers only."
Bill.
The fuck is this?
So you don't get spiders stuck
in your hair when you're down here.
Stanley, we're not afraid
of fucking spiders.
I stand corrected.
That's a first.
Touché.
Hey, Rich, your ten minutes are up.
What are you talking about?
The hammock.
Ten minutes each was the rule.
I don't see any sign.
Are you being this way right now?
Really? No, no, no.
Why would there be a sign
if it was a verbal agreement?
And I remember you agreeing
on the fucking rule!
- I can see your vagina!
- Ten minutes each.
Go back in your dumb little corner!
I fucked your mom!
No, you didn't.
Take that back!
Fuck you.
You're awfully good at this, new kid.
I totally did your mom.
You really think so?
There's actually a summer program
in Bar Harbor.
Teaches you, like, everything
about architecture.
- I was thinking about applying.
- I'll do that.
I'll do anything
to get the hell out of Derry.
Man, when I graduate,
I'm going to Florida.
What's in Florida, Mike?
I don't know.
You know, I guess it's just a place
I always wanted to go.
Stan, you should go
with Mike to Florida.
You already act 80.
You'd clean up with all the grandmas.
Do you guys think
we'll still be friends?
When we're older?
What?
Why wouldn't we be?
Do any of your parents still hang out
with their friends from middle school?
I mean, things might be different then.
We all might be different.
We'll always still be friends.
I don't think that just, you know,
goes away because we get older.
Yeah, Stan. Come on.
You don't have to be so...
Sad.
He was old before his time.
Yeah.
I wonder what he was like all grown up.
Probably what he was like as a kid.
The best.
Here.
All right, Mike. What are we doing here?
The ritual.
To perform it requires a sacrifice.
Sacrifice? I nominate Eddie.
Wait, what?
Because you're little.
You'll fit on a barbeque.
I'm 5'9". It's, like, average height
in most of the world.
It's not that kind of a sacrifice, guys.
Mike?
The past is buried.
But you're gonna have to dig it up.
Piece by piece.
And these pieces...
these artifacts...
that's why we're here.
They are what you'll sacrifice.
And since Stan isn't here to find his...
I figured we should all be here together
to find his artifact.
I think Bill just did that.
Okay, Mike,
so where do we find our tokens?
Yeah, I gotta be honest, man.
All due respect.
This is fucking stupid, all right?
Why do we need tokens? All right?
We already remember everything.
Saving Bev, defeating It...
I mean, we're caught up!
It's not everything.
We fought. But what happened after that?
Before the house on Neibolt.
Think.
We can't remember, can we?
See, there's more to our story.
What happened that summer.
And those blank spaces...
like pages torn out of a book.
That's what you need to find.
We need to split up.
You each need to find your artifact.
Alone. That's important.
When you do...
meet me at the library tonight.
Yeah, I gotta say...
statistically speaking,
you look at survival scenarios...
we're gonna do much better as a group.
Yeah, splitting up would be dumb, man.
Okay, we gotta go together. All right?
We were together that summer, right?
No.
Not that whole summer.
Take it back.
Bill!
You're just a bunch of losers.
Fuck off!
- Fucking...
- Stop!
We were all together when we hurt It.
That's why we're still alive.
Yeah? Well, I plan to keep it that way.
I bet by tomorrow,
we'll all be back together.
I don't think so.
Well, if we're gonna stop It,
we better be.
Maybe Richie was right.
Maybe we shouldn't do anything about It,
or maybe we can't.
Okay, don't let them get to you.
It's a little late for that.
You should go.
Before your dad sees.
Yes?
Sorry.
May I help you?
I thought I rang Marsh.
Marsh?
Alvin Marsh?
My father.
I grew up here.
Dear...
it's not for me to tell you this...
but your father passed away.
I'm so sorry. You didn't know?
We hadn't spoken in a while.
Well, won't you come in?
Let me offer you something to drink.
No, it's fine. I have to go.
It's the least I can do.
Sure. Okay.
Is it like you remember?
Cleaner.
Well, you feel free to look around
while I get the water boiling.
Oh, really, it's fine.
You don't need to do that.
Don't be so polite.
Today is her birthday.
I can still smell her perfume.
And she'd still be alive
if it wasn't for you.
Mama was sick.
You know
that's why she did what she did.
She did what she did...
because she was embarrassed
to be your mother.
You look like her.
But you are nothing like her.
Come here.
I said, come here!
Close your eyes.
You know that I would never hurt you.
You know that, don't you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You'll always be my little girl,
won't you?
Always.
"Your hair is winter fire...
January embers...
My heart burns there, too."
There. I do apologize.
It gets so very hot here
this time of year.
It's fine.
When you feel like you could
just about die.
But you know what they say about Derry.
"No one who dies here ever really dies."
But tell me,
how is it being back in Derry?
It's good. Strange.
Strange?
Oh, my.
Strange, how?
I had some cookies in the oven
before you came.
You stay right there.
Uh, I really... I shouldn't impose...
I'm gonna...
No, no, no. I insist.
Mrs. Kersh, are these your family?
Yes, dear.
My father came to this country
with $14 in his pocket.
And he didn't ask for a handout the way
the people coming here these days.
You know what he did?
What did he do, Mrs. Kersh?
My father joined the circus.
I was always Daddy's little girl.
What about you?
Are you still
his little girl, Beverly?
Are you?
Mustn't lie to our father!
Help!
Run, run, run.
Run, run.
You haven't changed anything yet.
You haven't changed their futures.
You haven't saved any of them.
Close your eyes, Bev.
Fuck you!
If you don't believe...
close them...
and see!
Come on, you.
Come on.
- Ken, you little bitch...
- Yes!
You're fucking good.
Game over.
- I gotta go.
- Hey!
Um...
How about we go again?
Play some more, you know?
Fuck you, man.
Only if you want to.
Shut up.
Dude, why are you being weird?
I'm not your fucking boyfriend.
Whoa, I...
- I didn't...
- What the fuck's going on here?
You assholes didn't tell me your town
is full of little fairies.
Richie fucking Tozier?
What? You're trying
to bone my little cousin?
Get the fuck out of here, faggot!
Fucking move!
Want a kiss, Richie?
It's not real.
It's not real. It's not real.
I think I just shit my pants.
Canal Days Festival.
- Closing performance is tonight.
- Shit.
Hope to see you there, handsome.
Did you miss me, Richie?
Fuck!
'Cause I've missed you.
No one wants
to play with the clown anymore.
Play a game with me, would ya?
How about Street Fighter?
Oh, yes. You like that one, don't you?
Or maybe Truth or Dare?
Jesus.
Oh, you wouldn't want...
anyone to pick "truth," though,
would ya, Richie?
You wouldn't want anyone to know
what you're hiding.
I know your secret
Your dirty, little secret
Oh, I know your secret
Should I tell them, Richie?
This isn't happening.
This isn't real.
It isn't real. It isn't happening.
It isn't real.
Come back and play!
Come back and play with the clown!
Hi!
Whoa!
- I'm so sorry.
- Watch it, you jerk!
Sorry.
Oh, man!
- Can I help you?
- Hi.
Yeah, I want to see about the...
Baseball card?
The bowling ball?
No, the...
Banjo?
Beaver?
Fucking bike.
You wanna use that kind of language...
take it out in the street.
I'm sorry.
Can we just start over and pretend
that I just walked in?
How can I help you?
Thank you. Yes.
I want to buy the bike.
Aren't you William Denbrough,
the writer?
Yeah, that's...
That's me.
That bike used to be mine.
Well, it's mine now.
But you're the big author.
You want it, you can afford it.
All right. How much?
Three hundred.
You can afford it.
I'll get it.
I guess that's kind of a deal.
You, uh, want me to sign it for you?
Nah.
I didn't like the ending.
Uh...
Three big ones.
All yours.
I don't know how fast she'll go.
Been there a lot of years.
You know what, mister?
She was fast enough to beat the devil.
Come on.
Yeah, I missed you, too.
Yeah!
Whoo!
Hi-ho, Silver!
Away!
Bye, Billy!
I know you're down there.
I know you can hear me.
There's something I have to know.
All of the kids in this town
you could have taken...
why Georgie?
Say something!
Why him?
Why him? Why him? Why him?
Why?
Because you weren't there, Billy.
Billy, don't leave.
Hello?
Billy.
I'm still here.
Help me.
Georgie.
Georgie?
Help me, Billy.
Take my hand.
I've got you, buddy. Come on.
He's coming.
Take my hand!
- I got you. Come on.
- Billy, please. He's coming.
- Take my hand.
- Billy!
Come on, take my hand!
I hate you!
I hate you.
Who are you talking to?
Move, move, move!
Move! Move!
You hear voices from that sewer,
you stay away from it.
You hear voices from the sewer?
No.
No. Just stay away from that sewer.
I only hear voices in the tub.
You know. From the drain.
What kind of voices?
Kids.
And other times, like a...
Like a clown?
You listen to me.
You listen good.
You need to get out of this town.
All right? Tell your parents.
Make up a reason.
You make up a fucking lie.
I don't care what you do.
Just get out of this town.
Make them never bring you back.
Do you understand?
You leave Derry
and you stay out of Derry!
Do you understand me?
I'm supposed to be at the festival.
Tell me you understand!
I gotta go.
Just be careful!
Come on,
let's get the fuck outta here.
Wake up, fat-ass.
Fucking loser.
Whoa.
Easy. It's just me.
What are you and your little buddies
up to in here?
Oh. Those guys
are definitely not my buddies.
No, I meant your real friends.
- Joey. Jonathan. Donnie. Danny.
- Oh.
Are you smoking in school?
Secret hideout.
Don't tell anyone.
You okay, new kid?
Yeah, no, I'm fine.
I guess I'm just worried...
that we're not all gonna be the same
after the fight.
As long as we can still hang out,
who cares?
You really mean that?
Well, yeah, of course, dummy.
You and me.
Oh, my God!
I meant as a friend.
You actually thought
I could like someone...
as fat and gross
and disgusting like you?
No matter how many
stupid poems you write...
"Your hair is winter fire.
January embers.
My heart burns there, too."
That's not the real Beverly.
Beverly would never say
anything like that.
She'd never say that.
Kiss me, fat boy.
Oh, nobody wants to kiss the fat boy.
Just leave me alone.
Alone?
Oh, you've always been alone.
That's not true. I have real friends.
Bill. Eddie. Mike. Stanley.
Richie. Beverly.
They're my real friends.
Oh, kiss me as if it were the last time.
What the hell are you doing, kid?
Guys?
Hey.
So, what did you see out there?
Something I wish I hadn't.
So, what, we just...
we kill It, and then we just
forget everything again?
I hope so. Don't you?
I don't know.
Uh, I guess I want to hold on
to the good stuff, you know?
Mmm.
Come on. There must be
something from the past
that you don't want to forget again.
I remember being scared shitless.
Cold.
I remember you guys
in your tighty-whities.
Okay. Please forget that moment.
I remember this.
I remember the boy who wrote it for me.
Not him, so much...
but how he made me feel.
And a kiss.
It's...
It's still blurry,
but I think the longer
we're here, the more I can see it.
The more I can see that moment.
The more I can see...
Bill.
I think.
I don't know. Do you remember...
Bev, um...
- Move. Move.
- What's wrong?
I'm leaving.
What? You can't leave, man.
We split, we all die.
Yeah, I'll take my chances.
We're gonna die, anyway.
Rich. Um...
Rich.
Hey, kids! It's Burrow the Beaver!
Come on down. It's the last day
of the festival here at Canal Days.
Argh!
Asshole!
Hello?
Can I help you?
Yeah, I had prescription called in
for Kaspbrak.
Kaspbrak?
It's an inhaler.
Ah.
Eddie Kaspbrak?
Mmm-hmm. That's me.
I remember you.
Yeah.
How's your mom?
Oh, uh, well, she died a few years ago.
It's very sad. It was from liver cancer.
What's that?
- What's what?
- That.
All right.
Okay.
No, it's not gonna pop.
It's a mole.
It might not be cancer.
Cancer?
Ah...
But it might be.
You just stay here.
I'll get you something.
Okay.
You came here
for your stinky breath pills?
My breath is fine.
Thank you.
That's not what my dad said.
He said you have a tumor.
On your dick.
But you don't
take pills for...
Wait, what did your dad say?
There you go.
I hope your dick feels better.
Thank you.
For the inhaler,
not for the penis thing.
Eddie!
Eddie bear!
Mommy?
Eddie, come help me! Quick!
Eddie!
Mommy?
Eddie?
Eddie, help me!
Quick, help me!
Mommy?
Eddie bear,
come help me, quick!
Eddie?
The fuck is she doing here?
What is taking you so long?
I don't know. Why are you here?
Mommy!
He's coming!
You gotta get me outta here!
- Who's coming?
- Eddie.
What the fuck is that?
Mommy.
You gotta
get me outta here.
He's coming! He's gonna kill me!
Eddie!
Help! Please, help me!
He's going to infect me!
Eddie! He's gonna infect me!
Eddie!
Help me!
Help me, Eddie!
He's coming, Eddie!
Eddie, hurry!
He's gonna infect me, Eddie!
Oh, my God! Eddie!
Hurry up, Eddie!
Eddie!
I can't do it!
Eddie! Eddie!
I'm sorry, I can't do it.
I knew you would leave me, Eddie!
Eddie, help me!
Eddie!
What's all this shit doing here?
Why is that curtain still here?
Okay, all right.
Are you gonna do this, Eds?
It's just a memory.
It's just a memory. You're fine.
Deep breath. Deep breath.
Okay. You gonna do it?
Shit! Oh, shit! Oh, fuck!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
That's right!
Fuck you!
What the fuck?
What?
Push, don't pull, you moron.
Oh. Heh. Thanks.
Oh, my God. What happened to you?
Nothing. I'm fine.
I'm fine. Everything's fine.
Hey, how you doing?
Where's everybody else?
Richie wants to leave. Ben's upstairs
trying to get him to stay.
He's just scared.
So am I, Bill.
Aren't you?
We're all scared.
That's what worries me.
Because that's what It wants.
We can do this...
but we have to stick together.
Should we be running?
This is Derry.
I'm kinda getting used to it.
What does that mean?
Shit. It's the kid.
What?
It's the kid from the place.
The Chinese place.
I saw him on the way here.
He lives at my old house.
He was going to the fair, and...
He's going to the fair.
I gotta help him.
Okay, okay. Listen to me.
We'll go together.
I'm gonna get Richie and Ben
and we'll go.
There's no time.
I can't let it happen again.
What happened before wasn't your fault.
None of it was.
I wish that were true, Bev.
Bill! Bev!
What is this? What happened?
Did Bill just leave?
I couldn't stop him.
Everybody's leaving.
It's all right. It's Bill.
He'll be back.
He'll come back.
Well, at least I got Richie to stay.
Fuck. Oh.
And then the leper,
he threw up all over me.
"Hey, it's Mike Hanlon.
Why don't you come back to Maine?"
It's your time, Eddie.
What?
Why?
Why did you do that?
Because he says it's your time.
Who says it's my time?
You know, Eddie.
You know.
Time to float.
Where did he go?
Now give me back my fucking knife!
You should cut that fucking mullet.
It's been, like, 30 years, man.
Guys!
Oh, shit.
Eds?
Jesus, Eds. What the hell?
- Bowers is in my room.
- Oh, my...
- Is it bad?
- No.
Oh.
I'm gonna carve my whole
name onto this cottage cheese!
One down!
Fuck yeah!
Hey!
Hey, kid! Kid!
I'm sorry.
Hey!
Excuse me.
Hey! Hey!
Fuck.
Fuck!
Kid! Hey, kid!
Fuck.
Kid?
Hey!
Kid.
Kid? Hey! Hey!
Kid!
Fuck.
Shit.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
No, I'm here to help.
Stop following me!
I'm gonna get you out of here.
No.
Please.
Ah.
I'm here this time.
Just take me.
Ah.
Son of a bitch!
Help!
I should go back there.
I just fucking left them in the lurch,
man. I should go back there.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Fuck that.
Fuck them.
I got dates in fucking Reno, man.
Reflecting on
the meaning of what I just read...
the word "Leshanot" comes up a lot...
which means "to change, to transform."
Which makes sense, I guess...
because today I'm supposed
to become a man.
It's funny, though.
Everyone, I think, has some memories
they're prouder of than others, right?
And maybe that's why change is so scary.
'Cause the things we wish
we could leave behind...
- Good morning, Mike.
- How you doing?
...the whispers
we wish we could silence...
His pa is the one.
The one that set that fire.
...the nightmares
we most want to wake up from...
the memories we wish we could change...
...the secrets we feel
like we have to keep...
are the hardest to walk away from.
The good stuff?
The pictures in our mind
that fade away the fastest?
Those pieces of you it feels
the easiest to lose.
Maybe I don't want to forget.
Maybe if that's what today
is all about...
forget it, right?
- Thank you, Stanley.
- Uh...
Today, I'm supposed to become a man...
but I don't feel any different.
I know I'm a loser.
And no matter what...
I always fucking will be.
Thanks for showing up, Stanley.
Mike! Help!
Help us!
- Please, Mikey, help!
- Help us!
Please, Mikey, help!
Mikey!
You should have burned, Mike.
Just like your druggie parents.
Can you see them yet?
Crisping?
Like fried fucking...
I guess you could say
that was long overdue.
Get it? 'Cause we're in a library.
No.
Mike?
- Hey.
- Hey. Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
No, I'm not all right.
I just fucking killed a guy.
I was talking to Mike.
Where's Bill?
Bill, we're all at the library.
Where are you at?
He took a little kid, Mike.
He took a little kid right
in fucking front of me.
No, no, no.
Look, just come here to the library.
We can talk about the plan.
- I'm gonna go kill It.
- No, no, no.
I don't want any of you
to get killed with me.
Bill! Bill!
He's going to fight It alone.
- What?
- Alone.
It's about the group.
The ritual doesn't work
without the group.
Doing it together is why it'd work.
Mike, did he tell you
where he was going?
If he really wanted to kill Pennywise,
there's only one place he'll go.
The same place the ritual
needs to be performed.
Oh, we're not gonna like this, are we?
Fuck.
Bill!
No, no, you guys, no!
I started all this.
It's my fault that you're all here.
This curse, this fucking thing
that's inside you all.
It started growing the day that
I made you go down to the Barrens...
because all I cared about
was finding Georgie.
Now, I'm gonna go in there
and I don't know what's gonna happen...
but I can't ask you to do this.
Well...
we're not asking you, either.
- Bev...
- We didn't do it alone then, Bill...
so we're not gonna do this alone now.
Losers stick together.
So, does somebody want to say something?
Richie said it best
when we were here last.
I did?
- "I don't want to die"?
- Not that.
"You're lucky
we're not measuring dicks"?
No.
"Let's kill this fucking clown"?
Let's kill this fucking clown.
I love what he's done with the place.
Beep-beep, Richie.
All right.
Hey, hey.
That's the basement, right?
Ben?
No! Hey, hey! Ben!
Ben!
Ben? What's wrong?
Okay. All right.
Ben!
Okay, that can't be good, right?
Help! Hey!
It's Stan.
It can't be real.
Oh!
- Oh, God.
- Oh, shit.
I'd still be alive
if it wasn't for you, Bill.
No.
Beverly!
Richie, what's happening to me?
You gotta be fucking kidding.
Fuck!
Oh, God damn, get it away from me.
Oh, God!
Eddie.
Are you okay?
I'm...
Oh, there he is.
Get it off of me!
Richie!
- Richie!
- Richie! Hey!
- Get it off of me!
- I wanna go home.
Get the knife!
God damn it, Eddie, get the knife!
Bill!
Get it off of me, Bill! Quick!
Eddie, get the knife!
Fuck!
What?
Is everybody okay?
You all right?
He could have
fucking died, man.
You know that, right?
I can't see.
Georgie's dead. The kid's dead.
Stanley's dead.
You want Richie, too?
I don't want Richie, too.
I don't. I don't.
Please don't be mad, Bill.
I was just scared.
That's what
he wants, right?
Don't give it to him.
A lot of memories, huh?
All bad.
Oh, man.
Gray water.
Shit. This is it.
This is where it happened.
No, no, no.
No, no. Ugh.
Bevvie.
Bev, what is it?
I thought I heard something.
Bev!
Time to sink!
Guys.
Okay, guys. Come on.
Hey, guys.
Guys, come on. Please, come on.
I don't want to walk out of here alone.
You okay?
I feel like crying.
Mike. Where do we go from here?
In the depths is where It crept.
In the beneath, to find belief.
Is he okay?
I think at this point,
that's a relative question.
What's on the other side?
I don't know. No one does.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Mike.
- Mike, don't.
- All right.
- See you down there.
- Mike!
Wait!
- Stay together.
- Okay.
You guys, I can't do it.
I can't. You saw what happened up there.
I was gonna let you die.
I just fucking froze up.
If you let me go down there with you...
I'm gonna get us all killed.
Hey, hey, hey. Give me that.
- Richie.
- Give me that. Let go, you little turd.
Just let me get...
- I got it.
- Stop.
Listen to me.
You had a moment. Fine.
But who killed a psychotic clown
before he was 14?
Me.
Who stabbed Bowers with a knife
he pulled out of his own face?
Also me.
Who married a woman ten times
his own body mass?
- Me.
- Yeah.
You're braver than you think.
All right. Thanks, Rich.
- Ow.
- Sorry.
Hey. Here.
Take it.
It kills monsters.
- Does it?
- Yeah.
If you believe it does.
Thanks, Bev.
- You guys good?
- Yeah.
- Can you get through that?
- It's the only way. This way.
It's in here!
Through here.
It's tight, but we can get through.
This is where It hit.
So, all this has been
under Derry, like, forever?
Not forever.
Just a few million years.
It can only be attacked
in its true form.
The ritual will show us that.
And what is It's true form?
I hope it's a puppy.
Like a Pomeranian or...
I'll shut up.
It's light.
A light that must be snuffed out
by darkness.
Your artifacts.
Place them in the fire.
The past must burn with the present.
Uh, this is the boat that I built...
with Georgie.
It's, uh, my inhaler.
Come on, dude.
Something that I wish I had held on to.
Uh, this is a page from my yearbook.
That only one person signed.
I probably should have forgotten it...
but I couldn't,
because I kept it in my wallet...
for 27 years.
This is a token
from the Capitol Theater.
You brought an actual token?
Yeah, man. That's what
we were supposed to do, asshole.
Do you have any idea how long
that's gonna take to burn?
Yeah, but so is your inhaler, dude.
Guys, come on.
All the toxic fumes and the plastic
and shit, so...
Look closely, Bev.
You see it?
That's where you hit Bowers.
The rock fight.
The day these bonds were forged.
That's not gonna burn, either.
Oh, wait.
Couldn't forget about Stan...
again.
Okay.
Grab hands.
Come on.
The Ritual of Chüd.
It's a battle of wills.
The first step was our reunion.
The second was the gathering of tokens.
This is the final step.
What the...
Fuck is that?
Don't look at them!
- Are those the Deadlights?
- Don't look at it!
Okay.
Turn light into dark.
Turn light into dark. Say it!
- Say what?
- Say it!
Turn light into dark.
- Turn light into dark.
Mike, what's happening, man?
Keep chanting!
Turn light into dark.
Turn light into dark!
Is it working? Did we do it?
What is this? Is this part of it?
Mike, is this supposed to be happening?
- What? No, no, no.
- Keep chanting!
- What?
Turn light into dark!
- Turn light into dark.
- Come on!
Turn light into dark.
Whoa!
Hey! Hey!
Shit!
Move, move!
Bev. Bev.
Richie.
Are you okay?
- I can't hear shit.
- He's okay.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. No, no, no.
- Wait, where's Mike?
- Mike!
- I'm here!
- Hey, guys.
Did we do it?
We put the tokens in the thing.
That's good, right?
We did it, right?
Boo!
Shit! Shit!
Oh, did it work, Mikey? Did it work?
Tell them why your silly little ritual
didn't work.
Tell them it's all just a...
What's the word, Eds?
Gazebo?
Mike, what's he talking about?
Mikey?
Oh, Mikey, you never showed them
the fourth side, did you?
Didn't want them to know
what actually happened
to the poor Shokopiwah?
Fuck, Mikey. You lied to us, again?
No, but they didn't believe!
They didn't believe they could kill It!
That's why it didn't work back then!
Are you fucking kidding me, Mike?
- We hurt him.
- Fuck!
Fuck you, Mikey.
I needed something, anything,
for us to remember.
Anything for us to believe!
- God damn it!
- Fuck!
The Deadlights!
Don't look at them!
For 27 years...
I dreamt of you.
I craved you.
Oh, I've missed you!
Mike! Move back!
Waiting for this very moment.
Mikey! You gotta move, Mikey!
- Sorry. I'm sorry, guys.
- Mike, come on, man!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Time to float!
- Oh, shit!
- Sorry.
Mike, come on, get up!
Get him up!
- Go, go!
- Run!
Oh, shit!
Run! Go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
Go!
- Where'd he go?
- Don't worry. We'll find a way out.
- Oh, shit!
- Can he see us?
- Oh, my God!
- Shit.
Oh, shit.
Holy shit! Holy shit! Run!
Oh, shit!
Shit.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
We're trapped.
Where do we go?
Ahhh!
God damn it!
Um, all right. "Not Scary At All."
All right?
No, no, no.
Wait. Why?
They're flipped. He's fucking with us.
Are you sure?
- Trust me.
- Positive?
- Yes!
- Okay.
Where's my shoe?
What the fuck?
You told me to trust you!
He's not fucking with us.
- Let's go to "Not Scary At All."
- Okay.
It's all right. Let's go.
Oh, shit.
No way am I falling for this shit again.
Oh, yeah.
That thing's a fucking monster.
Richie, make it sit.
I know your moves, you little bitch.
Rich?
It's gone, man.
- Yeah. Wait.
- Okay.
Okay.
Sit.
He did it.
Oh, that's cute.
- That's a good boy.
- That's actually super cute.
That's a good boy.
- Are you a good boy?
- Good boy.
Shit!
Yo, next time,
we just go with regular "Scary."
Next time?
I lost it, Billy.
It... It just floated off.
I'm not mad at you.
It's your fault what happened, isn't it?
You weren't really that sick
that morning, were you?
No.
I just pretended...
because I didn't want to play with you.
I just didn't want to.
You lied and I died.
You lied and I died!
It happened because of me, Georgie. Me.
No, no, no.
Lied and died!
You lied and I died!
You in there, you little shit?
I can smell you.
You smell just like Lois Lane.
Here's Johnny!
All that success...
all those sit-ups...
but deep down, still just
a little fat, fat, fatty loser...
who always knew he would die alone.
No!
- Slut!
- Bev!
Beverly!
Bevvie.
Just open up the door for me, okay?
Beverly, can you hear me?
Come to Daddy, now.
Bev, don't listen!
Bev!
Are you still my little girl, Bevvie?
Beverly, I love you!
Ben!
Are you still my little girl, Bevvie?
Are you still my little girl?
Not anymore!
You little...
"Your hair is winter fire.
January embers.
My heart...
My heart..."
No!
Ben!
"January embers."
"My heart burns there, too."
It was you.
We deserve to die.
No.
You were
the best big brother there ever was.
No! We killed our little brother!
He loved you.
And just because you didn't want to play
on a rainy day...
just one time...
that does not make it our fault.
And it never...
ever...
...did.
Bill.
Miss me?
I know what you are.
That's why I'm not afraid.
Well, I know what you are.
A madman.
Hey, fuckface!
You wanna play Truth or Dare?
Here's a truth.
You're a sloppy bitch!
Yeah, that's right!
Let's dance! Yippee-ki-yay...
This kills monsters.
If you believe it does.
Beep-beep, motherfucker!
Holy shit!
Rich!
Hey, Rich, wake up!
Hey.
Yeah, yeah! There he is, buddy!
Hey, Richie, listen!
I think I got him, man!
I think I killed It!
I did! I think I killed It for real!
Eddie.
Richie.
No!
Eddie.
Uh-Oh!
No!
Eddie!
Eds!
- Eds! Eds!
- Eddie!
Eds, come on, man.
Be careful! Be careful!
Come out and play, Losers!
He's hurt. He's hurt really bad.
- We gotta get him out of here.
- Ahhh!
How are we supposed to do that, Richie?
I almost killed It.
The leper.
My hands around his throat.
And I could feel him choking.
I made him small.
He seemed so weak.
He seemed...
The Shokopiwah.
Huh?
All living things must abide by the laws
of the shape they inhabit.
Guys!
There's a passageway. Through here.
The tunnel.
Pennywise has to make himself small...
to get through the entrance
of the cavern, right?
Okay, so, if we can get back there,
we can force him down to size.
Yeah.
We make him small.
Small enough so we can kill him.
I can smell
the stink of your fear!
- Let's go! Go!
- Come on! Come on!
It's tight. Be careful!
I need a little rest. Oh, thanks.
Hey.
Hey, Richie?
I gotta tell you something.
What? What's up, buddy?
I fucked your mother.
Losers out!
Go. Go!
Gotcha!
You filthy little children.
You got a plan B, man?
What the hell do we do now?
You die. That's what you do.
Mike?
There's more than one way
to make someone small.
Oh!
Make him believe that he is.
- What?
- Make him believe that he is.
Oh? Me? Small?
I am the Eater of Worlds.
Not to us, you're not.
You're just a clown.
You're a weak old woman.
The Eater of Worlds.
A headless boy!
Impostor!
You're a mimic!
A mimic!
You're a fucking bully!
You're just a fucking clown!
Eater of Worlds!
A clown! A dumb fucking clown!
Clown!
A leper!
You're a clown!
A painting!
- You're a clown!
- I'm not afraid of you anymore!
A motherfucking stupid mummy!
You're a clown!
Clown! Clown!
- Clown!
You're a fucking clown!
You're a clown!
- A stupid mummy!
- Clown!
Clown, motherfucker!
I am the Eater of Worlds!
Clown!
- Clown!
- You're just a clown!
Clown!
I am the Eater of Worlds!
A clown!
Whoa.
No one's afraid of you.
No one's scared of you.
- Clown! Clown!
- Clown.
Clown. Clown. Clown.
Clown.
A clown.
With a scared, beating heart.
Look at you.
You're all grown up.
Eddie. Eddie.
Eddie. We got Pennywise, man.
Eddie?
Richie.
He's gone.
He's all right. No, he's just hurt.
We gotta get him outta here.
He's hurt. Ben.
Bill, he's okay.
We gotta get him outta here.
Bev.
Richie.
What?
Honey, he's dead.
We have to go. Come on, Richie.
We gotta go.
Come on, buddy. Come on.
Let him go, man.
Let him go.
Got it.
We can still help him, guys!
We can still help him!
Go! Go! Get up!
Guys, we can still help him!
No! Eddie!
Come on! Let's go!
Move, move!
- Move, move!
- Run!
Run!
- Eddie!
- No, no, no!
Eddie!
We gotta get in there and get him!
He's still in there!
Eddie!
You know what?
Eddie would have hated this, guys.
What? Cleaning ourselves in dirty water?
Yeah.
He'd be telling us
we'd get streptococcal something.
Yeah.
But he would have made us laugh, though.
Oh, yeah.
He'd be looking out for us.
The way he always was.
Ain't that right, Richie?
Hey.
Thank you.
I don't have my glasses on...
so I don't know who you people are,
but thank you.
You asshole.
I legit can't find my glasses.
You're serious?
- Glasses?
- Go that way.
Around here somewhere?
- I can't see them.
- Oh, I see them. Right there.
Where?
Look. Right...
If you just go, like...
Anybody have any luck?
Hey, guys.
Look.
Nothing lasts forever.
I can't go home like this, guys.
My mom will kill me.
Dude, you've been gone
for 24 straight hours.
Your face is definitely
on a milk carton by now.
Also, that puke smells worse
than your mom's slippers.
Oh, shut up, Richie.
Okay, first of all, my mom's slippers
smell like potpourri, asshole.
No, they don't.
Yes, they do. And, also,
how would you know
what they smell like in the first place?
Can we just keep it quiet,
please, until we get home?
"Potpourri" is literally
a French word meaning "rotten pot."
I knew there was
something rotten about it.
- Mike?
- Hey.
I just thought I'd check up on you.
You know, just to see if you learned
how to finish a book for once.
I just finished the first chapter.
And I think I actually know
where I'm going this time.
Good.
- Say, can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Why do you think we're not forgetting?
You know, like last time?
Maybe 'cause It's dead.
Or maybe 'cause we have more we want
to remember than we want to forget.
I like that one.
You decide what you want to do?
About leaving Derry?
Man, I've been in this cell
for 27 years.
Just seeing what It wanted me to.
I think it's time
I saw the sky for a change.
Go get it, Mikey.
Oh, did you get the letter?
Uh...
What letter?
You'll know when you see it.
Well, hold on. I just got the mail.
We all got one.
Patricia Uris?
Just...
Just read it.
Okay.
And call me. Anytime.
I will.
And, Bill...
I love you, man.
I love you, too.
All right. See you around.
Dear Losers...
I know what this must seem like...
but this isn't a suicide note.
You're probably wondering
why I did what I did.
It's because I knew I was too scared
to go back.
And if we weren't together...
if all of us alive weren't united...
I knew we'd all die.
So, I made the only logical move.
I took myself off the board.
Did it work?
Well, if you're reading this,
you know the answer.
I lived my whole life afraid.
Afraid of what would come next.
Afraid of what I might leave behind.
Don't.
Be who you want to be.
Be proud.
Sleep okay?
Yeah.
I had a beautiful dream.
And if you find someone worth
holding on to...
never ever let them go.
Follow your own path.
Wherever that takes you.
Think of this letter as a promise.
A promise
I'm asking you to make.
To me.
To each other.
An oath.
See, the thing
about being a Loser...
is you don't have anything to lose.
So...
Be true.
Be brave.
Stand.
Believe.
And don't ever forget...
We're Losers...
and we always will be.