Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard
LORRAINE: I had a vision
in Amityville.
I had a premonition
of your death.
(SCREAMS)
We have both seen the same
inhuman spirit.
Mom, who's that?
LORRAINE: The demon
in your painting is real.
(WIND HOWLING)
(METAL CREAKING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Are you certain we're
making the right decision?
We have no other choice.
(SISTER VICTORIA
BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SISTER JESSICA SIGHS)
Will the relic truly save us?
Have faith, Sister.
(CRYING) Our Father,
who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done on Earth
as it is in heaven.
Give us this day
our daily bread.
And forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
- (CHAINS RATTLING)
- (SISTER JESSICA SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERING LOUDLY)
(CONTINUES WHIMPERING)
SISTER JESSICA:
(PANTING) Take it!
This evil needs a vessel
to escape.
It will come after you next.
Don't let it have you.
- You know what you must do.
- I can't.
- Then not even God can save...
- (BOTH SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
(SISTER VICTORIA YELPING)
(PANTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SISTER VICTORIA CRYING)
- (DOOR OPENING)
- (GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
Forgive me, Father,
for the sin
I'm about to commit.
(CRYING)
(GASPS)
(CONTINUES CRYING)
Forgive me, Lord.
(CHAIN RATTLING)
(CREAKING)
(MAN SINGING IN FRENCH)
(GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES SINGING IN FRENCH)
- (CROWS CAWING)
- (PANTING)
(CAWING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(IN ENGLISH) Oh, God.
(CROWS SQUAWKING)
- (DOOR OPENS)
- (FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
BISHOP PASQUALE: Father Burke?
Bishop.
BISHOP PASQUALE:
So the last time you were here
was what night?
Six, seven years ago?
FATHER BURKE:
After my time as a chaplain
ended in the war, yes.
Well, we appreciate you
coming again
under such short notice.
(DOOR OPENS)
Father Burke.
Sit.
We have received news
that a nun has taken
her own life
at an abbey
in the mountains of Romania.
Suicide is a terrible,
terrible sin.
But it doesn't strike me
as strong enough reason
for a reunion.
But the news of it
would not bolster
our argument to keep
with the faith and the Church.
You're not
telling me something.
Why do you say that?
Because we're in the Vatican.
Let me put it this way,
Father.
In this, albeit,
rare instance,
we do not believe
we're the ones
with the secret.
BISHOP PASQUALE: Those are
your travel documents
and contact information
on the man
who discovered the nun.
He lives near the abbey
in a small village
called Biertan.
You will want
to talk to him first.
Also in the file is the name
of a postulant who can help
assist you in your inquiries
since it is
a cloistered convent
and your access
will be limited.
She's also familiar
with the territory.
SISTER IRENE: I have survived
many terrifying encounters.
But nothing could have ever
prepared me for this.
My only hope now was that
the beast could not smell me.
But then,
the wind changed and...
- (ROARS)
- (STUDENTS GASP)
- (SCREAMS)
- (STUDENTS LAUGHING)
Run for your lives!
Mother Superior says
that dinosaurs
were never really alive.
God just put their bones here
to test our faith.
That seems like a pretty
dirty trick, don't you think?
GIRL: But they're not
in the Bible.
SISTER IRENE: Well, do you believe
in penguins and koala bears?
ALL: Yes.
They aren't in
the Bible either.
The Bible is
God's love letter to us,
but it doesn't mean that He
doesn't want us to ask questions
about the wonders
of His creation.
- But Mother Superior says...
- (GASPS)
Wait a minute. You've got a
little something on your nose.
- There.
- (STUDENTS LAUGH)
Ahem.
(STUDENTS GASP)
STUDENTS: Ooh!
- SISTER IRENE: The Vatican?
- I'm as surprised as you.
I haven't even taken
my vows yet.
Oh, he's aware of that.
He's waiting for you
in the garden.
And change into your habit.
This is an official visit.
FATHER BURKE: It shouldn't take
more than a few days, at most.
You were recommended
for the journey
because of your familiarity
with the territory.
"The territory"?
Yes. Romania.
I'd never been
in that part of the world.
Really?
There must've been
some mistake.
I apologize if you coming here
was a waste of your time.
Oh, no, no.
No apology necessary.
Every decision the Vatican
makes is with purpose.
I'm sure they had their
reasons for selecting you.
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
What is it?
Mr. Theriault?
Hi.
Jealous husband
or angry father?
I'm sorry, what?
Well, usually
it's one of the two
when an older man
and a young, beautiful,
not-so-innocent girl
show up on my doorstep
at this hour of the morning.
I beg your pardon,
Mr. Theriault,
but you and I have never met.
Oh.
Oh. Then perhaps
it's time we did.
Call me Frenchie.
Everyone does.
Mr. Theriault, we are here
because of the nun
you found at the abbey.
How'd you...
Are you priest?
And she is a nun.
Oh. (CHUCKLING)
Forgive me for
my impure thoughts, Sister.
I had no idea.
Never seen a nun
out of her vestments.
Not that I'm opposed to it.
Excuse me.
Monsieur Theriault,
the abbey.
Is it far?
In matter of distance, no,
but it takes time to get to.
If I may ask,
why were you there?
I was delivering
the quarterly supplies.
Apparently, the abbey has had
some kind of arrangement
with the village
for centuries.
FATHER BURKE: Do you think you
could take us there sometime soon?
FRENCHIE:
I don't think so, Father.
Is there someone else
in the village, then?
Everyone in this village
pretend like the abbey
doesn't exist.
Even talking about it
might get you in trouble.
It's settled, then.
You will take us.
With all due respect,
Father, I...
Please, Frenchie.
(BOTH SPEAKING ROMANIAN)
You took a plane from Rome,
a bus from Bucharest.
Now, my friends,
you're in the Dark Ages.
- In the backwoods of Romania.
- (ENGINE STALLS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Now, you travel by horse.
- Where are your things?
- (LAUGHING)
(WHISTLES)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
FATHER BURKE:
"The postman's charge."
Ten letters with an "L."
Deliveries.
You have a knack for this,
Sister.
SISTER IRENE:
What brings a Frenchman
to the countryside of Romania?
Actually, I'm French-Canadian,
but don't tell anyone.
Doesn't sound as romantic.
I came here looking for gold
but when I met
the people here,
I just knew this was the place
I was meant to be.
Wanted to help them.
Any way I could.
That's very noble of you.
I know.
Tell me, Sister,
how long have you been a nun?
I'm not a nun yet.
I'm still just a novitiate.
You still haven't taken
your temporary vows?
"Temporary"?
I didn't think
there was anything temporary
about being a nun.
Temporary vows
would help prepare me
for a life
of total consecration.
"Would," Sister? Or "will"?
Whoa.
What happened?
- Everything all right?
- (HORSE WHINNIES)
FRENCHIE: We walk
the rest of the way.
The horse won't go
any further.
(SISTER IRENE GRUNTS)
Maybe you should get
a new horse.
Well, it's not the horse,
Father.
It's what lies ahead.
He's scared.
The locals say
it's a cursed place
and the horse agrees.
SISTER IRENE:
If I may ask, Father,
why is it the Church sends you
on such tasks?
The Church reaches out to me
when it needs an investigation
into unusual phenomenon
associated with Catholicism.
Unofficially, they call it
"miracle hunting."
I thought we were here
because of a suicide.
We are, but it's only part
of our investigation.
I also have orders
from the Vatican to determine
if the grounds
are still... holy.
FRENCHIE: Well, I can give you
my opinion
on that now, Father.
A result of the war?
Bombing raids, yes.
I've heard stories of how the
ground shook for days after them.
I've tried to find more
information on the castle itself,
but there's no record of it
in the village.
And the locals only spit
when it's mentioned.
- "Spit"?
- Yeah, to ward off evil.
It's an old
and silly superstition.
And if you ask me,
these crosses that surround
the abbey
they keep the evil in,
not out.
Did you try to contact someone
inside when you found the nun?
FRENCHIE: I did.
No one responded.
But then again,
in the two years I've been
delivering supplies,
she was the first one
I'd seen.
FATHER BURKE: Frenchie, when you
found the nun, what did you do?
FRENCHIE: I moved it to protect
the body from the elements.
FATHER BURKE:
Where did you move it to, son?
The icehouse.
It's where
I leave my deliveries.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
When I found the sister,
I thought
maybe moving her in here
would help preserve her.
Uh...
(MUMBLES)
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKS FRENCH)
(FRENCHIE SIGHS)
I should tell you
one more thing, Father.
What?
That's not how I left her.
What do you mean?
She was laying down
when I left her here.
Not like that, sitting up.
FATHER BURKE:
There have been cases
of bodies twitching
or sitting up,
not long after death.
Yeah, but, Father, who knows
how long she was dead
when I found her?
You're not helping.
Sorry.
SISTER IRENE:
Father, what is it?
It seems to be a key
of some kind.
(DOOR RATTLING)
That's the door the nuns
would enter from
to retrieve the supplies.
So they wouldn't have
to leave the castle.
We should give her
a proper burial.
(PRAYING IN LATIN)
(BELL RINGING)
(IN ENGLISH)
It was common practice
during the plague.
When people feared to be
buried alive.
If you were unfortunate enough
for it to happen,
you could ring the bell
to let those above ground know
they have made a mistake.
I think being here
is a mistake.
(RINGING)
FRENCHIE:
That's where I found her.
How is that possible?
It's been weeks.
I told you. This place is...
What's the opposite
of a miracle, Father?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SISTER IRENE GASPS)
(SHUDDERING)
Hello?
Please excuse us
for our unannounced arrival.
Hello?
THE ABBESS:
What is it you want?
I'm Father Anthony Burke.
This is Sister Irene.
Are you the Reverend Mother?
THE ABBESS: I am.
You haven't taken
your vows yet.
Uh...
(STAMMERS) No.
- Please...
- Why are you here, Father?
We come on behalf of Rome,
to inquire about the
recent death in your convent.
THE ABBESS: "Recent death"?
One of your nuns.
I found her outside.
Hanged from the neck.
(THE ABBESS SPEAKING FRENCH)
(IN ENGLISH) Would you
allow us a moment, please?
THE ABBESS: You should leave
with him.
Are you saying
you weren't aware
of the recent passing
of the nun?
Rome is concerned
about the safety
and well-being
of your cloister.
I'd like to speak
with the sisters
so I can offer my assurances
to the Church.
THE ABBESS: I can offer
the assurance you seek.
I'm afraid that won't suffice.
They will just send more,
and, uh,
perhaps less diplomatic,
church officials.
THE ABBESS: Yes, Father.
However, the gate
will be closing shortly
as we are about to take
our vespers.
Followed by the Great Silence
which ends midmorning.
Come back tomorrow
and you will find the answers
you seek.
There is lodging
in the convent.
You may stay there.
Thank you.
FRENCHIE: Why could you
not talk to the sisters now?
Why must it wait till morning?
The sisters take
a vow of silence
from sunset to sunrise
that must be respected.
You should begin
heading back yourself.
I imagine you don't want to be caught
on those roads when night falls.
Better the roads than here,
Father.
We'll be fine, son.
Come back in a few days.
That should give us enough
time to get what we need.
Yes, Father.
(SINGING IN FRENCH)
(GASPS)
Hello?
(LEAVES RUSTLING)
Hey.
Hey!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (DISTANT ANIMAL SOUNDS)
- (CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SNARLS)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
- (PANTING)
- (GROWLING)
(YELPING)
I'll take (GRUNTS) that.
(PANTING)
Okay.
All right.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
- SISTER IRENE: Father?
- Hmm?
You mentioned
"miracle hunting" before.
Is that...
Is that a role you sought out?
No.
God, no.
(CHUCKLES) I'm a part
of a small select few
the Church relies on to
look into their more
unusual matters.
So, you know Bishop Forne?
How do you...
Because he helped me
when I was younger.
I had a series of visions
when I was a girl.
My father believed
I was mentally unstable.
Or worse, a liar.
But word of my visions
reached the Church.
Cardinal Conroy, specifically.
And he sent Bishop Forne
to meet with me.
What were your visions?
(SIGHS) There were many.
Never the same one repeated.
But after each one ended,
the same thought
would be stuck in my head.
Which was... what?
"Mary points the way."
(FATHER BURKE SIGHS)
What is it, Father?
I was thinking
of a similar incident
I encountered in France.
During the war.
I was stationed there.
Near Lyon.
I was told to investigate
a boy with visions.
(DANIEL BREATHING HEAVILY)
But, unlike your case,
after what I believe
was careful evaluation...
(SNIFFS)
I made the judgment
he was possessed,
and proceeded
to act accordingly
within the laws of the Church.
My God. Daniel...
What have they done to you?
(DANIEL SNARLING)
Was it a success?
The Church thought so.
They believed the evil
was cast out.
But not you.
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
Most Glorious Prince
of the Heavenly Armies,
Saint Michael, the archangel...
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(CRYING) Help me, Father!
Come to the assistance
of Daniel,
whom God has made
in His likeness!
- (SCREAMS)
- Behold the Cross of the Lord!
Why won't you help me?
Ye hostile forces!
(SCREAMING)
Daniel sustained
severe injuries
during the exorcism.
Ones from which
he could not recover.
Daniel, I'm so sorry.
He died days later.
I often wonder
if I was too eager
with my determination.
That is a puzzle.
(STATIC)
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
- (FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
- (OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
DANIEL: (WHISPERS) Father.
(RUSTLING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(TWIG SNAPS)
(RUSTLING)
DANIEL: (WHISPERS) Father.
Daniel?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(DANIEL GAGGING)
(YELPS)
- Wait! No! Help!
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
Help! No!
(BELL RINGING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
Help!
Somebody.
(EERIE CHANTING)
(EERIE CHANTING CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
(SHUDDERS)
(GROWLING)
(YELPS)
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (CROSS CREAKING)
(GASPING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RINGING)
Help! Sister Irene! Help!
(BELL CONTINUES RINGING)
Father! Father?
(PANTING)
Father?
(CONTINUES PANTING)
(CONTINUES RINGING)
(GASPS)
(BELLS RINGING)
(RINGING INTENSIFIES)
Help!
Help me!
(GASPS)
(SINGLE BELL RINGING)
- Father?
- (MUFFLED) Sister?
- Sister Irene!
- Father, I can hear you!
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
- I'm right here!
(PANTING) Oh, thank God.
Thank you.
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INAUDIBLE)
(SCRATCHING)
(SISTER IRENE GRUNTING)
(SCRATCHING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
(THUDS)
(SHOVEL THUDDING)
(SIGHS)
(YELPING)
Hurry!
(CONTINUES YELPING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
- (GRUNTS LOUDLY)
- Wait! Wait!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FATHER BURKE GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
- (PANTING)
- (COUGHING)
Thank you. Thank you, Sister.
(GRUNTING)
How did you get in there?
The ground was covered.
There is a powerful
evil presence in this place.
Maybe those books will help
shine a light on our answer.
SISTER IRENE:
There's more of it.
How is that possible?
- Another puzzle.
- (CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
Abbess?
As requested,
we are here to speak
with the nuns.
It seems like that's as much
as an invitation as we'll get.
I'll go find the Abbess.
Take this.
See what you can find out
about it.
It was obviously important
to the deceased.
Sister. Be careful, please.
I will, Father.
- (CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
Hello?
Wait!
(SISTER RUTH PRAYING IN LATIN)
Sister?
(SISTER RUTH
CONTINUES IN LATIN)
SISTER OANA: (IN ENGLISH)
Sister!
We mustn't stop praying,
even for a second.
This convent has had
perpetual adoration
for centuries.
The sisters pray in shifts
to maintain a constant vigil.
I am so sorry
to have disturbed her.
Sister Ruth has withstood
more than just someone
sneaking up behind her.
I'm Sister Oana.
We were told you were coming.
Please, follow me.
(SISTER RUTH
CONTINUES IN LATIN)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What?
Another round.
I told Luca
it was on the house.
FRENCHIE: Why did she cover
the mirror?
It's tradition here
when someone dies.
You cover the mirror,
so the deceased
doesn't see their reflection
and become a ghost.
Someone died?
You didn't hear? Luca's
daughter committed suicide.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I can't believe it.
She was just a kid.
Twelve years old.
Hanged herself in his barn.
Hanged herself? Why?
Why did Addi Constantine's
crop turn to dust?
Why was little Stefan
struck blind?
It is that place. The abbey.
Whatever evil is up there,
it's leaking out,
poisoning us.
(SPITS)
And that, uh, couple you took
up there yesterday.
- Who were they?
- Priest and a nun.
Are they still up there?
Yeah. Pick them up tomorrow.
You recently discovered a body
up there, didn't you?
Yeah, Grigore, yeah.
Well, I believe you're about
to discover two more.
FATHER BURKE:
And out of the ground
formed every beast
of the field
and every bird of the sky.
And whatever the man
called the demon creature,
that was its name.
Valak.
The Defiler.
The Profane.
The Marquis of Snakes.
(RATTLING)
Sister!
Sister Irene!
SISTER OANA:
Sister Victoria's death
was a terrible tragedy
for the convent,
but we still
feel her presence.
She was the most devoted
out of any of us.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Excuse me, Sister.
- Sister Vic...
- (DOOR LOCK CLANKS)
(DOOR CREAKING)
Forgive us,
we're highly protective
of our privacy.
Some of the sisters
would prefer
I not speak to you at all.
We appreciate your willingness
to do so.
Sister Oana,
can you tell me about
the history of this abbey?
It was built by a duke
in the Dark Ages.
The Duke of Saint Carta.
He wrote countless texts
on witchcraft and rituals,
in which to call upon
the forces of hell.
Hell used him
to open a gateway
so that an unspeakable evil
would walk amongst us.
(RUMBLING)
But the Church
stormed the castle.
They sealed the gateway
using an ancient relic
containing the blood
of Jesus Christ.
The Church claimed the castle
for their own
and our perpetual
praying began
to secure the abbey
and contain the evil.
For centuries it worked
and evil was kept at bay
until the bombs of war
shook the abbey
and evil found another way
to open the gateway.
Sister Oana,
last night in the chapel,
I saw a nun.
She was...
She felt anything but holy.
Do you see her, too?
I've seen her stalking
the hallways at night.
We all have.
She looks like us,
but she's not one of us.
It's something unholy.
It takes on different forms
to deceive us
and prey on our weaknesses.
It appears as a nun so it can
hide among our cloister
until it can corrupt us all.
I fear her presence means
the portal has opened again.
It made Sister Victoria
commit the ultimate sin.
SISTER ABIGAIL: Sister Oana.
Sister Ruth is nearly finished
with her prayers.
It's time you attend to yours.
SISTER OANA: Yes, Sister.
You haven't taken
your vows yet?
No.
Then this is not a place
for you.
- You need to leave now.
- SISTER OANA: She can't.
The gates have closed.
You must stay
until they open again.
When do they open?
SISTER OANA: Sunrise.
You must stay the night.
Sister Irene.
Good night, Sister.
Sister, wait.
Yes?
Sister Victoria had this
in her possession
when she died.
Do you happen to know
what it's for?
No.
Now, please, I must go pray.
(LOCK CLICKS)
(FOOTSTEPS RETREATING)
Where are you?
THE ABBESS: You won't find
another way in, Father.
Abbess?
THE ABBESS: What is it
that concerns you?
I'm afraid
there's something very wrong
with this place, Abbess.
THE ABBESS: Like many places
in this world,
the abbey has a long history.
Not all good but we repent.
That nun, I found her
clutching the key
in her hands.
What does it open, Abbess?
THE ABBESS:
It's too late, Father.
Sister Irene is lost.
(BONES CRACK)
Abbess?
- (FATHER BURKE YELPING)
- (CANDLE CLATTERS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
FATHER BURKE: Sister Irene.
SISTER IRENE:
Mary points the way.
(ECHOING) Mary points the way.
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
(SHUDDERING)
(RUSTLING)
(VOICE PRAYING IN LATIN)
- Who are you?
- (BONES CRACKING)
(PRAYER BEADS CLINKING)
(SHIVERING)
- God save you.
- (GASPS)
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
(SISTER IRENE
BREATHING HEAVILY)
SISTER VICTORIA:
Sister, please come.
Sister Oana?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(SISTER IRENE
BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
(GASPS)
Oh, God.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WIND HOWLING)
(GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES GRUNTING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SCREAMING)
- (PANTING)
- (ROARING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(MUFFLED WHIMPERING)
(WHISPERS) Quiet.
The evil grows stronger.
Get your things and meet me
in the chapel, Sister.
Only prayer will
get us through the night.
Go. Leave.
Now.
(WHISPERING VOICES)
(SISTER ABIGAIL
PRAYING IN LATIN)
SISTER IRENE: Hello?
(SISTER ABIGAIL
CONTINUES PRAYING IN LATIN)
SISTER IRENE: Sister Oana?
(SISTER ABIGAIL CONTINUES
PRAYING IN LATIN)
DANIEL: How long
have I been dead, Father?
How long?
Daniel?
I'm sorry.
(SHOUTS)
Why won't you help me?
(RUMBLING)
(GASPS)
- (GRUNTING)
- (SNARLING)
(SISTER ABIGAIL
PRAYING IN LATIN)
SISTER RUTH:
We need to pray, now.
And whatever happens,
whatever you may see or hear,
keep your eyes forward
and don't stop praying.
(ALL PRAYING IN LATIN)
(GASPING)
(PRAYING IN LATIN)
- (ALL CONTINUE PRAYING)
- (SISTER IRENE PANTING)
(SISTER IRENE
PRAYING IN LATIN)
(SCREAMS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PRAYING IN LATIN)
FRENCHIE: That's the door
the nuns would enter from
to retrieve the supplies.
So they wouldn't have
to leave the castle.
(BELL RINGS)
(BELL RINGING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROWLING)
No, no.
(FATHER BURKE GRUNTING)
- (OBJECTS CLATTER)
- (SNARLING)
(FRENCHIE GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Holy mother of God.
Frenchie!
Thought you could use
some help.
(FATHER BURKE
BREATHING HEAVILY)
Thank you.
But please, by all means,
next time, do use the shotgun.
Well, I'm saving that
for emergencies, Father.
(PRAYING IN LATIN)
(SNIFFLES)
(NUNS GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
- (NUNS CONTINUE PRAYING)
FATHER BURKE: Sister!
Sister Irene!
(POUNDING CONTINUES)
SISTER IRENE: Father Burke.
(GROANS)
It's Father Burke.
He will help us.
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
- FATHER BURKE: Sister!
(LOUD POUNDING ON DOOR)
Sister Irene!
(SISTER IRENE GRUNTING)
SISTER IRENE:
Oh, thank God, Father.
- Are you all right, Sister?
- (EXHALES SHARPLY)
Frenchie?
What happened?
We, we've been praying,
all of us together.
Perpetual adoration,
it's the only thing that's
been holding back the evil.
Who's been praying?
All of us. The other nuns.
They were here.
They were praying
when we were attacked.
The nuns tried to warn me.
Visions.
They felt so real.
There's no one left.
We have our answer, Father.
As if there was
any doubt before,
this place is no longer holy.
(FATHER BURKE SIGHS)
- Oh, Father. Lord Jesus...
- (SNARLS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
FRENCHIE:
Father, what do we do?
(SNARLING)
Get my bag, Sister!
Hand me the cross!
Put some holy water on it.
Here, hurry!
Please, Father, hurry!
- (CHANTS IN LATIN)
- (SNARLS)
Hold it down! Cover its face!
(FRENCHIE GRUNTING)
(FATHER BURKE CHANTS IN LATIN)
(IN ENGLISH)
I cast out the demon in you,
in the name
of God the Father Almighty!
And the power
of the holy spirit,
I ask this in the name
of our Father, Jesus Christ,
who is coming to judge
both the living and the dead,
and the world of fire!
(GROANS LOUDLY)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL PANTING)
That felt like an emergency.
We're too late.
The evil is free.
No.
For the demon
to enter our world,
it must possess a human soul.
Sister Victoria must have been
the last nun in this cloister.
SISTER JESSICA:
You know what you must do.
I can't.
- Then not even God can save...
- (SCREAMING)
It wasn't suicide.
It was a sacrifice,
so the evil
wouldn't take her soul.
I did not understand a word
you just said, but, uh...
Sounds like
your investigation's complete.
So, let's get outta here.
We can't just leave.
Oh, come on. Why the hell not?
We have to seal the gateway,
to contain the evil.
SISTER IRENE: The gateway
is in the catacombs.
- (FATHER BURKE GRUNTS)
- But we can't close it
without the relic.
The blood of Christ.
"Christ." Jesus Christ?
Did the sisters tell you
where it is?
The Abbess was found dead
in the tunnel
to the catacombs.
(SIGHS)
I think I know
where that tunnel is.
Good. Then, that's where
we look first.
But, Father, before we do,
I'd like to take my vows.
Are you certain?
My visions.
I now know
they are a miracle of God.
And I am ready to commit
my life to Him.
FRENCHIE: Now, that, Sister,
is a noble act.
It's a shame, but...
FATHER BURKE: By the authority
entrusted to me,
and in the name of the Church,
I receive the vows
you have taken.
I earnestly
commend you to God.
That your gift of self,
is made one
with the sacrifice
of the Eucharist.
And might be brought
to perfection.
May the love of God
unite you forever and ever.
(PRAYS IN LATIN)
(WATER DRIPPING)
FRENCHIE:
Well, there's nothing here.
SISTER IRENE: There has to be.
They told me this key unlocks
a door to the relic.
That could be
anywhere in the castle.
It is here.
Don't you see it, Sister?
What?
Mary points the way.
(GASPS)
FATHER BURKE:
The blood of Christ.
Holy shit.
The holiest.
Only a true bride of Christ
can wield something so sacred.
Wait.
What is it?
Shouldn't we say
a prayer or something, first?
There's a time for prayer,
and a time for action, son.
Now is the time for action.
Also still feels like a time
for prayer as well, Father.
"Finit hic, Deo."
God ends here.
(DOOR OPENS)
SISTER IRENE: We need
to search everywhere
to find the gateway.
(METAL CLANGING)
(FRENCHIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR CREAKS)
- (SNARLING)
- (GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING)
VOICE: (WHISPERING)
Sister Irene, this way.
(SISTER IRENE GASPS)
Hello? (GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
(NUN SNARLING)
Sister Irene!
Sister!
(PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
- (SISTER IRENE SCREAMS)
- (GASPS)
Irene!
(GRUNTS)
(WHISPERING VOICES)
(NUNS CHANTING)
- (BONES CRACKING)
- (CHANTING STOPS)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
Lord Jesus, in your Holy Name,
I bind all evil spirits
to this fire!
Protect us from evil
with your holy light!
(LANTERN GLASS SHATTERS)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
SISTER IRENE:
Frenchie. Help me.
Of course.
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(FRENCHIE PRAYING IN FRENCH)
- (SCREECHING)
- (FRENCHIE SCREAMING)
No!
You failed.
Just as you have failed
everyone in your life.
(GRUNTING)
Tomorrow, a village will be
missing its idiot.
You should've kept running
when you had the chance,
Frenchman.
I am French-Canadian.
(FRENCHIE GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
Run!
(FRENCHIE GROANING)
SISTER IRENE: Frenchie!
(FRENCHIE SCREAMING)
No!
(HISSING)
(SCREAMING)
- (CHOKING)
- (SNARLING)
(GASPING)
Sister!
Sister Irene!
- (SNARLING)
- (FATHER BURKE GRUNTING)
(SNAKE HISSING)
(CHOKING)
(HISSING)
(GROANING)
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHIMPERING)
(SISTER IRENE SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
(CHANTING IN LATIN)
(SCREAMING)
(SNARLING)
(GASPS)
(SPITS)
(SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
(FRENCHIE GRUNTING)
No, no, no, no, no!
(PANTING)
Come on.
(COUGHING)
Okay.
(GROANS)
FRENCHIE:
I hope you don't mind.
It's called
"the kiss of life."
It's just called that way.
It's just, it's not really...
Frenchie,
what's your real name?
Maurice.
Thank you
for saving my life, Maurice.
You're welcome.
We should get going.
SISTER IRENE:
Into your hands, O Lord,
we humbly deliver
your servants.
The nuns of Saint Carta.
They served you in this life
with strength and faith.
Deliver them now
from every evil.
And let them live with you
in perfect grace, forever.
Amen.
Thought this ground
wasn't holy anymore.
It is now.
Will you stay on in Biertan?
FRENCHIE: Oh, I think
I've had my fill of Romania.
My father was a tomato farmer.
Maybe I'll try that
for a while.
Sounds a little boring
for a world traveler like you.
(CHUCKLES) Certainly hope so.
ED: An exorcism can be
very dangerous.
Not only for the victim,
but for anyone in the room.
Take Maurice Theriault,
his friends
called him Frenchie.
He was
a French-Canadian farmer.
Nothing more
than a third grade education.
Yet, after he was possessed...
- (SNARLS)
- (CHOKING)
ED: ...spoke some of
the best Latin I'd ever heard.
LORRAINE: And like that,
an upside-down cross
started to appear
from within his body.
ED: Which brings me
to the three stages
of demonic activity.
Infestation, oppression,
and possession.
(LORRAINE SCREAMING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Resync by GoldenBeard