AGATHE: Once upon a time in the
hidden heart of France.
A handsome young prince
lived in a beautiful castle.
PLUMETTE: Poof! Poof!
Although he had everything
his heart desired,
the Prince was selfish and unkind.
COGSWORTH: Master, it's time.
He taxed the village
to fill his castle with the most
beautiful objects.
And his parties with the most
beautiful people.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
♪ Oh, how defined ♪
♪ Glamour music and magic combined ♪
♪ See the maidens for anxious to shine ♪
♪ Look for a sign that in the hands,
chances, ♪
♪ She'll be his special one ♪
♪ What a play ♪
♪ What a breathtaking, thrilling array ♪
♪ Every prince, every has a day ♪
♪ Let us sing with passion,
gusto, fit to bust, oh ♪
♪ Not a care in the world ♪
♪♪
(KNOCKING ON GLASS)
(ALL GASP)
(THUNDER CRACKING)
AGATHE: Then one night,
an unexpected intruder arrived
at the castle,
seeking shelter from the
bestest storm.
As a gift, she offered
the Prince a single rose.
(LAUGHING)
(ALL LAUGH)
Repulsed by her haggard
appearance,
the Prince turned the woman away.
But she warned him not to be deceived
by appearances.
For beauty is found within.
When he dismissed her again,
the old woman's out with her appearance
melted away.
(WOMAN GASPS)
To reveal...
a beautiful enchantress.
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
The Prince begged for forgiveness,
but he was too late.
Cause she had seen that
there was no love in his heart.
Chip! Chip! Oh, Lord!
As punishment...
she transformed him into
a hideous beast.
And placed a powerfull
spell on the castle...
and all who lived there.
(THE BEAST ROARING)
As days bleed into years...
The Prince and his servants
were forgotten by the world.
For the enchantress had erased
all memory of them,
from the minds of the people
they loved.
But the rose she had offered was truly
an enchanted rose.
If he could learn to love another...
and earned their love in return
by the time the last petal fell,
the spell would be broken.
If not, he would be doomed to remain
a beast for all time.
As the years passed,
he fell into despair and lost
all hope.
For who could ever learn to love
a beast?
(ROOSTER CALLING)
*BEAUTY AND THE BEAST*
Synchronized by srjanapala
♪ Little town,
it's a quite village ♪
♪ Everyday, like the one before ♪
♪ Little town, full of little people ♪
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
♪ Waking up to say... ♪
Bonjour.
- Bonjour.
♪ Morning. ♪
♪ There goes the baker
with his tray, like always ♪
♪ The same all bread and rolls
to sell ♪
♪ Every morning just the same ♪
♪ Since the morning that we came
to this poor provincial town. ♪
Good morning, Belle!
Good morning Monsieur Jean!
Have you lost something again?
Well, I believe I have.
The problem is, I can't remember what!
I'm sure it'll come through me.
Where are you off to?
To return this book to
Pere Robert.
It's about two lovers in fair Verona.
Sounds boring.
SCHOOL BOYS: ♪ Look there she goes that
girl is strange, no question ♪
♪ Dazed and distracted, can't you tell? ♪
♪♪
♪ Never part of any crowd ♪
♪ 'Cause her head's up on some cloud ♪
♪ No denying she's a
funny girl that Belle ♪
♪ Bonjour, good day!
How is your family? ♪
How is your wife? ♪
(MAN GRUNTS)
♪ I need six eggs,
that's too expensive. ♪
♪ There must be more than
this provincial life. ♪
Ah! If it isn't the only bookworm
in town!
So, where did you run off to
this week?
Two cities in northern Italy.
I didn't want to come back.
Have you got any new places to go?
I'm afraid not.
But you may re-read any
of the old ones that you'd like.
Thank you.
Your library makes a small
corner of the wall seems big.
(BIDS GOODBYE IN FRENCH).
Bye.
ALL: ♪ Look there she goes that
girl is so peculiar ♪
♪ I wonder if she's feeling well? ♪
Otherwise
♪ With a dreamy far-off look
and her nose stuck in a book. ♪
♪ What a puzzle to the rest of us
is Belle. ♪
♪ Aaaaaaaaah~ Isn't this amazing? ♪
♪ It's my favorite parts, because ♪
♪ you'll see.. ♪
♪ Here's where she meets Prince Charming
♪ But she won't discover that it's him,
'til chapter three ♪
♪ Now it's no wonder that her name
means "beauty" ♪
♪ Her looks have got no parallel ♪
♪ But behind that fair facade
I'm afraid she's rather odd ♪
♪ Very different from the rest of us ♪
♪ She's nothing like the rest of us ♪
♪ Yes, different from the rest of us ♪
♪ Is Belle ♪
♪♪
GASTON: Look at her, LeFou.
My future wife.
Belle is the most beautiful girl
in the village.
That makes her the best.
But she's so well-read.
And you so..
Athletically inclined.
I know.
Belle can be as argumentative
as she's beautiful.
Exactly! Who needs her, when you've
got us?
Yes..
Ever since the war, I felt like,
I've been missing someting.
And she is the only girl
who gives me that sense of...
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
I don't know what that means.
♪ Right from the moment when
I met her, saw her. ♪
♪ I said, "she's gorgeous"
and I fell ♪
♪ Here in town there's only she,
who is beautiful as me. ♪
♪ So I making plan to woo
and marry Belle. ♪
♪ Look there he goes. ♪
♪ Isn't he dreamy? ♪
♪ Monsieur Gaston, oh!
He's so cute! ♪
♪ Be still my heart
I'm hardly breathing ♪
♪ He's such a tall, dark, strong and
handsome brute ♪
(GIRLS SQUEAL)
It's never gonna happen, ladies.
(GIRLS SIGH)
(SINGING) ♪ Bonjour!
Pardon! ♪
♪ Good day!
Mais oui! ♪
♪ You call this bacon?
What lovely grapes! ♪
♪ Some cheese­
Ten yards ♪
- One pound
- Excuse me ♪
♪ I'll get the knife
Please, let me through! ♪
♪ This bread
Those fish ♪
♪ It's stale!
They smell ♪
♪ Madame's mistaken ♪
♪ There must be more than
this provincial life! ♪
TOWN SFOLK
♪ Just watch, I'm going
to make Belle my wife! ♪
♪ Look there she goes a girl
who's strange but special ♪
♪ A most peculiar mad'moiselle ♪
♪ It's a pity and a sin
She doesn't quite fit in ♪
♪ 'Cause she really is a funny girl
A beauty but a funny girl ♪
♪ She really is a funny girl! ♪
♪ That Belle~ ♪
Good morrning, Belle!
Ah! Wonderful book
you have there!
Have you read it?
Well, not that one.
But, you know, books...(CHUCKLES)
For your dinner table.
Shall I join you this evening?
Sorry, not this evening.
Busy?
No...
So, moving on?
No, LeFou.
It's the ones who play hard to get
that are always the sweetest prey.
That what makes Belle
so appealing.
She hasn't made a fool of herself
just to gain my favour.
How would you call that?
Dignity?
It's outrageously attractive, isn't it?
WOMAN: Gaston!
Mmm.
(MUSIC BOX PLAYING)
(SINGING) ♪ How does
a moment last forever? ♪
♪ How can a story never died? ♪
♪ It is love we must hold onto. ♪
♪ Never easy, but we try. ♪
♪ Sometimes our happiness is captured. ♪
♪ Somehow a time and place stand still. ♪
♪ Love leads on inside our hearts. ♪
♪ And always will. ♪
Oh, Belle!
Could you..?
Hand me a...
Thank you.
And I also need..
No. No.
Actually...
Yes, that's exactly what I need.
Thank you.
Papa, do you think I'm odd?
Odd?
My daughter? Odd?
Where did you get an idea
like that?
I don't know. People talk.
This is a small village, you know.
Small minded, as well.
But, small also means safe.
Even back in Paris, I knew a girl
like you, who would be so...
ahead of a time.
Different.
People mocked her.
Until the day they all found themselves
imitating her.
Please, just tell me one more thing
about her.
Your mother was..
Fearless.
(EXCLAIMS)
So,
what can I bring you from the market?
A rose.
Like the one in the painting.
You ask of that every year!
And every year you bring it.
Then I should bring you another.
You have my word.
Bye, Papa.
Bye, Belle.
Come on, Philippe.
(PHILIPPE WHINNIES)
You know the way.
I'll see you tomorrow!
Right!
Tomorrow, with the rose!
(CHUCKLES)
Stay safe.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
GIRL: What are you doing?
The laundry.
Come! Come!
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
"The Blue Bird.."
"that flies over..."
"the dark..."
"wood".
That was amazing!
What on earth are you doing?
Teaching another girl to read?
Isn't one enough?
We have to do something.
(MEN GRUNTING)
You are the wildest,
most gorgeous thing
I've ever seen.
Nobody deserves you.
But at least I know our children
will be beautiful.
Am I catching you at a bad time?
- What is it, LeFou?
- A damsel is in distress.
It's hero time.
I'm not done with you, yet.
Me, neither.
GASTON: Belle! I heard you had trouble
with the headmaster.
He never liked me either.
Can I give you a little advise
about the villagers, Belle?
They're never gonna trust the kind of
change you're trying to bring them.
All I wanted was to teach a child
to read.
The only children you should concern
yourself, will be..
Your own.
I'm...
not ready to have children.
Maybe you haven't met the right man.
It's a small village, Gaston.
I've met them all.
Well, maybe you should take
another look.
Some of us have changed.
Gaston,
we could never
make each other happy.
No one can changed that much.
Oh, Belle.
Do you know what happens to spinsters in
this village after their fathers died?
AGATHE: Coins? Could you spare me coins?
They beg for scraps,
like poor Agathe.
This is our world, Belle.
For simple folk like us,
it doesn't getting better.
I want to be a farm girl.
But I'm not simple.
And..
I'm never going to marry you, Gaston.
I'm sorry!
(EXHALES)
(SINGING) ♪ Can you imagine? ♪
♪ Me? The wife of that boorish, ♪
♪ brainless... ♪
♪ Madam Gaston, can't you just see it? ♪
♪ Madame Gaston, his little wife.
Ugh! ♪
♪ No, Sir. Not me, I guarantee it ♪
♪ I want much more than this
provincial life ♪
♪♪
♪ I want adventure in the great wide
somewhere ♪
♪♪
♪ I want it more than I can tell ♪
♪ And for once it might be grand ♪
♪♪
♪ To have someone understand ♪
♪ I want so much more than
they've got planned ♪
♪♪
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(PHILIPPE NEIGHS
The woods are lovely.
I only wish I'd recognized them.
Do you know where we are, Philippe?
Cause I don't.
(WHINNYING)
It's all right. It's all right.
Philippe.
Hmm
Yes, we can go this way.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Go on. To the right.
That's it! Steady!
Walk on.
One door closes,
another one opens.
All right, boy.
Just a bit of snow.
In June.
Mind your step.
It's slippery.
(NEIGHS)
(GROWLING)
Go, go Philippe! Come on! Come on!
- (HOWLING)
- Whoa
(WOLVES GROWLING)
Come on!
Go, Philippe! Go! Go! Go!
(MAURICE YELLS AND GRUNTS
(PHILIPPE WHINNYING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
(EXCLAIMING)
Philippe!
Good boy.
Go, boy! Go!
(WOLF HOWLING)
Oh! Philippe, you saved my life!
Well done. Ehh.
They'll have to get their dinner
somewhere else, won't they?
(CHUCKLES)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
Look!
It's hay!
And water.
You are safe, my old friend.
I'll go pay my respects to our
unwitting host.
Whoever that may be.
Thank you.
Thank...
Hello?
Sorry to intrude.
I'm a.. just a traveler,
seeking shelter from the storm.
Sorry to disturb you.
Anyone home?
Anyone awake?
He must"ve lost his way
in the woods.
You have to keep quite!
Excuse me?
Beautiful.
Extraordinary.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
A man of taste.
He was talking about me.
Oops!
(MAURICE STUTTERS)
Well, wherever you are..
I'm just going to warm myself
by the fire.
(COUGHS)
That's better.
Oh, much better.
(DISTANT CLATTERING)
Ooh.
Thank you.
Mom said I wasn't supposed to move,
because it might be scary.
Sorry.
It's alright.
I cannot..
Thank you enough for your hospitality.
I'll..
bid you. Aah!...
(THUNDER CRACKING) And...
good night.
Come on Philippe, go! Go!
No, wait, wait, wait!
Roses. I nearly forgot.
Stay here.
I promised Belle a rose.
(EXCLAIMS)
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTING AND HUFFING)
There!
(THE BEAST ROARING)
(WHIMPERING)
(WHINNYING)
(PHILIPPE WHINNYING)
Philippe!
What happened?
Where is Papa?
Take me to him!
(WIND BLOWING)
(PHILIPPE WHINNIES)
LUMIÈRE: Look! Cogsworth!
A beautiful girl!
COGSWORTH: Yes! I can see it's a girl.
I lost my hands, but my eyes.
But, what if she's the one?
The one who'll break the spell?
Who said that?
Who's there?
(MAURICE COUGHS DISTANTLY)
Uh-oh.
(MAURICE CONTINUES COUGHING)
Papa?
Papa, is that you?
Belle!
How did you find me?
Your hands are iced.
We need to get you home.
Belle, now you must leave!
This castle is alive!
Now, go before he finds you!
Who?
(THE BEAST GROWLING)
Who's there?
Who are you?
THE BEAST: Who are you?
I've come to my father.
Your father is a thief!
Liar!
He stole a rose.
I asked the rose.
Punish me, not him!
No!
He means forever!
Apparently, that's what happens
around here when you pick a flower!
A life sentence for a rose?
(ROARING)
I received eternal damnation for one.
I merely locking him away.
Now, do you choose to
take you father's place?
Come in to the light.
(GASPS)
Choose.
Belle, I won't let you do this.
I lost your mother.
I won't lose you, too!
Now, go!
Go! (COUGHS)
All right, Papa.
I'll leave.
I need a minute alone with him.
(GRUNTS)
You are so cruel,
did you won't allow a daughter
to say her father goodbye?
Forever can spare a minute.
When this door closes, it will
not open again.
I should've been with you.
No. Belle, listen to me.
It's all right.
Now, go.
Live your life.
And forget me.
Forget you?
Everything I aim is because of you.
I love you, Belle.
Don't be afraid.
I love you too, Papa.
I'm not afraid.
And I will escape, I promise.
Wh.. What?
You took his place.
He is my father.
He's a fool.
And so are you.
Belle..
Papa!
(GROANING)
Don't hurt him!
- Papa!
- MAURICE: No!
I'll come back!
I promise!
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
LUMIÈRE: Forgive my intrusion,
Mademoiselle.
But I have come to escort you
to your room.
My room?
- But I thought...
- LUMIÈRE: Oh, what?
That "Once this door closes,
it will not open again"?
(IMITATES ROAR) I know.
He gets all dramatic.
- Hallo!
- (GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(SHRIEKS)
Oh, you are very strong.
This is a great quality.
What are you?
I am Lumiere!
And.. You can talk?
COGSWORTH: Well, of course,
he can talk.
It's all he ever does.
Now, Lumiere, as the head of
the household,
I demand that you to put her
back in her cell at once.
What do you want to be
for the rest of your life, Cogsworth?
A man or a mental clock?
Ready, Miss?
- Trust me.
- COGSWORTH: Oh! ho ho hoh.
LUMIÈRE: You must
forgive first impressions.
I hope you are not too startled.
BELLE: Why would I be startled?
I'm talking to a candle.
Candelabro, please.
You know there's a difference.
But consider me at your service.
The castle is your own now,
so feel free to go anywhere
you like.
Except the west wing.
Uh, which we do not have.
Why? What's in the west wing?
- Oh! Nothing.
- COGSWORTH: Nothing.
- Storage space.
- COGSWORTH: Storage space.
- That's it
- COGSWORTH: That's it.
Yes, that's it!
COGSWORTH: This way, please.
To the east wing.
LUMIÈRE: Or as I like to call it,
it's the only wing.(LAUGHS)
Watch your step, s'il vou plait!
(BOTH EXCLAIM)
Welcome to your new room!
It's modest, but comortable.
It's.. beautiful.
LUMIÈRE: But of course,
The Master wanted you to have
the finest room in the castle.
(COUGHS) Oh, dear.
We were not expecting guest.
PLUMETTE: Enchanté, Mademoiselle.
Don't worry.
I'll have this place spotless
in no time.
This plan of yours is dangerous.
I would've risk anything to kiss you
again, Plumette.
No, my love.
I've been burnt by you before.
We must be strong.
How can I be strong when
you make me so weak?
(COUGHS)
(SNORING)
Is everything here alive?
Hello. What's your name?
(BOTH LAUGH)
That is a hairbrush.
(HIGH PITCH VOCALIZATION)
Do not be alarmed.
This is just your wardrobe.
Meet Madame De Garderobe.
A great singer.
When you can stay awake.
Cogsworth! A diva needs
a beauty rest. (YAWNS)
Ah! Stay with us, Madame.
We have someone for you
to dress!
(GASPS) Finally!
A woman!
Pretty eyes.
Proud face.
A perfect canvas.
Yes!
I will find you something worthy
of a princess.
I'm not a princess.
Non sense!
Let's see what I got
in my drawer.
(GASPS) How embarassing!
Froufrou, come help Mama.
(BARKING)
(GASPS)
(EXCLAIMS IN SPANISH)
Subtle, understated. I love it!
(BIDS GOODBYE IN FRENCH)
Froufrou, send my love to
the maestro.
(SNORING)
GASTON: Picture it, LeFou.
A rustic cabin,
My latest kill roasting on the fire.
Adorable children running around us,
while my love...
rubs my tired feet.
But what did Belle say?
"I will never marry you, Gaston!"
You know, there are other girls.
A great man doesn't waste
his time.
(SINGING) ♪ Gosh, it disturbs me
to see you, Gaston ♪
♪ Looking so down in the dumps. ♪
♪ Every guy here'd love
to be you, Gaston. ♪
♪ Even when taking your lumps. ♪
♪ There's no men in town as admired
as you. ♪
♪ You're everyone's favorite guy ♪
♪♪
♪ Everyone's awed
and inspired by you ♪
♪ And it's not very hard
to see why ♪
♪ No one's slick as Gaston ♪
♪ No one's quick as Gaston ♪
♪ No one's neck's as
incredibly thick as Gaston's ♪
♪ For there's no man in
town half as manly ♪
♪ Perfect, a pure paragon! ♪
♪ You can ask any Tom, Dick, or Stanley ♪
♪ And they'll tell you whose
team they prefer to be on ♪
♪ Who plays...? ♪
♪♪
♪ Dart like Gaston! ♪
♪ Who breaks hearts
Like Gaston! ♪
♪ Who's much more than some of this...
like Gaston. ♪
♪ As a specimen, yes, I'm intimidating. ♪
♪ My, what a guy, that Gaston! ♪
♪ I needed encouragement. ♪
♪ Thank you, LeFou ♪
♪ Well, there's no one as easy to bolster
as you ♪
Too much?
Yep.
♪ No one fights like Gaston ♪
♪ Douses lights like Gaston ♪
♪ In a wrestling match
nobody bites like Gaston ♪
♪ When I hunt, I sneak up with
my quiver ♪
♪ And beasts of the field say a prayer ♪
♪♪
♪ Cause I'm carefully aimed for
the liver ♪
♪ Then I shoot from behind ♪
♪ Is that fair? ♪
I don't care.
♪ No one hits like Gaston ♪
♪ Matches wits like Gaston ♪
♪ In a spitting match
nobody spits like Gaston ♪
♪I'm especially good at expectorating! ♪
ALL<: Ooh!
♪♪
Ten points for Gaston!
Thank you. Thank you.
♪ When I was a lad
I ate four dozen eggs ♪
♪ Every morning to help me get larger ♪
♪ And now that I'm grown
I eat five dozen eggs ♪
♪ So I'm roughly the size of a barge! ♪
(GIRLS SQUEAL)
- (ALL CLAPPING RHYTHMICALLY)
- Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
(ALL WHOOPING AND CHEERING)
(YELLS AND GRUNTS)
(EXCLAIMS)
(MAN YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(MEN GROANING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(GIGGLING SHRILLY)
♪♪
♪ Who has brains.. ♪
♪ Like Gaston? ♪
♪ Entertains
like Gaston? ♪
♪ Who can make up these endless
refrains like Gaston? ♪
♪ I use antlers in all of
my decorating ♪
♪ Say it again ♪
♪♪
♪ Who's a man among men? ♪
♪ Who's the super success? ♪
♪ Don't you know?
Can't you guess? ♪
♪ Ask his fans and his five
hhangers-on ♪
♪ There's just one guy in town
Who's got all of it down ♪
♪ And his name's
G-A-S-T.. ♪
♪ I believe there's another T.. ♪
♪ It just occurred to me that
I'm illiterate ♪
♪ And I've never actually had to
spell it out loud before.. ♪
♪ GASTON! ♪
(ALL CHEERING)
(LAUGHS)
LeFou, you are the best.
How is it no girls snatch you up yet?
I've been told that I'm clingy.
But I don't really get it.
Please, please.
Someone, someone.
Help, help..
You must help me.
It's Belle! He's got Belle.
She's locked in a dungeon!
TAVERN KEEPER:
Who's got her?
A beast!
A huge, horrid, monstrous beast!
(LAUGHTER)
My daughter's life is in danger.
Why do you laugh? It's no joke!
His castle is hidden in the woods.
It's already winter there.
Winter in June?
- (ALL LAUGH)
- Crazy old Maurice.
Listen to me!
The beast... is real.
Do you understand?
Well, no one help me?
I'll help, Maurice.
What?
You will?
Everybody,
stop making fun at this man at once.
Captain, thank you.
Don't thank me, Maurice.
Lead us to the Beast.
(PANTING)
Come.
Mama! There's a girl in the castle!
Yes, Chip! We know.
What kind of tea does she likes?
Herbal, Oolong,
Chamomille?
I'm too excited!
Slow down, before you break
your handle.
- Heads up, Mrs. Potts.
- Oh!
(GRUNTS)
THE BEAST: Lumiere!
COGSWORTH: Oh!
- Be calm. Let me do the talking.
You're making her a dinner?
We thought you might appreciate
a company.
Master, I just want to assure you...
that I had no part in this
hopeless plan.
Preparing a dinner, designing a gown
for her, giving her a suite...
in the east wing.
You gave her a bedroom?
No, no, no.
He gave her a bedroom.
This is true.
But, if this girl is the one
who can break the spell,
then maybe you could stop by
using dinner to charm her.
- Good thinking, Cogsworth!
- What?
That's the most ridiculous idea
I've ever heard! Charm the prisoner?
But you must try, Master.
With every passing day...
we become less human.
She's the daughter of a common thief.
What kind of person do you think
that makes her?
Ow, you can't judge people by who
their father is, now can you?
You'll join me for dinner.
That's not a request.
Gently, Master.
The girl lost her father
and her freedom in one day.
Yes, the poor thing is probably
in there, scare to death.
MRS. POTTS: Exactly.
Just a minute.
You see? There she is.
Now remember, be gentle.
- Kind!
- Charming!
Sweet!
And when she opens the door,
give her a dashing smile.
Come, come, show me the smile.
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, no.
Will you join me for dinner?
You've taken me as your prisoner, and
now you want to have dinner with me?
Are you insane?
- (GRUNTING)
- Uh-oh. He's losing it.
Oh, dear.
I told you to join me
for dinner!
I told you, no!
What, what time is it?
What's happening?
I'd starved before I ever
ate with you.
Well, be my guest!
Go ahed and starve!
If she doesn't eat with me,
then she doesn't eat at all.
Idiot!
You can't talk to us like that.
I forbid it.
Am I too late?
Shame, I was ready enough
to tell him off this time.
Oh, Master! You've returned!
- (EXCLAIMS)
- (LAUGHS)
- Oh! Very funny.
- I got you there!
Show me the girl.
Another petal fell.
Lumiere...
I grew three more feathers.
And I just plugged yesterday.
I know, darling. (EXCLAIMS)
I'm getting more metallic
everyday.
Oh, no. It's happening again.
Pardon me.
Oh, everyone, calm yourself.
We still have time.
Mama,
am I ever going to be a boy again?
Oh, yes, Chip.
You'll have your days
in the sun again.
You just leave it to me.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
I told you to go away.
Don't worry, dear.
It's only Mrs. Potts.
Oh, I own you a vision!
How lovely...
to my Miss.
It's a very long journey.
Let me fix you up
before you go.
I have found..
That most of the troubles
seem less troubling,
after a bracing cup of tea.
Slowly now, Chip.
(CHIP GIGGLES)
Pleased to meet you.
Wanna see me do a trick?
Chip!
That was a very brave thing
you did for your father, deary.
Yes.
We all think so.
I'm worried about him.
He's never been on his own.
Cheer up, my puppet.
Things will turn out in the end.
You'll feel a lot better
after dinner.
But he said, "if she doesn't eat
with me, she doesn't eat at all".
People say a lot of things
in anger.
It is our choice whether or not
to listen.
You coming, puppet?
Go.
They're coming! Final checks, everyone!
No, you don't!
If the Master finds that you buy and
order them... He will blame me!
Yes, I will make sure of it.
But, did you see us stand up to win?
I am telling you, this girl is the one.
They must fall in love,
if we are to be human again.
And how can they fall in love if
she stays in her room?
Ay, Chapeau, you missed
this spot.
You know, she'll never love him.
A broken clock is right two times
a day, mon ami.
But this is not one of those times!
Stand up straight!
It's time to sparkle!
I have no taste buds,
but I can tell this is exquisite.
Get off me while I work!
Pepper!
Salt!
Not so loud.
Keep it down.
Of course, of course.
But what is dinner without a little music?
Music?
Maestro Cadanza, are you ready?
(MAESTRO CADENZA CHUCKLES)
It has been so long since
I've performed.
I can't barely even remember how.
(PLAYS CHORDS
AND STOPS ABRUPTLY)
- Oooh!
- Shh Ah!
Another cavity.
Maestro, your wife is upstairs.
Finding it harder and harder
to stay awake.
She's counting on you to
help us break this curse.
Then I shall play through
the dental pain.
Maestro, play quartet, please.
Oh, quartet. Sotto voce!
Of course!
Are there any other tasteless demands
you wished to make upon my artistry?
No, that's it.
MRS. POTTS: There you are, dear.
♪ Ma chere Mademoiselle! ♪
♪ It is with the deepest pride ♪
♪ and greatest pleasure ♪
♪ that we welcome you tonight! ♪
(CLEARS THROAT)
♪ Here. And now, ♪
♪ we invite you to relax. ♪
♪ Let us pull up a chair ♪
♪ as the dining room proudly presents ♪
(MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
- (STOPS ABRUPTLY)
- (MAESTRO CADENZA EXCLAIMS)
♪ Your dinner! ♪
♪♪
(SINGING) ♪ Be our.. Guest.
Be our guest ♪
♪ Put our service to the test ♪
♪ Tie your napkin around your neck,
cherie. And we'll ♪
♪ provide the rest. ♪
♪ Soup du jour! Hot hors d'oeuvres!
While we only live to serve. ♪
♪ Try the grey stuff, it's delicious. ♪
♪ Don't believe me? Ask the dishes. ♪
♪♪ (LAUGHING)
♪ They can sing, they can dance. ♪
♪ After all, Miss, this is France! ♪
♪ And a dinner here is never second best ♪
♪ Go on, unfold your menu ♪
♪ Take a glance and then you'll
be our guest. Oui, our guest. ♪
♪ Be our guest ♪
♪♪
♪ Beef ragout ♪
♪ Cheese souffle ♪
♪ Pie and pudding "en flambe" ♪
♪ We'll prepare and serve with flair
a culinary cabaret ♪
♪ You're alone and you're scared ♪
♪ But the banquet's all prepared ♪
♪ No one's gloomy or complaining
while the flatware's entertaining ♪
♪ We tell jokes I do tricks ♪
♪ With my fellow candlesticks ♪
CHORUS: ♪ And it's all in perfect taste
that you can bet ♪
♪ Come on and lift your glass ♪
♪ You've won your own free pass
to be our guest ♪
♪ If you're stressed,
it's fine dining we suggest ♪
♪ Be our guest ♪
♪ Be our guest, be our guest ♪
♪ Life is so unnerving for a servant
who's not serving ♪
♪ He's not whole without
a soul to wait upon ♪
♪ Ah, those good old days
when we were useful ♪
♪ Hey, Cogsworth? ♪
♪ Suddenly those good
old days are gone ♪
♪♪
♪ Too long we've been rusting ♪
♪ Needing so much more than dusting ♪
♪ Needing exercise, a
chance to use our skills ♪
♪♪
♪ Most days we just lay around the castle ♪
♪ Flabby, fat and lazy!
You walked in and oops-a-daisy! ♪
♪ It's a guest! It's a guest!
Sakes alive, well I'll be blessed ♪
♪ Wine's been poured and thank the Lord
I've had the napkins freshly pressed ♪
♪ With dessert, she'll want tea
And my dear that's fine with me ♪
♪ While the cups do their soft shoeing ♪
♪ I'll be bubbling, I'll be brewing ♪
(ALL VOCALIZING)
♪ I'll get warm, piping hot ♪
♪ Heaven's sakes! Is that a spot? ♪
♪ Clean it up! We want
the company impressed ♪
♪ We've got a lot to do ♪
♪ Is it one lump or two ♪
♪ For you, our guest? ♪
♪ She's our guest ♪
ALL: ♪ Be our guest, be our guest
Our command is your request ♪
♪ It's ten years since we had anybody here
And we're obsessed ♪
♪ With your meal ♪
♪ With your ease ♪
♪ Yes, indeed, we aim to please ♪
♪ While the candlelight's still glowing ♪
♪♪ (LAUGHS)
♪ Let us help you We'll keep going ♪
♪♪
♪ Course by course ♪
♪ One by one ♪
♪ 'Til you shout, "Enough! I'm done!" ♪
♪ Then we'll sing you off to sleep
as you digest ♪
♪ Tonight you'll prop your feet up
But for now, let's eat up ♪
♪ And be our guest ♪
♪ Be our guest ♪
♪ Please, be our guest ♪
♪♪
Pudding?
(LAUGHS)
BELLE: I don't understand why you'e all
being so kind to me.
Surely, you're as trapped here
as I am.
Don't you ever want to escape?
The Master is not as terrible
as he appears.
Somewhere, deep in his soul
there's a prince..
Of a fellow just waiting
to be set free.
Lumiere mentioned something
about the west wing.
Never you mind about that.
Off to bed with you, puppet.
- Good night.
- Nighty night.
MRS. POTTS: Straight to bed.
(PANTING)
What are you doing here?
What did you do to it?
Nothing.
Do you realize what you could've done?
You could've ruined us all!
Get out of here!
Go!
(PANTING)
LUMIÈRE: Check mate. Again.
Wait, No! You're cheating again!
Mademoiselle, what are you doing?
Getting out of here!
- Stop!
- (BARKING)
Go! Go, Froufrou!
Yes­, Froufrou.
Stop her!
LUMIÈRE: Don't let her leave!
- MRS. POTTS: Stop her!
- (BARKING)
No, no, Froufrou!
COGSWORTH: No, no! it's not play time!
LUMIÈRE: Not now, silly boy!
COGSWORTH: Bad dog! Bad dog!
LUMIÈRE: No! No! No!
Please, don't go.
It's dangerous!
Oh, my!
(PANTING)
(HOWLING)
- (GROWLS)
- (ALL HOWLING)
(PHILIPPE WHINNYING)
(GROWLING)
(Gasps)
(YELPS)
(WOLVES GROWL)
(PHILIPPE WHINNYING)
(GRUNTS)
(WOLF GROWLS)
(WOLVES ATTACK THE BEAST)
(PHILIPPE WHINNYING)
(GRUNTS)
(WOLF POOUNCES ON THE BEAST)
(GROWLS)
(BREATHS HEAVILY)
(ROARING)
(WOLVES HOWLING)
(THE BEAST FALLS DOWN)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
(THE BEAST BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHISPERING) You have to help me.
You have to stand.
(WOLVES HOWLING)
MAURICE: No! I'm sure this is the way.
Do you hear those wolves?
That means we're getting very close
to the castle.
Look, enough is enough.
We have to turn back.
Stop!
That's it! There it is!
That's the tree!
I'm sure of it.
It.. It was down by lightning
at the time.
But now it's..
Resume to an upright position,
to some sort of..
Magic, or.. Or other.
You really want to marry
into this family?
So that means..
The castle is that..
No.
That. No, it's...
(WHISTLES
AND BLOWS RASPBERRY)
That way!
Definitely, that way!
I'm done playing this game, Maurice.
Where is Belle?
The Beast took her and she..
There are no such things
as beasts.
Or talking teacups.
Or magic!
But there are wolves, frosbite,
and starvation!
Deep breaths, Gaston.
Deep breath.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
So why don't we just turn around,
go back to Villeneuve?
I'm sure Belle is at home,
cooking up a lovely dinner.
If you think I've made all this up,
then why did you offer to help?
Because I want to marry your daughter!
Now, let's go home.
Belle is not at home!
She is with the..
You say "beast" one more time,
I will feed you to the wolves!
Gaston! Stop it!
Breath!
Think of happy thoughts.
Go back to the war.
Blood.
Explosions.
Countless widows.
- Widows.
- Yes, yes.
That's it.
(EXHALES)
(CHUCKLES)
Maurice!
Please, forgive me, old bean.
There's no way to talk to
my future father-in-law,
now, is it?
Future father-in-law?
Yeahs!
You will never marry my daughter.
(GRUNTS)
I saw that, Captain.
If Maurice won't give me
his blessing,
then he's in my way.
Once the wolves have finished
with him
Belle will have no one to take of her,
but me.
Let's say we're adjusting
our all options...
Do we maybe wanna consider
a slightly less gruesome alternatives?
Are you coming?
Yah!
(WOLVES HOWLING IN DISTANCE)
(THE BEAST GROWLING IN PAIN)
That hurts!
If you held still, it wouldn't hurt
as much.
If hadn't runaway,
none of this would've happened.
If you hadn't frightened me,
I wouldn't've runaway!
Well, you shouldn't've been in
the west wing!
Well, you should learn to control
your temper!
(GRUNTS)
Try to get some rest.
Thank you, Miss.
We are eternally grateful.
Why do you care about him
so much?
We've looked after him
all his life.
But he's cursed you somehow.
Why?
You did nothing.
You're quite right there, dear.
You see, when the Master
lost his mother
and his cruel father took that
sweet innocent lad, and
twisted him up to be
just like him.
We did nothing.
LUMIÈRE: Let him sleep.
YOUNG PRINCE: ♪ Days in the sun ♪
♪ When my life has barely begun ♪
♪ Not until my whole life is done ♪
♪ Will I ever leave you? ♪
♪ Will I tremble again? ♪
♪ To my dear one's gorgeous refrain ♪
♪ Will you now forever remain ♪
♪ Out of reach of my arms ♪
♪ All those days in the sun ♪
♪ What I'd give to relive just one ♪
(YAWNS) Night, Mama.
♪ Undo what's done ♪
♪ And bring back the light ♪
♪ Oh, I could sing ♪
♪ of the pain these dark days bring ♪
♪ The spell we're under ♪
♪ Still it's the wonder of us
I sing of tonight ♪
♪ How in the midst of all this sorrow ♪
♪ Can so much hope and love endure ♪
♪ I was innocent and certain ♪
♪ Now I'm wiser but unsure ♪
♪ Days in the back
I can't go back into my childhood ♪
GARDEROBE: ♪ Oh, all those precious days
That my father made secure ♪
♪ I can feel a change in me ♪
BELLE: ♪ I'm stronger now
but still not free ♪
ALL: ♪ Days in the sun ♪
♪ Will return, we must believe ♪
♪ As lovers do ♪
♪ That days in the sun ♪
♪ Will come shining through ♪
♪♪
What happens when the last petal
falls?
The Master remains a beast forever.
And we become..
- Antiques.
- Knick knacks.
Lightly used housewares.
Rubbish.
We become rubbish.
I want to help you.
There must be someway to break
the curse.
Well, there is one.
Uhh!
It's not for you to worry about,
lamb.
We've made our bed
and we must lie in it.
(MAURICE BREATHING SHAKILY)
(HOOTING
Drink.
(SIPPING)
(EXHALES)
Thank you, Agathe.
BELLE: "Love can transpose to form
and dignity".
"Love looks not with the eyes,
but with the mind"
"And therefore is winged Cupid
painted blind".
You know Shakespeare?
(GRUNTS)
I had an expensive education.
Actually, "Romeo and Juliet"
is my favorite play.
(GROANS) Why is that not a surprise?
I'm sorry?
Well, you know that heartache,
pining, and blublb.. (RETCHING).
So many better things to read.
Like what?
Well, there are a couple things
in here, you could start with.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
Are you all right?
It's wonderful!
Yes, I suppose it is.
Well, if you like it so much,
then it's yours.
Have you really read every one
of these books?
What?
(SCOFFS) Well, not all of them.
Some of them are in Greek.
Was that a joke?
Are you making jokes now?
Maybe.
(BELLE CHUCKLES)
(SHRIEKS EXCITEDLY)
(LAUGHS)
(SLURPING)
BELLE: The air is blue, keen and cold...
"and in a frozen sheath enrolled.
"Each branch, each twig...
"each blade of grass,
seems clad miraculously with...
"glass".
I feel like if I'm seeing it
for the first time?
Is there anymore?
(LAUGHS)
"But in that solemn silence
is heard the whisper...
"of every sleeping things.
"Look. Look at me.
"Come wake me up.
"For still here I'll be".
(NEIGHS SOFTLY)
(SHUSHING)
(SINGING) ♪ There's something
sweet and almost kind ♪
♪ But he was mean and he was coarse
and unrefined ♪
♪ And now he's dear and so unsure ♪
♪ I wonder why I didn't see it there
before ♪
♪♪
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHS)
♪♪
♪♪ (CHUCKLES)
♪ She glanced this way...
I though I saw ♪
♪ And when we touched, she didn't shudder
at my paw ♪
♪ No it can't be, I'll just ignore ♪
♪ But then she's never looked at me
that way before ♪
(BOTH SLURPING)
(CHUCKLES)
♪ New and a bit alarming ♪
♪ Who'd have ever thought
that this could be? ♪
♪♪
♪ True that he's no Prince Charming ♪
♪ But there's something in him that
I simply didn't see ♪
♪♪
PLUMETTE: ♪ Well, who'd have thought?
MRS. POTTS: Well, bless my soul ♪
♪ Well, who'd have known?
Well, who indeed? ♪
♪ And who'd have guessed they'd come
together on their own? ♪
MRS. POTTS: ♪ It's so peculiar,
wait and see ♪
♪ We'll wait and see
A few days more ♪
♪ There may be something there
that wasn't there before ♪
And here's a thought..
Perhaps there's something there
that wasn't there before
- (PLUMETTE CHUCKLES)
- CHIP: What, Mama?
♪ There may be something there
that wasn't there before ♪
What is it? What's there?
I will tell you when you're older.
Okay, I'm older.
(SCOFFS) Chip.
(LAUGHING) You are a one.
What are you reading?
Nothing.
Guinevere and Lancelot
Well, actually..
King Arthur and the Round Table,
Knights, men, swords, and things.
Mmm.
Still...
it's a romance.
Alright.
I never thank you for saving
my life.
Well, I never thank you
for not leaving me to
be eaten by wolves.
(LAUGHS)
(ALL CHATTERING EXCITEDLY)
BELLE: They know how to
have a good time.
Yes, but when I enter the room,
the laughter dies.
Me, too.
The villagers say that I'm
a funny girl.
But I'm not sure they mean it
as a compliment.
I'm sorry.
Your village sounds terrible.
(SIGHS) Almost as lonely as your castle.
What dou you say we'd runaway?
Another little gift
from the enchantress.
A book that'll allow you to escape.
(BLOWS)
Amazing!
It was the cruelest trick of all.
It was just another curse.
The outside world has no place
for a creature like me.
But it can for you.
Think of the one place you've always
wanted to see.
Now, find it in your mind's eye.
And then feel it in your heart.
Where did you take us?
Paris.
Oh, I love Paris.
What would you like to see first?
Notre Dame?
The Champs-Élysées?
No?
Too touristy?
It's so much more that I imagined.
(SINGING) ♪ This is the Paris
of my childhood ♪
♪ This what the borders of my life ♪
♪ In this crumbling dusty attic ♪
♪ Where an artist loved his wife ♪
♪ Is it to remember? ♪
♪ Or it to move on? ♪
♪♪
♪ Knowing the Paris of my childhood..
♪ Is gone. ♪
What happened to your mother?
It was the one story, Papa can never
bring himself to tell.
I think, better not to ask.
Oh. A doctor's mask.
Plague.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
You must leave. Now.
BELLE'S MOTHER: Quickly...
before it takes her, too.
(BABY BELLE CRYING)
I'm sorry I ever called
your father a thief.
(WHISPERS) Let's go home.
LEFOU: This is some storm, huh?
At least, we're not tied to a tree
in the middle of nowhere,
surrounded by bloodthirsts
and wolves.
You know, it's not too late.
We could always turn back..
It's just..
everytime I close my eyes,
I picture Maurice stranded alone.
And when I open them,
he is..
Maurice?
Gaston,
did you try to kill Maurice?
(ALL MURMURING)
Maurice!
Thank heavens!
I've spent the last five days
trying to find you!
You tried to kill me.
You left me to the wolves.
GASTON: Wolves?
It's one thing to rave about
your delusions
and another, to accuse me of
attempted murder.
JEAN: Maurice,
do you have any proof of
what you're saying?
Ask Agathe.
She rescued me.
GASTON: (LAUGHING) Agathe!
You'd hang your accusations
on the testimony
of a filthy hag?
No offense, Agathe.
Monsieur LeFou.
He was there.
He saw it all.
Me?
You're right!
Don't take my word for it.
LeFou!
My dearest companion.
Did I,
your loyal friend and most loyal
compatriot,
try to kill the father of the only woman
I've ever loved?
Well, it's a complicated question on a
number of accounts.
(GASPS)
But, no.
No, he did not.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
You!
(GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE GASP)
(MAURICE GROANS)
Maurice,
it pains me to say this, but you've
become a danger to yourself and others.
No wonder, Belle runaway.
You need a help, Sir.
A place to heal your
troubled mind.
Everything is gonna be fine.
Just fine.
THE BEAST: Well, I'd saw her
in the ballroom,
and said, "You're making everything
looks so beautiful,
we should have a dance tonight".
I never imagined she'd actually say yes.
What was I thinking?
LUMIÈRE: No, Master.
It's perfect!
The rose has only four petals left,
which means tonight..
You can tell her how you feel.
I feel like a fool.
She will never love me.
Do not be discouraged.
(SPITS)
She is the one.
I wish you'd stop saying that!
(SIGHS)
There is no "one".
You care for her, don't you?
Well then, woo her with beautiful music
and romantic candlelight.
Yes, and when the moments just right.
(GIGGLES)
Well, how will I know?
You'll feel slightly nauseous.
Don't worry, Master.
You'll do fine.
MRS. POTTS: Just don't be so nervous and
tell Belle how you feel.
Because if you dont,
I promise, you'll be drinking cold tea
for the rest of your days!
- In the dark.
- Covered in dust.
- Dark and very, very dirty.
- (DINGS)
Start with the hair.
Women love nice hair!
How tidy the fingers and toes?
Chapeau, brush those teeth.
They need it.
LUMIÈRE: Dip, dip.
Snip, snip.
Polish the nails.
Shine the horn.
PLUMETTE: Eyes closed. Poof, poof.
LUMIÈRE: And to top final look.
Voilà!
Okay, I can fix this.
(SIGHS)
Oh, beautiful!
But something has missing.
Oh, yes!
The finishing touch!
MRS. POTTS: (SINGING)
♪ Tale as old as time ♪
♪ True as it can be ♪
♪ Barely even friends
Then somebody bends unexpectedly
♪ Just a little change ♪
♪ Small, to say the least ♪
♪ Both a little scared ♪
♪ Neither one prepared ♪
♪ Beauty and the Beast ♪
♪ Ever just the same ♪
♪ Ever a surprise ♪
♪ Ever as before ♪
♪ Ever just as sure ♪
♪ As the sun will rise ♪
♪ Tale as old as time ♪
♪ Tune as old as song ♪
♪ Bittersweet and strange ♪
♪ Finding you can change ♪
♪ Learning you were wrong ♪
♪ Certain as the sun ♪
♪ Rising in the east ♪
♪ Tale as old as time ♪
♪ Song as old as rhyme ♪
♪ Beauty and the beast. ♪
♪ Tale as old as time ♪
♪ Song as old as rhyme ♪
♪ Beauty and the beast. ♪
♪♪
(SIGHS) I hadn't dance in years.
I almost forgot how to feel it.
(EXHALES)
It's foolish, I suppose,
for a creature like me, to hope..
That one day he might earn
your affection.
I don't know.
Really?
You think you could be happy here?
Can anybody be happy
if they're free?
My father taught me to dance.
I used to step on his toes
a lot.
You must miss him.
Very much.
Would you like to see him?
I'd like to see my father.
Papa!
What are they doing to him?
He..
He's in trouble!
Then you must go to him.
What did you say?
You must go to him.
No time to waste.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
No.
You keep it with you.
And you'll always have a way
to look back on me.
Thank you.
(EXHALES)
Oh!
Well, Master, I have had my doubts,
but everything's moving like clockwork.
True love really does win the day!
I let her go.
You what?
Master, how could you do that?
I had to.
But, why?
Because, he loves her.
Then, why are we not human?
Because, she doesn't love him.
And now, it's too late.
But she might still come back.
No.
I set her free.
I'm sorry I couldn't do the same
for all of you.
Now, go.
Our time is almost passed.
Come, my love-(SIGHS)
(SINGING) ♪ I was the one who had it all ♪
♪ I was the master of my fate ♪
♪ I never needed anybody in my life ♪
♪ I learnt the truth too late ♪
♪ I'll never shake away the pain ♪
♪ I close my eyes but
she's still there ♪
♪ I let her steal into
my melancholy heart ♪
♪ It's more than I can bear ♪
♪ Now I know she'll never leave me ♪
♪ Even as she runs away ♪
♪ She will still torment me
Calm me, hurt me ♪
♪ Move me, come what may ♪
♪ Wasting in my lonely tower ♪
♪ Waiting by an open door ♪
♪ I'll fool myself, she'll walk right in ♪
♪ And be with me forevermore ♪
♪ I rage against the trials of love ♪
♪ I curse the fading of the light ♪
♪ Though she's already flown so far
beyond my reach ♪
♪ She's never out of sight ♪
♪ Now I know she'll never leave me ♪
♪ Even as she fades from view ♪
♪ She will still inspire me ♪
♪ Be a part of everything I do ♪
♪ Wasting in my lonely tower ♪
♪ Waiting by an open door ♪
♪ I'll fool myself, she'll walk right in ♪
♪ And as the long, long nights begin ♪
♪ I'll think of all that might have been ♪
♪ Waiting here forevermore ♪
♪♪
This man is weak, please!
He needs a hospital.
Not an assylum!
(GRUNTS)
Have you ever see the inside
of a mad house, Maurice?
You wouldn't last a week.
Just give me your daughter's hands,
and I'll set you free.
Never.
Take him away!
(HORSE WHINNYING)
Stop!
Papa!
MAURICE: Ah, Belle.
I thought I'd lost you.
Let him out! He's hurt!
We can't do that, Miss.
We will take good care of him.
My father's not crazy!
Gaston, tell him!
You know how loyal I am
to your family,
but your father's been making
some unbelievable claims.
It's true, Belle.
He's been raging about a beast
in a castle!
I've just come from the castle
and there is a beast!
You'd say anything to set him free.
Your word is hardly prove!
You want a proof?
Show me the Beast!
(ALL GASPING)
(ALL MURMURING)
That's your proof!
This is sorcery!
Look at this beast!
- Look at his fangs!
- (ALL EXCLAIM)
His claws!
No, no, don't be afraid!
He's gentle and kind.
(ALL MURMURING)
The monster has her under a spell!
If I didn't know better, I'd say
she even cared for him!
He's not a monster, Gaston!
You are!
The Beast wouldn't hurt anyone.
I've heard the effect of
dark magic,
but I've never before see it with
my own eyes!
This is a threat
- to our very existence!
- (ALL AGREEING IN UNISON)
We can't have her running out
to warn the Beast.
Lock her up, too.
- No!
- TOM: Come here!
- (GRUNTS)
- Shut up!
BELLE: You won't get away
with this, Gaston!
- MAURICE: Oh, Belle.
- (PEOPLE MURMURING)
Gaston, with all due respect..
Do you want to be next?
Fetch my horse.
Stand guard!
Don't let them escape!
This creature will curse us all
if we don't stop him!
(ALL AGREEING IN UNISON)
What I say, we kill the beast!
ALL: Kill the beast!
(ALL AGREEING)
♪ We're not safe until he's dead ♪
♪ He'll come stalking us at night ♪
♪ Set to sacrifice our children to his
monstrous appetite ♪
♪ He'll wreak havoc on our village
if we let him wander free ♪
♪ So it's time to take some action, boys ♪
♪ It's time to follow me ♪
(ALL SHOUTING)
♪ Through the mist, through the woods
Through the darkness and the shadows ♪
♪ It's a nightmare but
it's one exciting ride ♪
♪ Say a prayer, then we're there
At the drawbridge of a castle ♪
♪ And there's something
truly terrible inside ♪
♪ It's a beast, he's got fangs
Razor sharp ones ♪
♪ Massive paws, killer
claws for the feast ♪
♪ Hear him roar, see him roam ♪
♪ But we're not coming home
'Til he's dead ♪
♪ Good and dead! ♪
ALL: ♪ Kill the beast! ♪
♪ Light your torch, mount your horse ♪
♪ Screw your courage to
the sticking place ♪
ALL: ♪ We're counting on
Gaston to lead the way ♪
♪ Call it war, call it threat
You can bet they all will follow ♪
♪ For in times like this,
they'll do just as I say ♪
♪ There's a beast running wild,
there's no question ♪
♪ But I fear the wrong monster's
released ♪
ALL: ♪ Sally forth! Tally ho!
Grab your sword! Grab your bow! ♪
♪ Praise the Lord and here we go! ♪
Show me the castle!
At least, they've
finally learnt to love.
A lot of good that does us,
if she does love him in return.
No, this is the first time of
at any real hope she would.
(HORSE WHINNYING IN DISTANCE)
Did you hear that, Mama?
Is it her? Is she coming back?
LUMIÈRE: Could it be?
PLUMETTE: I told you!
Sacré bleu!
Invaders!
MRS. POTTS: Rufianes!
Well, where do you go?
So much for true love.
Frame the barricades!
And oppose!
Move aside!
(SINGING) ♪ Hearts ablaze, banners high
We go marching into battle ♪
♪ Unafraid although the danger's just
increased ♪
♪ Raise the flag, sing the song
Here we come, we're fifty strong ♪
♪ And fifty Frenchmen can't be wrong ♪
Let's kill the Beast!
(GRUNTING)
COGSWORTH: We need help.
I have to warn the Beast.
Warn him?
How did you get away from him?
He let me go, Papa.
He sent me back to you.
(STAMMERS) I don't understand.
Where did you..?
He took me there.
I know what happened to Mama.
Then you know why I had
to leave her there.
I had to protect you. I.. I've always
tried to protect my little girl.
Probably, too much.
I understand.
(KISSES)
Will you help me now?
It's dangerous.
Yes!
Yes, it is.
I could try to pick the lock.
After all,
it's, it's only gears and springs.
But I would need
something long and sharp.
Like that.
Perfect.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(PANTING)
Oh, excuse me, Master.
(STAMMERS) I'm sorry to disturb you.
She's not coming back.
No.
They're breaking down the doors.
Doesn't matter now.
Just let them come.
MOB: Kill the beast!
This isn't working.
I know what to do.
MOB: Kill the beast! Kill the beast!
Kill the beast!
(PEOPLE GROANING)
Are you not at least be concerned
that this castle might be haunted?
Don't lose your nerve, LeFou.
MAN: Where are we?
This place seems familiar.
Like I've been here before.
Oh, hello there.
You must be
the talking teacup.
And you must be
his grandmother.
(GASPS) Grandmother?
- Attack!
- (GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING) (GROANING)
(DINGING) (GROANING)
(GROANS)
Gaston!
Help me.
Sorry, old friend.
It's hero time.
Ooh, ouch!
(EXHALES)
Hello.
Oh, uh, I believe this is yours.
(PHILIPPE WHINNYING
She is very headstrong.
Do you have children?
- (ALL SHOUTING)
- (GASPS)
PLUMETTE: No one to protect you now, huh?
(PLUMETTE GIGGLING)
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight. (GROANING)
Good show, Chip, my boy!
(LAUGHS)
Excellent!
- The infantery's arrived!
- (EXCLAIMS)
Now, go and teach some lessons.
Go!
Yes, those are called books,
you low-grade musketeers!
Oh! I'm off.
(SCREAMS)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY) Just a clock.
(LAUGHS) Come here,
little boys.
I spin you this way, I put it on.
Yes, pretty little boys.
Yes! (SCREAMING)
Beautiful!
Go! Be free!
Be free! Be free!
(ALL SHOUTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
How do you like your tea?
- Piping hot?
- (ALL SCREAMING)
Or boiling?
Mr. Potts!
(SCREAMING)
Mama!
Thank you!
(BOTH GRUNT)
- (BLOWS RASPBERRY)
- MRS. POTTS: Take that!
Nicely handled!
Well, I used to be on Gaston's side,
but we are so in a bad place
right now.
You're too good for him, anyway. Yeah.
Should we get back to it then?
(MEN GRUNTING)
MAESTRO CADENZA: (LAUGHS)
Such sweet of music!
Stand back
Silence that harpsichord!
MAESTRO CADENZA: What?
GARDEROBE: Maestro!
Darling! I've lost!
I'm coming, my love!
This is it!
The fat lady is singing!
(VOCALIZING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
Bravissima!
(ALL GROANING)
LUMIÈRE: Watch your toes!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(LUMIÈRE LAUGHING)
LUMIÈRE: That's it! Go! Go!
- (VOCALIZING AND GIGGLING)
- LUMIÈRE: Bon voyage!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Safe trip home.
And stay out!
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Hello, Beast!
I'm Gaston.
Belle sent me.
Are you in love with her?
Did you honestly think she'd want you?
(GROWLS)
(GROWLING)
Belle!
Where is he?
When we return to the village,
you will marry me!
And that beast's head
- will hang on our wall.
- Never!
(GRUNTING)
- (YELLS)
- (BELLE GASPS)
GASTON: I'm coming foryou, Beast!
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
No!
Belle?
Belle!
You came back!
I tried to stop them!
THE BEAST: Stay there!
I'm coming!
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Gaston!
- No!
- (GROWLS)
(GASPS)
- Don't let me go.
- (BREATHING SHAKILY)
Please.
I'll do anything.
Don't hurt me, Beast.
I am not
a beast.
- (GROWLS)
- (GRUNTS)
Go!
Get out!
Don't!
It's too far!
(GROWLING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (ROARS)
BELLE: Please!
Come on.
(ROARS)
(WHIMPERS)
(SCREAMING)
(THE BEAST BREATHING HEAVILY)
You came back.
Of course, I came back.
I'll never leave you again.
I'm afraid it's my turn to leave.
We're together now.
It's gonna be fine.
At least I could see you.
One last time.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
No!
Please, no!
(SOBBING)
Come back!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
LUMIÈRE: We did it, Plumette!
Victory is ours!
- Oh!
- Plumette?
Plumette?
Oh, my darling, Plumette.
Oh, no.
GARDEROBE: Maestro, you were so brave.
Goodbye, my love.
MAESTRO CADENZA: Amore!
No! Don't leave me!
(CRYING)
(WHIMPERING)
MRS. POTTS: Chip!
Chip!
Have you seen Chip?
He ran off.
(CRYING)
Where is my little boy?
- CHIP: Mama!
- Oh, no!
Mom!
Lumiere,
(STAMMERS) I, I can't
speak.
It's all right, Cogsworth.
I can't..
Lumiere,
my friend.
It was an honor to serve
with you.
The honor was mine.
(BELLE SOBBING)
Come back!
Please, don't leave me!
I love you.
(GASPING)
(RUMBLING)
Oh. Maestro!
(GASPS AND COUGHS)
MAESTRO CADENZA: Madame!
Maestro!
(LAUGHING) (GASPS)
- Lumiere!
- Ah?
Cogsworth, we beat the clock!
- (LAUGHS)
- - Mon ami!
LUMIÈRE: Plumette!
Plumette!
Oh, Mon amor!
(PLUMETTE MOANS)
(GASPS)
Oh. Oh.
(BOTH WHOOPING)
(BOTH SHOUTING)<
Chip! Look at you!
You're a little boy again!
What did I tell you, darling?
Ohh..
You smell so good.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(ALL TALKING EXCITEDLY)
MAESTRO CADENZA: Froufrou, lamer!
Darling?
Oh! Mr. Potts!
Beatrice!
I remember!
I do!
CLOTHILDE: Henry?
Henry!
Oh, dear.
I've been so lonely.
Turn back into a clock.
Lumiere, look!
Oh! My Prince!
Hello, old friend.
It's so good to see you.
You saved our lives, Mademoiselle.
CHIP: Belle! It's me!
It's Chip!
(SINGING) ♪ Tale as old as time ♪
♪ Tune as old as song ♪
♪ Bitterweet and strange
Finding you can change ♪
♪ Learning you were wrong ♪
(LAUGHS)
MRS. POTTS: ♪ Winter turns to spring ♪
♪ Famine turns to feast ♪
♪ Nature points the way ♪
♪ Nothing left to say ♪
♪ Beauty and the Beast ♪
What? What is it?
How would you feel about
growing a beard?
- (GROWLS)
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
GARDEROBE AND CHORUS
♪ Certain as the sun ♪
♪♪
♪ Rising in the east ♪
♪ Tale as old as time ♪
♪ Song as old as rhyme ♪
♪ Beauty and the Beast ♪
♪♪
♪ Tale as old as time ♪
♪ Song as old as rhyme ♪
♪ "Beauty and the Beast" ♪
♪♪
Synchronized by srjanapala
WOMAN: (SINGING)
♪ How does a moment last forever? ♪
♪ How can a story never die? ♪
♪ It is love we must hold on to ♪
♪ Never easy but we try ♪
♪ Sometimes our happiness is captured ♪
♪ Somehow a time
and place stand still ♪
♪ Love lives on inside our hearts ♪
♪ And always will ♪
♪ Minutes turn to hours ♪
♪ Days to years then gone ♪
♪ But when all else has been forgotten ♪
♪ Still our song lives on ♪
♪ Maybe some moments
weren't so perfect ♪
♪ Maybe some memories not so sweet ♪
♪ But we have to know some bad times ♪
♪ Or our lives are incomplete ♪
♪ Then when shadows overtake us ♪
♪ Just when we feel all hope is gone ♪
♪ We'll hear our song
and know once more ♪
♪ Our love lives on ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ How does a moment last forever? ♪
♪ How does our happiness endure? ♪
♪ Through the darkest of our troubles ♪
♪ Love is beauty, love is pure ♪
♪ Love pays no mind to desolation ♪
♪ It flows like a river through the soul ♪
♪ Protects, proceeds, and perseveres ♪
♪ And makes us whole ♪
♪ Minutes turn to hours ♪
♪ Days to years then gone ♪
♪ But when all else has been forgotten ♪
♪ Still our song lives on ♪
♪ How does a moment last forever ♪
♪ When our song lives on ♪
WOMAN: (SINGING)
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Tale as old as time ♪
♪ True as it can be ♪
♪ Barely even friends ♪
♪ Then somebody bends unexpectedly ♪
MAN:
♪ Just a little change ♪
♪ Small to say the least ♪
♪ Both a little scared ♪
♪ Neither one prepared ♪
BOTH:
♪ Beauty and the Beast ♪
♪ Ever just the same ♪
♪ Ever a surprise ♪
♪ Ever as before ♪
♪ And ever just as sure ♪
♪ As the sun will rise ♪
MAN: ♪ Oh ♪
WOMAN: ♪ Hey ♪
♪ Ah ♪
MAN: ♪ Ooh ♪
BOTH: ♪ Uh-huh ♪
♪ Ever just the same ♪
♪ And ever a surprise ♪
♪ Ever as before ♪
♪ And ever just as sure ♪
♪ As the sun will rise ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
WOMAN:
♪ Tale as old as time ♪
♪ Tune as old as song ♪
♪ Oh ♪
BOTH:
♪ Bittersweet and strange ♪
♪ Finding you can change ♪
♪ Learning you were wrong ♪
MAN: ♪ Certain as the sun ♪
WOMAN: ♪ Certain as the sun ♪
MAN: ♪ Rising in the east ♪
WOMAN: ♪ Tale as old as time ♪
MAN: ♪ Song as old as rhyme ♪
BOTH: ♪ Beauty and the Beast ♪
WOMAN: ♪ Tale as old as time ♪
MAN: ♪ Song as old as rhyme ♪
BOTH: ♪ Beauty and the Beast ♪
MAN: (SINGING)
♪ I was the one who had it all ♪
♪ I was the master of my fate ♪
♪ I never needed anybody in my life ♪
♪ I learned the truth too late ♪
♪ I'll never shake away the pain ♪
♪ I close my eyes but she's still there ♪
♪ I let her steal into
my melancholy heart ♪
♪ It's more than I can bear ♪
♪ Now I know
she 'll never leave me ♪
♪ Even as she runs away ♪
♪ She will still torment me
Calm me, hurt me ♪
♪ Move me, come what may ♪
♪ Wasting in my lonely tower ♪
♪ Waiting by an open door ♪
♪ I'll fool myself
she'll walk right in ♪
♪ And be with me for evermore ♪
♪ I rage against the trials of love ♪
♪ I curse the fading of the light ♪
♪ Though she's already flown
So far beyond my reach ♪
♪ She's never out of sight ♪
♪ Now I know she'll never leave me ♪
♪ Even as she fades from view ♪
♪ She will still inspire me ♪
♪ Be a part of everything I do ♪
♪ Wasting in my lonely tower ♪
♪ Waiting by an open door ♪
♪ I'll fool myself she 'll walk right in ♪
♪ And as the long, long nights begin ♪
♪ I'll think of all that might have been ♪
♪ Waiting here for evermore ♪
♪♪