["The Best Things In Life
Are Free - Live" playing]
[speaker] In October 1957,
the Soviet Union launched
the world's first artificial
satellite, Sputnik 1, into orbit.
Their achievement
fueled a space race
between the United
States and the Soviets.
There has been some debate
about what followed,
but I was there, and this
is the real story. Mostly.
[anchorperson 1]
Until two days ago,
that sound had never
been heard on this earth.
♪ Oh, the moon
Belongs to everyone ♪
♪ The best things in
life They're free ♪
[anchorperson 2] America
attempted to launch her satellite
with disastrous results.
[anchorperson 3] The Soviet
Union has sent a man into space
and brought him back alive.
[anchorperson 4] The Soviets
made the most of the flight
in their worldwide propaganda.
Naturally, there was
jubilation in Russia.
Recognizing the head start
obtained by the Soviets,
I believe that this nation should
commit itself to achieving the goal,
before this decade is out,
of landing a man on the moon and
returning him safely to the earth.
♪ The best Best
things in life ♪
♪ They're free ♪
[John F. Kennedy] We choose to
go to the moon in this decade
and do the other things,
not because they are easy,
but because they are hard.
Because that challenge is one
that we are willing to accept,
one we are unwilling to postpone,
and one we intend to win.
[Gus Grissom] Command Pilot.
One, two, three, four, five.
Five, four, three, two, one.
[Grissom] Flame!
[Roger Chaffee] We've got
a fire in the cockpit.
Let's get out!
We're burning up!
Astronauts Virgil Grissom, Edward White
and Roger Chaffee have been killed.
[anchorperson 5] Press officials
say because of the tragedy,
the Apollo 1 flight has now
been postponed indefinitely.
I... It's, uh... [chuckles]
It's a groovy trip,
but there are a lot more important
things to do first in the United States.
Maybe when all
that's taken care of,
we can afford to go to the moon.
[Richard Nixon] We find
ourselves rich in goods
but ragged in spirit.
Reaching with magnificent
precision for the moon
but falling into raucous
discord on Earth.
We are caught at
war wanting peace.
We're torn by division
wanting unity.
This giant Saturn rocket
and all the rest of the equipment
here began as part of a race
to beat the Russians
with the national goal
of putting a man on the
moon in this decade.
But their trip will cost more
than anyone thought it would.
And their chances of landing on the
moon in the 1960s are increasingly slim.
[alarm sounding]
[people chattering]
First week as manager, Stu.
Doesn't sound like
it's going great.
So either our meters are off
or there's a breach
in one of the tanks.
But there's no
protocol for this.
- And we can't source the leak because it's liquid hyd...
- Liquid hydrogen.
It's colorless and odorless.
Everybody out! Let's go!
Reed, Kyle, pencils down.
It could be burning, and we
wouldn't know it. Find a door.
Come on! Run, run! No walking.
What's he doing?
Is he cleaning?
No, no. It's an... It's an
old-school leak detection process.
It's a broom.
Stu, you're better than this. Come on.
Straw plus liquid hydrogen equals...
[grunting]
All right, we're good! Don't
worry about it. Come on.
We got work to do. Let's go.
[coughing]
Uh, the new protocol
is the broom method.
We need a new broom.
I for sure thought he was dead.
[grunts] Come on.
- [sighs]
- It's still broke
from the last time
you were in a mood.
Yeah, I can see that.
- Boeing called again.
- Call Congress, Henry, not me.
I don't have their number.
Every day, every day, something
is breaking around here.
Or blowing up. We're underfunded,
under... understaffed.
But yeah, we're still expected to
beat the pants off the Russians.
You mind telling me how the
hell we're supposed to do that?
Could start by being a little
nicer to the vending machines.
Ooh! There it is!
- What?
- There's a cat.
-[Henry] So what?
-It's a black cat, Henry. It's bad luck.
- [grunts, sighs]
- Okay, it's gone.
-All right. Thank God.
-Okay. Let's go. [breathes shakily]
- Call security.
- I won't.
- I will not. It...
- Yes, you will.
The last thing that we need
around here is a black cat.
[Henry] They don't deal
with things like this.
Yes, they do. They do now.
- Y-You're overreacting.
- No, you're not overreacting enough.
Call 'em right now. Right now.
How do I look?
You're glowing. Good luck.
- [laughing]
- Good afternoon, boys.
Wrong room, sweetheart.
We don't need dictation.
I'm Kelly Jones. I'll be
running the meeting today.
You must be Phil Hunley,
Neil Brown and...
Ooh. [chuckles] Zack Tanner. You
don't mind if I sit down, do you?
Uh, all due respect, Mrs. Jones,
we're a progressive company.
We employ 16 women
in our steno pool.
We're selling
sports cars to men.
We're selling a
300 horsepower...
355, 428 cubic inch V-8
beast is what you're selling.
You want to focus on the car's
speed. Something like this.
Look familiar? Chevy Camaro.
Pontiac Firebird. And Oldsmobile.
All from last month.
Thankfully, you have something
that your competition
doesn't have.
The Mustang Fastback. "355 horses
for him. Seat belts for the family."
The seat belts? We only put them in
because they might be mandatory next year.
Let's play a game.
Now I'm gonna guess what kind of
car each one of you gentlemen drive.
Zack, Ford Mustang '66
convertible. It's poppy red.
Oh, no Mustangs for
you husbands though.
A Lincoln Continental for Neil.
A station wagon for poor Phil.
Oh, Phil. You know what
the best part of my day is?
When my husband Charlie
comes home at night.
I can't even imagine what it would be
like if-if one night he... he didn't.
- [sighs]
- Now imagine the conversation
if someone told your
wife that this car,
its 355 horses
and 105 top speed,
this car is what brings her husband
home safe to her family every night.
Now she wants you to have it.
She says the words every
married man dreams of hearing...
"I'd feel so much better if you bought
yourself that Mustang, sweetheart."
[swallows]
How did you guess what
kind of cars they drive?
What, bribe their
secretaries or something?
Kelly, seriously?
Two packs of Virginia Slims
and a bottle of Paco Rabanne.
- Everyone has their price.
- [chuckles]
I'm just lucky that my water
didn't break in there. Oh, God.
Hi, Ron. How's the wife?
Now, the baby bump,
dry-clean only.
Yes, I have that noted. A-Also,
Omega confirmed for next week,
I finished the
Baskin-Robbins artwork,
and that guy from Palmex
asked for your
address to send roses,
but I gave him
mine because I know
- how you feel about roses.
- How I feel about roses.
Also, John called. Again. He wants
to take you to dinner Tuesday.
Tell him I moved to LA. And
call Bruce from Dow Chemical.
I hear they're looking for
a new agency for Ziploc.
People should be boycotting
Dow. They make napalm.
People say they're boycotting, but
they're still buying sandwich bags.
They also sell Saran
Wrap and Styrofoam.
Think people are going to stop using
Styrofoam? What's your coffee in?
Now, I know you and your
friends want to save the world,
and by the time you're
running this place in 1984,
there's gonna be no nukes
and equal rights for all.
But until then, we've
got a job to do.
Kelly! Kelly! Kelly. Kelly.
We've got a big problem.
I just stormed off set,
and, yes, it was justified.
I cannot work with
these Hoover people.
Apparently, they have issues with the
way that I am shooting their commercial.
They actually said that.
"Their." It's my commercial.
They make vacuums. I make art.
- Sorry, did we have a meeting set?
- No. No.
I'm sorry. I didn't
realize I had to set a time
to speak to one of
my dearest friends.
The last time we spoke, you fired
me. And I don't work for you.
You know what, Kelly, I didn't
come in here to be berated.
I came in to be agreed with!
You have that
Nestlé pitch in ten.
Very important.
- That is a lie. Goodbye.
- [sighs]
Lance, getting you
this directing gig
- was a Christmas miracle.
- [scoffs]
It took me three weeks to
convince them that you were stable
after your Jell-O
shoot from hell.
[gibbering] Jell-O
was not my fault.
- Ugh. That actor wa...
- Was five. You made him cry.
Well, I did that child a favor.
Hollywood is no cakewalk.
What about the Heinz commercial?
You went 40,000 over budget.
- It was about ketchup.
- It was not about ketchup.
It was about the
promise of ketchup.
No one sees what I'm
doing for their products.
I am elevating them.
I should be in film by now.
I passed on directing
Valley of the Dolls.
That is on me, but still.
Now, what do we call you, right? The
Kubrick of commercials. All right.
Oh, my God. Stanley is a hack. He does one
good movie, and suddenly he's a genius.
You are a legend,
right? Creative genius.
You're also hotheaded, mercurial and
can't stick to a budget for shit.
- Oh, thank you.
- That wasn't a compliment.
It is when you stop listening.
If you quit Hoover,
you'll be unhirable.
- [grunts]
- Okay.
Lance, why don't you march
your ass back to set,
and you apologize for
whatever fit you threw, okay?
Buy your boyfriend something nice for
Christmas for putting up with you.
Get something for me too, okay?
- [kisses] Merry Christmas, Lance.
- Merry Christmas.
Can you get me a
decent job, please?
[anchorperson 6] Apollo 8 launched
successfully this morning.
A much needed win for NASA. In
Vietnam, more men were lost today.
And 15 million miles...
I'll have another round, please,
and a look at the dinner menu.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Thanks.
Two specials tonight. Chicken
potpie and Oysters Rockefeller.
We'll do the chicken.
She's allergic to oysters.
And I'll take a shot of Macallan,
a lemon and a cutting board.
-Yes, sir.
-Oh, I'm sorry. Do I know you?
Seat belts in a sports car.
I mean, that's a great angle.
Unfortunately, they're
about to kill the account.
Why would they do that?
Because someone told them
that you don't really
have a bun in the oven.
Phil. [chuckles]
Let me explain.
That's the last time
I trust a woman.
- [laughs] - I actually
sent you a baby gift.
Which was so sweet, by
the way. Let me just...
Neil, let-let me
explain. If you...
What is this? Who do
you work for, Ogilvy?
Huh? You can't outsell
me, so you got me fired?
Just the opposite.
I wanna hire you.
[scoffs]
Name's Moe Berkus. I work
for the president's office.
Of what company?
The president.
[bites, clears throat]
We need a, uh,
marketing specialist,
and word has it you
are the very best.
[chuckles]
So I did a little digging,
and, uh... [mumbles]
You have quite a
colorful past, Kelly.
Or should I call you Jane?
Stewardess from Chicago.
Or perhaps you would prefer
Amy, the nurse from Ohio.
Face like that, who's
gonna check references?
Page you're looking
for isn't in there.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh, sure you don't.
And I get it.
Hey, I have dozens of IDs,
and my real name's not Moe.
[chuckles] With all the names you
could've picked, you landed on Moe?
You have singular talent.
Why waste it selling cars
when you can think bigger?
Well, Moe, what's
bigger than Ford?
You ever been to
Florida? [chews]
They want you to sell the moon?
The moon. The Apollo mission.
The whole thing.
And this Moe guy works for NASA?
Yeah. I mean, y... Well, no. Um, kind
of. He-He-He works for the government.
Oh, which part?
Kelly?
Does this guy... Are we
working for Richard Nixon?
Because, Kelly, I will not
work for Richard Nixon.
I'm a card-carrying feminist.
I actually have a card.
I can't even believe he's
going to be president.
I had no idea I disagreed
with this much of the country.
We are working for
NASA to sell the moon.
Nobody disagrees about the moon.
- [stammers]
- No. You and I both know
that everywhere around us every day
something terrible is happening.
- Everywhere.
- [sighs]
Except in space.
I hate that this
is working on me.
They definitely need our help.
Did you know of NASA's
first 29 missions,
only 48% have been successful?
That can't be. That's crazy.
Did you know the ratio of men to
women in Cocoa Beach is 5-to-1?
[chuckles] Wow.
As long as you got us a quiet
place that's not on Frat Row.
The... The guidebook
said it's quaint.
["Sweet Soul Music" playing]
[people cheering]
♪ Do you like good music? ♪
♪ Huh, that sweet soul music ♪
You're fired.
Who are all these people?
It is a Wednesday.
It's like they're on
a different planet.
They call it Florida.
Please tell me you booked
a room away from the pool.
♪ Dancing with the music ♪
♪ Oh yeah, oh yeah ♪
♪ Spotlight on
Otis Redding now ♪
-[radio announcer] sixteen and 21...
-[radio chorus] Weather!
Clear to partly cloudy tomorrow.
A few isolated thundershowers during
the afternoon and early evening.
A low tonight, 65 to 75.
Currently 77 in the
Moonport cities.
That's KO twenty-twenty
news, sports and weather.
[radio chorus] WKKO...
["These Foolish Things" playing]
-Hey, Joe.
-Evening, Cole. What'll it be?
Coffee. Black.
And whatever takes the
least amount of time
to put in a bag, my friend.
♪ A cigarette that bears... ♪
[sighs]
♪ ...A lipstick's traces ♪
♪ An airline ticket ♪
♪ To romantic places ♪
♪ And still my
heart Has wings ♪
♪ These foolish things ♪
♪ Remind me of you ♪
♪ A tinkling piano ♪
♪ In the next apartment ♪
Uh, miss, you're on fire.
[chuckles] Very original.
No, I do not wanna stop,
drop and roll with you.
No, your book is on fire.
[gasps] God.
- [chuckles] Okay.
- [yelps, shrieks]
-All right. All right. All right.
-Oh, my God.
-I'm sorry. Thank you. I just...
-Just as a rule of thumb,
alcohol and flames, they...
they like each other.
Yeah. Oh, gosh. [breathes
shakily] I-I-I ruined your jacket.
No, this thing's seen
worse. Been through worse.
Let me buy a drink
for your troubles.
- That's not necessary.
- I insist.
I don't drink. It's okay.
Oh, really? An astronaut
who doesn't drink.
That's very intriguing.
What makes you think
I'm an astronaut?
Because you have an Apollo pin,
and only astronauts get those.
So you know a thing
or two about NASA.
Yeah, well, I'm a recent
fan. I'm Kelly Jones.
[chuckles] I'm no astronaut. I
just work at Kennedy. Cole Davis.
Well, what do you do there?
[stammers] Uh... Look, the
last thing I want to do
- is make small talk about my job.
- Oh. [chuckles]
Sorry. That didn't sound...
- I didn't mean it for it to... Uh.
- That's okay.
No. You were being honest.
- [Joe] Order up, Cole.
- [stammers] Um...
["These Foolish
Things" continues]
♪ Oh, how The ghost
of you clings ♪
♪ These foolish things ♪
♪ Remind me of you ♪
♪ Let me tell you ♪
♪ First daffodils... ♪
[sighs]
♪ ...And all excited cables ♪
♪ And candle lights On
little corner tables ♪
I wasn't being honest.
If I was being honest,
I'd have told you you're
the most beautiful woman
that I've seen in longer
than I can remember,
and I have a very good memory.
All I really want to do is just buy
you a drink and talk to you for hours,
but I can't so I'm trying really
hard to just forget that you're here.
It was nice to meet you, Kelly.
I really am sorry.
♪ And the scent of roses ♪
♪ And waiters whistling
As the last bar closes ♪
♪ And, oh, a beauty
That is spring springs ♪
♪ These foolish things
Remind me of you ♪
[press agent on megaphone]
Welcome to Rockets Road,
also known as Alligator Alley.
You'll wanna keep your arms
and legs inside the cart
if you wanna keep
your arms and legs.
[chuckles]
No, that's just a little joke.
They mostly attack in the water.
Now, today's tour will take approximately
two and a half to three hours.
So let's get comfy-cozy.
Now on the right is
our testing facility.
State-of-the-art.
- [Kelly] It's on fire.
- It is often on fire.
Up ahead, we have the
vehicle assembly building.
That's where they
assemble the rockets.
That is the tallest single-story
building in the world.
You can fit four Statue of
Liberties inside that building.
[Ruby] Wow. Life Magazine
really doesn't do it justice.
This is so gre... I'd
love to go inside.
It's highly
restricted. I'm sorry.
Come on, let's
get a closer look.
Oh, no, no. No. [stammers]
There's no entry here.
You need a special
access badge to enter.
Oh, like... like this one?
Yeah. That's, uh... Oh, no, no,
no, that's... that's my badge.
-Uh, hey... Oh.
-Look at this place. It's enormous!
- It seems like it's much bigger...
- They took my badge!
[Ruby] I mean, look
at this building.
-Hello? That's-That's my badge.
-Hello, sir. Hi.
Kelly Jones from
NASA Public Affairs.
Here's our all-access pass
for both of us. Thank you.
- [Ruby] Thank you.
- Wait, wait. My card.
Now, this I can sell.
Yoo-hoo!
Hello. Boys, boys!
Hi. Kelly Jones.
I'm from the new NASA
Public Affairs team.
Can I ask you two
a few questions?
Name, age, and
what's your job here?
Uh, I'm Stu Bryce. One of the,
uh, head engineers, and I'm 24.
- We'll say 35.
- Yeah.
And you?
I'm Don Harper.
I-I work for him, and I'm 23.
You guys are babies.
The average age at
NASA is 26. [chuckles]
But w-we do know some old
people that work here as well.
- Yeah, like, 32, 33.
- Yeah.
I'll try not to kill both
of you for saying that.
So, tell us, Stu, what brings you
to join this great American mission?
Well, I s... saw a, uh, flyer
in my college dorm. [chuckles]
- "A childhood love of the stars."
- That's good.
- That's very moving.
- That's very good.
- And you?
- [Cole] Excuse me?
What are you doing here?
Well, I...
I tracked you down to
give you my phone number,
'cause I felt we
had a connection.
- What?
- Relax. I'm joking.
I work here now. Moe Berkus brought
me on to revamp NASA Public Affairs.
So you're the killer
from Manhattan.
And you must be the
launch director.
This is my associate,
Ruby Martin.
Yeah, I don't care.
Look. This building is
completely off-limits.
Everything in here can burn
you, freeze you, fry you,
poison you and crush you.
- So let's go. Out.
- [Kelly] How long have you worked here?
- A substantial amount of time.
- Hmm.
- What are you writing?
- Your quote.
That's not a quote. It was
just a thing that I said.
I'll punch it up. Do you have
time today for an interview?
And also, I need to sit down
with your senior officers.
- The photogenic types first.
- I can help with the selection process.
Look, my guys are too
weird for interviews,
and they're actually busy
doing life-and-death work.
[chuckles] Well, you know, I
don't need your permission.
The Americans are over their long
and expensive honeymoon in space,
and I'm here to remind them why they
fell in love in the first place.
Is that right? Well, Americans
should be very grateful
that these men are putting their
lives on the line for the mission.
[chuckles] Well, you don't know
much about American people, do you?
[chuckles] You don't know very much about
your office I'm about to show you, do you?
Is this a storage closet?
Nope. Storage
closet has a window.
Okay, so, instant coffee...
[sighs] ...is in the break room.
Just run the tap for a
minute to flush out the rust.
Do either of you know how
to work a fire extinguisher?
No? Mkay. PASS
method's pretty simple.
Just, uh, pull the pin,
aim, squeeze, sweep.
If you need anything else,
uh, maybe just go back to New
York and get it. Have a good day.
Well, at least he's
easy on the eyes.
He's hard on the ears though.
Not a great welcome wagon. I thought
you said they wanted our help.
Oh, no. I said they
needed our help.
And I do believe that
now more than ever.
How are we supposed to do that
if we can't talk to anyone
or look at anything?
[screams]
Aw, it's a cat. It's a cat.
- [Ruby] It's a cat!
- It's a cat.
You know what they
say about black cats?
If they cross your path, they're
probably going someplace else.
Okay, time to dig
out the old Rolodex.
Let's get creative. [blows]
Apollo 11 will land
our men on the moon,
and that makes us first.
If we do our jobs, we will
launch right from there,
July 16, bright and early.
Between now and then,
we will piece together
the biggest jigsaw puzzle
in the history of mankind.
Six million parts spread
out around the country,
and we will assemble, test,
and retest every single one
until we are certain that
Apollo 11 will take off
without a hitch and
head to the moon in...
Henry, sing it.
Seven months. Huh?
Seven months.
Please help me congratulate
the astronauts of Apollo 11.
Armstrong, Aldrin and Collins.
[cheering]
Hey, hey! How'd you like
the White House, boys? Huh?
Yeah, it was all right, except Neil
wouldn't let me steal the china.
- [KSC Apollo Team laughs]
- [Henry chuckles]
All right. Because in eight
months, when this is all over,
and they need new history books to
cover what we've accomplished here,
each and every single one of
you will be able to say that
"I did the hardest thing that
has ever been done." Yeah?
Yeah!
[KSC Apollo Team] Let's do it.
Let's get to it!
[whistling, cheering]
- Beautiful. Perfect.
- [grunts] Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Sir,
you said to tell you when the new
lady did anything you wouldn't like.
I'm here at the
Kennedy Space Center
with Deputy Launch
Director, Henry Smalls.
What's going on? That's my name.
He's got my name and my job!
It's been a great time for all of us.
You know, for me, this is very personal.
My father was an airman...
Who is that?
- It's not me.
- he died in the line of duty
- when I was a child...
- I'm not that handsome.
So this is for you, Dad.
- Oh, that's it.
- So sorry to hear that.
- Thanks for sharing. That must've been...
-My dad's still alive.
- [phone ringing]
- [drill buzzing]
Right. What is it that we can do
to sort of make 6:00 p.m.? Yeah.
NASA Public Affairs,
this is Kelly Jones.
Kelly, ABC wants next
week's press reel.
They also want the best photo
we have from the Apollo 8.
Tell them they can have it if they
give us their 6:00 p.m. time slot.
- Got it.
- If you air an animated segment,
I can offer you an exclusive...
[journalist] Thank you so much.
Your father was a
hero. You are a hero.
We so appreciate
you working at...
That was the head of NBC News.
Yeah, I don't
care. Who is that?
Thank you. See
you on the moon.
To the world,
that's Henry Smalls.
- That's not Henry Smalls.
- No, but you told me
that your guys don't do interviews,
so I had to hire new guys.
You have two of the best engineers
on the planet installing a window.
Phil, if you hammer one more time, I
swear to God I'm gonna lose my mind.
Put down the hammer, take your stupid
belts off and get back to testing.
On the move. Here we go.
Can you believe that view?
- We got the first photos from Apollo 8.
- It's better than mine.
The first shot of the
Earth from the moon.
Isn't that the most beautiful
thing you've ever seen?
How'd you get this before me?
They're calling
it "Earthrise."
It's going to be at the top
of every news segment tonight.
I mean, '68 has been
such a terrible year.
Assassinations, this heinous war,
we've seen the worst of humanity.
Now NASA gives us this? A
whole new way to see the world.
And I'm gonna make
sure everybody sees it.
You can't just fake people!
- Hey, I'm here for the casting.
- Oh!
- Who's he?
- You. You're a juicy part.
So, here's the scenes
and the character bio.
This is the man that you're playing,
so you wanna up the charisma a bit.
- Can do. I'll up the...
- Okay? Okay.
- Sixty missions in Korea?
- Yeah.
- [chuckles] It's an honor.
- I flew 52 missions in Korea.
I rounded up.
"I flew 52 missions in
Korea." How was that?
- What?
- I'll work on it.
She has a fake me now.
- She got a fake me.
- She got a fake me and a fake you.
- You can't fake me and you.
- There's nothing here.
There's no Moe Berkus. I
checked every spelling.
I have a Moe Berkus on the line.
-Do you want me to talk?
-Oh, no, no. I'm gonna enjoy this.
This is gonna be the fastest
firing in NASA's history.
- Hey, Moe.
- Cole, I hear you're looking for me.
I am. Kelly Jones hired
actors to play NASA engineers.
It is unacceptable. I want
her desk cleared today.
Calm, calm, calm down, okay?
Washington watches TV.
Apollo is now on TV.
Every channel, every day.
So, you want to get to the moon?
I suggest, focus on your job.
Let Kelly do hers.
If she's made you the
belle of the ball,
why don't you just slip on
your tutu and do some dancing?
- She fired?
- Mm-mmm.
Are we fired?
["Security" playing]
[TV] Apollo 8, carrying astronauts
Borman, Lovell and Anders
was launched into
space by a Saturn V.
[Ruby] Every single network
is airing the Earthrise shot.
I mean, it's... it's
gonna be everywhere.
You know, I tried a
little something on it,
but I just don't think
it's working yet.
It's not enough.
We need a hook,
a way to weave the moon landing
into people's everyday lives
without them realizing it.
Uh, hi. Do you have
anything close to a salad?
Pickles come on a burger.
It's gonna be a minute, though.
Apollo news has business picking up.
All the tourists love to come in
and see little pieces of history.
- Pieces of history?
- Yeah, like... like that pen.
John Glenn ate here
every night in '61.
He would work on his flight manuals,
and he'd use one of our pens.
That one ended up on Mercury 6.
You're at the only restaurant in the
world whose name's been in space.
[chuckles] That's cool.
[press agent on megaphone]
And right up ahead,
it's the famous Mercury rockets.
Be sure to get a picture here,
but don't stand too close.
They might go off.
[Kelly] He recovered
after that weekend.
[secretaries laughing]
Does it bother you that a room
dies every time you walk into it?
You're supposed to
stay on your side.
- I missed you.
- Hmm.
I'd like you to approve
our new ad campaigns.
Why don't you just sidestep
me like you did last time?
I wanna apologize for blindsiding
you with the interviews.
I have a fix for
our money problems.
Well, your apology is rejected,
and so is whatever this is.
- Omega.
- Look, this isn't Madison Avenue.
- We don't pay for this stuff.
- No, it's cost-free.
The brands get a
tie-in money can't buy,
and NASA works its way into
the minds of everyday people.
A watch ad? That's-That's
your big idea?
- [chuckles] Ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Toothpaste.
Tang. "The energy breakfast drink
chosen for Apollo astronauts
- on their trip to the moon."
- Moon coupons?
But, my personal favorite,
Fruit of the Loom. Right?
The guys gotta wear something
under those big suits, don't they?
Nothing says NASA like
Fruit of the Loom.
Look, I am not turning this
ship into a flying billboard
no matter how much
you want it to happen.
And by the way, we don't have time
to test all this before liftoff.
We don't have to send any of this up
into space as long as we say it went.
Oh, so you're gonna lie?
It's called selling. We're
not lying to the customer.
- We're changing the way they think.
- No, it's called lying.
Everyone is just a
customer to you, huh?
Look, I know that you're a big
old fancy ad shark and everything,
but NASA's not something that you
sell with a jingle and a slogan.
You do not know who we are.
Yeah, okay. Who's
Margaret Hamilton?
- Who?
- She works here for you.
There are 400,000 people
that are affiliated
- with this space program, Ms. Jones.
- She's one of your engineers.
- Who's JoAnn Morgan?
- She works in the firing room.
Did you ever ask her why she took
this job in the first place? I have.
She says it's because she
has rocket fuel in her blood.
And NASA's not just
a logo, it's people.
People who wake up every morning
and commit to accomplishing
the impossible.
And all while wearing the same
underwear as the rest of us.
[giggles]
Ella, can I help you
with anything at all?
Mm-mmm.
[breathes shakily]
Thank you.
So I ran the projections,
and this is what
you stand to make
if you accept key sponsorships.
[sighs] We-We can't
take private money.
[stammers] It
doesn't matter, okay?
I'm about to make
NASA so popular
that Congress will finally turn
the taps back on around here.
And all I have to do is just let
Armstrong put on an Omega watch?
[sighs] No. If we get
the money flowing,
then you've gotta prove to me
that Cocoa Beach has a
decent place to get dinner.
Um...
- Deal. I...
- Yes! Deal! Yes! Whoo!
Uh, no, wait. I'm drawing the
line at toilet paper though,
because the world does not get to know
what our guys wipe their ass with.
Well, shit.
[interviewer] Would you like to go for
a vacation when you come back to Earth?
The situation being
what it is now,
the place I would
most like to go, uh...
Lose the table
next time, Walter.
Neil looks like he's giving
GE's quarterly profit report.
[chuckles] That's
always been our table...
TV brings them in to
people's living rooms.
They should look like
they belong there.
- It'd mean that we succeeded.
- [crowd clamoring]
You're still in charge,
Walter. Don't you worry.
When I'm done helping though,
those men are gonna be
bigger than The Beatles.
I'm getting to go 99.9% of the way
there, and that suits me just fine.
["Big Bird" playing]
What's the name of
that VP at Kellogg's?
I believe it's
Harrison Driscoll.
All right, Harrison.
So instead of "Snap,
Crackle, Pop,"
"Neil, Buzz and Mike."
It's cute, right?
["Big Bird" continues]
[Henry] Cole!
[speaks indistinctly]
[chattering, indistinct]
- Make sure that doesn't rust, Henry.
- Can you mark these?
[cat meows]
- [Henry] Hey, hey.
- Did you see that?
You didn't see the cat?
Go closer on the Tang bottle.
Make the font bigger and
put bacon with the eggs.
Let's not forget, we're
selling America, here.
"Peter Pan Peanut Butter. Peanut butter
that's out-of-this-world smooth."
"Hasselblad. See the
world the way they do."
Larry, this is
Omega's big chance.
On the back of every Speedmaster
till the end of time,
"The first watch worn
on the moon." Right?
Now we just gotta stand her up.
[Henry] It's all
gonna be worth it.
["Big Bird" continues]
- Hey. Hey! You're in my spot.
- We're setting up a shot for Kelly.
[Walter] We've got three astronauts
on the Apollo 11 mission.
There they are in front of
three beautiful American cars.
Oh, this is great. You gotta be
in the test facility right now.
[astronauts] Talk to Kelly.
Kelly said we could take a
Corvette home for a dollar.
- There you are.
- A dollar?
I'm gonna need them for 15
minutes, but that's all.
I needed them 15
minutes ago, Kelly.
You know how expensive
those suits are? [yelps]
[Walter] Oh, don't worry.
It's just the launch director.
[interviewer 2] This
strange looking bird,
the LEM, Mr. Kelly.
How does it work?
[Thomas J. Kelly] Well, this
is a spacecraft that's used
to take men down to
the lunar surface.
And two of the three
astronauts in the LEM...
[Neil Armstrong]
Flight, we missed target
and are drifting
into the vast abyss.
[alarm blares]
[sighs]
- And we're dead. Again.
- [Cole] Yeah.
Ran out of fuel 30
seconds before touchdown.
Yeah, but the landing, though,
- it was smooth... It was good.
- Great pitch. Forward.
You're both bad liars.
Neil, Mike, Buzz, if I
can get one more photo
for Ms. Jones and Omega?
Who are you, man?
- All right, watches up, boys.
- [clears throat]
And smile for Omega.
[phone ringing]
- Davis.
- Am I interrupting?
- Always. [sighs] - There
should be a box in front of you.
- Why don't you open it?
- [chuckles]
Omega thanks you
for your service.
Your boys are all over TV,
the taps are
flowing again. So...
dinner?
Yeah. Canaveral
Pier. Five o'clock.
Wear your watch.
3:00 p.m. is their best and final
time slot to air the interview.
For an exclusive with Armstrong? 3:00
p.m. is for children and deadbeats.
They said they have
breaking news from the war.
[anchorperson 2] Unknown
size enemy force.
Enemy casualties are unknown,
but you've seen
how it really was.
So much for keeping Apollo
back in the news cycle.
Heroism, danger, fear,
all rolled into one.
Words don't describe it.
Richard Threlkeld, CBS News.
Near the Cambodian border.
Thank you, Captain
Scotty. Appreciate you.
Okay.
Well, you spare no
expense on a lady.
Just try it.
Shrimp, mayo, bun.
And that happens to be the
best meal in a hundred miles.
- Mmm.
- Told you.
How'd I not know about
this place? [smacks lips]
Not everybody
likes to advertise.
Nice one. That's good.
That's where the rocket will
launch out of. Right there.
That watch looks great on
you. You wear it very well.
Thanks.
That night at the bar,
what I said to you...
That you couldn't
take your eyes off me,
and I was the most beautiful
woman that you'd ever seen?
Y-Yeah, that part.
That... Yes. Mm-hmm.
It was impulsive.
It was meant for a stranger,
and we're working together now.
So, I just don't want you
to think that I was...
Interested?
I just wanted to clear the air.
Oh. Well, the air was clear.
Good.
[chuckles] I had a thought.
[inhales sharply] Yeah. It
was perfect for 30 seconds.
What are the networks
covering night and day?
You think I have
time to watch TV?
Vietnam. They're broadcasting
straight from the action.
And people don't want to
just hear the news anymore.
They wanna see it in the making.
Okay.
- Why not let 'em?
- [chuckles]
Oh, you want to put a live
television camera on the LEM?
Yes.
My guys are trying
to survive up there.
They don't have time to figure
out how to film a movie.
We'll figure it out for 'em. All
they have to do is point and shoot.
You don't get it. It's
a logistical nightmare.
There's power issues,
storage, weight.
There's not even a camera
that would work up there
'cause it's negative
200 degrees at night
and over 250 degrees
during the daytime.
Can you imagine seeing it?
No. I just said
it's impossible.
- Yes. That's the point.
- Mmm.
It would be the greatest
televised event ever.
Do you think this
is a game show?
There is a very good reason
why the Soviets aren't
broadcasting their space walks.
Because they're a
tight-lipped dictatorship.
- Yeah, that's not us.
- Wow.
When we succeed, we
do it as a nation.
- And when we fail, we grieve as a nation.
- Right.
That's what it means
to be American.
Oh, stop telling me what
it means to be an American.
There's only one of us here that has
served their country their entire life.
I'm sorry. We're not putting
the camera on the LEM.
I mean it. We're not.
We are.
There's no way he can
do it without more fuel.
[buzzer sounds]
- Have him run it again.
- Yeah.
Okay. [sighs] I'm on a
tight schedule. What is it?
Kelly briefed me on the
camera idea, and we like it.
We like it a lot.
-She misspoke. We can't do it.
-[chuckles]
There is no such technology
that even exists.
Actually it does. You know?
The Department of
Defense designed this
to find downed fighter
pilots in Vietnam at night.
Now, it's classified but the
DOD is going to let you use it
as long as nobody
knows what it is.
There's absolutely no space
for equipment that heavy.
We are weighing
screws for God's sake.
What... I mean, what
is this, 15 pounds?
Okay. So, just,
like, lighter screws.
We're trying for
another fuel cell.
So our men, when they get to the moon,
they still have enough fuel to lift off.
Out of all her bad ideas,
this one is the worst.
Actually, the
president loves it.
So, now it's a great idea.
So, let me put it
to you simply, Cole.
Find a way to put this on that.
This is an order.
From the tippy top.
[Cole sighs]
Don, Stu. Can you
come in here, please?
Thank you. Let's not
make everything so hard.
Please help Miss Jones strip
this top secret camera down.
I don't want 'em to
know it's top secret.
Well, now they do.
Please strip this
top secret camera.
Mount it onto the LEM
for live broadcasting.
[Moe] Cole. One last thing.
Last week, a CIA spy plane took
some surveillance photographs
of the new Russian N1 rocket.
And Congress saw it,
and some of the members
are having cold feet
- about the final round of funding.
- [sighs]
We're months away from
winning this thing.
I'm gonna send them down here,
and you're gonna convince
them to sit tight.
No. I'm... I'm gonna write
up some talking points.
Huh.
Don't take it personally.
Pilots fight gravity.
It's part of their nature.
[sighs]
[engine starting]
Henry?
Oh. [chuckles]
Well, I'm... I'm
glad you're not Cole.
- Oh?
- Yeah.
- [chuckles]
- He don't like me smoking.
[chuckles] What, are you
worried he's gonna ground you?
[chuckles]
Uh, no. I, uh... [chuckles] I had
emergency bypass surgery last year.
Yeah. That son of a bitch. He's
hell-bent on keeping me alive.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
[sighs] Yeah.
Nobody here does.
Just Cole.
Yeah. He came to the hospital and
held my wife's hand for three days.
Yeah. It's a long way
from the day we met.
[sighs]
Kid had just got
back from Korea.
The top pilot in the Air Force.
Silver Star. Flying Cross.
He was first in line at Edwards when
they were looking for astronauts.
But, uh, he ended up
not making the cut.
So, what got him?
It was his temper.
[chuckles] No, no. His heart.
Doc found an A-fib.
A little thing but enough to
keep him out of the program.
Cole Davis is the best pilot
who will never get to space.
You know, I've been looking at this
view every day for the last 15 years.
But lately, it's like I'm
seeing it for the first time.
Apollo 1 cast a big
shadow on this place.
It's nice to have some
light back. [sighs]
Hey, I keep seeing Cole
drive out there every night.
What's he doing?
Gardening.
[sighs]
[engine starts]
- [Henry] You ready?
- Yeah. [sighs]
[Henry sighs]
All right. Look, we just...
We give the senator a tour.
We play nice for 30 minutes.
We keep the lights on.
[sighing] Okay. Fine.
[gasps] Oh. [shushes]
- [Henry] What?
- [Cole] She's just there.
- Don't run.
- No, no. [shushes]
- Just don't run. Don't...
- Wait. [shushing] Shut up.
No. See, you scared it.
[Henry] I just ate.
Henry, come on! Come
on! [breathes heavily]
I hate that cat. [pants]
[pants] I see what
y... you mean. [pants]
That's an asshole cat. [pants]
Did you see the look it gave me?
- [sighs]
- It's just taunting me now.
- What is that?
- [pants] That's cat food.
- Somebody's feeding that thing.
- Who's doing that?
Find them. [pants] Find them
immediately, and fire them immediately.
Mr. Davis. Sir, uh,
Senator Hopp is here.
All right. What?
You look fine.
[sighs] Senator.
-Hello, Mr. Davis.
-[Henry] Senator. What an honor.
- [Cole] It's an honor and a pleasure.
- Very nice to see you.
[Cole] Well, the Apollo
11 capsule has arrived,
and next week, we will be attaching
it to the Saturn V rocket.
And that gets us off the ground
and out of Earth's atmosphere.
Well, that's all very impressive,
but I have to be up-front.
Georgia had some devastating
floods this year.
And I'm voting to put this
money toward our relief fund.
That seems a little
selfish, don't you think?
- Excuse me?
- Uh, that's a figure of speech.
- Here's what he means.
- My voters mostly think
we are overspending on the moon.
- [Cole] That's funny, because...
- [Kelly] Yoo-hoo!
[in Southern accent]
Excuse me. Senator Hopp.
Oh, you probably
don't remember me,
but you spoke at my
sophomore year of college.
Georgia Tech. '55.
You're a Buzz?
- [chuckles] Yes, sir.
- Of course I remember.
Your words inspired me that day.
You said, "Commitment means
staying loyal to a cause."
Two years later, I graduated with
honors. Now I run this department.
You know, in '62, you
said that you would fight
for Kennedy's dream
no matter what.
I know that the moon mission
was more popular back then,
but it would be just a shame
if the man whose words
inspired me to work at NASA
didn't live by those
very same words.
It would be a
shame, wouldn't it?
Sir, you are just
such a wonderful man.
- Thank you so much.
- Mmm.
You are a wonderful man.
Isn't she just a wonderful
Georgia peach here?
- Oh, my.
- Oh. Yes.
- You are so sweet.
- Yes, I am.
Let me take you on the special VIP
tour they didn't tell you about.
- Oh, I'd love that.
- [chuckles] Wonderful.
Do you go on this tour with me?
[Kelly] I absolutely will.
[Hopp] That's so sweet.
[Henry] She teared up.
I mean, it's scary.
Wave and smile.
Bye-bye!
["People Sure Act
Funny" playing]
The space program is
not only a bloated mess,
but Apollo flies in
the face of our creator
and the true father
of this country.
I would remind you
that we don't...
We landed Hopp. We
need two more votes.
Looks like it's not
gonna be Vanning.
- Definitely not Vanning.
- Next, we have Senator Cook.
Cook's a little scary.
I'm not gonna lie.
He's a Cold War conservative.
He's worried that our
budget takes away from
weapons development at the DOD.
Now, Senator, with
the N1 rocket,
the Russians still could
land on the moon before us.
What we're about to show
you is our most recent intel
on what they plan
to build if they do.
["People Sure Act
Funny" continues]
- And these are photos?
- [Cole] No, sir.
Those are, uh, renderings
of a possible future.
Future photos?
Is that a laser?
It's going towards Earth, sir.
- What are they calling it?
- "Killer Lunar Laser Eliminator," sir.
- "Killer Lunar Laser Eliminator"?
- [Cole] Yes, sir.
Damn it. That's good.
And, finally, we
have Senator Hedges.
Now, he's always
been a fan of Apollo,
but he's getting pressure from
his state party not to fund.
He can't take in oxygen without
a camera pointed at him,
and we're about to have a
few of those around here.
Any questions?
No, ma'am.
Well, let's get him then.
- Hello, everyone!
- [launch attendees cheering]
[chuckles]
Gentlemen. [chuckles]
It's... It's... It's great
to be back, everyone.
You know how much I
love the Apollo program.
[cheering]
[chuckles]
Senator. Apollo 10 will
just be orbiting the moon.
But it's gonna get us information
critical for the touchdown of 11.
- Like landing conditions and location.
- Amazing.
And we've a special seat for you
here, Senator, amongst your fans.
- For me? Oh. Thank you.
- [chuckles]
[controller on speaker]
Apollo launch control,
and we are go on the countdown
for the Apollo 10 lunar
mission at this time.
[Cole on speaker] We have
ignition sequence start.
Five, four, three, two...
All engines running.
Liftoff. We have liftoff.
Forty-nine minutes
past the hour.
Tower clear. Tower clear.
Houston, she's all yours.
Glorious launch. Can't wait to
be right back here for Apollo 11.
We cannot thank you enough
for your support, Senator.
It's gonna cost you more
than a pair of binoculars.
I owe a favor to the
news fellas back home.
I'd like you to give them
an on-camera interview.
Uh, Senator, I'm
the very last person
that you want in
front of a camera.
Uh, I d... I don't
do interviews.
Except for you, Senator
Hedges. We would be delighted.
[chuckles] Smart lady.
- Good night.
Kelly?
- [stammers] It's okay.
- [stammers]
- Got it all under control.
- Mm-hmm.
["Slip Away" playing]
♪ What would I give ♪
♪ For just a few moments ♪
♪ Just to have you near ♪
♪ Tell me you will try ♪
- [Kelly] Hey. [chuckles]
- Hey. [chuckles]
You're entitled to a
night off too, you know.
[chuckles] If I
am, it's to sleep.
[chuckles] Oh, you
actually have a house?
I thought you slept
at the office.
Well, yeah. Usually. But, uh... Well,
I mean, sometimes I sleep with Jenny.
Oh, yeah. Right. Oh.
I'm sure she's great.
Jenny? Yeah. She... She is.
You wanna meet her?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. She'll love you. Come on.
♪ Love, oh, love ♪
Jenny.
Jenny, uh, this is Kelly.
- Kelly, meet Jenny.
- [chuckles]
She's just like the
one I flew in the war.
Keep her here so I can get my flight
hours on the weekends. Saves time.
[Kelly] Oh.
She's quite a lady.
[chuckles] Yeah. She is.
- Wanna go up?
- No.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- [chuckles] Okay. Come on.
- [chuckles]
Show you the second-best view.
["Do I Love You
(Indeed I Do)" playing]
♪ Here I am on bended knees ♪
♪ I lay my heart
down At your feet ♪
- You see those dark parts there?
- Yeah.
We call them the seas.
The gravity is stronger
in the seas, so...
We've looked to land in, uh, pretty
much every single one of them.
You got the Sea of Serenity.
Sea of Crises. We crossed that
one off the list pretty quick.
- Yeah. That's bad PR.
- [chuckles]
And then we finally settled
on, uh, the Sea of Tranquility.
That's the sweet spot.
You know, come to
think about it,
I... I know a lot
more about the moon
than I know about
you by a long shot.
I don't even know
where you're from.
Kansas.
Kelly from Kansas.
How'd you get into
advertising, Kelly from Kansas?
[sighs]
Uh, well, I was four
when my dad left,
and my mom lost the house.
We lived in a car.
And... [inhales sharply]
a church gave her a job
selling cookie tins.
So, she had this idea that we'd sell
more if it was me going door-to-door.
- Oh, yeah. Smart lady.
- [chuckles]
Cookie tins, then
it was vacuums,
then beauty goods
when I got older.
Yeah. Traveling the
country, me and my mom.
It's how we got
back on our feet.
Well, I'm sorry you
went through that.
Well, don't be. I...
Yeah. I learned early
on how to survive.
Plus, we all have our
share of tough breaks.
[chuckles, grunts]
Henry told me about the A-fib and you
getting kicked out of the program.
Hmm. I'm gonna have to have a
little conversation with Henry.
[Kelly laughs]
You know, I don't totally
agree with you though.
-How's that?
-[inhales sharply] Well, I just don't...
I don't think that our sad
stories are supposed to
teach us how to
survive the world.
[stammers] I think they're supposed
to make us wanna change it.
- Hmm.
- [Stu] Cole!
Buzz is trying to
hot-wire your Camaro!
- Come on, man.
- [chuckles]
Well...
You better go stop
him. [chuckles]
Yeah.
[gasps, yelps] Jesus! [gasps]
- We need to talk.
- [sighs]
[grunts]
[Kelly sighs]
You have done
outstanding work, Kel.
Public interest is way up.
You landed the senators
and secured the launch.
And that's why you broke
into my motel room?
As a thank-you?
Now that we know the whole
world will be watching,
we can't afford to lose.
We need to be prepared to
present an alternate version
of the moon landing.
An alternate version?
The... Artemis version.
She was the twin sister of
Apollo, uh, you know, the backup.
So we just need to be ready
to shoot a little picture.
Something showing us, you
know, up there walking around,
waving at the camera.
- You mean, to fake it?
- All goes well, we never use it.
But if not...
Hmm.
You know why I never
went to prison?
[chuckles] Probably,
but humor me.
'Cause I quit while I'm ahead.
Can't keep a secret this big.
Thousands of people work here.
Well, thousands of people work at
a classified location in the desert
that experiments on a fleet
of extraterrestrial pods
that we found at the
bottom of the ocean.
And you never heard
about that, did ya?
[chuckles] Come on,
that's not true.
Uh, maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
But the one thing
you can be sure of
is that the world will watch Americans
plant an American flag on the moon.
And you are telling me that
President Nixon supports this?
He probably would. He
doesn't know about it
in the same way that Cole
Davis will never know about it.
And that shouldn't be a problem
considering what else you
haven't shared with him
while you've grown closer.
I mean, what would a clean-cut
guy like that think about...
You made your point.
No one can outrun their past.
But I can make it
go away. Forever.
No more running.
[sighs]
I'm gonna need my assistant.
[chuckles]
Of course.
And we'll get you a
team of secure agents.
Now, who's the best director you've
got that no one's ever heard of?
["It's Your Thing" playing]
You're gonna love him.
This is the most remote
hangar on the base.
No one can go in or out
without my permission.
Wait, no one? Not even Cole?
Especially not Cole.
Unbelievable, Kelly.
You have me... [grunts]
forced onto a plane,
and brought to
godforsaken Florida!
Do you mind?
I'm a member of the DGA.
I will not be treated this way.
- I am calling my agent.
- You can't.
- Watch me.
- Remember we talked about this.
This is a high-security
government job.
- I'm doubling your quote.
- Okay.
- With a bonus.
- Mmm.
Yes. The only caveat being
that no one can ever
know what we're doing.
- I cannot accept that.
- They will shoot you.
What is my budget?
Your budget is whatever it costs
to turn this into the moon
for two-and-a-half hours.
It's shorter than Ben-Hur.
♪ I can't tell you ♪
♪ Who to sock it to ♪
♪ It's your thing ♪
♪ Baby, do what you wanna do ♪
♪ Ooh, I can't tell you ♪
♪ Who to sock it to ♪
I will need a fridge
full of Tab over there.
And an army of minions
who don't ask questions.
♪ It's your thing, now ♪
♪ You do what you wanna do ♪
♪ Ooh, I can't tell you ♪
♪ Who to sock it to ♪
- Kelly, these aren't real actors.
- [music ends]
- Well, this is the best you're gonna get.
- [grunts]
Neil's 5'11". Anybody 5'11"?
Okay. The rest of
you are dismissed.
- Take your pick.
- Mmm. Hold on. You.
You're gonna be my
personal assistant.
I'll just call you Joseph
so you can't take
things personally.
Go stand somewhere.
All right. Can we take these
sunglasses off, please,
so I can see your eyes
and believe your truth?
Now, I want each of
you to do a monologue.
Preferably something
classical, and by God,
don't make me watch
seven Hamlets.
You're not gonna see their
faces. They're wearing helmets.
Wh... [scoffs]
All right, how do I convey the gripping
fear of being on the moon for the first time
if we can't show a human face?
Acting is a sport, Kelly.
- It is energy, body, bu...
- [person] Where do I set up?
- Edvard?
- Ah.
- How did you get in here?
- I just walked through the door.
What part of "talking about this is gonna
get us killed" do you not understand?
- And he's the slowest DP in New York.
- I pick the cinematographer.
- It's in my contract.
- What? You don't have a contract.
He's the best, and
all DPs are slow.
What we need to have a serious
conversation about, Kelly,
is production design, hmm?
What materials are we using
to recreate the lunar surface?
It's just a big rock, right?
I can't work like this, Kelly.
You know this about me. Hmm?
I need details.
We need details. Specifics.
Is it dusty, rocky, windy?
What is the light source? Hmm?
- It's the sun. Big light.
- Do not smart-mouth me, Edvard.
And what is the sun's position
in relation to the landing area?
And are we building a
replica? Do we have a plan?
Do we have suits, and how do
people move in those suits?
And what, Kelly, does
space even look like?
You know, I gotta...
[sighs] I gotta lie down.
Where is my trailer? [sighs]
We need to find a way to copy
everything in that simulation room.
- Okay.
- ASAP.
Wait a second. Do I
even have a trailer?
Your silence tells me
what I already know.
You haven't thought about
how to recreate the moon,
why would you think
about a trailer?
I think we should've
gotten Kubrick.
[Henry] We've got to
get this new ship right.
I mean, Armstrong,
he was pissed off
- and we can't have that again.
- Sorry.
Buddy, buddy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is sensitive material.
- Henry. Henry.
- Uh-uh. You can't be here.
These photos are for the archival
book that Penguin is doing.
- What book?
- Yeah, didn't you get the memo?
- No.
- What? You're writing the foreword.
- I... I'm writing the foreword?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Me?
- Yes, of course.
I've never written a foreword.
The editor wants
to hear from you.
- We all do.
- He wants me to write it?
Don't be so humble, all right?
Let's get a photo of you with the...
- with the LEM.
- I mean, I can do it, but...
Say, "we're going
to the moon."
- We're going to the moon.
- There you go!
Aldrin and Armstrong will practice
every single movement that they make,
um, right here for months.
- That is incredible.
- Yeah.
So, this is, like, the
surface of the moon?
- Well, yeah. It's...
- Yeah.
It's our best approximation.
This just looks like a dirty
beach. I don't believe it. No.
- It is... It's based off sediment we got.
- Joseph.
It's from NASA...
Wait. I do not believe
this is what NASA uses
to go to the moon. You
cannot tell me... No.
Want you to walk as if you're carrying
your mother across the desert.
She's frail but also heavy.
Oh. Whoa. Hey.
- So sorry. Hey. Sorry.
- Oh, no, no. No.
-This is classified. You're not allow...
-Stu, we're good.
-Very classified.
-We're good here. This is for the book.
No, you'll hear about it.
I'm doing the foreword,
- so you'll hear about it soon.
- Okay.
My Armstrong is a
whiny, little bitch.
We have to recast.
No... We're not recasting.
All right. Well,
mediocre it is.
Edvard! Where is my sun?
- [yells]
- Nice!
- Very nice.
- A countdown at least.
Okay. Try it again.
- Gonna try it again.
- Do a three, two, one!
- Come on! Ah!
- Happy?
J... Joseph, bring me my Tab.
You're gonna have to find me
'cause I can't see a thing.
Come on. How long does it
take to give someone a Tab?
My hand's right here.
Uh, this will be great. You
guys should all come around
- and we'll do a shot for the book.
- Great?
Hey, how about this? Everybody,
"We're going to the moon!"
We're going to the moon!
[Henry] My eyes might have been
closed. You wanna do one more?
[sighs] I haven't seen
you around lately.
Well, I can say the
same thing about you.
[chuckles]
[sighs] How do you do
it on the first try?
[chuckles] It's not rocket
science. Okay. You good?
- About the questions, I...
- Yes.
I went over them.
Nothing about Apollo 1.
They promised me. Okay?
You're gonna be great. Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Go on.
- Okay.
- Go.
Mr. Davis. You are what
we call "a tough get."
Ha! No. Thank you.
Is there any legal importance
to what we'll be watching
when Neil Armstrong and Buzz
Aldrin walk on the lunar surface?
Will the area they land on be considered
property of the United States?
[Cole] We're sending
a plaque that says,
"We came in peace
for all mankind."
And that is precisely
what we mean.
What else will
NASA leave behind?
Footprints, an American
flag and 12 bags of feces
that I was told many times
- that I should not bring up, but...
- [chuckles]
Should've put him in
front of a camera sooner.
You wear an Apollo pin.
I do. Um,
the wives of Apollo 1's men,
after we lost them,
they gave me this.
You were launch director
on that tragic day.
What went wrong with Apollo 1?
- In your own words, what happened?
- [scoffs]
Take me back.
Okay. Here's some
facts for you.
The New York Times reported
there were 20,000 safety
reports filed about that ship.
So many, that Gus Grissom
hung a lemon outside it.
[mission controller] All right,
crew. To be confirmed. Location.
- [Grissom] Flame!
- [Chaffee] We've got a fire in the cockpit.
Let's get out!
Mr. Davis? Did you
read those reports?
[mission controller] Pad leader,
get in there and help 'em.
[mission controller]
Pad leader, stay on C3.
[interviewer] Mr. Davis?
Did you read those reports?
- Did you read those reports?
- Of course I read the reports.
I read every single one of them.
Overpressured oxygen and a bad
wire on a "plugs-out" test.
I was supposed to
catch everything,
and I missed it.
And I failed them.
And I will live with that every
single day for the rest of my life.
Is that the quote that you were
looking for, you piece of shit?
Get me on the phone with
your boss. Now. Now!
Oh, uh, wait. W-What are you
doing? We have another 20 minutes.
Go to hell.
Don't be angry with me.
I'm not the reason three
astronauts are dead.
- Say one more thing about those astronauts.
- Hey, hey, hey! Whoa!
Get off me. Let me hear
you say one more thing...
Let me hear you say one
more thing about them!
You don't know those men! You
don't talk about those men!
Get off me! Get off!
Get off!
Do you understand me?
So, I spoke to the producers, and
they've agreed to seal the film
if we give them the exclusive
with Armstrong after he lands.
[sighs]
We lost Hedges though.
He's voting no.
- You said they wouldn't ask about it.
- Yeah. Well... they lied.
You know, people do
that sometimes, Cole.
You could have done yourself
and this program a favor
and maybe tried it
yourself. Right?
- Blame NASA.
- [scoffs]
Blame the system.
I mean, there was half a billion
dollars worth of funding on the line.
Lying must be so easy for you
when you do it all the time.
It's just always an option. What
you should try is the truth.
What is this
sanctimonious bullshit?
I'm never going to lie
about those men or that day.
Do you understand that?
You think what
you want about me,
but I didn't cost the world a dream
because I lost my goddamn cool.
[tour group
chuckling, chattering]
This is Launch Complex 34, where
the Apollo 1 tragedy occurred.
This is a tribute to
our fallen heroes,
the brave men who paved
the road to our success.
Please, let's take a
moment of silence for them.
[Kelly] Edvard, that
looks incredible.
I can't see the wires at
all. How did you do that?
I just put a flag.
It's very simple.
- Old school.
- Huh.
No. Again. From the top.
And maybe let's get some
more bounce this time.
You are on the moon.
Good.
[grunts]
-[Ruby] Oh, my God.
-I-I can't. I can't with this day.
Oh, dear. Uh... Okay, hold on.
[Lance] Joseph,
there's a fire.
I got it.
Don't forget to PASS.
Okay. Can you bring them
down? Actually, leave them up.
Let them think
about what they did.
I give up. I'm taking lunch.
["Moon River" playing]
You see what you did? You
made her take lunch early.
That's on you.
♪ Dream maker ♪
♪ You heartbreaker ♪
♪ Wherever you're going
I'm going your way ♪
I'll bet you $5 you're
bad at apologies.
I've been looking
all over for you.
- You owe me five bucks.
- I got an idea.
- What?
- Come on.
I'll tell you on the
way to Louisiana.
No. You wanna take
a shot at Vanning?
I got us a dinner invite,
for tonight. Come on.
Tonight? We're never gonna
make it. It's 500 miles away.
We're gonna make it. Come
on. You gotta trust me.
Oh, wait. No.
- No, no, no.
- What do you mean, "no"?
We don't... There's
other... We could...
Do you want Vanning or not?
- Ugh. No. I don't...
- Come on. Let's go.
I think we could just take a
commercial flight. If we left...
Nope. No commercial flights
are flying right now.
Come on. Just hop on in.
This is it. This is all you gotta
do. You can hop up, you can get in.
- Put your foot there.
- [Kelly] Okay, well, take these.
- Look, we gotta go.
- [Kelly] All right.
Hold on. Hold on. [mumbles]
[yelps, chuckles]
- [yelps]
- Perfect.
- Hold on. [yelps]
- We're good.
♪ Two drifters ♪
♪ Off to see the world ♪
♪ And such a lot of
world There is to see ♪
You enjoying the view?
Wow! It's stunning!
I bet your eyes are closed.
No.
♪ Moon river and me ♪
[music ends]
So, I'm betting you have
some other Southern accents
in that bag of tricks of
yours. Can you do Louisiana?
Yeah. New Orleans
or Baton Rouge?
- Wherever his wife's from.
- Okay.
[doorbell chimes]
Cole Davis.
And you must be
Miss Kelly Jones.
- Please come in, y'all.
- Oh. [chuckles]
Thank you so much for
having us for dinner.
Oh, now... now, I was told
you were a New York City type.
Oh, God, no. I just work
there. I'm from Louisiana.
Born and raised and,
one day, buried.
- I'm from Virginia.
- No? We're family.
You know, Tex Ritter always said
Virginia was the mother of Texas.
Well, we never knew
who the father was.
We always suspected
it was Louisiana.
-Oh! [laughs] -Huh? My
mother loves that one.
- She was the one that came up with it.
- Oh, just so colorful.
- [chuckles] You're fun.
- This is a beautiful home.
So, h-how is the
campaign going, Senator?
Truth be told, politics
is more of a hobby to me.
Serving Christ, that's
my full-time job.
You know, there's a war on
religion in this country.
And some say
science is to blame.
Well, science is what
brought us to this table.
You learned a little lesson
on the provocation of pride
on Apollo 1, now,
didn't you, Cole?
[sniffles] Science has actually
brought me closer to God, sir.
Took the Lord six days to put forth
everything that we know as creation.
And on that sixth day, he
gave us dominion over it.
And, personally, I take
that as a responsibility.
You sound like a man who
knows his way to church.
Well, I can't think of
a greater act of faith
than pursuing the stars.
"The heavens declare
the glory of God.
And the firmament shows
us his handiwork."
- That's one of Jolene's favorite Psalms.
- [chuckles]
You see, our men, when
they come back from space,
they believe more
in God, not less.
But when we land on the moon,
and thanks to Miss Jones here,
the world watches us do it.
And it's my hope that people everywhere
feel the presence of that divine.
Well... [sighs]
you've, uh, certainly given
me a lot to think about, son.
You really sold the
hell out of that.
I wasn't selling.
For the record, you can win people
over just by being who you are.
You know, we're not in a rush, so
we don't really have to fly home.
Ooh. That wasn't flying.
Come on. Open your eyes.
You trust me?
Hold tight.
[exclaims]
Now, this is the fun
part. Just slide off.
- [chuckles]
- Perfect.
[NASA employees chattering]
[Senator Vanning] I've
had my disagreements
with the NASA
program in the past.
But after a great deal
of thought, and prayer,
I've decided to vote yes.
- [Cole grunting] - [NASA
employees cheering, laughing]
- [laughs]
- Come on. [grunts]
[Kelly, Ruby speaking
indistinctly]
I have something
that you need to see.
- What...
- Follow me.
[Henry] Whoo! I didn't know
which way it was gonna go,
'cause you can't
tell with these guys.
I never liked that guy
before, but... [stammers]
- I like him now. [laughs]
- [laughs]
All right!
[Kelly] It's so
dark in here. You...
-[Cole] Almost there.
-[Kelly chuckles] I'm a little scared.
[Cole] Yeah, it's
right around here.
["Why Don't You Do
Your Thing" playing]
We wanted to show
you our appreciation.
-Oh, my gosh. This is too much.
-Thank you.
- I can't believe it.
- It was all Walter.
Oh, Walter? I know that you
did all of this, didn't you?
-[Walter] A little. That's all.
-Yeah, I know you did.
- They all helped.
- Not too bad, huh?
["Why Don't You Do
Your Thing" continues]
[chuckles]
Before I forget. Here.
It's a list of things for you to
say when you take your first step.
I... I know everybody's asking you.
I thought I'd give you some options.
Well, I was just gonna say,
"Look at all those cool
rocks," or something.
- I got this one, Kelly.
- Okay.
And thank you, though.
And I mean it. For,
uh... For everything.
You know, I don't think anyone cares
about this program more than Cole Davis.
It's nice to see he's found
something else to care about.
["To Love Somebody" playing]
♪ There's a light ♪
♪ A certain kind of light ♪
I know I'm no, uh, astronaut,
but can I steal you for a dance?
- Yes. Yes.
- Yeah? Come on.
♪ I want my life To
be lived with you ♪
♪ Lived with you ♪
So, you just counting down the days
until you, uh, can get back to Manhattan?
Not really.
Good.
♪ I live and I
breathe For you ♪
♪ But what good does it do ♪
♪ If I ain't got you ♪
♪ Ain't got you, baby ♪
♪ You don't know
What it's like ♪
♪ Baby, you don't know
What it's like... ♪
Up, up, up. Perfect. Right,
now, move the light in.
All right, keep
going. Don't be shy.
Keep going. Keep going. Keep
going. Keep going. Keep going.
[Lance] Milk it. Good. Mm-hmm.
Ladies, what do we think?
- Lance, it's incredible.
- It's great.
I think it needs a little
more dust and better actors,
but I lost that battle.
I will let it go.
And stop. Okay.
We've got our sun.
I always went along
with every web you spun
because it was fun or, like, we were
pulling one over on the bad guys,
but this feels...
I know.
We're almost done.
This is from me.
It is for launch day.
Promise you will
wait until then.
- I promise.
- [chuckling] Okay.
[Lance] Remember,
you're not monsters.
[Ruby] Are they
gonna be that high?
[Lance] Uh, I just need
to give them any length
that looks like they're on the
moon. But thank you for the note.
Buzz, take it down some.
And, Armstrong, stop
looking at me for approval.
Just be on the
moon. I'm not here.
[Ruby] He's having
fun. He's having fun.
[Lance] He keeps locking eyes with
me. Stop flirting and be on the moon.
[anchorperson] Yesterday's
science fiction is today's fact.
The methods are different,
but the important thing
is that tomorrow morning,
man will lift off
toward the moon.
Good evening. I'm
Walter Cronkite.
And on this eve of man's first
flight toward a landing on the moon,
all preparations go smoothly.
The weather prediction,
along with the help of
astronauts, Neil Arm...
Yes?
Well, you know how
to hurt a fella.
No courtesy call?
Well, I don't have your number.
You ran.
That's what you do best.
Your alternate version is wrong. I
never should've been a part of it.
I quit.
Sit.
[Kelly sighs]
So, who are we gonna be today?
Let's see.
[British accent]
Ooh, Helen Parker.
[normal voice] I bet you
do a killer British accent.
You wanna take off and
be Helen? Go ahead.
Helen doesn't have to
look over her shoulder.
No one is coming for you.
Unless?
Unless you ever tell anyone
that Project Artemis was real,
and the moon landing was fake.
Oh, on that score,
change of plans.
Um,
we're going to air
the alternate version.
No matter what.
Oh, you were never gonna
broadcast the real thing.
This isn't just a
race for the moon.
It is a race for which
ideology gets to run things.
I got one of my men to rig the LEM
camera so that it just beams back audio.
We're gonna sync with their sound and,
uh, use your fake stage broadcast,
start to finish.
Let me be the first to thank
you on behalf of America.
Come on, don't feel bad.
Everybody gets what they want.
You get a new life with
no past to run from.
And the world doesn't have to
sleep under a communist moon.
Mmm.
- Okay. Panama beckons.
- [sighs]
You better hurry.
You're going to...
[British accent] miss
your flight, Helen.
[narrator on TV] This is a
typical meal served to astronauts
aboard Apollo space flights.
Oatmeal, toast,
and a special zero-gravity pouch.
Tang, the energy breakfast drink.
And more vitamin C
than orange juice.
Energy Tang, for spacemen
and Earth families.
[Walter Cronkite] CBS News
presents Man On the Moon.
The epic journey of Apollo 11
on the eve of that
historic event.
Sponsored by Western Electric,
manufacturing and supply
unit of the Bell System.
And by the International Paper
Company, where good ideas roll on...
[Walter Cronkite
continues indistinctly]
[sighs]
[people speaking indistinctly]
What are you doing here?
I need to show you something.
It was supposed to be
a contingency plan.
That's how he sold it. It
was an insurance policy.
In case we failed.
It's good to know...
[chuckles] ...that you
never believed in us.
I know you're upset.
- I understand...
- Oh, what do you understand?
Please tell me what
you understand.
'Cause you don't understand
shit about truth.
If you fake this mission...
If you fake this mission,
every single thing that we have
sacrificed will have been for nothing.
I know I messed
up. I know that.
But you know you couldn't have
made it to this day without me.
I could've walked away
last night, but I didn't.
I came back to fix this.
Fix what?
Moe cut the LEM camera, and
if we don't fix this together,
then this is gonna be the
version that the world sees.
It's not a contingency.
God, you're so good at
leaving me no options.
Fine, let's fix it. [sighs]
But when this is over, I never
wanna see your face again.
This is what happens when
you work for Richard Nixon.
I got your book, Ruby.
You opened it early.
It came at just the right time.
[sighs]
[public affairs officer on PA]
proper atmosphere for launch
which is a combination
of oxygen and nitrogen.
Sixty percent oxygen and
40% nitrogen atmosphere.
Of course, the astronauts
themselves are breathing pure oxygen
through their space suits.
Coming up shortly will
be another key test
in which both the, uh,
launch crew for the...
the launch vehicle crew
and the spacecraft team,
uh, combine together with the
commander, Neil Armstrong,
to make a thorough check of
the Emergency Detection System.
- This is the system...
-[reporter] We're live from the Cape,
where it's a beautiful
day to make history.
We'll be handling the launch
portion of the broadcast from here,
and our counterparts in Houston
will be covering Apollo
11's historic flight,
guided by Mission Control.
[Stu] Guys!
[panting] It's busted.
The camera's video preamplifier.
- It's destroyed.
- Okay, can you fix that?
I could maybe repurpose
a part from a TV, but...
Well, that's fine. There's
plenty of TVs around here.
NASA's TVs... They
are all too old.
I mean a brand-new
solid-state color TV.
Well, how fast can you get one?
How fast can you get me
to an electronics store?
- Me?
- In the worst traffic in Florida history.
I can't. I have
to prep the guys.
Give me the keys.
[Cole] Fine, I'll stall.
Hurry. Go, go, go,
go, go, go, go.
["Hold On I'm Coming" playing]
[reporter] Hotels
are at capacity.
Kennedy Space Center
is so crowded,
we're hearing it's nearly
impossible to get in or out.
[tires squeal]
[gasps] Kelly, slow down.
Are you guys good back there?
- Yes.
- No.
Whoo-hoo!
Please, please
stop. Please stop.
[Don] There it is.
There's the store.
[tires screech]
♪ Hold on, I'm coming ♪
♪ I'm on my way
To you, lover ♪
♪ If you get cold
I'll be your cover ♪
- No!
- They're closed.
- Oh, what?
No, no. No, they are not.
- [Ruby] Kelly.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa!
What are you waiting for? Go!
- Oh. Yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
[Don] Okay.
-[Stu] Okay. Yes, this one. This is great.
-[Don] Yeah, okay.
-I would help. I'm just not tall enough.
-Come on, Don. All right.
-[Stu] All right. Slowly, all right.
-[Ruby] Guys, come on.
Oh, my God. I
can't go to jail.
Let me handle this.
["Hold On I'm Coming" continues]
♪ Hold on, I'm coming ♪
She's good.
Yeah.
[applause]
[cheering]
Have a good ride, boys.
[public affairs officer] In a
matter of, uh, five minutes or so,
we'll be ready for the spacecraft
commander, Neil Armstrong,
to come across the sill
at the 320-foot level.
- The trip in the transfer van...
- Come on!
Could take some 15 minutes
or so to reach the pad.
At which time the astronauts will
board, uh, the first of two elevators
for the trip to the 320-foot
level at the launchpad,
uh, where they will then proceed
to ingress the spacecraft.
Whoa. We are locked
and loaded, kid.
No, no. Flight Deck
wants this on the ship.
[phone rings]
-This is Flight Deck. Let him through.
- Got it.
Go.
Okay, we need to initiate
prelaunch, or we lose the window.
Just give him one minute.
[public affairs
officer] 320-foot level,
all three astronauts now
aboard the spacecraft.
A few minutes ago,
Astronaut Buzz Aldrin,
uh, came in and took
the center seat...
I'm hearing the cabin's now being
sealed. Countdown has begun.
[public affairs officer] These are the
positions they will fly at liftoff.
[test conductor on radio]
CDR, STC, how do you read?
[Neil Armstrong on radio]
STC, loud and clear.
-[test conductor] Good morning, Neil.
-[Henry] Gantry is cleared.
[test conductor]
Welcome aboard.
Apollo 11 is a go for launch
in T-minus ten minutes.
[sighs] Okay.
He's here.
It's connected.
[panting] At least I
think I connected it.
- Stu, what the hell does that mean?
- [Stu panting]
I only had a few seconds. I didn't
have time to stress test it. I...
Okay. Sit down.
[sighs]
All right, listen up!
Whatever happens here today,
I will stand by every
decision that you make.
Over 400,000 people have
worked on this program
for nearly ten years.
All to keep one man's
promise to the world.
So, let's keep it.
All right. Give me
"Go/No go" for launch.
[mission controller on radio] Ah, roger.
All stations, stand by for final "Go/No go."
- MACE.
- [technician 1] Go.
- ECS.
- [technician 2] Go.
- EPS.
- [technician 3] Go.
- Sequencer.
- [technician 4] Go.
- GNS.
- Go.
- [mission controller] SCS.
- This is the best part.
They go down the line
and every single...
every single technician has to
say, "Go," or, "No go," for launch.
Any one of them can stop it.
[mission controller] CFAT. CSE,
can you give me a "go" now?
CSE is go.
Okay. Uh, Eagle is go.
CBTS, this is CSA 9.
[Cole on speakers] Twenty
seconds and counting.
T-minus 15 seconds.
Guidance is internal.
[Cole] ...Twelve,
eleven, ten, nine...
Ignition sequence starts.
Five, four, three, two, one.
All engines running.
Liftoff. We have liftoff.
Tower clear.
Houston, she's all yours.
[cheering]
[speaking indistinctly]
Moe Berkus is here.
For both of you.
[Walter Cronkite]
Apollo 11 is on the way.
250,000 miles away,
where the moon is waiting
for man's first arrival.
Flight to take, uh, three days.
And, uh, the, uh,
spacecraft to reach there...
[Cole] Kelly told
me everything.
[Walter Cronkite] The landing
to take place on Sunday.
And Neil Armstrong to set...
Bravissimo.
- Shove it.
- That was history.
Hi, Helen. Uh, sorry, Kelly.
I heard you came back,
so I came back too.
I... I took a little
peeky-poo at the moon set,
and it is perfection.
Great job.
If you think that I'm
gonna let you broadcast
some fake version of this,
I'll go to the press right now.
[chuckles] Cole.
Cole. Cole.
You, uh... You go to the press.
Bring 'em by the moon set,
but just know that no one will ever
trust the legitimacy of NASA again.
This is a matter of
national security.
This broadcast must take
place in a controlled setting.
You of all people
must understand that.
The mission isn't about
landing on the moon anymore.
It is about the world watching
America beat Russia on TV.
I got a flight to catch.
I'll be back in time
for the lunar broadcast.
I thought I'd watch it here.
With you, Kelly. On the moon.
Hey. We're making history.
[sighs]
Everything you said
about me is true.
I'm a con artist, and
I always have been.
My real name is not even Kelly.
All those stories
that I told you
about my mom and I selling
products door-to-door,
those were true.
They were all scams.
And we started out small,
and then they got bigger.
Like real estate and insurance.
And...
when I was 16, a guy in
North Dakota pulled a gun
and my mom pulled hers out
first and she killed him.
And she told me
to run and I did.
And she went to prison
and I never saw her again.
And I forged documents and
used fake names to get jobs.
And when I went to New
York, I found advertising.
And that was like the scams that
my mom taught me, but it was legal.
And I lied to so many people.
The worst lies were
the ones I told myself.
That everybody does it. You
know. It's just a big game.
But then I came down here...
I met you.
I learned what it was like to
be a part of something real.
Moe offered me a way
to erase my past.
I thought that's
what I wanted, but...
I don't wanna run anymore.
Moe is a worthy opponent,
but he has met his match.
I promise this is the last
time I will trick anyone
into getting what I want.
I promise.
Do you think you can
do it without lying?
- Absolutely not.
- Yeah, I didn't think so.
So, what's the plan?
[Don] Why are we
meeting out here?
Because Moe bugs everything.
The guy's like Houdini.
He's everywhere.
Okay, so, Moe doesn't know
that we fixed the LEM camera.
We build a plan around that.
All we have to do
is convince him
that we are broadcasting
the fake moon landing,
when in reality, we're
broadcasting the real one.
Is there a way that we
could rig the equipment
so that it actually sends
out the real LEM video feed?
[Cole] Come on, boys.
You figured out how
to land on the moon.
Give me a hypothetical.
Okay, um, hypothetically,
we could rewire it.
So that it only picks up the
broadcast signal from Mission Control.
- Sure, then sync it with our feed.
- [Stu] Hmm. Right.
Hey, fellas.
Moe Berkus sent these guys
to test the broadcast feed.
-Moe... Moe Berk... Yes.
-[coughing] Moe Berk... Moe Berkus.
[Ruby] Telling me none of
you got the phone call?
[smacks lips] Great. All
right, where's the camera?
[Don coughing]
- Are you okay?
- Mmm.
[Ruby] Can you guys
hurry up, please?
[Don coughs]
Don, maybe just take
the cigarette out.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I've just
never smoked a cigarette before.
I don't like it.
[capsule communicator]
uh, 11, this is Houston.
Uh, you are go for LOI. Over.
[Buzz Aldrin] Confirmed.
On track for the moon.
[capsule communicator]
Apollo 11, this is Houston.
All your systems are looking
good. Going around the corner.
We'll see you on the
other side. Over.
[public affairs officer]
And we've had loss of signal
as Apollo 11 goes
behind the moon.
It's now 3:30 Eastern
Daylight Time.
At 3:46 we should be getting the
first signal from the Lunar Module.
The estimated audience:
hundreds of millions.
Perhaps 400 million
persons or so are watching
this broadcast today of,
uh, the greatest event...
Boys.
All right. Let's go.
A little bit more.
Well done, guys.
[Lance] Boys, when you hear
my voice, you hear God.
Now, this is a fake moon,
- but to the world, it's real.
- It's showtime, folks.
It needs to... Remember
where I left off.
Your government thanks you for
the work you're about to do.
Now, don't fuck it up.
What is this nasty
shit doing here?
- God.
- Excuse me.
This is a Tab set,
and that is my chair.
- Kelly, let's deal with this.
- Lance, thank you so much.
So, these screens...
This is our feed.
Yeah.
Okay. And then...
And the TV's a live
broadcast. Okay.
[Moe] Right.
Joseph, I'm sitting.
-[Moe] Oh, my God. Are you real?
-[sighs]
[Lance] I am the director,
Lance Vespertine.
[Moe] Stay out of
my way, will you?
[Lance] All right, I'd say it was nice
to meet you, but so far, it is not.
The pigeon's in the coop.
Copy that.
[Michael Collins] Okay, you
should have him now, Houston.
[capsule communicator] Eagle, we've
got you now. It's looking good. Over.
We've got the Earth right
out of our front window.
Flight, we are go for landing.
[flight director] Roger. Understand.
Go for landing. 3,000 feet.
[capsule communicator] Eagle,
looking great. You're go.
[Neil Armstrong] Position checks
downrange show us to be a little long.
[public affairs officer] 1,400
feet. Still looking very good.
-[Neil Armstrong] P30.
-[capsule communicator] Six plus two-five.
[Buzz Aldrin] Looks
like about 820.
[capsule communicator]
Throttle down.
[Neil Armstrong]
Flight, this is Eagle.
Sea of Tranquility is
rockier than expected.
We're gonna have to extend
another thousand feet.
Hey, boys.
- Where does that put us?
- It'll give 'em
- 15 seconds of fuel left.
- They're gonna wanna abort.
[sighs] Neil can do this,
they just gotta let him.
[flight director]
Stand by, Eagle.
We are calculating what that
will do to our fuel reserves.
ECOM puts that within 15
seconds. Prepare for abort.
Flight... [sighs]
we have run successful
tests within that range.
Let 'em land.
[capsule communicator]
Thirty. Thirty seconds.
- That's a lie.
- You lied.
I've learned some
new tricks. Sit down.
[capsule communicator] Okay, the only
callouts from now on will be fuel.
Come on.
Eagle, looking
great. You're go.
[public affairs officer] 1,400
feet. Still looking very good.
[Buzz Aldrin] 350
feet, down at four.
[capsule communicator]
Thirty. Thirty seconds.
[Buzz Aldrin] Down two
and a half. Forward.
- Forward. Good.
-[capsule communicator] Roger that.
[Buzz Aldrin] Eleven
forward. Coming down nicely.
200 feet, four and a half down.
Five and a half down. Five
and a half down, nine forward.
That's good.
Contact light.
Engine stop.
Flight.
Tranquility Base here.
The Eagle has landed.
[capsule communicator] Roger,
Tranquility, we copy on the ground.
You got a bunch of guys
about to turn blue.
We're breathing
again. Thanks a lot.
Whew. Boy. [chuckles]
[Neil Armstrong] We're going
to be busy for a minute.
All right, all right,
all right. Come on.
Let's focus. We're
only halfway there.
Yeah, we've got it from
here. Thank you, guys.
Places. Places,
everyone. Look sharp.
[Lance] Let's look sharp!
Edvard, Edvard, off the
stage. You're killing me.
Edvard, we are done. Uh-uh.
You're done. No more tweaking.
- What are you, the repeater?
- No, I'm not the repeater.
This is the system we
created before you got here.
[Neil Armstrong]
Camera is coming down.
Three, two, one, and action.
[capsule communicator] And we're
getting a picture on the TV.
[Buzz Aldrin] You got
a good picture, huh?
[capsule communicator] Uh, there's
a great deal of contrast in it.
[Buzz Aldrin] Roger, TV
circuit breaker's in,
and read you loud and clear.
[capsule communicator] Roger.
[Buzz Aldrin] Okay. Will
you verify the position, uh,
the, uh, opening I ought
to have on the camera?
[capsule communicator]
Stand by.
Armstrong, prepare to disembark.
Your visor.
[Neil Armstrong] I am
opening the door for egress.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[capsule communicator] Okay, Neil, we
can see you coming down the ladder now.
Okay, left.
And right.
Left and right.
Now, left foot
off. Left foot off.
Easy. Easy. Step down.
And land.
How do you know what, uh,
he's gonna do ahead of time?
NASA rehearsed all of this,
and Kelly appropriated it.
Oh, stole it.
I knew I hired the right people.
[Lance] Okay, here we go.
It's seamless.
It's incredible.
[Neil Armstrong] I'm at
the foot of the ladder.
The LEM footpads are only
depressed in the surface
about one or two inches,
although the surface
appears to be very,
very fine-grained as
you get close to it.
It's almost like a powder.
Down there, it's very fine.
I'm gonna step off the LEM now.
That's one small step for man...
one giant leap for mankind.
We could have spent years coming
up with something that good.
- Yeah.
- [chuckles]
- Was that, uh, in the script?
No.
That's a good line.
[Buzz Aldrin] It's
a very simple matter
to hop down from one
step to the next.
Neil is now
unveiling the plaque.
[Neil Armstrong] "Here
man, from the planet Earth,
first set foot upon
the moon, July 1969 AD.
We came in peace
for all mankind."
You ready for the camera?
[capsule communicator] Uh, Neil, this
is Houston. The field of view is okay.
We'd like you to aim it a little
bit more to the right. Over.
[Neil Armstrong] Okay.
[capsule communicator]
Too much to the right.
Can you bring it back left
about, uh, four or five degrees?
Okay. That looks good, Neil.
Columbia, Columbia, this
is Houston, AOS. Over.
[Jack King] Neil Armstrong has
been on the lunar surface now
almost 45 minutes.
[capsule communicator] Uh,
Tranquility Base, this is Houston.
Could we get both of you on the
camera for a minute, please?
The President of
the United States
would like to say a
few words to you. Over.
[Neil Armstrong] That
would be an honor.
[capsule communicator] All
right, go ahead, Mr. President.
This is Houston. Out.
Hello, Neil and Buzz.
I am talking to you by telephone
from the Oval Room
at the White House...
They have Secret Service
all over this place.
And this certainly has to be the most
historic telephone call ever made.
And as you talk to us...
He actually reminds
me a lot of you.
Do not say that. No, don't
even joke about that.
We're still holding while the
president drones on. Don't move.
Armstrong, I'm
watching you the most.
[Richard Nixon] For one priceless
moment in the whole history of man...
[Neil Armstrong]
Kennedy, let's go direct.
Cole, are you receiving picture?
The video feed light
isn't on up here.
Uh, what do you mean,
Neil? It's not working?
[Neil Armstrong] You tell
me. Do you see picture?
We're getting a power surge
warning on the camera.
I think it crapped out.
Can you still see us?
Yeah, I can still see you.
Um, one second, Neil.
Neil's saying the video feed
light isn't on up there.
Are you sure that
camera's working?
I installed the new part.
It should be working
just fine but...
- But what?
- But I... I was in a rush.
Shit.
[phone rings]
What's wrong?
We're not sure
that the camera on
the LEM is working.
I think that's your
feed broadcasting.
[Cole] Does the feed on
your TV look like your set?
I... I can't tell if it's us.
Test it. Have one of your agents
give a little wave or something.
[scoffs] I can't.
Everyone is here.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[meows]
- [grunting]
- [gasps]
[gasps] Oh.
- What the hell is that?
- I don't know.
He is two inches away
from being on that screen.
It's... It's one inch.
Is that in your goddamn script?
Joseph, were there new pages?
[Neil Armstrong] representing
not only the United States
but men of peace
of all nations...
[gasps] Oh, Mischief! Oh, God. Kitty,
kitty! Pss, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Mischief! Mischief!
Where are you going?
- [Kelly] Mischief. Mischief.
- K... Kelly.
- [Kelly] Come here.
- The cat?
Come here. Come
here. Come here.
[meows]
- Do you know this cat?
- [shushes]
[shrieks]
[Kelly] Kitty, kitty, kitty!
Come here, you sweet...
Come here, you little bitch.
[Kelly] Kitty, kitty, kitty.
- Come here, you!
- [Kelly] No!
Kelly, what the hell
is going on over there?
Kelly? Kelly?
- [Lance yells indistinctly]
- [Kelly] Go round the back!
[Ruby] Mischief! Mischief!
Kitty, kitty, kitty!
Catch him! Catch
him! Oh! Go, go.
Let's go! Come on.
[Lance] Come here. It's okay.
Mischief. Just come here.
Just shut up. Just shut up!
[shushes] Come here,
kitty, kitty, kitty.
Come here, little
baby. You know me.
No!
[Richard Nixon] And
thank you very much
and I look forward,
all of us look forward,
to seeing you on the
Hornet on Thursday.
[Neil Armstrong] I look
forward to that very much, sir.
Those are your guys, Cole.
Yes! Those are our guys!
[sighs]
Yes. I know you know that.
Just reminding everybody
what we're doing here today.
Those are our guys.
Carry on.
[Mischief meows]
What am I looking at here?
Oh, that's the moon.
[capsule communicator]
Neil, this is Houston.
Did you get the
Hasselblad magazine...
That's really the moon?
[Neil Armstrong] Yes, I
did. And we got about, uh...
- Jesus, it looks fake.
- I'd say 20 pounds of, uh...
[Neil Armstrong] carefully
selected, if not documented samples.
-[laughs] -[capsule
communicator] Houston.
Roger. Well done. Out.
[flight director] Unofficial time
off the surface at 111:37:32.
["Fly Me To The Moon (In
Other Words)" playing]
I never thought I would
see the moon up close.
Me neither, Walter.
-[Kelly] I didn't get it. Oh, my God.
-[Lance] Sorry.
-[Kelly] Not like last time.
-[Lance] No. Don't point it at us.
In Polish, we call
it "na zdrowie."
-[Kelly] All right. Na zdrowie.
-Okay, okay, okay. Kelly.
- Kelly. Kelly.
- It's getting a little better.
-Yes? What?
-Christ, just say it. Just say it once.
You are the best
director I know.
I am. [inhales sharply] Now, I know
we're not supposed to talk about this,
but, Kelly, this would be so great
on my résumé if I... Just feels...
Anyone mentions this to anyone,
you will spend the rest of your
life in a dark, dank prison cell
on a nameless island.
- [smacks lips] Oh.
- Now, to wash down the bubbly,
on behalf of the US government,
have a little, uh, scotch.
- [Edvard] Hmm.
- Edvard.
I'll take one of those.
I had a billion-dollar TV show
for an audience of one.
- Hope you enjoyed it.
- [laughs]
- [Lance] Cheers.
- It was a perfect failure.
-That's right. Cheers. Cheers.
-[chuckles] Cheers.
- [chuckles]
- Mmm.
[exhales sharply] Can I
talk with you a moment?
Not many people have
gone against my orders
and lived to talk about it.
Then again, not many
people have saved my ass.
It would've been a real doozy to explain
how the cat ended up on the moon.
You're a goddamn American hero.
Great job.
Now, this place is
crawling with press.
So, uh, we can't really clear
anything out until after splashdown.
In the meantime, shred any
documents associated with the shoot.
Your name will be wiped
from the history books.
The story, rewritten.
- Then I'm free to go.
- You are.
Although, I could use someone
like you for an upcoming project.
No, thanks.
Suit yourself. Hard
to get, but okay.
If you ever need me... just
holler. I'm probably listening.
Oh. Moe.
Are there really
aliens out there?
They walk among us.
[Moe] ♪ Fly me to the moon ♪
♪ Let's play among the stars ♪
♪ Let me see what spring Is
like on Jupiter and Mars ♪
[Walter Cronkite] A
quarter of a million miles.
Just think of it as,
uh, Neil Armstrong said,
the first words as man
stepped foot on the moon,
"A small step for man, a
giant leap for mankind."
And a day that can
never come again.
A day that shall forever live
in history, as will those words,
which will be memorized
by schoolboys...
Armstrong, you've got a future.
Not in acting. My God, no.
Well, Kelly, Patty...
Patty, right?
- My name is Ruby.
- [Lance] Uh-huh.
- We did it.
- [Kelly] No, we didn't.
[anchorperson 1] This
is, uh, landward here.
Uh, Swim One has Apollo visual.
[anchorperson 2] Well, if it's
coming down nine miles away,
uh, that's just going to be at the,
uh, outer limit of, uh, visibility...
Come on. Come on,
baby. Come on, baby.
[anchorperson 3] They're
back from the moon.
[anchorperson 3] Astronauts
Armstrong, Aldrin and Collins
landing in the Pacific
Ocean, southwest of Hawaii.
I guess you deserve a
cigarette. [chuckles]
[sniffling, chuckles]
- Aw, buddy. [chuckles]
- Yeah, yeah. I, uh...
[stammers] I didn't wanna
lose it in there. You know?
You know, I know you didn't
want the camera up there,
but, man, seeing that was, uh...
[chuckles] It was
life-changing.
- We did it.
- We did. We did, man.
[both laugh]
Hey, it's 1969, right? We
got it in before the decade.
-[sighs] I know. Not a moment to spare.
-Oh. Yeah, we did.
- [Cole] Look who it is.
- [Henry] Hey.
- Go. Get out of here.
- [Henry] Yeah.
Listen, uh, it's not too
late for you either, kid.
- Thank you, Henry.
- All right.
Hey.
We did it.
Hey, guys, huh?
Sent a man to the moon.
You know...
I never did catch your name.
[sighs]
Winnie.
[chuckles]
Winnie. Nice to
meet you, Winnie.
You know, the Russians,
they... they're saying
that we shot the whole
thing on a soundstage.
I wonder where they got
a crazy idea like that.
Who cares what they think?
Truth is still the truth
even if nobody believes it.
Lie is still a lie even
if everybody believes it.
You know, you
really nailed this.
All the way down
to the lunar dust.
Too bad it's all fake.
Was that fake?
No, that felt very real.
["Nothing Can Change
This Love" playing]
♪ If I go ♪
♪ A million miles away ♪
♪ I'd write a letter ♪
♪ Each and every day ♪
[Mischief meows]
♪ Nothing can ever change ♪
♪ This love I have for you ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Make me weep ♪
♪ And you can make me cry ♪
♪ See me coming ♪
♪ And you can pass me by ♪
♪ But honey Nothing, nothing ♪
♪ Can ever change This
love I have for you ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[announcer] Twelve, eleven, ten,
nine... Ignition sequence, five...
["Destination Moon" playing]