This Saturday night
on a brand-new Pink Opaque.
Drain Lords, hundreds of them,
coming out of the drains!
Isabel's bathroom has a new
supernatural infestation
that no exterminator
can take care of.
It's "The Attack of
the Drain Lords."
10:30p.m./ 9:30 Central,
this Saturday night on
the Young Adult Network.
They can't hurt you
if you don't think about them.
They can't hurt you if you
don't think about them.
Five, four,
three, two,
one!
It was raining last night
and I couldn't sleep,
so I started my
favorite TV show again.
The Pink Opaque.
Thank you, ma'am. Yes.
Enjoy your night. Yeah.
Hey.
Oh, let me take two,
yeah. Thank you.
Owen! Owen, honey.
Come on, honey,
we're ready to go in.
Come on.
I don't know what he's doing...
Ready?
Owen, I know you're
not too old for this.
It's been four years.
It's time to vote for
the saxophone man again.
Mom!
Okay. Come on.
Come on. Come... Owen, come on.
Please.
I don't know. I
don't think so.
Hey.
Are your parents voting too?
No.
Ms. Driscoll lets me use
the dark room after school,
so I'm just waiting for
my pictures to dry out.
That looks like
the best book ever.
Yeah, it is.
That's like the TV show, right?
The Pink Opaque?
Yeah. It's the
official episode guide.
Do you watch?
- No.
- Oh.
What grade are you in?
Ninth.
What about you?
Seventh.
My God, you're a baby.
Election Night is cool, right?
It's like Colonial Day.
Or when they bring the
inflatable planetarium
into the gymnasium.
It's like the school
gets transformed
into something else, you know?
It's special.
It's a kids show, right?
The Pink Opaque?
No. No way. Who told you that?
I mean, yeah, technically it's
on the Young Adult Network.
But it's way too scary,
and the mythology's way too
complicated for most kids.
I see commercials
for it all the time.
It looks amazing.
You can read about the
episodes here, if you want.
It's got quotes and pictures,
and info about the
double bill of bands
that plays each week
at the Double Lunch.
It comes on at
10:30 p.m., right?
Yeah. Every Saturday night.
It's the last show in the block
before they switch to
black and white reruns
for old people.
My friend Amanda and I watch
it together every week.
My dad won't let me
stay up that late.
10 p.m.'s my bedtime.
Damn.
That absolutely sucks.
My mom basically doesn't
give a crap when I go to bed.
Hey.
You know what you should do?
Mom? Hmm?
Can I have a sleepover
at Johnny Link's
house Saturday night?
Johnny Link?
I didn't even know you guys
were still friends anymore.
Well, honey, you'll
have to ask your father.
Can you ask him for me?
Frank, Owen wants to go
have a sleepover
at Johnny Link's.
Well... He's old enough.
He's a good kid.
Honey!
You remembered your
inhaler, right?
Yeah.
All right.
And what about a husband?
If I have to.
What about Evan Dando?
I mean, he's cute
but he's so tortured.
I'd have to, like,
save him every day.
Fine. Then what about Beck?
He's such a spindly
little cutie.
Okay, but we need
more, like, gross guys.
Ugh, what about Joe from Math?
No, he's cute.
What about, like, Michael Stipe?
I like Michael Stipe.
[ON TV] And now, a
brand-new The Pink Opaque.
Hey.
Is it okay if I come sit down?
Shut up. It's starting.
[ON TV] Tara is my
imaginary best friend,
and I'm hers.
We met at sleepaway camp
and discovered we had an
ancient psychic connection.
Now, even though we live
on opposite sides of the county,
we help each other fight
the forces of evil.
We are... The Pink Opaque.
The last Sprinkly
Stick of the summer.
What a bummer.
Definition of.
It's not fair, man.
Why does the winter
have to be so cold
that you can't eat ice
cream during the winter?
You know what I wish?
I wish the Ice Cream
Man didn't have to leave
when the weather got
cold in the winter.
I wish...
he never went away.
You can go out and
join her, if you want.
No, I don't smoke cigarettes.
It's not a cigarette.
It's a Black & Mild.
Are you sure you
don't want a ride home
with Amanda's mom?
I told my parents
it was a sleepover.
So, did you like it?
The show I mean?
Yeah.
It was... It was
really interesting.
Isabel's a scaredy-cat.
She's kind of the
main character,
but she's also kind of a drip.
Tara's my favorite.
She's super hot,
and she doesn't take
shit from anybody.
Plus, she's an
expert on demonology.
And they never meet
up in person, right?
No.
Just in the pilot episode,
back at sleepaway camp.
But they can communicate
via "the psychic plane."
So, each episode, they help
each other fight a new monster
from across the county.
Okay.
Is the Ice Cream Man
in every episode?
No.
That's just a
Monster of the Week.
Mr. Melancholy is the Big Bad.
Mr. Melancholy?
The Man in the Moon.
Oh, right.
He's always messing
with time and reality.
He wants to rule the world,
to trap Isabel and Tara
in the Midnight Realm.
So each week,
he sends a new
supernatural foe their way.
Because they're part
of The Pink Opaque.
No, because they
are The Pink Opaque.
Right.
Sorry.
Don't apologize.
Well, I'm passing out.
Are you sure it's okay
that I sleep down here?
Just be out by dawn.
If my stepdad catches you,
he'll break my nose again.
And where... where
will you be sleeping?
In my bed... creep.
Sometimes...
The Pink Opaque feels
more real than real life.
You know?
So,
how you feeling about my
little health scare, buddy?
I'm fine.
It just...
seems like you're always
somewhere else lately.
I don't know...
I'm not sure if it's
'cause of me, or...
I don't know. I...
Maybe I'm just making it up.
Just want to know that
you're on the right
path, you know?
Can I stay up late to watch
The Pink Opaque tonight?
What time does it come on?
10:30 p.m.
You know your
bedtime is at 10:15.
Yeah, but...
no one in the ninth grade
even has a bedtime anymore.
Isn't that a show for girls?
Not tonight, honey.
After that first sleepover, I
couldn't work up the courage
to say more than three words
to Maddy Wilson at a time.
But when I told her I
still wasn't allowed
to watch the show,
she started leaving
tapes for me.
I watched these tapes
over and over again.
But they never got old.
His henchmen are close by.
Marco and Polo.
Nasty little demons.
And he... he's...
Mr. Melancholy.
That's right.
What's happening to me?
How do I know these things?
Am I going crazy?
No. Never let anyone
convince you of that.
You're like me.
You're special.
We are The Pink Opaque.
It's our destiny.
I knew it from the moment
I saw your tattoo
in the dining hall.
Heck, I knew it
before I even met you.
Can you feel it?
I don't even have my
learner's permit yet.
- How can I have a destiny?
Hey.
What's up?
Nothing much.
Um, I was wondering...
Do you, um...
Do you and Amanda
still watch The Pink
Opaque together every week?
I haven't talked to
that asshole in a year.
Amanda told the entire school
that I tried to touch her tit,
which is a total lie!
And then surprise, surprise,
11th grade comes around
and suddenly it's been
her lifelong dream
to join the cheer squad! Ugh!
Secret agent sent here to make
my life miserable, I swear.
If you wanted, I
could come over again.
I've been watching the
tapes you've been making me
but I wanted to
watch The Pink Opaque
on Saturday night again.
While it airs.
I like girls. You
know that, right?
I'm not into boys.
I wasn't... I...
Totally. That's fine.
Okay. I'm just making sure.
What about you?
Do you like girls?
I don't... I don't know.
Boys?
I... I think that
I like TV shows.
When I think about that stuff,
it feels like someone...
took a shovel and dug
out all my insides.
And I know there's
nothing in there,
but I'm still too nervous
to open myself up and check.
I know there's
something wrong with me.
My parents know it too,
even if they don't say anything.
Do you ever feel like that?
I don't know.
Maybe you're like Isabel...
Afraid of what's inside you.
Hey, Bozo! Estee
Lauder called.
They've got a few suggestions
about this whole look
you're going for.
I'm getting out of this town.
Did you know that?
Soon.
I'll die if I stay here.
I don't know how exactly,
but I know it's true.
If you leave,
I won't have anyone to
watch The Pink Opaque with.
Sit up.
Pack as much as you can
in your overnight
bag next Saturday.
You can't tell
anyone we're leaving.
Not your mom.
Not anyone.
Where will we go?
We'll know when we get there.
Owen? Uh, Johnny's
not home, but...
You have to tell my dad
that I've been lying to him.
I've been pretending
to sleep here
while my mom's in the hospital.
And I need to be grounded.
Okay. Slow down, honey. What?
You can't let me go with her.
I don't want to leave my home.
My mom passed away
the next July.
And a few weeks later,
Maddy disappeared
without a trace.
All they found was her TV
set burning in the backyard.
And the strangest
part of it all was,
that exact same month
that Maddy disappeared,
The Pink Opaque got canceled.
[OVER SPEAKER] Welcome
to Burger Express.
Hello?
Hi.
- Are you ready to take my...
- What would you like, sir?
- Yeah, sorry. Can I get...
- Are you there?
I just want... Can I get
two double cheeseburgers
and a small fries
and a root beer?
- $11.09. Drive around.
- Okay. Okay, thank you.
Answering his phone,
so I can't start...
the projector until
I get the key.
Um, so if you could call me back
and just let me know...
What the hell!
Sorry! Sorry!
Uh, hey, Owen, um,
did you like what
you saw earlier?
Me and Erica?
You know, because, if you want,
I can put in a good
word with Erica for you.
She's, like, obsessed
with you, man.
She's like, "Oh,
I love that guy."
"He's so cool! Oh, my God!"
It's "on" for you, brother.
Come on, man.
Hey, why don't you
look at me. Please.
Just make eye contact
with me. Seriously.
What the heck?
Hello?
Is somebody there?
"Season Six, episode one:"
"Escape from the
Midnight Realm."
I'm sorry that I'm late.
There was a downed power line.
Within hours,
90% of Earth's
population was destroyed.
The invaders changed
the planet's atmosphere,
creating an eternal night.
The sun forever covered
by the dark clouds.
The survivors fled underground,
living in fear of the machines
that now ruled the Earth.
Ma'am? Are you...
Do you need help?
Do you remember me?
Maddy?
Oh, my God!
Jesus, Maddy, where
have you been?
I know a place on
the edge of town.
It will be safe for
us to talk there.
♪ I saw the TV glow
♪ I am in the eighth grade
♪ Sending grown
men grainy photos
♪ Of my ribcage
♪ My bedroom has no doors
♪ So I can never close them
♪ I paint the ceiling black
♪ So I don't notice
♪ When my eyes are open
♪ I paint the ceiling black
♪ So I don't notice
♪ When my eyes are open
♪ And somewhere
south of Tallahassee
♪ A teenage boy
with a summer job
♪ He's driving grown
men around a golf course
♪ He's going home
to a manicured lawn
♪ And digging holes
in his manicured lawn
♪ I think I was born bored
♪ I think I was born blue
♪ I think I was
born wanting more
♪ I think I was born
already missing you
♪ But my heart is
like a claw machine
♪ It's only
function is to reach
♪ It can't hold
on to anything ♪
I just... I really think that
you need to go to the police.
They think you're dead, Maddy.
I don't know.
Sometime.
And you won't tell me where
you've been this past decade?
I'll tell you everything.
I just...
I need to ask you
something first.
Does your mom know
that you're alive?
I need to ask you
something first.
Okay. Okay.
What do you need to ask me?
♪ When it's me who's making it
♪ It's always the wrong thing
when it's me who's saying it ♪
Do you remember a TV show
we used to watch together?
It was called...
The Pink Opaque.
Of course, I remember
It's my favorite TV
show of all time.
Always will be.
That's all you wanted to ask me,
if I remembered The Pink Opaque?
No.
I guess what I mean is...
When you think back on
watching The Pink Opaque,
how do you remember it?
How do I remember it?
Yeah.
Do you remember it
as just a TV show?
Yeah. I remember
it as a TV show.
The Pink Opaque was a TV show.
We watched it in your
basement on Saturday nights
from 10:30 to 11:00
p.m. Remember?
The last show before
the Young Adult Network
switched to black and
white reruns for the night.
Yeah.
But are you sure?
Are you sure that's all it was?
Listen.
I know this might
sound crazy, but...
When you think back
on The Pink Opaque,
when you remember
watching it in my basement
on Saturday nights from
10:30 to 11:00 p.m.,
do you ever get confused?
Like, maybe the memory
isn't quite right?
What do you mean
"not quite right"?
Like...
Does time ever feel like
it's not moving normally?
Like it's all out of whack?
Do you ever feel like you're
narrating your own life
watching it play in front of you
like an episode of television?
Or do you ever have a
hard time distinguishing
between what
happened in the show
and what happened in real life?
Like somehow the memories
got jumbled around?
Shook up in your head.
Like a snow globe.
I'm trying to go slow.
I don't want to alarm you.
Maybe we should
talk to somebody,
the police or my dad...
No!
You can't tell
anybody about this.
Not like last time.
You have to promise.
Okay, Maddy. Jesus.
Yeah, I promise.
I came a very long
way to see you,
and to ask you this...
Will you just...
Will you tell me where
you've been all these years?
That's what I've
been trying to do.
I've been there.
Inside the show.
Inside The Pink Opaque.
♪ Why have I have
been punished?
♪ I've been banished
from the sky
♪ Clinging to his mighty
chest Bury my face and cry
♪ I bow to him just
to sleep next to you
♪ A force I can't deny
♪ When I'm spread on the bed
♪ You remain the
luscious fruit
♪ Help me, I'm
so chained to you
♪ Someone tell me what to do
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ Feeling like a psychic wound
♪ Help me, I'm
so chained to you
♪ Someone tell me what to do
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah
♪ Feeling like a psychic wound
♪ Feeling like a
psychic wound ♪
I can't stay in this
place much longer.
I'm going back there.
Do you remember how it ended?
The final episode?
The end of season five?
You can't trust
anybody in your life.
They're all working for him...
Mr. Melancholy.
I'll be at the high school
tomorrow night at midnight.
I hope you'll come.
A little while after
Maddy disappeared,
she sent me one more
tape in the mail.
Mr. Melancholy is coming.
If we're going to
defeat him this time,
we're going to need to harness
the full potential
of our shared powers.
We're going to need
to meet again...
in person.
Isabel follows the
sound of Tara's voice
in the psychic
plane... Isabel?
Tara?
- Back to their old
sleepaway camp.
She finds her at the
dock by the lake,
the place where they first
spoke five seasons ago.
But then, as Isabel approaches,
she picks something up.
A stray signal from
the psychic plane.
Help me. Help me.
It's a desperate
message from Tara.
The real Tara.
She's buried underground...
in terrible danger.
Help me, Isabel.
Mr. Melancholy had
got to her first.
Marco.
Polo.
They cut out her heart.
They feed her the Luna Juice.
And then he makes his entrance.
Mr. Melancholy...
the big bad.
Don't fight it.
Let my poison work its magic.
You're gonna love
the Midnight Realm.
It's such a wonderful,
wonderful prison.
It's okay.
Soon you won't
remember anything.
Your real name.
Your superpowers.
Your heart.
You won't even remember
that you're dying!
They bury her... alive.
And then...
it just ended...
forever.
This isn't my home!
You're not my father!
I made it all the way to Phoenix
on the money I had saved.
The trees looked different,
but everything else
was exactly the same.
I started using a new name.
Sleeping at the cheapest
hostel I could find.
The Pink Opaque was over.
I got a job at the mall.
At Build-A-Bear.
Filling the dolls
up with stuffing.
I got out of that town.
That place I knew would
kill me if I stayed.
But something was still wrong.
Wronger, even.
Time wasn't right.
It was moving too fast.
And then I was 19.
And then I was 20.
I felt like one of those dolls,
asleep in the supermarket.
Stuffed.
And then I was 21.
Like chapters skipped
over on a DVD.
I told myself...
"This isn't normal."
This isn't how life
is supposed to be.
I thought about
running away again.
About moving to Santa Fe
and changing my
name one more time.
But I knew that everywhere
would be just the same.
I had seen how it ended.
I knew where I was.
A little bit after
my 22nd birthday,
I paid this burnout kid
who used to hit on
me in the food court
$50 to bury me alive.
I mean...
he didn't know he
was burying me alive,
but I doubt he would have
cared too much even if he did.
I bought a coffin.
I dug a hole.
I got inside and
I closed the lid.
I said to myself,
"This is crazy."
"What you're doing is crazy."
But another part of me
knew that it wasn't.
That it was survival.
And that I didn't
have much time.
That what felt like
years in this world
was actually just seconds.
So I waited.
And then finally,
the first spadeful of dirt
hit the top of the box.
And then another.
I sang songs to myself.
I counted to 10,000 without
skipping any numbers.
I pissed and I shit my pants
and I forced my mouth
to produce whatever
saliva it could muster
just so I would have
something to drink.
I screamed as loud
as I could for help.
I apologized for
the whole thing.
And I begged God for someone
to come along and save me.
I tried and tried
to claw my way out,
but that burnout guy had
packed the dirt in too tight
just like I had asked him to do.
And then,
after I don't know how long,
I felt myself start
to leave myself.
And it was like I
was watching myself
on TV from across the room.
And I was moving further
and further away from the screen
until the screen was so small
that I couldn't even
see myself anymore.
And then I was clawing my
way up out of the ground.
And then I was at the surface,
gasping for air, rain
pouring down on me.
Thunder and lightning.
And I was finally back there.
Back at our old sleepaway camp.
And just like I was waking
up from a bad dream,
that whole life...
that whole reality where
I was Maddy Wilson...
drifted away.
Like a brief hallucination
that, after a few moments, I
could hardly even remember.
And all those memories
that had felt so real
washed away with the rain
back at our old sleepaway camp.
And I was me.
I was finally me again.
And it was the
season six premiere.
I tried looking for you,
but Mr. Melancholy had
covered his tracks too well.
I knew you must be buried
somewhere close by,
but I didn't know where.
And your signal...
That signal that I used to
be able to close my eyes
and feel so vividly...
was nowhere.
I wasn't picking up anything
on the psychic plane.
I found my heart.
Isabel, oh, my God!
I found yours, too.
And it was still beating,
stored indefinitely in...
In an industrial freezer!
I left our hearts there
because I knew I
wasn't done yet.
And I found
Mr. Melancholy's cauldron.
I found the Luna Juice
he used to send us to
the Midnight Realm,
then I took a big sip
straight out from the ladle.
And I laid back down...
and I waited to
fall back asleep.
I knew I needed
to come back here.
I knew I needed to
come back and save you.
So that the show can continue.
So that we can
get to season six.
Maddy.
That's not my name.
And I haven't told
you anything tonight
that you don't already know.
Tell me.
Tell me you know it's true.
I...
You told me yourself
you felt it.
Remember? On the bleachers?
You know what he put inside you.
This... This is insane. I...
I remember... I remember...
playing in the snow.
Driving to baseball
games with my dad.
Cooking with my mom.
Those memories were put
there to distract you.
To keep you trapped.
This isn't the
Midnight Realm, Maddy,
it's just the suburbs.
I told you that's not my name.
And we need to go back
down into the soil.
Tonight.
The longer you wait
the closer you get
to suffocating.
I've got everything ready.
That spot behind
the football field
where the stoners used
to get high after school.
No one will find us there.
Come on.
I know it's scary.
That's part of it.
It's like the Drain Lords.
Just like the Drain Lords.
It's not real if I
don't think about it.
Isabel.
After that night on
the football field,
I locked myself inside.
I didn't leave the
house for days.
I kept waiting for
her to show back up
to force me underground.
But she never did.
I never saw her again.
I told myself I made
the right choice.
Maddy's story was insane.
It couldn't be true.
But some nights,
when I was working late
at the movie theater,
I found myself wondering,
what if she was right?
What if she had been
telling the truth?
What if I really
was someone else?
Someone beautiful and powerful.
Someone buried alive and
suffocating to death.
Very far away,
on the other side of
the television screen.
But I know that's not true.
That's just fantasy.
Kid's stuff.
The movie theater
closed the next fall.
My manager brought
me along with him
to the Fun Center.
I work there now restocking
the ball pit with balls.
My father passed away in
2010 after his second stroke.
Time moves fast these days.
Years pass like seconds.
I just try not to think
too hard about it.
I decided to stay in the house.
It was time for me
to become a man.
A real adult.
A productive member of society.
And that's exactly what I did.
I even got a family of my own.
I love them more than anything.
Anyway, like I was saying,
it was raining the other
night and I couldn't sleep,
so I started The
Pink Opaque again.
It's available to stream now.
You don't even need a disc.
I started The Pink Opaque again.
And it was nothing
like I remembered it.
Hey, Mr. Ice Cream Man.
Stop turning all my friends
into popsicle sticks!
But I'm so lonely.
I have nothing to do all winter.
The whole thing felt
cheesy and cheap.
Dated, and not scary at all.
[ON TV] I know!
In the winter time, instead
of selling ice cream,
you can sell soup instead.
Why didn't I think of that?
Let's all have a soup party!
Yay, a soup party!
I just felt embarrassed.
Marco.
Polo.
You got me!
Go, go, go! Get it! Get it!
Money! Money! Money!
Money! Go, go, go, go!
Get that money!
Come on, get in there.
Come on, we're doing it.
All right, guys, come on!
♪ Happy birthday to you
Come on!
♪ Happy birthday, dear Charlie
♪ Happy birthday to you
Come on!
Everybody!
♪ Happy birthday to you
♪ Happy birthday, dear Charlie
Come on!
Let's go again from the top!
One more time!
♪ Happy birthday to you
Faster!
Louder!
♪ Happy birthday, dear Charlie
♪ Happy birthday...
You need to help me!
I'm dying right now!
Sorry. Ignore me. I...
Mommy!
Owen?
You okay in there, buddy?
I'm fine.
Out in a minute.
Sorry about that before.
Sorry about before.
Just a new medication I'm on.
Sorry.
I'm sorry about before.
Sorry about that before.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.