"A worthwhile dream
is one that is laughed at".
Hey, hurry up.
The bride is waiting.
Ten years ago,
I was in high school.
Before my mom became
a Korean pop culture fan
and a little after the
Olympic Games in Beijing.
That spring, they started building
the Sky Tree in Tokyo.
Hi, Kosuke.
This is Junon Akiyama.
Unfortunately for him
his mom named him
after a popular teen magazine.
His family owns an inn so
he gets a generous allowance.
This is Kazuki Sugimura,
nicknamed Ikki.
An ever-cheerful
social butterfly.
But his nose bleeds on
the rare occasions that he lies.
It must mean
that his heart is pure.
He lives with his mom,
a piano teacher.
I'm checking your hair and
the length of your skirts.
Our school was known
for having strict rules
and annoying teachers who believed
in military-like discipline.
The "certification
for naturally curly hair" was
conceived at this school.
Stop.
I told you
to submit the certification.
Oh yeah... There.
Mizushima!
Reflect on your stupid behavior.
Sit facing the wall today.
I've known Utako Komatsubara
since kindergarten.
I thought of her
as a little brother until
her breasts started growing
in 5th grade
and I warily realized
she was a girl.
A cat lover who's
good at drawing.
Why do you always pull a stunt
like that? It won't fool anyone.
Let's get it measured.
Stop playing games.
As usual,
Junon is quick to react down there.
But there was no rule
to prohibit that.
"Don't cry, Mother?"
She would if she could see you now.
I don't care who told you
to sit like that.
Face forward.
Thank you.
You two, switch places.
Hayase, help him study.
Is that clear?
Two right triangles.
Mana Hayase.
The daughter of a reputable doctor
and the best student in school.
She has a thick,
invisible wall around herself
but everybody can't help
looking at her.
But... she gets on my nerves.
Let's go to the bookshop
after school.
I wanna listen to this
on your big speakers.
This is ancient.
Where did you excavate this?
Use my machine
for only the latest CDs.
One steps back into the future
by reflecting on the past.
You sound like a phony evangelist.
Butt poke!
You reveal things
that ordinary people don't.
Because you're honest.
Also honest down there.
Shut up.
So childish.
Girls are nice and complicated.
Too bad I can't show you.
Let me see.
Kosuke.
What? This?
I wanna listen.
You should join us.
Junon has huge speakers.
Cool. Wanna come?
No. I'm not interested
in that person.
Who do you like?
Beethoven.
Beethoven?
But I'd like to study pop music.
Study?
Come to my place.
My mom has many Beethoven CDs.
I like
listening to Beethoven alone.
Sorry.
- Sorry.
- No big deal.
I'm gonna have my "bento-ven".
What?
Lunch.
You're so nice to the guys.
If you were nice to them,
they'd go crazy.
What do you mean?
Am I too uptight?
That's what's so endearing
about you.
And that sweet, coy face.
My brain is half male.
What?
Wicked.
What is?
What's wicked?
You guys hungry?
Wanna go to Gojuban?
- I'm in.
- Me too.
Let's ride after the girls
part of the way.
Seriously?
Okay!
No riding bikes inside the gate.
We'll get in trouble.
I'm jealous of those bike seats.
Be a bike seat when you grow up.
I will.
There they are!
Girls!
Targets in sight!
I win!
A portrait of youth that's seen
all around the world.
The elements of youth are
ambition, uncertainty,
delusion, sexual desire.
Regret, humiliation.
And first love.
- Papa.
- Yes?
- Two meat buns.
- Me too.
Okay.
Mama, four dumplings.
Okay. In a minute.
"Here's the delivery meal".
It's for the Satos so no onions.
"I thought it was for the Katos".
Satos, not Katos.
"Sato? As in sugar?"
Not sugar. Onions.
"Onions? Oh, the Negishis".
Forget it. I'll do it.
This is Yohei.
His dad is Taiwanese.
His mom is Japanese and
Yohei goes by her family name, Ohno.
He's an outstanding student
and acts
like he's too good for us.
Hey... You guys are gonna
listen to the CD, right?
Yeah.
Can I join you?
Opening up to us?
Of course you can come.
I'm gonna go listen to music.
Good for you.
I was worried
because he studies too much.
Your Japanese is improving.
Definitely.
Practicing?
Practicing.
I saw a kitten in
front of Takagi Shrine.
I think it was just born.
Really?
I'll go check it out.
You're not going to Junon's?
The kitten first.
Maybe Kosuke will pass by.
What kind of person
is Kosuke Mizushima?
A childhood friend, right?
Yeah.
His hair has always been
naturally curly.
He thought
it'd eventually grow straight.
How should I put it?
Inside, he's both...
an artist and a criminal.
I think it confuses him.
That's why he acts weird
on purpose.
Criminal?
Yeah... Maybe.
He's more a cat
than a dog.
What does that mean?
I'm going home.
See you tomorrow.
Yeah, tomorrow.
"Hayase Clinic"
Utako.
I decided
not to go to Junon's today.
She doesn't look well.
I'm gonna stay here.
A cat is more important
than friends?
Of course.
It goes without saying.
You shortened your skirt.
I'm free outside school.
Your panties will show.
Wanna peek?
I'm wearing Spiderman today.
No thanks.
See ya.
We're gonna go listen to the CD.
"Every time"
"we say goodbye"
"I die a little".
Again?
"Every time we say goodbye
I die a little".
You've said that 1,000 times
but you never die.
You keep growing.
Right... See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
This is my house.
A humble tofu shop that
my great grandfather opened.
I'm so hot.
Nice and cool.
Hi.
Find something to eat
in the freezer.
I ate already and I'm going out.
Going out?
It's already September.
College entrance exams
are coming up.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Not interested.
Beer.
Nice and cool.
- I'm going now.
- Okay!
Your mom is working part-time
to send you to college.
For me?
For a spa retreat.
What?
I got a call
from your homeroom teacher.
A certification
for naturally curly hair?
I'll go talk to her.
Dad, don't bother.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Nice and cool.
It's so hot.
"Enemy"
Master, I have returned.
Wonton. Chow mein.
"Oiwakeya Inn"
Yo.
Go inside.
Um...
Where are the girls?
Utako's not coming.
I meant... Mana Hayase...
So that's why you came.
No, no, no... Let's go.
Us four, Mana, Utako.
And another guy
I'll introduce later.
Unrequited love
starts swirling in
multiple directions
among us seven.
It can only be described
as youth.
Isn't male bonding great?
You're a dork.
But a big bath
is definitely great.
Yohei has a crush on Mana.
Hey!
I'm more an Utako fan.
Really?
Hey...
People used to call Mana
"outdated ethics" last year.
Why?
Because she's old-fashioned.
"Outdated ethics", huh...
No wonder
she thinks we're childish.
Junon...
This is the men's bath.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
Mana...
Impossible.
Numbers and symbols don't
have any appeal whatsoever.
Master,
I'd like to stop thinking
and go to sleep now.
Sweet and sour pork.
Spring rolls.
Yes, sir.
Stand up.
Bow.
Open your textbooks to page 38.
Don't tell me
you forgot to bring it.
You again?
No certification. No textbook.
Why are you here?
To eat lunch?
Lunch is important.
Then what's the point
of attending class?
Face the wall.
"Mana is pretty if
she wasn't so serious"
Apple of his eye?
A person that is loved...
more than any other?
- Are you buying something?
- Um?
Yeah.
What do you want?
Thank you.
Whatever.
I'm used to it.
Tell me something.
Tell you what?
Why don't you study math
for the college exams?
How are integrals
and logarithms useful?
We don't know.
That's the point.
Looking for answers
with pure language,
not spoken words.
When I open a math textbook
I stop being me and
turn into a serious daughter
of a doctor.
Idiot.
This is Kento Machida.
His dad works at a tire factory.
Since he was a kid,
he used tires to
develop muscle and increase
lung capacity.
An athletic genius and a leading
competitor in a variety of sports.
Come.
Yes!
Kento...
When did you start taekwondo?
Um... Day before yesterday.
This is depressing.
I've been practicing Chinese
martial arts for a year.
Talent is something
you're born with.
I'm not consoled.
I thought
you're focusing on basketball.
Martial arts
is part of my training.
I'm emulating the great Ichiro,
not trying
to get physically bigger.
I hope you have a talent
for something too.
Mana Hayase.
Your back looks like
it's steaming.
I was practicing.
You're early.
My brothers nag at me so
I study here in the morning.
Utako said you have twin
brothers who are both doctors.
That's right.
The stethoscope rumba
and the endoscope samba?
What's that?
"In the morning, exercising stimulates
the brain more than studying".
"For breakfast, protein is better
than carbs for the brain".
"Intelligence runs in the family
so take advantage of your DNA".
They won't stop pestering me.
Can I go watch?
Huh?
Oh yeah.
Look.
Utako drew this.
It's exactly like them.
You also want to be a doctor?
I don't think I'm cut out for it.
Why not?
When I was small,
I peered into a window
of a patient's room.
The curtain was fluttering
and I could see inside...
Then?
A gaunt young woman
was lying on the bed
with her bony knees sticking out.
Two flies were flying around her.
One of them came
and flew into my forehead.
It apparently made me pass out.
You're talkative today.
I just don't talk during class.
You two are too close
to each other.
What's your problem?
This movement.
It stimulates the brain.
American scientists proved it.
How long were you listening to us?
I wasn't. I didn't hear anything
about two flies.
He's like my brothers.
Surprisingly, Mana is cute
once she starts talking.
And Kento too.
I guess he's cute.
Year 1956.
The Japan-Soviet Joint Declaration.
Japan and the Soviet Union
made a joint declaration.
The treaty with the Soviets
did not sit well
with the Americans.
They were perplexed.
What choices did Japan have
during the Cold War?
A difficult decision.
What?
You were sleeping.
I chose Japanese history
as an elective.
I'm talking about your duty as
a student, not about the exam.
Show some respect for the teacher
who's trying to teach us.
"Outdated ethics".
That hurts.
Hayase, are you listening?
Yes.
Even if it's not
on the college entrance exams
studying world history will be
helpful in your future.
For example
when Japan lost the war,
the British prime minister said
"You cannot deal with the most
serious things in the world"
"unless you also understand
the most amusing".
Did you hear that?
Ow...
Hayase.
Give me a quote by another
famous person in history.
"Anybody can become angry".
"But to be angry
at the right time and"
"for the right purpose is
not within everybody's power".
Practice that.
Right purpose...
A useful concept
for everyday life.
Who said that?
Aristotle.
A friend of yours?
Him?
No. He also wears clothes.
Next. Komatsubara.
Yes.
Your favorite quote?
"Keep doing
what you can't stop doing".
"Be lazy".
"Believe in an invisible world".
What? Who said that?
Comic artist Shigeru Mizuki.
That one struck a chord.
Hey.
Why do you keep poking me
with that?
A math test.
Finish it by tomorrow.
Will you get off my back?
It really is math.
Now what?
A textbook I found most helpful.
Study the marked problems.
You'll do better
in your next test.
You have to pass this stage
sooner or later.
Later is fine with me.
"I count him braver who
overcomes his desire".
Mr. Aristotle.
Listen to the forefather.
Why kindly order me around?
I don't want to scorn you.
I get scorned
for a math test score?
What I scorn is
someone who makes no effort
but belittles other people's.
Who'd do that... "totle"?
Childish.
What?
The test.
You bombed it.
You didn't read the textbook.
The answer to this problem
is in there.
And this formula
doesn't work for this.
Correct them in 10 minutes.
You'll lose time
for your own studies.
It's okay. I get distracted when
I'm frustrated by someone.
It's even more time consuming
and a waste of life.
That's harsh.
Here's the next test.
Kosuke was reading a textbook
in the courtyard.
Was he?
Is he still there?
We should leave him alone.
You're dedicated.
Is it love or maternal instinct?
I think it's more like sympathy.
Oh... That's a noble sentiment.
Is it like the way
I feel toward cats?
You're being silly.
They're hopeless.
When will I ever use this?
Let's go. Hurry.
Wait up.
He studied all night
and practiced in the morning.
Did his brain awaken?
Awaken and now asleep.
He's not used to this.
He was studying?
Reading a difficult textbook
Mana lent him.
Mana?
Yeah. He asked me to
explain some problems.
He should've asked Yohei.
Strong pride.
Weak academic skills.
Who ate my fried rice?
Ikki?
What was that "aha" for?
You sounded lewd.
It was a legitimate "aha".
My brain understands
and is crying out with joy.
You like talking about the brain
these days.
Stop bothering me.
Are you starting to panic?
You're my son so you're smart.
It's just that
you're also your dad's son.
There's your problem.
Anyway, study hard.
Thanks.
Yohei Ohno, 89 points.
- You could do better.
- Yes, sir.
- Kaori Kikuchi.
- Yes.
60 points.
Try harder next time.
I will.
Kosuke Mizushima.
76 points.
Seriously? You traitor.
I'm a born genius.
The result of sitting
in front of Hayase?
Can I sit behind her now?
- Pointless, so no.
- Okay.
Mana Hayase, 89 points.
You and Ohno had the best scores.
Yuta Jinno, 53 points.
Yumi Sato.
I'll give you
harder practice problems.
How is studying like this
useful to me?
It's important to try without
expecting something in return.
Another lesson in ethics.
How is being childish
useful to you?
Kento is amazing.
He's good at everything.
You're watching him?
Not them?
You interested in someone?
No one in particular.
Your nose bleeds when you lie.
You're so nice.
You like Kento?
Here we go.
I won't tell.
Thanks.
But his brain and nerves
are made of muscle.
Why are you wearing underwear?
And why are you drinking
so early in the day?
Did something happen?
Nothing to speak of.
Just feeling the weight of
a lot of little things.
Kosuke...
I think we'll have to close
our tofu shop.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I should get a job.
Not before the exams.
We'll manage until then.
We have 6-months' worth of
frozen soy pulp I can sell.
Soy pulp is good for health.
Take off your underwear.
No need to hide anything
from your family.
Your mom should also get naked.
She should.
Don't be ridiculous.
Papa, are the meat buns ready?
Yep. Two, right?
Just one starting today.
- On a diet?
- No.
"A teenager on a diet?"
It's normal these days.
- Or they'll look like you.
- True.
"That's so sweet.
You're flattering me".
Hi.
You're getting close to Mana
these days.
Yohei.
Now is not the time
for delusions.
Studying comes first.
Look who's talking.
Me.
No...
I must not embrace defeat.
No!
A ship from China with tons of
human hair for hair extensions
sank in the Sea of Japan.
They might come drifting.
Not from the Sea of Japan.
Let's go check out Akakura Dam.
Will they reach the dam?
It was a joke.
I know another scary story.
When you sit in front
of that wall
you can hear voices of students
from the past.
You're kidding.
I'm not. From here.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Kosuke.
Stop teasing Mana.
She has a pure heart.
You were teasing me?
No. I was showing affection.
You're mean.
I didn't think
you'd believe me.
Why not?
Dead people live on in our brains.
I see.
Why do I have to be here
at night?
You're freaked out by that story.
I can't concentrate.
Sit in front of me.
So demanding...
That's also distracting.
Here.
With all these empty seats?
Yeah.
Dessert.
You want me to eat it whole?
Huh? Are you a princess
or something?
I'll take it home. Thanks.
Beautiful.
We should keep studying.
Do some math problems.
Don't get cocky with 76 points.
I can do it if I try.
I'll beat you next time.
Impossible. I'm teaching you.
Wanna bet?
You're so confident.
The loser has to change
his or her hairstyle
according to the winner's request.
So you'll have to shave
your head.
If I win,
a ponytail for a month.
Fine. Ponytail or pigtails.
I won't lose.
Joan of Arc. Sei Shonagon.
Takako Doi.
I like competitive women.
I'll study.
That hurts.
Step by step.
Face to face.
Shut up!
I'm studying English very hard.
Mouse. Mouse. Mouse.
The Incredible Butt Shaker.
I am happy.
I am a genius!
"I didn't grow
by winning all the time".
"Losing made me strong".
You're a sore loser.
Saori Yoshida's words.
Let's bet again.
You like to bet, don't you?
I guess I do.
I hate to admit it
but Mana could be charming.
Don't get rice on my head.
I'll look like a rice ball.
Where did you get it cut?
You know that convenience store
near the Kotobuki projects?
It was about 50 meters from there.
But it was gone
when I passed by this morning.
The barber
was a freaky-looking creature.
Maybe it was a different world.
A parallel universe
in a barber shop?
A mystery, huh?
Lame.
Did I really get a haircut?
You definitely did.
Yeah but...
I like girls with ponytails.
Damn it.
Just when I was trying to move on...
I don't know why she decided to
wear a ponytail.
But...
I felt encouraged all the same.
Stand up.
I'm Fujihira
in charge of this school's security.
There was a theft today
in the accounts office.
The safe for storing reserve funds
was broken into
and approximately 870,000 yen
was stolen.
We believe
the break-in occurred at 6:59
when we received
an automated notification.
We arrived here at 7:14
to confirm the theft.
Excuse me.
What does that have to do
with this class?
You should suspect outsiders first.
Now listen.
In the 30 minutes before
and after 7:00
nobody entered the school grounds.
The only people here were
Mr. Tokuoka, the physics teacher,
and 3 students.
Three students from this class.
I was here.
I was here too with Kosuke.
Me too.
Then I'd like the three of you
to come with me.
Are you suspecting us?
Sounds like you're already
accusing us.
No.
I just want to hear your stories
to make sure you're not involved.
You're lying.
You brought the security guy.
You don't trust us at all.
Does the school think
we're criminals?
Don't be stupid.
I think...
you're wrong.
Huh?
If you want to interrogate us,
take us to the police.
Not this security company.
Here's your evidence.
Go ahead. Check it out.
Why suspect only us students?
What about Mr. Tokuoka?!
Stop it!
Unless you want to be suspended!
This is wrong.
Yeah! This is crazy!
Mana, nobody's watching
so you can take it easy.
Here. Ikki's tissue paper.
Go ahead.
Don't look at me.
This is embarrassing.
Don't be embarrassed.
I was impressed with you
for the first time.
You also look cute crying.
Just don't look at me.
Math problems
always have correct answers.
But some problems in life
are impossible to solve.
The thief was never caught.
Kosuke.
Mana.
When my hair grew
to its usual length...
Three years ago
at our entrance ceremony...
Mana represented our class
at the graduation ceremony.
Our hopes for the future
were infinite
but we couldn't see anything.
But under
our instructors' supervision,
we fostered friendship
and we grew.
This school is a backpack
filled with memories.
Carrying it on our backs
we'll now spread our wings
to follow our dreams.
Let us fly
into a wonderful future.
Sexual lust, be gone!
So, have you decided?
About what?
Who you want to be with.
You won't even tell me?
If...
Yeah. I knew it.
I did.
How about you?
Mana.
That's not fair.
It's true.
Let's stay together
even after we graduate.
Of course.
Even if we go to different colleges.
Yeah.
Then we took the entrance exams
to the colleges of our choice.
Does anyone want tofu?!
Tofu, anyone?!
They're such kids.
Really.
I used to hate childish behavior.
And now?
You really are so childish!
I'm the king!
Hey.
What kind of adults will we be?
What science are you going
to major in?
I want to make mobile games.
Playful ones.
Nice. Me...
I'm going to study design
in art school
and develop cat toys.
I want to be surrounded by cats!
I don't care about college.
I'm gonna go overseas to
work and study at different hotels
and then expand our inn.
- Expand this?
- No!
I want to get
into the University of Tokyo
and then go to a famous American
university on government funds
to get an MBA.
I want an N, not an M. The NBA.
One day, I'll play in the US.
You three are going abroad.
And you, Mana?
I was scared of dissection so
I didn't think I could be a doctor
but I've been thinking
of studying psychiatry.
A doctor, one way or the other.
You can treat me when
I'm on the NBA injured list.
She said she's going
to study psychiatry.
I'll also fly in from wherever
to get an endoscopy.
She said psychiatry.
- Get an enema.
- You guys!
That'd be cool.
Listen!
You're so childish, as usual.
And finally, you?
I want to be one hell of a guy.
In what way?
Someone whose presence can
change the world a little bit.
What's up?
What's wrong?
My first choice...
I didn't make it.
I was sure I would.
I've been studying so hard
since middle school.
Why did I fail the most
important test of my life?
Our rival tofu shop
closed down first
so our sales went back up and
we were able to stay in business.
Not yet?
Meow, meow.
Shut up.
What do you think?
I think it's important
for the family to bond.
Be brave and get undressed.
Don't be ridiculous.
Utako got accepted
to an art school in Tokyo.
She was the first to leave town
in pursuit of her dream.
Yohei made it
into the University of Tokyo.
I'm going.
"You made your grandpa in Taiwan
so happy".
Be sure to eat well.
Okay. See you.
Kento's English
was too poor to get
into an American university but
he was accepted to one in Japan
with a strong basketball team.
"Mana"
Ikki set his sights too high
and failed miserably.
To his mom's delight, he's staying in
town to prepare for next year's exams.
"Congratulations on your departure"
Junon will be studying
hotel management in Nagoya.
A solid choice.
If there was a school for tofu
management, I might've gone there.
Mana failed her first choice,
a national university
but was accepted to a prestigious
private medical school.
The moon in daylight
is also beautiful.
Send me a photo of you
in a white coat.
Undergrads don't wear one.
She's a sympathetic
and caring person.
Your T-shirt from the other day.
She'll be a good doctor.
This is from me.
Let me see.
It's an apple.
Look it up in the dictionary.
"The apple of my eye".
Later. Okay?
You're acting weirder than usual.
What did you expect?
You're going away.
I'll miss you.
The train will be arriving soon.
Please stand behind
the yellow line.
See ya. I'll be in touch.
Yeah. Me too.
Please beware of closing doors.
I was accepted to a public college
in the prefecture.
I moved out of home, the tofu shop,
and entered
the brotherhood of a men's dorm.
I slid into the department
of literature
but as to what I wanted to do
or where I wanted to go
I was clueless.
"Incense Study Group"
"Tea Ceremony Study Group"
"Folk Dance Club"
Embarrassing as it is, I had never
held a girl's hand before this.
In the end, I joined this club.
"Chinese Martial Arts Club"
It was much more me
than folk dancing.
At times, I was overwhelmed by
the desire to hear Mana's voice.
Hello?
How's Tokyo?
There are so many people.
The air feels thinner than home.
I get tired so easily
when I go out.
Oh yeah?
There's a lot of oxygen here.
A good place to open your clinic.
I got a roommate.
You moved in with someone?
The daughter
of a respectable family?
Don't worry.
It's someone
who I feel comfortable with.
Is it a guy?
I'll put my roommate on the line.
Don't bother. I don't know him.
Hello.
How are ya?
It's me.
Utako?!
Correct.
Mana is so fun to live with.
She's surprisingly relaxed
and kind of an airhead.
Super cute.
What are you talking about?
I'm getting jealous.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll put Mana back on.
My batteries are dying.
I'll call again.
Okay. Take care.
Let me know how you're doing.
I started practicing martial arts
for real.
He's still into martial arts.
I think he's attractive
when he's practicing.
I keep thinking
about what you said.
He's an artist
and a criminal, right?
Did I say that?
I know what you mean.
We spent a lot of time
studying together.
That's why you're not
his girlfriend?
I don't know myself.
Not yet anyway.
To be honest...
since we were kids
I had a crush on him too.
You really didn't know?
But...
when we started high school
I still had feelings for him but
he was more like a brother,
like a family member.
That type of feeling.
Oh...
I want to see you two
get together.
I mean it.
Really?
Yeah.
Summer break.
We promised to see each other.
Look. There they are.
See?
I want this one.
- Cheers.
Yuck.
Just kidding.
Step back a little. Okay.
It should be here soon.
Here it is.
I got it.
Hurry.
It's gone.
- I missed it.
- You did.
I looked up the meaning
about the apple.
You got me.
Do you really feel that way
about me?
You should know the answer.
You think too highly of me.
Overrating me.
No, I'm not.
It feels really strange.
What's so strange?
You don't know me.
I'm a slob at home.
I'm grouchy when I wake up.
I lash out at Utako
over small things.
There's nothing special about me.
I think you fell in love with
a girl in your imagination.
We spent so much time together
in reality.
You're not an imaginary figure.
Tell me something.
What do you like about me?
I just do.
Come on...
Give it some real thought.
You're still so childish.
Did she...
just reject me?
What's your wish?
It won't come true
if you tell someone.
I didn't know
what I truly wished for.
I felt anxious because Mana
wrote hers without hesitation.
I also didn't know how Mana felt.
I wasn't being honest with myself
because I was afraid of the outcome.
I felt so pathetic.
Mana.
How do you feel about me?
You want to know?
No. Don't tell me.
You don't have to.
But... Not now.
Let me
keep on loving you.
To resolve my anxiety,
I'll show the woman I love
how I've grown.
It's the only thing I can do
for now.
"Mixed Martial Arts Championship"
Anybody interested in MMA
or combat sports?
MMA championship!
Let's see who's strongest.
Light your soul on fire.
You have to come and watch.
It's not some half-assed match
for fun.
You punch and kick other people,
right?
I don't want to see you do
that up close.
It's like dissection.
Face it square on and
you'll notice what you overlooked.
You think so?
But combat sports
are like violence, right?
Absolutely not.
There's no hatred or animosity.
It's an exercise
in soul searching.
How should I put it?
It's like a pure physical language
to search for
the answer to a problem
unsolvable with words.
It's like what math is to you.
I don't really get it but I'll go.
Cool. I'll be waiting.
Master...
give me power.
I thought there were only
weaklings on campus but
the captain of the taekwondo team
showed up.
Bow.
Put this on.
Fight!
No. Wait.
Fight! Fight!
Down!
Go back!
Counting.
Fight!
Was it fun?
I'm glad you came.
I saw you and felt revived.
Answer me. Was it fun?
What's wrong?
What's the purpose of a match
like that?
It's exciting.
A battle between men.
I don't understand you at all.
Now more than ever.
Why? How come?
There are two people inside you.
Which one is real?
Which one should I watch?
I'm totally lost.
What are you talking about?
I'm me.
It's all me.
Why don't you understand?
What can you learn from violence?
I'm not doing it to learn.
You really are childish.
Yes, I am.
That's why I fell for you,
a model student
and kept chasing you.
Why don't you stop?
Idiot!
I know I am.
A real idiot!
You don't get it at all!
I sure don't!
Growing up is cruel.
Girls mature faster.
And guys don't realize it.
Did you hear?
Hear what?
I'm at work right now.
Mana broke up.
Mana broke up with Kosuke.
She did, huh?
Kosuke and Mana broke up?
I have mixed feelings
but this is my chance.
I see...
You still weren't over Mana.
I'll be in touch.
Kento made his move quickly.
However...
his motorbike was too slow.
Yohei was the winner in the end.
To think about, this is the
first time we're alone together.
I always knew...
that you were in love with Kosuke.
I lack childishness.
Something you don't like.
I was always jealous of Kosuke
when you picked on him.
You looked beautiful when you did.
I always watched you from afar.
I want us to
talk more like this.
Take your time
to get to know me.
Junon told me that Yohei and Mana
dated for 6 months
before breaking up.
I wasn't surprised
or angry or jealous.
I was miserable beyond words
and made no contact with Yohei
much less Mana
for 2 and a half years.
There was a big hole in my heart
that couldn't be filled.
I'm going to have to live with
my mistake for the rest of my life.
Earthquake.
It's an earthquake.
Let's get out of here.
Shit.
Excuse me.
Emergency earthquake alarm.
At 19:42, there was an extremely
strong tremor exceeding level 6
in a wide region
along the Pacific coastline.
Aftershocks are expected.
Sorry.
Hello? Kosuke?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine. You?
I'm okay.
It was pretty big though.
I'm just glad you're safe.
We haven't talked...
in over 2 years.
Yeah.
How have you been?
Studying all the time as always.
Are you still punching people?
I haven't done that in a while.
That's good.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I might never find someone
who'll love me as much as you did.
That's touching.
You haven't changed.
Mana...
I have a question.
Why you didn't become
my girlfriend?
I'm not sure.
Probably because I was uncertain.
If we had gotten closer
I thought you'd be disappointed
to find out that
I'm not who you thought I was.
I also couldn't understand
your fascination with martial arts
or your mood swings.
I didn't know what you wanted and
I was afraid to get close.
I see.
The moon's beautiful.
Can you see it?
Yes.
We saw a moon like this once.
That night in the classroom...
It was a beautiful moon.
The day I cut my hair.
No. That was the night
of the rainstorm.
Was it?
I'm sure of it.
I used to think that
if you had cut
your hair on a moonlit night
and if I were the one
who cut your hair
we'd be together as a couple
right now.
Don't ask me why.
Mana...
Do you believe
in parallel universes?
A different reality that exists
at the same time.
In that world, we're...
together as a couple.
We'd be going out on dates.
I wish it were true.
Thank you for
falling in love with me.
Even as a senior in college
I still didn't know
where I was headed.
I'd quit martial arts halfway
and applied for jobs that
didn't really interest me but
I was rejected by them all and
ended up in school for another year.
But after I told Mana
about parallel universes
I developed an urge to write
about imaginary worlds.
The thought came to me
from nowhere
but I kept writing
for no one in particular.
A few online novels I concocted
caught the attention of publishers
and enabled me to get by
after graduation.
But I still didn't know what
I truly wanted to write
and I was a nobody
like I always had been.
Hello?
Are you busy, former classmate?
Not at all.
There's something I wanted to
tell you before anyone else.
You want to practice surgery
on me?
You're way off mark.
Then... you want me
to fall for you again?
That's not possible.
"A worthwhile dream
is one that is laughed at".
Hey, hurry up.
The bride is waiting.
Knock it off.
The first time we're together
since the day at the sea.
I never thought
Kosuke would become a novelist.
You finally found your talent.
You could say that.
You're always on TV.
Kento's dream about the NBA
still hasn't come true.
But he's a famous professional
player in the country.
You live in Singapore now.
I'm going back tomorrow.
The price of living
is so damn high.
Junon has been working
in hotels around the world
and is still amidst his studies.
He won't be taking over
his family business just yet.
I'll be traveling through
that region next month.
Yohei works for the government now
and achieved his dream
of studying in the US.
Amazing. You're serving our country.
You're a big shot president
of an IT company.
Ikki found an Indian boyfriend
and a mobile app they developed
became a huge hit.
My partner is a huge fan of yours.
Really?
Utako studied graphic art
in art school
and made it big
with her cat products and blog.
Thank you.
I'm glad we're all here.
I thought Kosuke was the groom.
I also thought you two
would get back together.
No... Not in this lifetime.
It's time.
You're right. Let's go.
Thanks.
I'm getting nervous.
Junon!
Why?
I felt it.
- Sorry.
- Our youth.
This?
Have you met her husband?
Yeah. He came over a few times.
What is he like?
He's much older than Mana.
A surgeon.
- A doctor.
- I wanted a chance.
Too late.
You should stick out your foot
and trip him.
Ladies and gentlemen,
here they are.
The bride and the groom.
Trip him.
Be quiet.
It was a revelation.
If you truly love someone
you can wish for her
to be loved and cared for
from the bottom of your heart.
For her everlasting happiness.
- Very nice. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Congratulations.
Next, please.
Okay. Good.
Smile, please.
Okay.
Nice. Here we go.
Smile.
You should've done that
when they entered the room.
But that's weird too.
Mr. Happy Groom, I have a favor.
What is it?
Will you...
let me kiss the bride?
Idiot.
If it's okay with her.
Yes.
Wait.
I'll have to make sure how
you're going to kiss her.
Kiss me first.
That's the condition.
That's more than I can handle.
Yeah.
If you won't do it,
then forget it.
Thank you.
A math test.
I was impressed with you
for the first time.
You also look cute crying.
Just don't look at me.
I want to be one hell of a guy.
What can you learn
from violence?
I'm not doing it to learn.
You really are childish.
Idiot!
I know I am.
A real idiot!
You don't get it at all!
I sure don't!
Sorry.
I was too childish.
Mana Hayase!
I love you!
How do you feel about me?
You want to know?
I want Kosuke
to confess his love for me.
"I love you. Mana"
In that world, we're...
together as a couple.
Thank you
for falling in love with me.
Hey!
I'll always be childish.
Promise me.
"Congratulations
on your marriage"
Kosuke,
write a story about us next.
Then I'm the main character.
The biggest superhero
of the school.
I'm the guy with brains
but awkward with girls.
That'd be my character.
You better not write
about my private parts.
I'd be the paragon
of a good high school...
You got it.
I just thought of the title.
That's right.
I should write about the most
precious days of my life.
Mana gave me wings and
the wind that blows beneath them.
I've already decided the title.
"The back of the boy's shirt
was covered with dots".
"I turned around
and became captivated
for years by a fleeting smile".
"Back in those days,
I always thought of you".
Yuki Yamada
Asuka Saito
Honoka Matsumoto
Takara Sakumoto
Naoki Kunishima
Keisuke Nakata
Ryosuke Yusa
Director: Yasuo Hasegawa
English Subtitles: Annie Iwasaki