Got here just in time
for the last train.
It’s so late that
this place is deserted.
What is up with that girl?
This is why you should
know your alcohol limit.
It’s like she’s dancing.
That’s hilarious.
I’ll just take one pic.
Damn.
Head butt...
Is that blood?
Is she okay?
Why are they blabbering on
about a ghost?
No way.
Where did she go?
What’s that?
Gupabal train is approaching.
You’re saying is,
she’s a man?
I didn’t know.
Who’d mistake her for a man?
Gender of this person
isn’t the issue at hand,
the problem is the fact that
you outed him without consent.
I absolutely got his consent.
Hello, I’m Kim Na-young
from Daily Modu,
could I take some pics
and used them in an article?
You’re perfect for ‘Summer It Girl’.
Thank you!
The victim was drunk at the time,
can you call that a proper consent?
You post fluff card stack articles
on social media,
and fake stories
for some loose change.
What’d kids nowadays learn from that?
What did you say?
Please calm down.
You can apologize and
post a correction as usual,
but what about the settlement?
Settlement?
How much would that be?
- $50,000?
- Yes.
That’s a lot of money, no?
Yes.
Have you met the accuser?
No, not yet.
Why not?
I don’t have his number...
How could a reporter not have
her subject’s number?
I’m sorry.
Is your family loaded?
Pardon?
To settle!
But my editor confirmed
that article.
So?
Why should I pay...
It was an unconsented photo.
I got his consent.
Got proof? A recording
or a consent form?
Who takes the fall if one publishes
an article based on false information?
The writer!
Have you read your contract?
Ma’am...
If I were you,
I’d beg the accuser
to retract the lawsuit,
or find scoops that’ll
get us more ads.
You still don’t get it, do you?
Clean up your own shit!
Hey, Choi Woo-won!
Yeah, Na-young.
You said she was a girl,
but she turned out to be a guy!
What are you saying?
The Summer It girl I took photos of,
they say she’s a man!
- A man?
- Yeah!
She was a dude.
I was so sure she was a chick.
I know, do you have
his contact info?
What for?
He reported me to
the press arbitration committee.
He’ll sue me if I don’t
settle for $50,000.
- $50,000?
- Yeah.
- So you got it or not?
- I don’t have it!
And I only called you because
you asked me for any scoops.
No?
I did, but why did she
have to be a man?!
Anyway, if you ever see him again,
keep him here and call me, got it?
What will you do?
I have to find new stories.
Something that’ll get a lot of
clicks, and bring in tons of ads.
What am I saying? I didn’t
become a reporter to do this.
My life has been a string
of unfortunate incidents.
Nothing’s ever easy.
At least you got a decent job,
and a home to boot.
My dad lent it to me,
it’s not free.
I’ll have to pay him back.
Na-young.
A man died last night at my station.
What about that?
I actually saw it on the news,
and told my editor about
the derelict Oksu platform,
but he wasn’t into suicides.
Na-young.
There’s more to it
than just suicide.
Hey.
Stop.
What’s wrong?
I don’t even want to think about it!
Why don’t you tell her yourself?
You were the witness.
Witness what?
Good evening, chief.
Are you bored?
- Sir.
- Yeah?
There’s a man on the old platform.
Yeah?
What the hell?
Shit, why is it acting up now?
Woo-won,
could you go check it out?
A deadhead train is en route,
he could cause an accident.
Yes, chief!
Sir! It’s dangerous,
please come up!
Dammit!
Christ!
What’s that?
There was a child?
Yes.
You sure?
I’m sure.
Could this be the start of
Oksu station ghost story?
Well, it’s too weak.
If there was another witness other
than him, it’d be a story.
The funeral director saw him too.
Funeral director? Who’s that?
You must be really into shamanism.
My father exhibited
great spiritual connection.
He should’ve been a shaman,
but ended up being an embalmer.
So, you inherited the job?
I embalmed bodies with
my father since I was 10 years old
when Oksu first opened.
You remember all that?
How could I forget?
My first body was an accident victim
as soon as Oksu opened,
his body was torn to pieces.
I see...
I heard you witnessed
a child at the accident yesterday.
Go easy on the booze already.
It’s not booze,
it’s coffee.
Why are you there?
What’s your name?
1211?
That’s your name?
- Sir?
- Yeah?
There’s a big one here,
it looks like a leg!
Okay.
She said her name was a number?
She nodded her head.
Have you met him?
Yeah, just as you said.
I could feel this article
getting a ton of views.
I actually have a favor,
could you get me a copy
of the security cam footage?
Why should I?
Articles like these won’t have
much credibility without photos.
I’ll protect your identity.
Please, Woo-won.
Detective!
Why are you harassing me
over old news?
There was no mention of the kid,
the funeral director saw her.
You believe that?
He’s always drunk,
maybe he was hallucinating.
It makes no sense.
The subway clerk who was
at the accident saw her too.
Look, stop trying to fish
a ghost story,
and act like a reporter.
Is anyone inside?
Is someone there?
If you’re sick or need help,
please let me know!
I shouldn’t just open the stall...
Were you scared?
You so were, dude!
Fuck off.
What the hell was that?
Sorry, dude.
I just thought it’d be funny.
Can’t you read the room?
1013?
What’s with him?
I’ll be back soon.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Chief, good evening.
I see you often at night.
I just feel so off
after what happened.
Are you all right, chief?
Nope, cleaning up the accident
is always a major headache.
I had so much trouble
writing the statement.
- Woo-won!
- Yes?
Don’t get caught up in this ordeal,
stay calm and stick with books, okay?
I will, thank you.
Holy shit...
I’m sorry...
0329...
This is confidential, got it?
I hear you, thank you.
By the way, the conductor...
What about him?
He was roaming around
the station like a lunatic,
he’s not a station affiliate.
It feels so odd to see him
around the accident scene.
- He’s still there?
- Yeah.
I just saw him,
he went towards the platform.
Hello, I’m Daily Modu’s
reporter Kim Na-young.
Would it be okay to interview you?
Why are you still here?
It won’t come off...
What won’t?
That.
That thing.
Did you by any chance
see anyone else at the accident?
Was the victim only one?
No...
Two, there were two...
0329...
Sir?
Yes, hello?
Na-young, this story is incredible.
Did you see the video?
Of course I did!
How did you secure it?
The boss wants this story
posted online ASAP.
I need to follow-up
on one more thing,
I’ll post it by 3 at the latest.
Okay, good work!
Excuse me?
Could you tell me the significance
of the number you said
on the platform?
I have to say it.
Say what?
1211?
1013?
Will you say it?
Will you call me?
Sir?
0329, 0329, 0329, 0329...
Say it, say it, say it!
Are you okay?
I have to say it!
Next stop is Oksu Station.
3, 4!
Congratulations,
congratulations!
Happy birthday, Kim Na-young
Congratulations,
congratulations!
Happy birthday, Kim Na-young
But today isn’t my birthday...
You’re the fastest reporter
to reach 300,000 views.
At this rate, the story will reach
a million views by tomorrow!
If this isn’t your birthday,
then what is?
It’s really not.
Go on, blow them out.
Kim Na-young.
Did you really interview
the conductor yesterday?
Yes.
What time was that?
It was about 10,
is something wrong?
He was supposedly dead by then.
- The conductor is dead?
- Yeah, you moron!
He committed suicide
around 9 last night!
Who the hell did you interview?!
That’s enough, please stop.
You really messed up
this time, Ms. Kim.
I’ll post a correction.
Correct what?
You really didn’t interview
the conductor?
But...
If you’ve never interviewed him,
and fabricated a story,
then you should resign, no?
Ms. Mo.
I got a call from the sister
of the Oksu victim asking for Kim.
She’s on a row.
Scoops are rolling into her lap.
What’s with your clothes...
Why aren’t you going?
Right...
Why did you want to see me?
My brother worked as a chef,
and I couldn’t understand
why he went down there
in the first place.
But I think he went there
to find a well.
A well?
Oksu district apparently had
a lot of wells.
But during the construction of
the station, they were sealed.
Actually,
my dad died at the Oksu station.
On the opening day of the station,
he fell off the platform,
and even though my brother
and I witnessed it,
we have no memories of it.
That’s plausible.
So, I tried hypnotherapy too,
and whenever I try to remember,
I just see the well.
I worked up the courage
to look down into it,
but that’s where it ends.
My hypnosis always ended there.
So, I thought maybe my brother
went to look for the well for me.
I see...
Why?
Why?!
Is it too far-fetched?
Interpreting his death as such?
Not at all.
I’m sorry for screaming at you.
But I want to believe that
he didn’t die in vain.
There’s no such a thing
as a meaningless death.
I’m ashamed of myself, actually,
the accident had a victim,
but I didn’t bother looking into him.
I know a place that could help us,
there is an archive with records
that pre-date the internet.
Have you seen the well photo?
Yes, it’s exactly how I remember it.
What about the next photo?
Do you remember the orphanage?
I remember the well so clearly,
but I can’t remember
the orphanage at all.
Okay.
Anyway, I think the well
was near the Oksu station.
What if your brother went to
the old platform to look for the well?
Thanks, I was too scared
to come alone.
Of course it’s scary.
- I’m scared too.
- That’s what I’m thankful for.
It’s fine,
I needed to cool my head.
Nail scratches are quite deep, no?
Nail scratches?
Do you know why
I allowed you to film this?
I’m not sure.
Over 30 years since opening
of the Oksu station,
everyone who died here
had these scratches.
And you’re trying to
expose it to the world.
I’m so thankful.
My father said there was a big grudge
surrounding the Oksu station.
Why are there so many
accidents recently?
Not many, but stacked.
Subway accidents are boring,
if it’s boring,
people won’t care.
Then why are innocent bystanders
receiving the curse?
Grudge forces one to lash out
at the one who harmed you,
but as time passes,
you realize no one will help,
and the hatred expands to anyone.
You’re blaming the world.
Why should innocent people
have to be cursed?
It’s simple.
Because they’re unlucky.
Unlucky...
1001, come here!
Hey, Kim Na-young!
Get over here! Come!
Come!
This morning’s article
already hit 1 million views!
Really?
Yeah, you’re my lucky charm!
People are taking selfies there.
They’re reacting to the story.
Selfies?
Come here, come.
This one too.
The Summer It Girl’s selfie.
She got over 100K likes already.
And we just sit back and watch?
If people keep posting these...
Why can’t we allow this to happen?
Posting selfies, mean comments,
it’s all in the fun.
What if they get into accidents?
We’ll get more clicks, more ads
and make more money.
Na-young.
We’re not an authentic news outlet,
it’s a gossip tabloid.
Do not forget what we are.
The boss is asking for you.
Did you want to see me?
$10K for yesterday’s,
$10K for today’s,
hit the jackpot 3 more times.
The company will take care
of your settlement.
Thank you.
What follow-up stories
do you have in mind?
I interviewed the embalmer
again yesterday,
over 90% of those who died
in accidents at Oksu
have nail scratch wounds
on their bodies.
Evidence?
He had photographic evidence.
This is turning into a major epic.
Good, anything else?
I’d like to write about the victim,
Mr. Kang Tae-ho.
Why him?
His reason for going
to the old platform is interesting.
He apparently went there to find
an old Oksu well.
I’m not feeling it.
I met his sister...
Her?
She was in and out of the asylum,
she can’t be credible.
- Really?
- Yeah.
This one feels off.
Shelf this one.
Got anything else?
What the hell?!
Sorry, sorry.
You’re on night shift?
Yeah, I am.
- What’s this?
- What?
What’s with the scratches?
I don’t know, it just appeared.
You were the one
who posted the Instagram selfie?
I just did it for fun.
It’s quite annoying
to see it get worse.
I’ll get it checked out
on my off day.
- Make sure to do so.
- I will.
I won’t die, don’t worry.
I wish you’d die, asshole.
Dude.
Isn’t he the Summer It Girl?
Shouldn’t we grab him
and call Na-young?
Let him be.
Her paper has decided
to take care of it.
Is that right?
- Have fun.
- Later!
What the fuck...
A complaint was reported.
Screams were heard from
women’s washroom by exit 3.
I’m just outside,
I’ll check it out.
If there’s anyone inside,
could you say something?
I’m here about a complaint.
If there’s someone here,
could you knock?
Excuse me?
Hello?
Anyone inside?
Sir, this is just wrong.
This story blew up
and went nationwide.
But this is the funeral
of a close friend.
You had no problem taking pics
at the morgue, so why not this?
Listen.
If people aren’t mad at you,
you’re not doing your job as a reporter.
You’re awfully busy.
Even came to the funeral
to do your reporting.
I’m not here for a report.
I told you not to write
a ghost story for some clicks.
Do not make accusations
without knowing the truth.
A subway conductor, a tranny,
and now a subway clerk.
How is it that anyone
associated with you end up dead?
How could you say that?
Are you insinuating that
I intended for this to happen?
Am I wrong?
Create an artificial buzz,
people mimic it,
and end up dead.
And yet, you walk scot-free.
Woo-won.
Hey.
Na-young...
- Have fun.
- Later!
Those numbers...
I didn’t want to say it...
It felt as though I was possessed.
The subway conductor,
the transgender...
and even Seung-joon...
They all died after
getting this scratch.
I’ll end up like them too, right?
Stop saying nonsense,
why should you die?
What do those numbers mean?
That’s not important right now.
If you don’t want to die
for nothing, stay alert.
Got it?
Yeah...
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I keep having the same dream.
What dream?
A well keeps showing up in it.
A well?
Yes, my friend keeps dreaming
about a well.
He has nail scratches,
and saw a 4-digit number.
I wanted to ask you
if it had anything to do with you.
If not, why’d he dream
about a well like you?
Am I right?
I was actually hesitating
to call you.
I remembered something
while looking at his belongings.
Really?
The Oksu Orphanage...
My father used to run it!
And those numbers are
the admission dates of the children.
And the dates when he got paid.
Someone mentioned there was
a big grudge surrounding Oksu station,
could it be about the children?
Well, I’m not sure...
Was there a phone
among your brother’s things?
It turns on.
There’s a video.
This is Oksu station’s
old platform.
If you go this way,
there’s an old construction tunnel.
Here it is!
No way...
Are these...
I found it, I finally found it!
Those are bones, right?
The children must be buried here.
Security cam.
I’ll go first.
Watch out for the cam,
you have to crouch down.
Do we really have to do this?
We have to do something.
Could they be asking us
to call their names
to tell the world about
the injustice they suffered?
That’s the least we can do.
Who knows,
it could lift their grudge.
Yeah, it’s better than
sitting around.
Let’s go.
- What are you doing?
- Christ...
I wanted to film it just in case.
Hold on.
Recording.
What’s wrong?
There’s something in front of us.
Woo-won, you okay?
Yeah, I’m fine...
Woo-won!
Na-young?
Woo-won! Woo-won!
Woo-won!
You okay?
I’m not sure...
I don’t know what’s going on...
You kept walking alone,
you don’t remember?
I did?
I think it was here somewhere.
It’s the same spot
we saw in the video.
How did they end up
getting buried here?
So it’s you guys...
I’ll tell the world about
your grudge.
How’s your wound?
Still the same.
It’s still a wound,
it’ll take time to heal.
Yes.
So, my brother can
have his funeral then?
Yes.
Go on.
Why?
Go.
Did you sleep well?
I wrote the incident report.
I was guaranteed an exclusive,
have you checked the article?
Children who were only called
by numbers,
wrongful deaths.
Truths covered up
by Oksu station construction.
That’s the gist of it?
I thought I asked you to
drop the well story.
And yet you still wrote it.
It wasn’t intentional, ma’am.
You thought I’d automatically bite
if you mentioned ‘exclusive’?
I don’t need disobedient reporters.
Yes, Ms. Mo?
Put Kim Na-young on suspension
effective immediately.
Ma’am!
On what grounds?
Should I list them?!
I’ll decide whether to
publish the article,
you just go home and
think about what you did.
Get out!
Has she gone mad?
What’s with her?
Listen to me,
she has a reason.
When she was manning the city desk,
she supposedly looked into that well,
but believing that her findings
could delay the construction,
her boss covered it up.
Then you brought that in
as an exclusive,
no wonder she went berserk.
But how could she suspend me?
Evening, sir.
- Going home?
- Yes.
Having gone through all that,
go home and get some rest.
Everyone must be tired.
I’ve never seen anything like it.
I’m going to sleep!
Good night, sir.
Wait, wait, please!
Where is it?
What’s with you?
Why...
Why do I still have the scratches?
Why do I still have them?!
Yours disappeared!
Tae-hee...
Why do I still have them?!
It’s simple.
I transferred it to someone else.
What are you doing?!
- Please stop!
- Repeat after me!
- 1211!
- No! Please!
- Repeat after me!
- Please!
Please don’t do this!
For the last time...
repeat after me!
- 1.
- 2.
- 1!
- 1.
1211!
Appease their grudge?
You thought such a deep grudge
would suddenly disappear
as if it’s nothing at all?
It won’t disappear
until their grudge is lifted.
Until they’re satisfied!
If it was so easy...
you could have done it
a long time ago!
Even if you know how,
you must figure out the grudge first.
But that woman came by
and told me everything.
She wanted to calm
her brother’s soul or something.
And then...
How did he find out
how to transfer the curse?
His father was almost a shaman...
But I’m here about something else.
I finally remember.
1211!
Appease the vengeful spirits?
It won’t disappear
until their grudge is lifted.
Until they’re satisfied!
I’m scared...
1211...
1211, don’t be scared,
it’ll be okay.
Today is civil defense training day.
I will punish you
if you even let out a squeak.
Be quiet.
1001, you come up.
1001...
Ask him call my name up there.
It’s really scary here.
- Me too!
- My name too!
- Mine too!
- Call my name!
Be Quite
Those kids...
still remembered...
That they could live
if their names are called.
That’s why they wanted
their names called.
My brother kept crying,
begging to get me out.
My name was called for his sake.
So your father wasn’t
your real father?
We were adopted later.
But why’d he bury them
while closing the orphanage?
I found this among
my father’s things.
It contains surgery dates
for the children.
Surgery dates?
That means...
organ trafficking?
He buried the children
to get rid of the evidence.
So...
who will you pass on the curse?
Hello?
Woo-won?
What happened?
I was worried, you weren’t
answering your phone.
What’s this number?
I lost my phone.
I wanted to change my number
with the new phone.
How’s the scratch?
Same old.
There will be a way,
let’s figure it out together.
Yeah, thanks.
I’ll give you my new number,
can you text me later?
Yeah, tell me.
010-1764-0816.
1764-0816.
Did I get that right? 0816?
Yeah, it is.
Woo-won, what’s wrong?
No way...
I’m sorry, Na-young...
Location isn’t important.
You just have to stay close.
How could you...
I’m sorry.
I really want to live.
But it’s not as easy as you think.
To transfer the curse,
you need a strong will.
Because someone else
will need to die in your stead.
Also, that person has to
know about the children.
Doesn’t matter if he
believes the curse or not.
Do you have someone in mind?
What the hell?!
Why is my byline missing
from my article?
How could you steal my article
by switching the headline?!
This is Head of HR.
Yes?
The boss would like you
to resign from your post.
Kim Na-young.
Is this what you wanted?
Look at all the mess you made.
If the cops link the killings
to your articles, it’s all over.
And I barely stopped
the lawsuit from happening.
But...
if you keep acting up,
I can’t help you.
I’m not interested in fighting either
But let me ask you one thing.
You knew the truth when you
covered the Oksu orphanage, right?
That they were trying to
cover up the organ trafficking.
Shortening the construction period
was just an excuse, right?
What are you talking about?
I came to resign,
can’t you at least tell me that?
Am I right?
Someone upstairs told you to bury it.
To cover it up.
Kim Na-young.
Is life all that easy to you?
I’m right,
it’s written on your face.
Read this for me,
out loud.
I’ve had it with you.
What the hell are you doing?!
Please read it for me.
Then I’ll shut up and walk away.
What is it?
Who cares what it is?
Read it for me,
then this letter is yours.
0816, happy?
Yes, happy.
That was easy.