Do you ever feel like
nothing you do matters?
You leave footprints
on the beach,
and tomorrow they're gone.
Like it's just today
over again.
They say your teen years
are for making friends
and having fun...
which made me feel even worse.
Hey, Amy. It's Jake.
I'm in your math class.
Hey, don't forget
your adult diapers.
Yeah, right.
Jake. Phone for you.
But that day,
everything changed.
Thanks for
the ride, Shelley.
So, how come you have to go
deal with your grandpa?
My dad couldn't
get out of work.
I didn't think he worked.
I'm just gonna call Grandpa.
Hello, this is Abe.
Hey, it's Jake.
No! Don't come here.
Listen to me.
It's not safe.
Stay away.
Grandpa, did you take
your pills today?
The key to my gun cabinet,
it was in the drawer.
And now it's gone.
Yeah, Dad took it,
all right?
For safekeeping. It's okay.
Your father wants I should
fight them without a gun?
God bless him.
What's his deal,
Alzheimer's?
Dementia.
That guy gave me
the heebie-jeebies.
Holler if you need me.
Grandpa?
Shelley!
What's goin' on?
Someone broke in.
I've got a.38 in my car.
You wait there.
Grandpa!
911. What's your emergency?
911? Yeah,
I need the paramedics.
It's at 2040 Palm Circle.
My grandpa...
Sir, what's your emergency?
Grandpa.
You have to get away
from here.
Sir, can you hear me?
Please. Listen.
Go to the island.
Sir, paramedics
are on their way.
Find Emerson.
The postcard.
Go to the loop.
September 3rd, 1943.
It's okay.
Just don't move. There's
an ambulance coming.
I know you think I'm crazy.
But the bird
will explain everything.
Will you do this, Tygrysku?
Promise me?
I promise, yes.
I thought I could protect you.
I should have told you
years ago.
Grandpa. Tell me what?
Grandpa!
Shelley, behind you!
There was no one there.
May I say, Jake...
that considering this
was only a month ago...
I think you're doing
exceptionally well.
Apart from being crazy?
Having nightmares and anxiety
doesn't make you crazy.
What about seeing things
which aren't there?
Actually,
in traumatic situations,
it's not at all uncommon.
Your subconscious mind drew
an image from a movie or...
It was a story.
My grandpa told me stories
when I was a kid...
about monsters that
he fought in the war.
So there you go.
He was
brutally attacked...
and in your head, the man who
did it was inhuman, a monster.
It wasn't a man, though.
The cops said that dogs
scratched up
the screen door...
and he chased them off
into the woods.
And the coroner said
he had a heart attack.
And the cops said...
that dogs go
for the soft parts.
They DNA tested the fork...
and it had animal DNA.
So, that's case closed.
He sounds like
an extraordinary gentleman.
Were you very close?
Puerto Rico.
Here.
There's a lake where the
water glows in the dark.
And a secret tunnel.
That's where I hid
from the monsters.
He used to
babysit me a lot.
When I was with him,
I felt special.
My duck was dry again.
Abe. It's, like, 11:00.
What is he doing up?
I'm gonna
be an explorer.
Grandpa's helping me
plan my first voyage.
Everything's already
been discovered, buddy.
They terrorize each other...
before wreaking havoc
on the rest of the island.
Pay no attention
to your father.
He knows bubkes.
Come, Tygrysku. Off to bed.
And they're not choosy.
These talons
come in squadrons.
Touchdown,
Florida! What a drive.
Can you tell me a story?
The usual?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay. Once upon a time...
there was a little boy...
With the pictures.
Pictures.
Once upon a time...
there was a little boy
called Abe.
That was you.
That was me.
And he lived in a
lovely children's home
on a little island
near Wales...
where the sun
shone every day.
The headmistress,
Miss Peregrine...
was very clever.
And she smoked a pipe.
She could turn into a bird.
Mmm-hmm.
It was a home
for special children...
like Bronwyn and Victor.
They were both as strong
as 10 men.
And Hugh...
Hugh had bees
living inside him.
Where's Emma?
She could float.
She was lighter than air.
She had to wear special
shoes made of lead
to keep her
from floating away.
Where is she now?
She's still on the island,
I believe.
My mama and papa
sent me there...
to live with
the special children.
And now, Tygrysku,
time for sleep.
He used to
call me Tygrysku.
It's Polish
for "little tiger."
He couldn't have picked
a less appropriate nickname.
I was always a chicken.
Why did your mom and dad
send you away?
Well, where we lived
in Poland, it wasn't safe.
There were monsters.
What kind of monsters?
Huge ones,
with long arms...
and no eyes...
and tentacles like this.
The dumb thing was...
for years, I actually
believed his stories.
And this is Millard.
He's invisible.
My teacher says
they were trick photos.
And did you believe her?
Dad says you probably
found them
at a junk store someplace...
when you went traveling.
I would never lie
to you, Tygrysku.
But you did, about the
home, the monsters.
Dad told me.
Your father knows very well
I went to live
in the children's home.
He said there really were
monsters in Poland...
just not the kind
with tentacles.
He said you got sent to Wales
'cause there were bad people.
People who wanted to kill
anyone who was different.
I don't wanna talk
about this anymore.
He said the children
were special...
but not the way you said.
I'm just saying,
tomorrow was
supposed to be a writing day.
Five years and
counting on that damn book.
And taking one day to be with
your son on his birthday...
is gonna be a big difference?
Fine.
You find something good?
Oh, look at that.
That's awesome.
You should take that.
Come on, buddy,
let's roll.
How are you so okay?
Jakey, you were a lot closer
to him than I ever was.
He was
a wonderful grandpa...
but not such a great dad.
Never seemed
to pick a job...
that didn't involve
late nights
or long trips away, though.
Me and Aunt Susie
always kind of thought
he was, maybe,
cheating on our mom.
I'm sorry, buddy. I know how
much you worshiped him...
but there it is.
Surprise!
Happy birthday, Cousin Jake!
J-dog, it's great
you're coming
to spend a summer with us.
Wait till you see
the new boat.
Can't wait.
It's Aunt Susie.
Thought you might
wanna open this one.
It's from your grandpa.
Found it while
I was packing up.
I figured he meant to
give it to you someday.
Thanks.
To Jake, and the worlds
he has yet to discover.
My dearest Abe...
I hope this card
finds you well.
The children and I yearn
to hear your news.
I do hope you will
visit us again soon.
We should so love to see you.
With admiration...
Alma Peregrine.
H mm. Only two years ago.
I suppose it's possible
she could still be alive.
Right.
I could meet her.
Maybe even find out
what it was
Grandpa wanted me to know.
But what if
she's dead?
Dr. Golan...
we are very concerned
with Jake's state of mind
right now.
There's no way I'm putting
my life on hold
to take you to Wales.
Dad could take me.
And he can look at birds...
and work on his book.
It means you get a break.
As Dr. Golan said...
maybe I can move on.
Like, closure.
Having an opportunity
to see this children's home...
and separate fantasy
from reality...
may be helpful.
And at the very least...
a trip like this provides
a chance to...
say goodbye.
"Cairnholm.
Population of 92.
"Best known
for its proximity...
"to the final resting place
of the cruise liner Augusta...
"which sank in 1915.
"There is just one hotel..."
That's us.
Yeah. I hope there's bourbon.
Oh, wow!
Jake, check it out.
That's a peregrine falcon.
A peregrine,
like the headmistress?
Sure.
That's probably
where Grandpa came up
with that whole turning
into a bird thing.
Or maybe,
maybe that's really her!
Hey, Miss Peregrine.
It's me, Jake.
I'm Abe Portman's grandson.
Please don't crap on us.
Oh, my God.
Dad, I'm kidding.
What the... Hello?
Hello?
Anybody home?
Oh, hey.
Any idea where I'd find
the manager of this place?
That's me.
Sorry to keep you.
Just helping Uncle Oggie
to the loo.
Oh. Oh.
I'm Kev.
There's room upstairs.
Oh, great.
I'll be back in a bit.
Okay.
Kev's just getting
our suite ready.
Um, while we're waiting...
I thought maybe we could go
check out the beach.
I thought we would go
to the children's home.
Is the beach
where the birds nest?
I thought we could just
check it out real quick.
I could go to the home
by myself.
Then, you can really
take your time and enjoy it.
Come on, Jakey. You know
your mom would freak.
What if we can find
someone to take me?
Hey, dudes.
Dad. Don't.
Shh! I got this.
I was just wondering
if any of you guys...
might be interested
in taking my son here
to the other side
of the island.
So, what are your names?
I'm Worm.
This is MC Dirty D.
MC Dirty Bizniz.
I thought you changed it.
No.
No, you did, remember?
When Ruth said
"MC Dirty Bizniz"
made it sound like
you cacked your trousers.
Yeah, but she said
"Dirty D" sounded like
a personal
hygiene problem.
Wait. Are these, like,
nicknames, or...
Stage names. We're the
sickest rappers in Wales.
Go on, Worm. Show this
Yank how it's done.
What? Now?
I like to get wrecked
down the Priest Hole
Your dad's always here
'cause he's on the dole
Our rhymes are tight
Yet I make it look easy
Our beats are hot
like chicken jalfrezi
Oh, yeah, no.
It's good.
Should we take
the shortcut, D?
We'll get there quicker.
Take it from me.
What, down here?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Go.
This way?
What the...
Is this even the way
to the children's home?
Right through those trees.
No use crying
over a lost shoe, boy-o.
The children's home.
What happened to it?
A German air raid.
Bomb fell right on the roof.
September the 3rd, 1943.
Where did they go after?
The headmistress
and the children.
Not one survivor.
Poor little buggers.
And they were lovely, too.
Why didn't he tell us that
they all died?
He leaves to join the army,
and 3 months later,
everyone he knows
gets killed?
Not even Grandpa could turn
that into a bedtime story.
Well, no wonder he was
scared of being a dad...
being close to anyone.
Listen.
You need to talk about all
this with someone, buddy.
We should call Dr. Golan.
Certainly
some enjoyment today.
Er, do you mind
if I go hang out
with those
other kids today?
They asked.
Yeah? That's awesome.
Abe?
No!
You're Emma!
And the twins.
And Olive.
And Bronwyn.
And he's Millard.
Mm-hmm.
No, you're dead.
All of you,
you're all dead.
He's invisible,
but he's still dead.
None of us are dead.
Oh, my God. Am I dead?
No.
You called me Abe.
In the house. Why?
You looked like him.
Just for a moment,
before you started
screaming...
running away,
and concussing yourself.
Wait. What's happening?
We're waiting until
the coast is clear...
before we go
into the loop.
You never know
who might be watching.
Wait. Before we
go into what?
Please, Jake.
Miss Peregrine's waiting.
She saw you on the ferry.
She sent us to get you.
Hey!
Where do you think
you're going?
To my room.
I'm a guest here.
Does this look like
a hotel to you?
Yeah.
No. I've got a key.
Talk to the manager.
He'll tell you.
I'm the manager, boy.
He's American.
Maybe he's army?
Bollocks.
Listen to his accent.
It's terrible.
He's a spy.
What?
No, I'm not.
I'm a tourist.
I say we should get
the truth out of him
the old-fashioned way.
Get down!
Come on!
Jake, get on!
Come on! Get on, boy!
I can't believe you're real.
You're all real!
We have been trying
to tell you.
But I'm special, too.
What?
In the pub.
Olive, you saw.
Right? Everything
was flying and breaking.
And that was me!
I was doing it
with my mind.
No, that was me.
Millard?
Yeah.
Are you naked?
Oh.
I don't...
A bomb dropped on you
in 1943.
It is 1943.
September the 3rd, 1943.
All day, every day.
It's our loop.
Right on time.
Miss Peregrine.
Delighted to meet you.
I do hope I'm not going
to have the pub landlord
knocking on my door
with the police again.
I've had to kill them
twice this month.
It's been
terribly inconvenient.
Millard broke a few things.
That's all.
And Olive may have
started a tiny fire.
But they were going
to hurt Jake.
Look at you.
The last time dear Abe
sent me a photograph...
you were just a tiny tot.
Don't just stand there.
Come in.
Your tea's getting cold.
How did you know
about the pub?
You weigh approximately
109 pounds, correct?
I don't...
Bronwyn and the twins returned
6 minutes after you ran away.
I think I'm
missing something.
And quite apart
from the fact
that the perceived safety
of the pub...
makes it the most likely place
to which you would flee...
it would take you
18 minutes to run there.
Emma and Millard would have
been moments behind...
on the horse and trap,
traveling at 8.2 miles
per hour.
Factoring in some sort
of kerfuffle at the pub...
and the return journey
with your added weight...
you would arrive here
at 13 minutes past 4.
Now, then,
do you take sugar?
That'll do. Thank you, Olive.
Nobody enjoys
over-boiled tea.
Let me help you
with those, Enoch.
Don't bother. Wouldn't want
to interrupt your tea party.
I'm so sorry
for your loss, Jake.
You know, then.
I know if Abe were alive,
he would have told me
you were coming.
Shall we take
our tea outside?
Thank you.
Before he died,
he told me to find you.
There was something
he wanted me to know.
He said you could
explain everything.
That's absolutely true.
There are very few things
I can't explain.
We're what's known,
in common parlance,
as "peculiar."
51 seconds late, Fiona.
Sorry, Miss Peregrine.
How many carrots
do you need for supper?
Just one will do.
As I was saying,
some people are peculiar.
It's a recessive gene
carried down through families.
Yet, many generations
can pass
without a peculiar child
being born.
And alas, peculiars have been
persecuted through the ages.
Hence, we live
in places like this.
In Wales?
Anywhere will do
if you pick the right day.
That's fine now, Fiona.
You see, I'm a type of
peculiar called an Ymbryne.
That means I can...
Yeah, you turn into a bird.
I do. Yes.
But that's not very useful.
An Ymbryne's main skill
is the manipulation of time.
We choose a safe place,
a safe day...
and create a loop.
What do you mean?
A loop preserves
the last 24 hours.
Reset the loop, and the day
is yours to live in again.
Reset it daily...
and you can
stay there forever.
Entirely safe
from the outside world.
Right on time, Bronwyn.
Good girl.
And that's why we Ymbrynes
are charged with the care
of the young.
And no one ever gets older.
It's best for everyone
this way.
I assure you.
Every Ymbryne
commits herself...
to the creation and upkeep
of a place like this.
A home for peculiar children.
You wanna muck around?
Your bees.
Get it!
You met the twins.
This is Claire.
Millard, pass the ball.
We're playing together.
Millard you met.
Ugh. Come on!
And that's Hugh.
Stop cheating, Hugh.
Millard,
that's a foul again.
No, it wasn't. Ref?
If you two can't play soccer
without squabbling...
I do wish
you wouldn't play at all.
Do you know
what a referee is?
Good afternoon.
I'm Horace.
Delighted to meet you.
Ow!
Careful!
We sorely need
some new blood here.
Super shirt, by the way.
Thanks.
Try harder.
You know Emma, of course.
And I think that's everyone.
Didn't Bronwyn
have a brother?
Yes. Victor's upstairs.
Wait, where did Enoch
and Olive go?
Heaven knows.
Enoch's been off sulking ever
since we went out to get Jake.
Miss Peregrine, there's
a policeman at the door.
He says it's about the pub!
We'll discuss this
later, Emma.
It wasn't their fault.
Honestly, they were
just trying to help.
Hmm.
Thanks.
You're not as wet
as I thought.
She's not really gonna
kill anyone, is she?
Not if she can
talk her way out of it.
Would you help me
with something?
Enoch usually does it,
but like I said,
he's off sulking somewhere.
Is that because of me?
He's possessive.
So, what did you
need help with?
One of my daily chores.
Put the baby squirrel
back in the tree.
What baby squirrel?
That happens every day?
Like clockwork.
Now, would you mind tying
that rope around my waist?
Uh, yeah.
Right. Promise to
hold on tight.
I nearly messed that up.
Abe did, too, the first time.
This used to be his job.
Emma, I need to
tell you something.
He's dead.
I know.
Miss Peregrine guessed,
and she's always right.
It's okay.
I said goodbye to him
a long time ago.
Were you close?
I thought we were.
For a while.
But I suppose not.
Can I ask, was he like you?
He was like you, Jake.
I need to go
and change for supper.
Will you be dining with us?
I can't stay out late.
Supper's at 5:30.
Uh... That
is pretty early.
The fact we're not
all eight years old
seems to have eluded
Miss Peregrine.
You can borrow
some of Abe's clothes.
His room's in the attic.
Jake!
Come and meet Enoch properly.
You must feel
pretty out of place.
Don't worry.
I'm used to it.
No. I wasn't worried.
Some advice for you though,
man to man.
If you're thinking of staying
just because you like Emma...
don't bother.
You see, she swore off
romance decades ago...
when she got
her heart broken.
And she's never gonna
change her mind. So...
Enoch, I wasn't...
What are you doing?
Isn't he amazing?
What did you do?
This?
Jake, this isn't
even the fun part.
Do you want to see
the fun part?
They're like puppets.
Just do anything I tell them.
It's even more fun
with people.
You should have seen some of
the epic battles
they used to have...
at my parents'
funeral parlor.
You'll need a necktie.
So what did my grandpa do
when he was traveling?
Visited other loops.
Really? To do what?
Jake, there's some questions
that I can't answer,
all right?
So, it would be a lot easier
for me if you just...
stopped asking them.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Millard.
Go and put some clothes on.
Polite persons do not take
their supper in the nude.
All right. All right.
You can sit here, Jake.
Look at Enoch.
He's jealous.
Why would I be jealous?
Olive can go marry Jake,
for all I care.
Don't be mean, Enoch.
She doesn't want to.
She's just excited
to have a visitor.
Nobody is marrying anybody.
Now, eat up your food
before it gets cold.
Hugh!
Where's your net?
Hugh! You have to
stop doing this, Hugh.
Go away!
Must be very strange
for you, Jake.
Meeting your
grandfather's friends.
Visiting another century.
Are there spaceships
in your time, Jake?
Like the Flash Gordon books.
Now, now, Olive.
What did I say
about asking questions?
We don't discuss
the future here.
We enjoy living in the
good old here and now.
Claire, why aren't you eating?
She's embarrassed
in front of Jake.
Don't be. Please.
So, Jake,
what's your peculiarity?
Oh, I'm not peculiar.
And that, my friends,
is why he will not
be staying with us...
no matter how hard
we try to persuade him.
We've spoken about this.
Jake is just visiting.
He might want to stay.
Don't you want
to stay, Jake?
Tonight? Or...
Forever. You should
stay forever.
Why would he,
if he doesn't have to?
He can live out there,
grow older...
have a good time instead.
He'll leave, just like
his grandfather did.
Emma!
Excuse me.
Where's she going?
That wasn't nice, Enoch.
You know perfectly well
why Abe left us.
To join the army.
And then he met a lady,
and had a nice wedding cake...
and a lovely little baby.
Children.
I know you'd all
like a new friend...
but I'm sure Jake has plenty
of his own back in Florida.
I think you should
all get ready
for movie time
while I answer that.
But you always
let us stay for it.
Hello, this is Abe.
How is everyone?
Yours has extra
marshmallows, Jake.
Millard, put
some pajamas on.
It's
too hot in here.
Stop moaning.
Excuse me.
My grandpa
told me about this.
Horace projects
his dreams, right?
He used to listen
to the radio.
Gets tedious when you know
every word off by heart.
Splendid. I'll take it.
He dreams
about clothes mostly.
Delighted to meet you.
Super shirt, by the way.
When did he dream this?
Last night.
Some of his dreams
are prophetic.
But, mostly
they're about clothes.
Prophetic as in,
he can see into the future?
An Ymbryne. Who is she?
Miss Peregrine,
do you know her?
Don't be silly.
Horace must have just had a bad dream.
That's all.
Aw!
That's quite enough of that.
Thank you, Horace.
I should probably
get going.
You could stay the night,
if you wanted to.
Rather than walk home
alone in the dark.
But the island
is very safe, isn't it?
Of course!
I only meant the path
is dreadfully bumpy.
Jake could trip.
Perhaps you could show him
the shortcuts.
Should he ever need
to avoid bumps.
Won't you at least
stay to see the reset, Jake?
It's really
quite spectacular.
Yeah!
Stay, Jake!
Come on, Jake!
Run, rabbit, run, rabbit
Run, run, run
Don't give the farmer
his fun, fun, fun
He'll get by
without his rabbit pie
So run, rabbit, run, rabbit,
run, run, run
Run, rabbit, run, rabbit...
Bang, bang, bang, bang
goes the farmer's gun
Don't give the farmer
his fun, fun, fun
He'll get by
without his rabbit pie
That was fantastic.
What was that?
It was my phone.
It's been dead the whole time in the loop.
I guess now...
Your phone?
Yeah. Like a telephone.
You can call people...
send written messages.
Wait, you'll love this.
You can take a picture.
Press that, there. Yeah.
See?
What's wrong?
It's just funny to think
that one day, you'll grow up.
Like Abe did.
Get married, have children.
Grandchildren.
You might even show them
this photograph.
And I'll still be here.
Couldn't you leave
some day?
And live in the present,
if you wanted to?
No.
More than a few minutes
in your time
and the years
would catch up.
You would age?
I think it's the Ymbryne
from Horace's dream.
Are you sure
it's not just a bird?
I don't know,
wouldn't it change?
She can't.
Not if she's hurt.
I need to take her inside.
You should go.
Please don't say
anything else.
I hate goodbyes.
I'll come back tomorrow.
There's no hurry.
I'll be here forever.
Hey!
I've been all over
this damn island.
Where the hell were you?
Um, I was just
on my way back.
I'm sorry.
I lost track of time.
I was having a blast
with Worm and Dirty D.
Dirty D?
You know what?
This is good.
This is healthy.
You're making
weird friends...
and doing teenage stuff.
I think this is normal.
I'm sure Doctor Golan
will approve.
Hey, you.
American!
Get over here.
Oh, look.
There they are.
There's D-Bag
and Worm Man.
Did you do this?
What? No.
Of course not.
It wasn't us.
Listen, sir. I don't know
what happened here.
But my son and his friends
have been together all day.
Jake would never
do anything like this.
Bollocks!
We haven't seen him!
You paid us yesterday.
Why would we hang out
with him today for free?
Jake? Were you with
them or not?
No. I'm sorry.
But you don't seriously
think I could do this?
I think we're
done here, sir.
Can you pass on
a message for me?
Can you tell
Doctor Golan...
that if she hadn't encouraged
this cockamamie trip...
maybe my son wouldn't be
moping around all day
in a derelict house...
having a
goddamn breakdown!
Hello?
Dad, I'm not.
I'm fine.
No. You're not.
You're not fine, Jake.
Coming here was a
terrible, terrible idea.
Look, I'm sorry I lied.
I just wanted...
Just set your alarm
for 8:00 a.m.
I wanna get
to the beach early.
The rest of the time
we're stuck
on this craphole island...
we're sticking together.
Where are you going?
Downstairs for a drink.
Dear Miss Peregrine...
I don't wish to alarm you...
but one of my informants
sent me this.
It would appear that some
of Mr. Barron's group...
are in Blackpool, England.
If I recall...
Miss Avocet has a loop there.
Please warn her and suggest...
that she make a new one
right away...
well-hidden.
And take
the greatest care yourself.
With love, Abe.
January, 2016.
Who's ready
to hit the beach?
Ugh.
Oh, my...
Unbelievable.
Right in the middle
of a nesting area?
What kind of idiot
does that?
Actually, the main
nesting area is over there.
I can show you
if you'd like.
It's marvelous to meet
a fellow bird spotter.
John Lamont.
Franklin Portman.
This is my son, Jake.
John Lamont.
That's a hell of a camera
you got there.
Oh, thanks.
It's absolutely fantastic.
I'm here to do some snaps
for a book I'm writing.
So, you gentlemen here
on holiday?
Unfortunately,
her wings were flapping
as much as the bird's!
I think you fellas are
thinking of another kind
of bird.
So, you're not going
to the beach today?
What's the point?
If that guy is gonna
cover Cairnholm
in some big, glossy book...
no one's gonna even
wanna look at mine.
Might just have
a nice afternoon nap.
I don't suppose
you saw Uncle Oggie
on your travels
this morning, did you?
He's usually here by now.
I could go look for him.
You're not going anywhere.
Jake, you're back!
Come and play!
Oh!
I need to see
Miss Peregrine first.
Do you know where she is?
From the darkest days,
the Canadian army...
Jake. You're back.
How wonderful!
How's it doing?
Emma said it was an Ymbryne.
"She." Not "it."
Ymbrynes are
always female.
And Emma was quite correct.
This is Miss Avocet.
Her loop's in Blackpool.
England.
That was a
private letter, Jake.
Who is Mr. Barron?
Miss Peregrine,
if my Grandpa
was involved
with dangerous people...
I need to tell the police.
Police?
Are you implying Abe
died an unnatural death?
I found him in the woods...
with his eyes missing.
I'd say that was
pretty unnatural.
Unless essential, I don't
discuss unpleasant matters.
An Ymbryne's duty is to
protect children, Jake.
I'm not a child.
He wanted you
to tell me everything!
Oh. How frustrating
for you.
Between Miss Peregrine's
rules...
and my housemates' little
pact not to scare you off...
it's like no one's
telling you anything!
Why don't you, then?
It's not like
you want me here.
Enoch, you can't.
You promised.
Olive's right.
I do know someone
who can get away
with breaking rules though.
Want to meet him?
Enoch, don't
do this. Please!
You want to spend time
with me and Jake,
we can all play together.
That's what you said.
Here we all are.
Move, Olive.
If you're going
to be like that,
then I don't want
to be your friend.
Enoch, leave Victor alone.
It really upsets Bronwyn.
Stop fussing, Fiona.
Don't you think Jake
should meet everybody?
He's trying to frighten
you away, Jake.
He was always jealous of Abe.
And now he's jealous of you.
Come and play
with us instead.
I'd quite like
to meet Victor.
After you.
Hello, Victor.
I'm Jake.
I'm sorry to disturb...
Yeah, he can't hear you.
Hello, Jake. I'm Victor.
Do you want to know
what killed me?
There you are.
Is Enoch with you?
It's time for
our daily walk.
Emma, who killed Victor?
Was it the people
with the white eyes?
I asked you
not to ask questions.
I saw one the night
my grandpa died.
A man.
If it really was one,
you have to
tell Miss Peregrine.
Could you recognize him
from a photograph?
Do you have one?
Come on. There's somewhere
I go to be alone.
I have things there.
Is this the place?
No. This is how we get there.
Oh! Emma! Your shoes!
Lead shoes!
Welcome to my
secret hideout.
How did you...
Air.
It's my peculiarity.
It does what I want.
Jake...
before your
grandfather retired...
he asked me
to keep this safe.
This is my grandpa's
old map.
It shows you
where the loops are.
That's him!
That's the man I saw.
Who is he?
That's Barron.
He's the leader.
The leader of what?
Who are these people?
Bad people. Bad peculiars.
Abe dedicated his life
to hunting them down.
These are the ones
he never found.
What do you mean, hunting?
They raided loops.
Whole homes full of children
left for dead.
Abe took lives
to save lives.
He only retired when you were
born to protect you.
From what?
If I tell you the rest,
you have to promise
not to run away.
Jake, you belong here.
You know I don't.
I'm not like you.
I'm just ordinary.
No, you're not.
Jake...
only a peculiar
can enter a time loop.
No. That can't be right.
I would know.
Fine.
Then I'll show you
something else.
Hurry. You'll miss it.
Ymbrynes usually pick the
perfect day to create a loop.
But Miss Peregrine had to
make this one in a rush.
Why?
Because the Germans were about
to drop a bomb on the house.
The point is...
September the 3rd, 1943
wasn't perfect.
The thing that killed
Victor came back.
Wait! Watch out!
You'll put her off!
You can see it, can't you?
No one else can.
It's invisible, Jake.
That was Abe's
greatest gift of all.
He could see the monsters.
We call them Hollowgast.
Hollows for short.
My grandpa told me about
people who turn into monsters.
Is that what they are?
I will explain
everything, Jake.
I fear it's my duty now,
considering.
But you should know
that in doing so,
I'm breaking
a solemn promise.
I knew you were peculiar
when you were born.
But your grandfather forbid
me to tell you anything.
His dearest wish was for you
to have an ordinary childhood.
I definitely had that.
He intended to tell you the
truth when you turned 18.
He hoped his bedtime stories
would pave the way.
Ah.
Here's my book.
Many years ago...
a splinter faction emerged
among our people.
Disaffected peculiars
tired of living in loops.
That's Mr. Barron.
He believed that
by harnessing the essence
of an Ymbryne's powers...
he and his cronies
could gain immortality...
and be able
to live outside loops.
He devised an experiment.
He kidnapped an Ymbryne...
not knowing or caring
whether she would survive
the experiment.
But the fate of Barron
and his group
was more horrifying still.
Why didn't Barron
turn into one?
He did.
But years later...
he found a way
to reverse the effects.
To regain humanity.
They had become not
immortal gods, but Hollows.
Invisible beasts, dangerous...
cold-blooded, deadly.
Remember I told you
they raided loops?
This is why.
Barron
discovered that by consuming
the eyes of other peculiars...
especially children...
he began to change.
Consume enough, and a Hollow
can fully regain
its human form.
Bon appetit.
Just as Barron
and some of his friends did.
Mmm.
The rest of them
are stuck as Hollows.
Are you saying
that Barron ate my grand...
He needs
no more eyes himself.
But I fear he led a Hollow
to your grandfather. Yes.
After the first attacks
on loops...
we all got better at hiding,
making new loops,
keeping our
whereabouts secret.
The Hollows grow more
desperate every year...
and Barron wishes
to help his friends.
Miss Peregrine, come quickly.
Miss Avocet's awake.
And suddenly,
I flew into it again...
Bang! Bang!
I couldn't see anything.
Oh, Miss Peregrine.
They found my new loop.
The children.
I tried to save them...
but there were
so many Hollows.
I don't know how I escaped.
You're safe now.
None of us are safe.
They set up the machine
in my loop.
They put it in the cellars
at Blackpool Tower.
They're still there.
Their machine?
The experiment.
They intend to do it again.
This time, he's using
more Ymbrynes.
He still wants
to be immortal.
Do Hollows
only attack peculiars?
Of course not.
They're monsters, Jake.
They'll slaughter anything
in their path.
Some sheep on the island
were killed.
You don't think they're here
already, do you?
Have you seen anyone
with white eyes?
I'm sorry, children.
We can't remain here.
What?
We'll leave on the first ferry
off the island tomorrow.
Pack anything
of importance.
Then it's sandwiches
and early to bed.
Are we leaving for good?
When are we coming back?
Never.
If Miss Peregrine's
not here
to reset the loop
tomorrow night...
the house gets bombed.
But our house.
Don't cry.
Miss Peregrine will find you
another lovely house,
somewhere else.
Once this loop closes,
that's it.
I can't get back
to my own time.
You didn't seem
very happy there.
I can't just leave!
I have a family!
And you felt ordinary.
Like, nothing you do
changes anything!
Now you have a chance
to do something
that changes everything!
Jake, we're in danger.
And you're the only one
who can see the Hollows.
Yeah, see them, sure.
But I'm not my grandpa!
I'm not, and I can't fight.
I can't kill somebody.
There's only one reason
that I'd stay here...
Please.
Just go.
Jake? Jakey,
there you are.
Thank God!
When I heard they found
a body, I freaked.
Are there stray dogs
around here?
What you talking about?
It's like...
when they find
an injured animal,
they go for
the soft parts first.
Same thing happened
to my father.
The police are
on their way.
Look, Dad. I've gotta go.
What? No.
You don't, Jake.
If this wasn't an accident,
there's a lunatic
on the island.
I've known everyone on
this island my whole life.
Except you, and him.
And he's been in the pub
all afternoon.
So have I.
I was sleeping.
What
about the blind fellow?
I assumed he was blind.
Gentleman with
the dark glasses...
arrived on
the same ferry as me?
I kept seeing him around.
Jake!
Jake! Wait!
Is your son all right?
No.
He has mental
health issues.
I can't go.
Let me.
I run 5-Ks all the time.
Hello?
Is that you, young man?
You came through...
You're peculiar?
Oh, yes.
And I'm extremely
grateful to you.
Terribly hard to find loops
these days.
So, you followed me from
the beach on purpose?
Oh, no.
I've been following you
much further than that.
Doctor Golan?
Sometimes.
When it suits me.
The breadth
of my peculiarity...
is purely limited
by my imagination.
The only thing
I can't change...
is my eyes.
Mr. Barron. How do you do?
I saw you
at your grandfather's.
I was hoping to get
Miss Peregrine's
address from him.
But, alas,
my traveling companion
got to him before I did.
As you know...
there's just no stopping
a hungry Hollowgast!
Speaking of
my traveling companion...
he's coming.
Believe me
when I say to you...
you don't want to be here...
when he arrives.
So, let's be on our way.
Shall we?
Excuse me.
Wait for me.
I mustn't
forget our calendar.
Could you fetch it
from the parlor
please, Miss Avocet?
Go and help the others.
Miss Peregrine,
what a pleasure
to meet you at last!
May we come in?
Children!
Would you make your way
down the stairs, please?
I give the orders
in this house, Mr. Barron.
Not today.
You should know that Jake
has served his purpose.
If you value his life,
I suggest
everyone does
as they're told.
Children!
Shush!
No one tells my children
what to do!
Children...
come down here, please.
Miss Peregrine...
I thought I told you
to be quiet.
Children...
for Jake's safety...
we're going to do
what Mr. Barron asks.
He wishes
to take me with him
to his rendezvous
in Blackpool.
So, for his protection...
he'd like me
to assume bird form,
preferably caged.
He'd like you to make your
way into a lockable room,
such as the parlor...
as he won't release Jake
if he fears
an attack could be mounted
upon him...
once he loses his leverage.
Correct, Mr. Barron?
You're sacrificing
yourself and all of us...
for Jake?
Mr. Barron travels
with a Hollow, Enoch.
Once it arrives here,
we're all dead.
Enoch. Only Jake
can see them.
She means
he's our only hope.
It's been my privilege...
to care for you all.
Goodbye, my children.
Now let him go.
Promise me one thing, Jake.
That you will try
to look after them all.
I promise.
Boo!
It's getting dark.
You won't even be able
to see their shadows.
We have to stay inside.
It's the only place
we stand a chance.
He's quite right.
Now, where does
Miss Peregrine keep
her weapon?
In there. Let's go.
Now, all right, children.
Make sure all the doors
are locked,
and the windows are latched.
Everything must be
sealed up tight. Now quickly.
Quickly! Go!
Here.
Jake, I think tonight,
you better answer that.
Okay.
Hello?
Hello, this is Abe.
Who's that?
You don't know me yet.
I'm Jake.
Ah, you're new. Welcome
to the family, Jake.
Now, I can't talk long...
so just tell Miss Peregrine...
I'm at the air base,
and I'm fine.
I just wanted to say
that I miss you...
and if I disappointed you...
I'm sorry.
You're the best grandpa
in the world.
Quickly.
Fiona.
Got it.
Miss Avocet.
Now, children.
Now that you're all here,
there's a few rules.
Your primary job
is to stay safe.
Leave the Hollow to me.
I don't want to see
any heroics.
Now those of you
with garden tools...
I must insist that you...
No, Enoch. Get back!
Whoa!
Go. Get to the attic!
Come on!
Take her.
Go. Get out!
Olive, come on!
Okay.
All right, uh...
Crap! It's almost reset!
Fiona, is there anything
you can do with that tree?
- Yes.
- Be careful.
We're going
through the windows.
Let's go! Quickly!
Come on!
Claire, come on down.
Be careful.
Go, Fiona!
Let's go!
Was that...
The loop closing.
It's gone.
I'm sorry, Jake.
What do we do now?
Is there any sign of Barron
and Miss Peregrine?
Gone. Barron must have
had a boat.
We have to go after them.
We know he's taking her
to Blackpool.
But Blackpool
is miles away.
The next ferry
doesn't go for hours.
We'll never make it in time.
Not unless
we go by boat, too.
So, there's a loop
here in Blackpool.
It's only six months old.
January 11th, 2016.
With Miss Avocet gone,
it can't be reset.
Won't the loop close?
Then it's back to real time.
Jake, you know what
this means, don't you?
You're gonna die.
That's not what I mean.
We have to get
to our own time,
but you don't.
You can continue
to live in 2016.
But why would I do that?
If we kill Barron...
he'll be gone,
but time will carry on.
He won't go to Florida...
Abe won't die,
and you can go home.
I could see my grandpa.
Listen, I can explain
everything to them.
I can persuade them to take
me to the island and...
Wait, will you
still be there?
Our old loop's gone for good.
We wouldn't see
each other again.
I thought you wanted me
to stay.
I know you'll choose Abe.
If I minded,
I wouldn't have told you.
So, have you found
Miss Avocet's
loop on the map yet?
It's here. But it's new.
She made it early this year.
That's my year.
If we don't get out
before it closes,
we're stuck
in January 2016.
Great.
Time catches up
with all of us,
we all die,
except you. Plan?
The loop closes at 4:30.
That means
we need to get in,
rescue the Ymbrynes
and then get out.
Yeah, if we're not
already dead.
Miss Avocet said the machine
is in the cellar
of the Blackpool Tower
building.
That means we will be
indoors... with Hollows.
No, we won't.
I've got a plan.
But I'm gonna need your help.
This can't be it,
can it?
Loop entrances
can be anywhere.
The one in London's
in a subway tunnel.
Are you sure this is it?
I think so.
Millard, there's something
I need you to do first.
All right. I know.
Look. There's the tower.
It's not far.
Easy for you to say.
I'm freezing.
Ready?
All of the doors
to the cellar are locked.
The only way to reach the
Ymbrynes is through there.
It's backstage.
How many Hollows
can you see?
Four. That's good news.
I think you and I have
a very different definition
of good news.
It means Barron's other
friends haven't arrived yet.
So they haven't started
the experiment.
We're not too late.
Okay, Emma.
You ready?
You know what to say.
Here, Jake.
Our brethren should be
joining us momentarily.
- This is a day to...
- Hey!
You down there!
We killed your Hollow friend,
Mr. Barron.
And now we've come
for Miss Peregrine.
Bring her
and all the other Ymbrynes
to the end of the pier
in five minutes...
or face the consequences.
These children must be
as insane as their
headmistress.
Still, the Hollows
will be glad of a feed.
Where are you?
I know you're in here
somewhere!
A-ha!
Good. Listen to me.
I want you to follow
Mr. Archer and Mr. Clark.
They're going to take you
down to the pier...
for a little afternoon tea.
Mr. Archer, Mr. Clark...
gather the Hollows
and take them to the pier.
Those children
killed Malthus?
Barron's had it in
for Malthus
ever since he killed
Abe Portman.
I tracked Abe Portman
for months.
All I needed
was a few minutes...
to get the location of Miss
Peregrine's loop from him.
But no!
Malthus couldn't wait.
Instead...
I had to masquerade
as a psychiatrist...
for three weeks...
in Florida!
Have you ever
been to Florida?
Did I not tell you to
gather the Hollows?
What if it's a trap?
Of course, it is, Miss Edwards.
But what of it?
A couple of children
against four Hollows.
Let's get this over with.
Jake, I'm stuck!
Hurry up!
Come on.
Watch out!
They're coming!
Let's go.
Enoch. Now!
Go! Now!
Starting to see them now.
Phase two.
Emma, go.
Don't just stand there.
Get them!
All right. Good job, guys.
It's time for step two.
Save Miss Peregrine!
That's sort of step three.
First, we've got to deal
with Barron.
Come on.
They should've been
back by now.
I said it was a trap.
If that's true...
perhaps we should
move the Ymbrynes now.
You're not serious?
Do I not look serious?
Do I not look like a man
who has searched the globe...
looking for just
one more eye to eat...
in hopes of regaining
sufficient humanity...
to return to his research?
A man who's spent years
hunting Ymbrynes...
in preparation
for this night...
and two, no, three days,
in Wales...
pretending to look at birds!
I assure you...
I will not stand idly by...
to see my destiny derailed.
Hugh, do it now!
Come back here!
Get them!
Go. Get down!
You think you can
stand in my way?
You, Jake,
content to age and die...
as if you had not the gift
of peculiarity at all?
I am a higher being.
I hold the secret
to eternal life!
Sorry to interrupt.
What the...
Bronwyn.
Huh!
You missed me again, Jake.
I take it accuracy
is not your peculiarity.
Abe was
a much worthier adversary.
Don't let him
get to the birds.
Ooh. Hmm.
You must put me
in contact with your tailor.
Ymbrynes, Ymbrynes!
Here I come!
Cold?
Wait till the blood
freezes in your veins.
Hey!
That was your attempt to
rescue your friend, was it?
Jake.
I'll hold him off
as long as I can.
When are you
going to realize
you are a terrible shot
with that thing.
Get the others. I'll meet
you at the loop entrance.
Let's get you out.
Eventually...
you're going to
run out of breath.
And it'll all be over!
Death for your beloved
Jake and Miss Peregrine...
everlasting life for me!
Ew!
And a mint for you.
Olive.
I'm so sorry, Olive.
All these years,
I never appreciated you.
I didn't see how lucky I was.
I got so used to having
you there, I never realized...
You never realized what?
Find your children.
Create new loops.
So, Jake...
I see you've inherited your
grandfather's peculiarity.
You're just as annoying
as he was.
Speaking of Abe...
if you should see him
in the afterlife...
give him my regards.
Please. We can't risk him
taking you again.
Enoch! Where
are the others?
They're safe. Olive is leading
them back to the Ghost Train.
Jake needs us.
Barron's too strong.
You've lost Miss Peregrine.
You've lost everything.
It's over.
Jake?
Emma?
No, wait. Look. That's not me.
It's Barron.
Don't listen to him.
He's Barron.
No, I'm Jake.
That's Barron.
I've got a better shot
than Jake.
So, neither of you move
until we sort this.
Listen to me. I'm Jake.
I grew up in Florida and
I wanted to be an explorer.
I thought nothing would ever
change because I was ordinary.
That's Jake. Get Barron.
No. Look.
I told him all of this.
She was my psychiatrist.
Look, you deal with him.
I'll go find Miss Peregrine.
Wait.
Look, I can prove
that I'm me...
because I'm not ordinary.
I can do something
no one else can
I can see the monsters.
No, wait. It's me!
Enoch!
We need to go.
The loop is closing.
Yeah.
Those of us who are leaving.
Emma.
You love your grandfather.
There's nothing
more to explain.
No, I promised Miss Peregrine
I'd look after you all.
And with her injured,
and you without a loop...
She'll recover.
Until then,
we'll be in 1943.
We'll only age
one day at a time.
Like normal people.
Which can be no bad thing.
What about the Hollows?
As long as they're out there,
you're not safe.
We don't need you
to make us feel safe, Jake.
Because you made us feel brave.
And that's even better.
Come on, guys.
Let's go.
Tygrysku.
And then we said goodbye...
and the loop closed.
I was so scared that
you wouldn't be here.
That I'd never see you again.
I'm safe.
Oh.
Let me give you
your birthday present.
Grandpa,
my birthday isn't for months.
For your travels.
Go to her, Jake.
You have the map.
You can get back to 1943.
No. Even so,
they took a boat.
I don't know where they are.
But you know where they were.
You have no idea how long
it took me to get here.
The closest loop
was in the California desert.
I used it to get to
the Tokyo loop.
And that led me to the nearest
loop back in 1942...
where I wound up
joining the Navy.
Don't ask.
Then I spent two months
in London trying to...
Ready for full speed ahead!
I tried to leave it all
behind me
But I woke up
And there they were beside me
And I don't believe it
But I guess it's true
Some feelings,
they can travel, too
Oh, there it is again
Sitting on my chest
Makes it hard to
catch my breath
I scramble
for the light of change
You're always on my mind
And I never minded
being on my own
Then something broke in me
and I wanted to go home
To be where you are
But even closer to you
You seem so very far
And now I'm reaching out
with every note I sing
And I hope it gets to you
on some Pacific wind
Wraps itself around you
and whispers in your ear
Tells you that I miss you
and I wish that you were here
And if I stay home
I don't know
There'll be so much
that I'll have to let go
You disappear
in all the time
But I still see you
in the light
For you, the shadows fight
And it's beautiful but there's
that tug in the sight
I must stop time traveling
You're always on my mind
And I never minded
being on my own
Then something broke in me
and I wanted to go home
To be where you are
But even closer to you
You seem so very far
And now I'm reaching out
with every note I sing
And I hope it gets to you
on some Pacific wind
Wraps itself around you
and whispers in your ear
Tells you that I miss you
and I wish that you were here
We all need something
watching over us
Be it the falcons, the
clouds or the crows
And then the sea swept in
and left us all speechless
Speechless
And I never minded
being on my own
Then something broke in me
and I wanted to go home
To be where you are
But even closer to you
You seem so very far
And now I'm reaching out
with every note I sing
And I hope it gets to you
on some Pacific wind
Wraps itself around you
and whispers in your ear
Tells you that I miss you and
I wish that you were here