In the time of the Great Sea pirate
The oceans are filled with men with ambitions for wealth, fame and power
It's a dream for a pirate
But some of them just like to plunder
For the weak these are times of endless persecution
Despite being under the jurisdiction of a world government the navy was powerless to protect the weak
So who can they rely on and what can they do to be saved?
We really don't have a choice no one cares about people like us
All I can do is cry...
That's what everyone says. Pirates are bad guys. And worse...
I'm so hungry
What are we supposed to do when the pirates have taken everything
Yeah, it's all because of the pirates
All because those selfish brutes took our joy
Do you understand now?
I'm begging you to do something about our unfortunate situation, okay
Only you only you can help us
I beg you
You're the only one who can help us
Just you
Please, please, please
I know, I know
I will create a new era for you that will make us all happy
Where are our seats?
I'd like to buy some peripheral products
What a long dragon
I have to go to the bathroom later. Oh, my God, your seat has food
Yeah because it's a platinum ticket
There must be a lot of people here
Because it was Uta's first time singing live in front of fans
Until now, we've only seen her in the telephony bug
To see Uta live in such a beautiful place, I really...
Mermaids are coming. It looks like it's gonna be fun. But why are we dressed like this
It's to make her sing better and then someone in costume can get these
I see
I'm looking forward to it
After all, she's the most loved person in the world right now
Is she really that great?
As the King of Souls, I don't normally say that
But the songs she sings really seem from another world
Uta, Uta, I love...
That's boring. What?
Damn swordsman You come back here and say it again if you dare and I'll fry you till you're juicy
Try it on me, Curly
Here we go
The concert started with Luffy
"We choose our own future."
"Try a new path."
"If I change the world..."
"Say goodbye to all those who oppose us."
"No one has the power to stop the change that music can bring."
"You can't stop the magic."
"Close your eyes and you can see the future right in front of you."
"Every word I sing leads you closer to your destiny."
"When you get there don't let go."
"If you want to play a real game, untie the chains."
"When the melody is strung we are walking on a tight rope."
"Don't want to cry don't want to try to forget"
"Let me live in this dream."
"I want to be free."
"I want to be free"
"And then embrace the new era."
"I know we can do this."
"Create a new world."
"We choose our own future."
"Try to take a new path."
"If I change the world"
"This infinite music can be transformative."
"Let the message in the song"
"Go further."
"This dream will come true."
"I believe you"
"Say goodbye to everything that's holding you down."
"Let colorful music take you away from reality."
"We have to move on."
"Close your eyes, hold my hand and let's run."
"We don't need to live like this. I know we can do better."
"I sing for freedom."
"If you want to play a real game, untie the chains."
"Let the melody light the way for new vistas."
"Don't want to cry don't want to try to forget"
"Let me live in this dream."
"I want to be free"
"And then embrace the new era."
"I know we can do this."
"Create a new world."
"We choose our own future"
"Try a new path."
"If I change the world"
"This infinite music can be transformative."
"Let the message in the song"
"Go further."
"This is the new era."
'This is the new era'
Hi, it's nice to finally meet you. I'm Uta
I'm sorry I'm a little moved
Uta we love you Uta we love you
Uta loves you...
Everybody, let's play together today
Are you guys ready?
Ready to go
Wealth and fame will be ours if we can kidnap the star Sorry Uta
Uta, Uta
Feeding Luffy
What? Did he try to kidnap her too?
Oh, it's you
Uta, are you right
It's me. Who is it?
Is it Luffy?
Long time no see Uta Luffy
That straw hat...
Isn't he the fifth starbelt on the sea?
Really? How could Uta be friends with a sea pirate?
Does Luffy know Uta?
If that guy really knew me at least he introduced me to Uta
Why are you friends with Princess Uta?
Why?
That's because she's Shanks's daughter
Isn't Shanks just...
One of the four Kings of a district evil villain?
I remember it a long time ago
He's the same seafarer who attacked Eligia
uttar
I was wondering what to do when I heard the concert was in Eligia...
You mean the legend
Yeah, but I didn't think the bigger news would get out
What do you want?
The fourth sea emperor, the red-headed Shanks, had a daughter
If that's true you're a redhead's biggest weakness
If we turn you over to some other powerful Hai Fu, we'll make a lot of money
So it's a shame that today's concert has been canceled
Hot air fist
Come out
That girl is ours now
Are you... Which branch branch?
I'm Borichun from BIG MOM, The Pirates
Who was standing next to her
I'm BIG MOM Charlotte Lingling's fourth son. Owen looks fun. Let me join in
Actually, I just came by to see what's going on and what's so interesting about this place
Uta, I'm sorry I have to take you home to make a letter for Mom
Wait a minute
it doesn't matter
Hey, you bastards are gonna have to beat me if you're gonna take Uta
We can't let these bastards ruin that beautiful stage
It's finally getting more interesting
Don't underestimate our ice Mother pirates
The song of blowing snow cut
Jellyfish fist
What a shame
The concert just started
Come and protect Uta
Rubber machine gun
Spider flower
Come on
Okay, time out Luffy and everyone thanks for protecting me but no more fighting
Now that you're all my fans, you should get along and enjoy the concert
But Princess Uta these men tried to kidnap you did you know that
And people like you don't listen to you
If we want something we will not fight for it or get it back. We are pirates
All right, Pirates
I forgive you for the bad things you've done
So does everyone else stop being a bad sea pirate and join me in making the world a better place
With my song everyone can live in peace and be happy
There is no such thing as peace in this world or I'll tear the face off this stupid kid
You don't mess with her. She's my prize
Guys, aren't you here to enjoy my music?
Don't forget we're pirates
We got more important things to do first than your song
We rarely come here to see a concert
To hurt our feelings and Uta's feelings like that
Too bad then let me write a song
"You don't need to worry from now on."
"There's no need to fret.""
"Your dream is our dream is what each and every one of you wants."
"As soon as you start singing your heart will become as clear as the sky."
"Don't worry. "
"I am the strongest"
"My Song"
"Makes the birds fly high in the sky. "
"Even the clothes that flutter in the wind."
"Rock like a dancer too."
"Your voice"
"Let me rejoice."
"If you accidentally get hurt."
"Come on, come on, let me protect you."
"A new landscape that I've never seen before."
"We can definitely see it."
"If you want to talk about why."
"Well, just because we're alive."
"Come on, let's hold hands."
"Go where the light shines."
"Everybody's dream."
"It is my happiness."
"Not anywhere."
"Only you have it."
"That softness"
"Make me stronger."
"I'm the strongest when you're with me"
Guys those bad pirates have turned into a song
It's safe now so don't worry
Yeah, well, they may be father and daughter but Shanks and Uta are different
That's great
You're getting so tough, Uta
I wonder if she ate some demon fruit
I don't know. I've never heard of it
What is this?
What are you doing We're going back
I have some good news for you
I used to rely on the telephony bug all the time and it made me feel tired
The live stream will be over soon but this time the concert is endless and it will go on forever
what
Yeah, it means I can be with you forever
For those of you watching and those of you watching let's keep having fun
That's impressive.
She's going ahead with her own concert
That's amazing
Uta...
One more thing and this is very important
The entire Navy and the governments of the world ask you not to interfere with my concert
Everyone is looking for fun and fun and you'd better be prepared if you go overboard
I am Uta who will create a new era and I will make people happy with my songs
All right, our next song
Redhead actually has a daughter as Cipher Pol reports
A new enemy has emerged against the age of the Great Sea pirate
It's complicated because a lot of people are supportive of her
We need to kill this revolution before it's too late
Is that girl really Friend's daughter
The presence of Tol Musica is also worrying
If it wakes up again be prepared we may not be able to defeat it
Yeah, the authorities have decided to arrest Uta and she's dangerous
It's weird that the whole world is watching when she's just a girl
Hey, are you underestimating her
She's on the Island of Eligia Music
That's where Tot Musica was sealed long ago
So how many people are you going to send
How many ships do we have right now to get to Eligia?
Thirty ships
Take all the companies and teams and send out all the ships
If the phone bug can't use the flagship command will use the flag signal to send out the signal thin code 044 every ship should know
Captain turn around follow the signal and cooperate with the others Don't rush but be prepared don't be lazy turn around quickly
The airflow meter measures a level 4 breeze with long waves on the water and lots of white waves
Attention Every ship Every ship must assemble their gunners and check every cannon
Make sure there are no cracks in the cannon and make sure there are no holes in the ignition and check the wheels
No moving boats were detected in the vicinity
There are no obstacles in sight and every boat is in perfect condition and ready to sail
Are you hungry?
Let me cook the good food and the fun stuff
That's impressive.
Can I really do this?
Of course,
Guys here you can eat anything you want and sing and dance and play with me whenever you want, okay
It's like a dream...
Every dream will come true if you stay with me and there's nothing here that scares you
The new era is the best!
She's more capable than we thought. Are we underestimating her
Mom Mom is more than just ability turns out she is the daughter of red hair
We're gonna get her
And those straw hat assholes are gonna hate it too and I'd love to see them beat me
Let me go to Eligia
I can't just lose my sister and stand by
This place is a chef's paradise
If you ask Uta, she might still be able to make wine
Yeah, Uta has access to unlimited treasure
What kind of power is that
She's pretty strong for a demon fruit user
Yeah, I've never heard of anyone with that kind of invincibility
Luffy, aren't you Uta's friend or do you know something?
She has always been a good singer
what
Someone may have given Uta this ability
Maybe that person is the god of music...
Hey, Luffy, did you guys have a good time
Very happy Princess Uta
You have so many rare ingredients and this place is heaven
It's so much fun here
I'm glad Luffy's friends are so happy
Hello? Is everyone here
Yes.
If you believe me, this hat is...
I'm not lying to you
Luffy, let's have a race
You can't beat me right now
What are you talking about that I've needed a meeting 83 times
Are you wrong? I'm the one who won 183 in a row
The two views are completely different
What competition?
Luffy and I used to have all kinds of competitions like knife throwing and arm wrestling and all that
Come on and make this the event of the day
The fastest chicken eater wins
Oh, I miss this and what else
Don't worry. I'm ready
Come on, get in position
start
Wow, thank you.
Uta won. She won
Not fair Uta
Do not fall into the sea
By the way, Luffy ate the devil fruit, didn't he? I'm sorry
You just broke the rules. Do it again
There you go again with the sore loser
I won, so you're gonna tell me where Shanks is
I don't know
So what happened to your straw hat and now I'm keeping it
Hey, how do you two know each other?
That's when she came to Faucha with Shanks and the others
Fosha Village is your hometown, isn't it, Luffy
Yes.
12 years ago...
Uta, you're daydreaming again
Come on over
Don't be boring. Let's have a race
You are so childish. What are you competing against
Chicken Eating Contest
wang
Whoever eats the fastest wins, okay
good
This is too dangerous for you two to fight
No way.
Uta Luffy
Let them compete
It was an important match for both of them
Come on
To prepare
Three two one
What are they competing for
Let's see who turns out to be a great sea pirate
Will Luffy win
You can have my juice. Yes, thank you
luffy
I can't believe you fell for the same trick again
Are you okay?
The competition... The game is not over yet
There you go again with the sore loser
You cheated you're supposed to be the sore loser
I'm a sea pirate. I'm not cheating. You're just a kid letting your guard down in a fair game
Shanks doesn't even think you're a pirate yet
Shut up. I'm Shanks 'daughter
Unlike you, I've gone on many adventures with him on boats and I'm in a different league than you
No, it is
Then come and fight me like a sea pirate
Sure.
That's enough of you two
You hit a child with a knife that's against the rules of sea thieving Shanks
Silly boy this is called love deep responsibility
You don't get love when it's a knife
Do you really love me
I love you, too, Shanks
Shanks
You two don't look around me and neither do Uta and Luffy
Why do you call your father Shanks
He's my dad but he's also my captain and he's cool, right
Now that I won Luffy today I'm in a good mood so I'm gonna sing a song
Shanks, I'm going out to sea
We don't need violent kids like you
Then why does Uta get to go
She'll take care of our ship while we're fighting but you can't
Yes.
I'm Gojiuta from the Red-headed One Pirates
I am a girl who makes music for a new era where all people can enjoy freedom
All right, it's time to welcome our Goliath
"Where is this wind coming from and where is it taking us?"
"I looked to the sky for answers but it didn't answer me."
"Where is this song that I'm singing going to go?"
"I try to find the answer inside."
"Once more we are bravely heading out into the unknown sea."
"I have only one wish"
Good enough for me to sing
Yeah, go ahead and sing. Yeah
Now that I think about it, it's like you just disappeared
Suddenly? What happened?
If I remember correctly
I waited for Shanks and the others every single time
But one day...
Welcome back. Do you have any adventure stories to share today?
What's wrong with you guys?
You know what? I'll ask Uta
Uta?
I want to hear about your adventures
Where are you, Uta
Where is Shanks-uta
Did something happen to Uta?
Don't worry Luffy Uta left our ship to become a singer
And just like that...
So Uta why don't you want to be a pirate?
You used to love red-headed One pirate so much
Instead of being a pirate I just decided to be a singer!
Look, I've got fans all over the world in two years
What about you, Luffy? What are you doing now?
Do you have to ask? I'm a sea pirate
To a sea pirate
Yeah, I want to be One Piece
Don't be a sea pirate, Luffy
Let's live happily here together
All of your friends are my fans
It would be fun if we were all together
Wait a minute. Are you listening? Luffy
Uta It's nice to see you again and I'm full so I'm going back to the Thousand SUNS to sleep now
You look like you're doing what you want
I'm happy for you. Goodbye
I won't let you go
Luffy and all of you must stay here forever and be happy with me
What are you talking about, shorty
Uta we love your music but we can't stay here forever
Her beauty
Guys, I found some more pirates. What am I supposed to do?
Uta...
Good!
Let me defeat these pirates for your sake
I don't care if she's a friend of Luffy's that's too much freedom
What are these things
There are more and more of them
Tang Cao Wa is boxing
Sore fingers
luffy
You shouldn't be a sea pirate
If you're my friend, give up being a sea pirate
What are you talking about?
I gave it up. It was boring
I have no reason to fight you
I'm gonna keep fighting even if you don't do anything
Six rounds of flowers. Slap in the face
Stop playing uta
"Sad memories are like passing through sorrow."
"Can't let go of the resentment and the gloom in my heart."
"Because of him."
"You have no idea, do you? The heartbreaking loneliness."
"Now is the time to unbind."
"Anger, right now."
"Blow these bad guys out of the sky. This is the punishment of love. I don't want to sleep anymore."
"There's no more sadness, there's no more sadness."
"Yeah, anger. Right now."
"Kick the bad guy in the air. That's the punishment of love. I don't want to sleep anymore."
"Don't feel lonely no lonely backlight ah"
What the hell are you doing Let go of me
Luffy can't be One Piece
Hey, guys, what do you think about pirates
My city was destroyed by pirates
My husband was killed by a pirate
Give me back my mother
Don't let a pirate drive away a pirate
Princess Luffy Uta did none of those things
Uta, my friend
You stay away from Uta you pirates
You are a demon fruit user who will weaken in the sea and we will not fear you
Hey, no.
We're screwed.
Wait a minute
It's gonna be okay. Let's just see what happens, okay
Ball of protection
Lomeo
Uta is really running wild and I don't think we can beat her
I haven't... Lose,
There you go again with the sore loser
They're gone. Where did they go? The pirate escaped
There are even hidden pirates
What? Where are we?
Are you a Uta fan too, Trafalgar?
No, I'm just going along
I'm here to keep paypal company
Excuse me
Thank you very much!
This is no time to laugh, straw hat boy
If we can't figure out what that girl's powers are...
Leave it to me because I've beaten her 184 times in a row
There you are!
There you are.
Luffy senior Uta baby captain
Let's go
The sea pirate escaped
Let's go get them together
SWORD's phone bug hasn't been working
Well, that's too bad it looks like Uta's really gonna go through with her plan
SWORD has been watching Uta, too
Aren't you from Cipher Pol What are they trying to do?
Isn't it time for a turf war where you can't use your doorfruit abilities
Maybe you know too much
And so do you.
I could but it's gonna take a lot of energy out of me
So what do we do
Gather our men first that's all we can do right now
It's a headache. They got caught
It looks like they're just stuck to that rope so they'll be fine
I didn't think that one day I could take the road to fly away I was so moved that I couldn't see the front straw hat boy
thank you
What are you doing, please
Wow, that's a lot.
We'll be surrounded if we keep this up
Here you go.
It's a good thing you saved us
You said you were Luffy, right
Yes.
And you?
Who are you
I was king of the kingdom of Eligia My name was Gordon
What kingdom has some buildings but no people
You're wrong.
Eligia was once the number one music island in the world
But it all disappeared overnight
A kingdom that big just disappeared in one night
There's a rumor that they were attacked by pirates
Let's talk about Uta
When Eligia was empty
I'm the one who raised Uta
Are you?
It's just the two of us on this island
She's supposed to feel very alone and she's pretending to be strong for me
But when she's alone she sings about her friends
"I think of us playing by the sea."
"Just you and me."
"But the smell of the sea is fading away."
"Slowly slipping away"
"So I sang a familiar song
"Hope you can hear me."
"I'll sing till you come back to me."
To encourage Uta
I made her the best singer in the world
Hello? Are you listening?
Just go ahead and ignore us
I'm sorry
Anyway, Uta doesn't seem to have any idea what Luffy's doing, does he?
My problem at that time was that I didn't know when and how to deliver her songs to the world
After all, she grew up without knowing anything about the outside world
But the timing was sudden
She happened to pick one up two years ago
The new image of the phone bug washes ashore
Uta was liberated to broadcast her music to the outside world
Her fans love her voice
It's as if the sound she transmits is all around the world
Thank you, Uta
I feel much better
Thank you Uta because you're the reason I'm alive
Me too. I'm glad people are so happy...
A new consciousness had sprung up within her that the age of the Great pirate was full of war and violence
It was meant to be heard by others
But somewhere along the way, more and more of Uta's fans started calling her the savior
And Uta just...
I understand your feelings very well
If you want me to do it a new era
Please stop Uta's plan
Luffy, you're her friend and I know you can do it
Is that the concert you're talking about?
I'm sorry
paypal
Ah cho
The paypal Bear
utta
Uta, why did you leave Shanks's ship
I thought you said you wanted to be the Gorgie of the Red-headed One Piece and go back to Shanks
Shut up. I don't want to talk about it
Forget all this boring stuff
We can eat delicious food and play chicken contests and arm wrestle and live happily as before
Give me my hat back Shanks 'hat
Well, Luffy New Era doesn't need you
ROOM migration
Where did they go?
Did the pirates escape?
Looks like they have a lot of different abilities
Forget it let's just make a game of it and find the escaped pirates
Let me out. I want my hat back
Shut up You can't do that That's why I put you in here
We just kept running...
There's a harbor on the other side of the island. Let's go that way
What port?
The Navy and the secret Service were at the concert
What are you talking about
Governments and navies around the world are watching Uta's capabilities
They watched her as if she were dangerous
So they're here to scout
I think they're somewhere around the island
If we can find the Navy we can find a way to get them to give us some Intel on Utta's capabilities
Not over there
Oops
Don't worry, my ball shield is pretty strong
But it won't stop
It's so tall.
Luffy senior hold on, hold on
Gordon are you still mad at me for throwing this concert without consulting you?
It's not an easy concert, is it
I see you found out that you're on my side, right
I... I...
It would have been easy for you to just run away
I don't want you to do this
But...
You just stay here for the time being
The governments and navies of the world will not stand idly by
It doesn't matter because I have this
This is Tol Musica
I always knew it was buried under this castle. Why didn't you throw it away?
Isn't it because you have new age ideals, too?
Uta you can't use it
uttar
Ah Autumn...
This ocean is so vast
Forget the Navy there's not a soul here
Let me ask you something.
What's going on?
The Thousand Yang is gone
Is it your boat
The regionalization
what
A thousand Yang, a thousand Yang
Really?
Are you really a thousand SUNS
Is that Uta's power again? I'm going crazy
The regionalization
Report to the forward deck lookout
No enemy duplication was found
No enemy was found
Watch the back of the ship for any raids
Prepare for land battle Deploy the first squadron to make sure the beaches are secure as soon as they arrive
The second team entered the island when the beach was secured
Armed Recon 2 continues its search with no sign of the enemy
Armed Recon Three is in and there's no sign of the enemy
We continued to advance but could not confirm any sign of the enemy or what looked like the enemy
Waiting for the next command
This is... What is this...
This is Armed Recon Seven We have no information on the people of Eligia
This is Armed Recon two and we have no sign of the enemy
This is Armed Recon Four reporting to Lieutenant Ratty
The audience is not awake and can't wake up Repeat they can't wake up
I don't think they're dead
They just fell asleep
But they're never gonna get up
If you kill me these souls will never return
Is that okay
The little girl
I know all too well what your demon fruit can do
Then you don't need me to explain, do you? Go home
After all, I'll be gone soon
Am I getting a wakeful mushroom
What are wakeful mushrooms
People who eat these mushrooms can't sleep and die from exhaustion
What are you...
Are you going to kill yourself and take the whole audience with you?
What? Your soul is more important than your body, isn't it?
In the new age every soul will live forever
I'm trying to solve this problem without violence if you could just drop it
Stop your plan to destroy the world
What are you talking about?
I just want people to be happy
It seems you don't want to listen to our advice
So are you
Don't worry
You can't do anything to me as long as we can't hear you
Unfortunately, it was too late
What do you mean, General Kirby
Guys, there are bad guys here
Let's get them for the new era
Don't hurt them they're just innocent citizens being controlled
"I've given up being alone. I want to be with someone else."
"I want a real relationship so let me take my feelings"
"Sing it all out (shout it out)"
"Listen, baby, I'm gonna make you happy whether you like it or not."
"Sneak up on you, keep you from escaping and wait for the beat."
"Listen to the surprise every word will bring you to me."
"(Oh) Be my sweet little boy and girl."
"Do you think you're good but I'm tired of it?"
"I got something better here. Come on. We can sing together."
"Let's unpack the fun and get on stage together. Let's go."
"(Aha) I want to make you happy."
"Do it proudly with me."
"(Hey) Tell me is it hard to live here?"
"Isn't this the country of our dreams?"
"It's been on the way a long time. It's time to stay. You can't deny it."
"It's a miracle of mercy that you can't stop even if you try to stop it."
"I don't think that's too much to wish for."
"The Savior has come to this age."
"I screamed for salvation."
"Because no one ever heard me scream."
"But that's not true anymore."
"I have to do this. They can't do it anymore."
"Stop me and get out of my way."
"There's no going back now let's sing together forever."
"Let the bass rock your head and the drums break your eardrums."
"Let those brass instruments touch your heart."
"Let me hear you scream oh wow!"
"Don't be brainwashed into telling the truth."
"Let me erase all traces of your brainwashing and stop listening to their lies."
"Look up and let my song bring back your consciousness that's what you need."
"This is my real voice."
Damn it This is bad I can't get out of here
This is so useless with your curly eyebrows
You can't get down either, you mossy head
So can Fledge and Jiping move
I can't move
I'm Brooke, too
Let's try again
Can you break free? I was so close to seeing Nami's underwear
what?
If you see that, I'll blow you out of the sky
Can I say something
Didn't Uta say, "Let me create a song"
I don't think that means it's a sheet music
It does look like a melody
The position of our head may be a note
Brooke, can you sing it?
But I can't see the whole score
All I can see now is...
You shut up and don't look at your underwear
Sure enough, the Straw Hat Pirates were able to discover that it was a musical score
what?
You guys... Why with Bruno?
I'll explain that later
Come on, sing
The mi to
Here we go.
Free to go
Good Brooke go ahead
Did you hear about that girl's power
Did you put my sister in a bag
The elder brother
Just this once but only if you cooperate with the Navy
Mia Ah Cho
Do I... The mi...
Thank you. You really are a very capable bear
Hello hello
Why?... I'm in here again...
We don't know what Uta is capable of so we can't let you out
A thousand SUNS... A thousand SUNS?
Why are you guys here
Long time no see Luffy
Kirby helped me get me out of here
How did you know to come here?
I sensed Luffy
The original is used to see color domineering
And then I borrowed Bruno's doorfruit power
Door door let me out
Cipher Pol is working with the Navy What's going on here?
Everybody wants to know what Uta can do, right
You know what Uta is capable of... what
You may not believe this but the world we live in isn't real
what
What you see is not reality The world Uta created with her powers
The ability to sing fruit allows the singer to transport the soul of the person who hears the song to sing about the world
The souls that are transported will feel like they're still alive
But not in the real world but in the world Uta created
It's like everyone's having the same dream
I think Uta said she could do it
what?
I mean when someone hears her sing they go to sleep
If you knew why didn't you say so
Sorry, I forgot.
So what's going on in the real world?
Our bodies stay in the real world
But they're all controlled by Uta
So how do we get back to reality?
If Uta falls asleep her powers will be taken away
But because we've been trapped in this world of singing fruit we can't lay a hand on the real Uta
The devil fruit has to have its limits, right
Yes.
It takes a lot of energy to maintain this world of singing fruit
It's like I can't use my door fruit ability all the time
So all it takes is Uta to get tired and go to sleep
Well, that's a conundrum because I confirmed that she ate sober mushrooms before her concert even started
That mushroom will keep you awake
The real world Uta will soon be dead
To die?
Is Uta going to die?
Can we get out of here if she's dead?
No, it's the opposite
If Uta dies the world will shut down
Everyone in here will be there
Including us would be stuck here
Her fans would be trapped forever in this world of singing fruit
This is Uta's plan
It's crazy
Kirby How are we gonna stop Uta
I snuck in here to find her weakness and I didn't find anything, you know
I just knew we had to at least get our people together so I got Hilumebo working with the other Pirates
As for the Straw Hat Pirates they have their own operation
Looks like they're all right
They headed for the castle of Eligia
Nicole Robin seems to know what happened to this island in the past
If there were records we might have a way to beat Uta
But the chances are slim
Can you trust Robin you mossy white head?
It's a fact you have beautiful eyebrows
There is a room with many books
Guys let's forget about the sea pirate and wait for a new era
How long before the real Uta dies?
Less than two hours
The sound insulation here is well done
Looks like Uta can't reach this place
The Navy says she's safe where her voice can't be heard
Are these old records?
How are we gonna find what we need?
Three knife flow extremely tiger hunting
Demon wind foot
Fried assorted platter
Strong right hand weapon left hand
Robin, you go find that book
But Robin
I won't let them hurt a hair on your head Don't worry
Very quickly... The bad guys will disappear and a new era will dawn
Can you hear me? Uta probably has an hour to live, Max
But those phone bugs with their souls are out of control
They keep showing videos of Uta singing about the fruit world
"It's dangerous if you don't turn the sound off and your soul is taken away as soon as you hear that song."
"Listen, baby, I'm gonna make you happy whether you like it or not."
"Snuck up on you, didn't let you run and waited for the beat."
"Listen to the surprise every word will lead you to me."
"Be my sweet little boy and girl."
"Do you think you're good but I'm tired of it?"
"I got something better here."
"Come on we can sing it out"
"Let's get on the stage. Let's go.""
Uta's concert has been going on for over six hours
The number of victims continues to grow
If this goes on for one more hour, 70% of the population will be teleporting to the world of singing fruit
Seventy percent? That's more than we thought
The world is going to be wiped out
We have to do something to stop her, okay
I told you that stuff doesn't work here
If I can't use you then I don't need you
What are you doing?
Are you okay? I'm here to help you
What are you marines doing killing this kid?
Didn't your navy say you'd be on the right side?
But the Dragons are like the gods of this world
I see
So you don't really want to do this guy's bidding? Okay, it's okay
In the new era, dragons and slaves are equal
What equality is so gross?
You have to kill her now
I'm sorry
Don't think I'll let you off the hook
Guys you have nothing to fear from these dragons
You can't do that, Uta
If you hurt the Draconians
World governments and navies will come after you
I told you it was gonna be okay
Sorry, Uta.
I got to get back to my flock
Thank you. It was a really fun concert
Wait a minute. I don't understand what you're talking about
Why would you go back and have a hard life when you can enjoy it here?
Did you not see that I caught these pirates?
It's time for Uta to stop
You're the navy and you're here to save the Draconians
I'm here to save everyone here
You send all the souls back to the real world
General Kirby
what
It's really General Kirby. It's Kirby
Are you a famous person?
He was the hero who saved the lives of many citizens at Lodgepole
I see. I've been in Algia the whole time so I don't know about the news
ok
Feed the hero
I'm using up too much power you tell them
good
Listen to me, everybody
The world you live in is a fake one
You've been duped
We have to get out of here
Uta did you really lie to us and keep us here
I'm not lying to you I'm not lying to anyone
No, you guys I'm just trying to lead you to happiness
Isn't this what everyone wants
The time of the Great Sea pirate is over and now it is the time of peace and freedom
Isn't that great? All the good food and fun things are here
No one here does bad things no pain no pain
Yeah, I think I'll be happy here
Me too.
So it is
But I have work to do
I told you you don't have to work and you don't have to study
Even so, we can't stay here forever
I still have something I'm working on
It's not so good to play all day
I want to go home...
Letting society end completely is kind of
I don't think I can do that
I do like Uta but this is crossing a line
Uta, you have to stop this
Wait a minute, everybody.
What happened to freedom
To be free from disease and persecution is it all a lie
Didn't you say you wanted to see a life where you didn't have to worry about pirates
We said we wanted to go home
What...
Don't do this Uta is doing this for our own good
I don't think it's funny anyway
So am I. You guys shut up
I agree with Uta. I don't like it here
I want to go to school and this has nothing to do with it
It does matter. It does matter
You've gone too far, Uta
That's too much. What? Why would she do that?
I'm sorry, I see
Just give you guys more fun stuff
See, now everyone's in a better mood
Let us live together in a new age of peace and freedom
Charrose St
We can't have any more victims and it's time to make a decision
With or without the Draconians
We all had a lucky escape
Who are you?
Bruno
Kirby, have you seen Uta?
This is...
I see you didn't succeed in persuading her
And you?
See?
Here we go.
Wait a minute. I didn't hear about working with the Straw Hat Pirates. I'd rather die
goodbye
Wait a minute
We will take Uta down in our own way
A thousand SUNS...
Where are my team members?
They haven't come back yet
We're not gonna win if they don't find Uta's weakness
I can't use the power of the door in this body
It's okay. They're gonna be fine
Rotating powder star
Is that okay?
People are scared and people are confused
Hide under Too Musica and run
Soft strength enhancement I hit... To play... To play..
Cold winds gather
Demonic wind foot belly Strike
One stroke of a knife and a horse ghost
Soul ballads are frozen and lost
Fish karate shark muscle palmar bottom
The laser beam is a giant whitewater whirl
It's going to collapse
I don't know who blew this place up
I'm so sorry
We're about to get our asses kicked but I might look good buried alive
Robin here
Brieri I know you're in there Let's get into the looking-glass world
Don't ignore me
Without our message you would never have escaped the world of singing fruit
You're never gonna see your family or your friends again Are you sure you want this?
Shall I never see Brother Katakuli again?
Yeah, yeah.
You guys all right?
luffy
The regionalization
What is this?
This is the Thousand Yang so cute
How is this transformed
I didn't think I'd be back here
I'm sorry, brother Owen.
Robin did you find anything to beat Uta
Based on previous records, there's no way around that
what?
But as long as the fruit users use Tol Musica we have a chance
What is Too Musica?
It contains the thoughts and feelings of people from the past
All the loneliness and pain and any dark side of the heart it's sometimes called "the devil."
Is it a weapon?
What I've learned is that this is something you shouldn't touch
So if we use that taboo against Uta what's our winning percentage
According to previous records the Demon was awakened by Too Musica
It doesn't just happen in the world of singing fruit it happens in the real world
So the Demon Lord can connect the singing fruit world with the real world
If the Demon Lord attacks in both worlds
Then the world of singing fruits will disappear when the Demon Lord is defeated
Really?
It must have been done before that's why it's on record We should try it
But will anyone attack Uta in the real world
We are all in this singing fruit world
If we're gonna attack Uta in the real world, it's gonna be the Navy
No way
As long as there are citizens
They won't be able to do it
There is one man who can
The captain
Is that paypal?
And who the old man is
He's the Gordon who raised Uta
What uta's
I tell you who you're talking about
Shanks
Shanks?
If Shanks shows up he can stop the real world Uta
Uncle, what happened to Shanks and Uta
This is...
uncle
Too bad he's going after Uta and he can't beat her
This is our captain and nothing can stop him
There's no time for this anyway. Why don't we just get it over with
But how
Since both worlds are going to attack her at the same time we'll just keep attacking her
Until the real world matches our attacks
I'm so scared it doesn't work but with the Straw Hat Pirates I know we're gonna win
We'll have to do it
Yeah, but then again,
What is this that you just figured out now
What are you doing here that you can't beat me no matter how many times we fight
It's not even a split yet
There you go again with the sore loser
It's like old times we decide who wins
ah
You're not serious at all
What you're doing right now is wrong
You're the one making the wrong choice
The era of the great sea pirate is over
Why do you want to be One Piece so bad
To create a new era
luffy
The era of the Great pirate began with the execution of Roger
And I'll end my flight because of you
Don't
uttar
you
Don't you love the Red-headed Pirates
Don't you love Shanks why do you hate pirates so much
It's all Shanks's fault
To me, Shanks is...
I really think of him as my real father
I thought everyone on that boat was my family
But it's all a lie to them
So Shanksy dumped me
He left me alone in Eligia
So you can be a good singer
It's not...
That's amazing. Your voice is the treasure of the world
There are a lot of professionals, instruments and sheet music
Please stay in Eligia and you are more than welcome in our kingdom
You look so happy and enjoying yourself when you sing here
Isn't it
Is it much more fun to sing in front of so many people than to sing to us
That's not true.
There is no peace or equality in this world
But your voice is the only one that makes everyone happy in this world
What are you talking about
I'm saying you can stay here
I'll be back for you when you're the best singer in the world
Fool, I'm the Goliath of the red-headed Sea
If studying music means I have to be apart from you and be apart from you
Yeah, I know. Let's get out of here tomorrow
But that night
Gordon
Are you awake
What's going on?
What about Shanks and them? Everything was stolen...
All of them were killed
Where is Shanks?
Their plan was to use your song to get close to Eligia and steal our treasure
You mean the red-headed sea pirate
That's them
You've been fooled by the red-headed pirate and Shanks
Shanks, don't leave me
Why?
Would Shanks do such a thing? You know the answer yourself
Then what have I been for 12 years
Luffy you're nothing more than a tool to Shanks
Shanks will be here
To save you? To save you
Save me? Why?
Because his daughter is doing this and Shanks is not gonna take it well
He abandoned me and he's never coming
Come on, Luffy.
goodbye
Shanks
Why?
I came to hear you sing
Long time no see
Just in time for my fans from all over the world to enter a new era
But before we go in, I want to finish with you
Everybody the worst of the pirates is here let's catch him together
Shanks is here, isn't he?
now
Do you still want to fight? So...
You're not singing.
The regionalization
Reinforcement of fur
transplant
Shroud ball sound
Uta, now your voice won't get through
Hello hello
Hold the cloth even if it puts your life in danger
Don't
You have to hang in there a new era is upon us
Yes we will use all the power of the navy to stop Uta
It doesn't matter if the audience gets caught in the crossfire
We have to sacrifice them to reduce the number of victims and protect the world
Destroy her
The Navy says it's on the right side but do they really want to kill civilians
Answer me yellow Ape
There is no justice without the victim
How cruel to sacrifice millions of people to stop a child
Eight feet Qiongyu
I'm sorry we're dealing with a domestic dispute
Would you stay out of it?
No we have the world on our shoulders
And even if it is, just stay out of it
If I could do that I would be able to see with this eye
North Township...
Looks like something big is happening in the real world
Sure enough, it was a wakeful mushroom
If you eat that mushroom it doesn't just wake you up it makes you go crazy and lose control of your emotions
I should have gone after you bad guys first
uttar
I just don't have the guts I don't have the guts to do that
But I won't hesitate now
Watch out that thing should be coming out
I... My perfect shield
That's...
Oh, that's a problem. We've got this specially prepared so I don't think we'll need it
How did that happen? She woke it up
When the singing fruit user sings that song, it wakes up
The old devil
That's Tot Musica
"With a wandering heart the clouds begin to cover the sky."
"The rain and my bitter tears began to fall."
"They have been the next stop Let I began to read a spell"
"Be my salvation."
"Let me begin to spell my salvation."
"These ancient lyrics are like hymns to which death cannot escape."
"I pray how to erase this confusion and I pray for peace from the future sea."
"It's time for redemption."
"I feel this anger making me stronger."
"These cries have echoed for so long now all I can do is scream."
"I know you feel new too so keep singing this song with me."
"We'll keep singing this song even if they torture you."
"When we sing this song together we'll start another big bang."
I can't block out that sound
No, it's no use
The Demon Lord has connected the real world with the singing fruit world
Uta Uta enough
Uta, can you hear us?
The world feels strange
uttar
Hot air fist
Damn it looks like we're really gonna hit Uta at the same time
Princess Uta you were trying to save everyone with your song Why is this happening
Lying cloth
I'm fine.
Leave Tot Musica to us
so
Don't leave Uta alone
Give her a good beating
Hey, can you hear me, Uta? This...
Luffy Senior
luffy
What are you doing to fight back
Uta, listen to me
I have nothing to say to the pirate
- Uncle. - paypal
I can't let you continue to hurt the friend you cherish so much....
He's the one who believes in Shanks, you know
No, Uta that was a lie
It wasn't the Red-headed Pirates who took out Eligia 12 years ago
It's Tot Musica
I'm sorry I haven't been able to tell you the truth...
Do you remember the party that day?
The ones who heard about the conservatory you're leaving with Shanks
Take advantage of this last chance to hear you sing song after song
Because it's such a special opportunity we've invited the entire nation to hear you sing
That's probably where it went wrong
Your voice summoned the music that was sealed beneath the castle
That sheet music was the Tot Muscia and before we knew it it was in front of you and started it all
It has used the fruit of your song for its freedom
The devil who unsealed the music
Take your little body and start using your powers on the people of this kingdom
Get up Uta don't let it control you
Don't
It's a good thing you were young and you started to get tired and pass out
But that kingdom...
Is the navy here yet
I was wondering if you could keep this from Uta
It would be cruel for her to know the truth
Okay, I'll tell the Navy this is my fault
It's not our fault Shanks and the red-headed pirate did it all you tell Uta that
Are you going to leave her here?
She has the best voice but we're being chased by the Navy all day and that's gonna limit her talent
You have the ability to turn her into an amazing singer
None of this is the fault of her singing
Shanks...
Okay, I... The King of Gorden Eligia swears to you on behalf of all my music-loving people
I'm gonna raise Uta to be an amazing singer who can bring joy to the world
Uta Even when we're apart you'll always be my daughter
So let's laugh and go
This is the beginning of our unique little singer's career
Uta, did you hear that?
Sure enough Shanks really...
That's the design I drew
I've drawn it
See what is this?
It's Shanks's straw hat
- Is this a hat? - Yes
You're a terrible painter
Let's take this pattern as a sign of the new age
Here it is. You can keep it
Stop it Uta
This is not freedom
This is not a new era
You know better than anyone without results
luffy
It's too late
What the hell is this....?
Everybody get in here and hide
Hey, how are we gonna fight this thing?
Would it be nice to know when our attacks became consistent
The strange navy is trying to kill the citizens but the pirates are protecting them
These titles mean nothing
Why protect them?
Let's not add another sin to our daughter's grief
Guys I don't want to see any bodies
Looks like we have to stop the Devil first
Uta ate the wakeful mushroom
She has become one with Tot Musica and the only way we can beat her is....
Uta, it's you
It's all your fault
You are the one who caused your SINS
Shut up. I know all about it
About a year after I was able to deliver my music to everyone
I picked up a phone bug that had captured a reflection of that day
Anyone who sees this watch out for that little girl Uta she's dangerous
Her voice will destroy the world
So what can I do that so many people around the world still want to hear my music
Uta I want to get away from here
Do you think there's a world where I can listen to you forever?
Yeah, Uta, who hates pirates the most
This is all for everyone who found me
I can't go back
For the New era
Hot goat
Brother Owen, be careful.
How could I let a lady get hurt?
And there are some things that only you can do
good
Kirby will take the lead
The main objective of the good guard formation is to protect the spectators
Namie Robin helped open an escape route
Everybody stay calm and get in that mirror
Bruno and the others protect them
Frankie and Voo-ping, you'll be flanking
Jabbar protects Luffy and Gordon
Shilumebo and I will play flanker
Lie Boo, you'll provide fire support in the back and Brooke and Sanchi you're the top defense at the defense center
The advanced attackers in the attack center are Sauron and Owen and I'm handing you over to RON
And then what? Let's get started
The French bazooka
Zeus flew with the wind
Uta, I'm sorry.
I was wrong to be afraid that your powers would stop you from performing in front of everyone
And as a person who loves music, I can't give up Tot Musica
I'm a fool and I'm a coward who's always looking for a reason to run away and I deserve it
My dad always left me alone, too
But you've always been there for Princess Uta
You lost the kingdom and you still kept your word
You're actually pretty good
Okay, I'm out of here
luffy
Luffy her singing can bring joy to all people in this world
But this one
I really feel sorry for her please Luffy go save her
Of course I would have saved her
Luffy let him go
We're running out of time and we're not gonna get back to the real world if this doesn't work out
Red hair
We must attack at the same time
We must attack the same place at the same time as the world of singing fruit
Why?
BIG MOM's son will be here
I'm here to save my sister
I used my eyes to see a little bit about my sister's situation
Both of us must...
I know
You're not the only one with new ideas here
But he's not ready. He's not calm
But Katakuli I'm glad you're here
We've got our hands full here with the Navy...
I want you to be a good boy
luffy
Shanks
It worked
It's connected to the real world
You son of a bitch.
Three streams of fire cut six tsuji
Will it ever end?
You'll regret stepping on you, you wicked swordsman
Didn't I say there was no time?
damn
If only we could get rid of those hands and feet
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Dad, you finally found your stupid son
I saw what I saw my dad see
luffy
All right, come on guys
Do your best on the ground
good
All right, let's do our best on the floor
We need to stop Tot Musica's hands and feet
Follow my instructions and hit your right foot first
The right foot
The left hand
- Left foot. Left foot.
All right
Let me give you a hand
Center right center right
Center left center left
Jesus, your father and your son are very close
The right hand
o
Fledge Fireball
luffy
Shanks
Now now
Did you see it? Because we went to war
So much love
We have good food these days
Treasure treasure
How did you get in here?
Maybe it was the pirates who took her
You've got to be kidding
All right, all right, stop crying
Go to sleep, baby quietly
Is this some kind of fate
Are you lonely, too
Shanks, I...
It's okay. It's over
If you take this medicine now and go to sleep, you'll be fine
Shanks... I don't want to see you...
But...
I'm dying to see you again
Stop talking and drink
What's going on?
I thought we defeated the Devil...
Don't... Stop it.
Stop it.
Why can't we go back Why?
It's too late.
Tot Musica's powers have taken our souls
Really!?
Uta drank the medicine quickly
I have to sing and I have to bring everyone back
Shanks... I thought you said that a long time ago
Do my songs have the power to make people happy?
I'm Gojiuta from the Red-headed One Pirates
"I think of us playing by the sea."
"Just you and me."
"But the smell of the sea is fading away."
"Slowly slipping away."
"So I sang a familiar song," "I hope you can hear it."
"I'll sing till you come back to me."
"I wanna believe, I wanna try to believe."
"On the far side of the sea or among the stars."
"I need you to hear me and I need you to believe me."
"A gust of wind blows my wings."
"Kept calling to me."
"Fly me to the sky."
The voice of an angel
uttar
"I wanna believe, I wanna try to believe."
"On the far side of the sea or among the stars."
"I need you to hear me and I need you to believe me."
"We'll meet again one day and continue in this dream."
"And then in the sunset we'll wake up again."
Hey, why didn't you punch me?
My fists are stronger than guns. Didn't I tell you
I thought you used to hit me with your little punches
I wasn't at full strength
There you go again with the sore loser
Since when are you taller than me?
This hat means a lot to me, too
You're gonna be the man to match that hat one day
Shanks Luffy
He's back.
The entire audience is safe
That's good
I'm sorry I didn't trust Shanks and the whole red-headed crew
Thank you! for saving my life
All right, it's time to hand over Uta to the super-criminal who wants to destroy the world
you
Are you fighting back?
With all of you
She... It's my daughter
She's a very important part of our family
If you're gonna take her away from me
You better prepare to die
You subjugates the entire population under the Vice admiral and that is the power of Shanks, one of the Four Kings
Forget it. We shouldn't be fighting here too close to the citizens
Are my fans okay? I hope they're not too upset
It's okay. Humans aren't that weak
And a new era is upon us
"Where is this wind coming from and where is it taking us?"
"I looked to the sky for answers but it didn't answer me."
"This song that I sing"
"Where is it going to go?"
"I try to find the answer inside."
"We are once again heading into the unknown sea."
"Go forth bravely."
"I have but one wish."
"Don't give up and keep going."
"Let all the ships in my heart raise their sails and let me hear the call of the sea."
"I have to keep singing."
Did you sleep well?
Where are Uta and Shanks
To the thousand Yang... The regionalization
I'm gonna be The Pirate King