VALERIAN
and the City of a Thousand Planets
Subtitled  by   TIEN SHEN LONG
♫ Ground Control to Major Tom ♫
♫ Commencing countdown, engines on ♫
♫ Check ignition ♫
♫ and may God's love be with you ♫
♫ This is Ground Control to Major Tom ♫
♫ You've really made the grade ♫
♫ And the papers want to know whose shirts you wear ♫
♫ Now it's time to leave the capsule  if you dare ♫
♫ This is Major Tom to Ground Control ♫
♫ I'm stepping through the door ♫
♫ And I'm floating in a most peculiar way ♫
♫ And the stars look  very different today ♫
♫ For here ♫
♫ Am I sitting in a tin can ♫
♫ Far above the world ♫
♫ Planet Earth is blue ♫
♫ And there's nothing I can do. ♫
♫ Though I'm past one hundred thousand miles ♫
♫ I'm feeling very still ♫
♫ And I think my spaceship  knows which way to go ♫
♫ Tell my wife I love her very much ♫
♫ she knows ♫
♫ Ground Control to Major Tom ♫
♫ Your circuit's dead, there's something wrong ♫
♫ Can you hear me, Major Tom? ♫
♫ Can you ... ♫
♫ Here am I floating round my tin can ♫
♫ Far above the Moon ♫
♫ Planet Earth is blue ♫
♫ And there's nothing I can do. ♫
The Alpha Intergalactic Space Station
has reached critical mass in orbit.
Its weight and size now pose a serious threat to Mother Earth.
In its great wisdom, the Central Committee
has decided to use all resources necessary to release
the space station from the Earth's gravity.
Its new course is set for the Magellan Current.
Like the great explorer Magellan,
The Alpha Station will journey into the unknown.
A symbol of our values and knowledge,
it will carry a message of peace and unity
to the farthest reaches of the universe.
Our thoughts and prayers go with you.
God speed and good luck.
VALERIAN
AND THE CITY OF A THOUSAND PLANETS
400 YEARS LATER
PLANET MÜL CONSTELATION QN34
- Good morning.
- Let's proceed.
So we return to nature what he gave to us.
- Give this pearl to my daughter, Princess Lhoha.
- What is that?
- Take cover!
- Come on, quickly!
- What happened?
- There are objects falling from the sky.
- Oh my ...
- Secure everyone, bring them to a safe place.
- Come on, quickly.
- Wait!.
- Dolark!
- They are coming.
- Quickly, take cover!
- Wait...
- Come on!
- All gather!
- Faster!
Come on, quickly!
- Come on.
- It's broken!
- Lhoha!
- I'm sorry.
- No!
- Please.
- Lhoha!
- Goodbye.
- You okay?
- Yeah, just a... bad dream.
- No.
- But I feel better now.
- Don't you think we should run through our assignment?
- That's the last thing I feel like doing.
- Not very professional, Major.
- Look, I scored a perfect 200 on my last memory test.
- Impressive.
- Unfortunately, you've forgotten something rather important today.
- What's that?
- My birthday.
- Hey!
- What can I do to make it up to you?
Beginning descent in three minutes.
- Nothing that you can get done in three minutes.
- Come on.
- Don't start what you can't finish.
Landing on planet Kyrian in five minutes.
- Sorry. Hey, look.
I know you're attracted to me. Why deny the obvious?
- It's obvious?
- Yeah, sure.
- Little goody two-shoes with an Ivy League education
are always attracted to galaxy-hopping bad boys like me.
- My Ivy League education taught me
to steer clear from bad boys like you.
- Yeah, well, you're not gonna find better than me
on the market. Straight up. Take a good look.
Handsome, intelligent,
- Modest.
- Brave.
- Suicidal.
- Determined.
- Pig-headed.
- Faithful.
- To yourself.
- Yeah, and to you. You're my partner.
- Yes, don't forget it.
- Look...
- Why don't you think with your heart
and not your head for once?
- I don't wanna be another name on your list of conquests.
Thank you very much.
- What are you talking about? What list?
- Alex, can we see the playlist, please?
- No, no, no, no, no, hey.
Most of those are coworkers, and that's it.
- Coworkers.
- Right.
- Where's MY picture, then?
- They mean nothing to me.
Okay? I took a few detours when I was younger.
- Your last detour was not so long ago.
- Yeah, but with you, it's different. And you know it.
I want my heart to belong to you and no one else.
- My heart will belong to a man who'll erase his playlist for me.
- That's what I'm talking about.
I'm that man.
- Look, we both know you're quite a lady killer.
So, why do you lose interest in a girl...
as soon as you win her heart?
- Because I'm looking for the perfect woman.
- But you've never stopped to look.
- That's not a crime.
- No, it's not a crime.
But just admit it. You're scared of commitment.
- Me? Scared of commitment?
Are you kidding me?
Nine years in the service.
Impeccable record.
Seven medals of honor.
Never lost a partner.
- Yeah, until now.
Refuel complete.
- Alex, did you enter the coordinates?
I took that liberty.
So you could both enjoy the beach a while longer.
- Oh, thank you.
You are welcome.
You will be leaving exospace in 30 seconds.
- You wanna take us down?
- Yes, sir.
- Alex, will you pull my brain charge for the last 10 minutes?
- I had a weird dream.
See anything abnormal?
Your cerebral activity is a little more intense than usual.
You received external waves.
- Explain.
These waves don't come from your memory.
Somebody is sending you the images.
- Do you know who? Where they come from?
Negative. They could come from the present or past.
And from anywhere in the universe.
Leaving exospace.
Three, two, one. Exit.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Easy, easy.
- We're late.
- Yeah, well, better late than dead.
- You wanna drive?
- Whoa.
- Put your hand back on the joystick.
Laureline, put your hands back on the joystick.
Laureline, will you please put your hand back on the joystick?
- Will you stop complaining about my driving?
- Yes, I'm sorry. You're a great driver.
You're the best driver in the entire universe.
- Aw, thank you.
- Intercom activated.
- Thanks.
Touchdown on Kyrian in two minutes.
Minister online.
- Sir.
- Agents Valerian and Laureline.
I trust you studied the assignment.
So as soon as you land, recover the converter and bring it to Alpha
for a top secret operation.
The converter is the last creature of its species.
- So we're counting on you.
- Yes, sir.
- Captain Gibson has further details.
And please, put on some more appropriate clothing.
- Good idea.
- Leaving manual.
Manual disarmed.
Intercom activated.
- Here they come. Intruder 980.
- Check parameters.
- Two people on board. No parasites.
- Where's the band?
- You plan on going on the mission dressed like that?
- We're supposed to mingle with tourists, aren't we?
- What do you expect us to wear? Panda suit?
- Nice hat.
- Major, this mission is in-and-out.
You enter Big Market, you find the suspect's store,
and you team up with Sergeant Cooper.
- I only work with my partner.
- Hi.
- We're a team.
- Sergeant Laureline will arrive at the drop in exactly 20 minutes.
You will have 10 seconds to make the transfer.
Didn't you read the memo?
- Yeah... of course.
- You better have.
- How about we look at the memo one last time?
- It can't hurt.
- You think you can survive 20 minutes without me?
- How could I possibly?
- Go on. Be careful.
- Oh, uh, you must be right, I...
... completely forgot. I have a question for you.
- Shoot.
What?
- Will you marry me?
- Not funny.
- Laureline, I'm serious.
- I've been thinkin' about what you said earlier.
And you're right. I need to move onward and upward.
I need to commit.
- Here? Just like that?
- Yeah, why not? They sell a zillion things here.
I'm sure we could find a priest who'd be happy to oblige.
- Go.
- Okay, let's go.
We remind you that if you want to enjoy
the experience of Big Market,
you must put on the equipment available to you.
Thank you.
- Welcome, everybody! Welcome.
Please, gather round. Gather round.
Now, my name is Thaziit,
and I am your guide for today, okay.
Now, whose first time is this at Big Market?
Okay, lovely, lovely. Wonderful, wonderful.
Now, let me remind you that
Big Market is in another dimension.
You won't be able to see it without your helmet
or touch it without your gloves.
But there are really a million stores in Big Market.
- Yes, okay, ah we have one hour.
- Now, please, watch the letters at the top
and verify that the U for human is full green, okay?
So everybody, please, get together
right behind your guide whose name is?
- Thaziit!
- Thaziit, come on, let's go!
Follow me, please. Put your helmets on.
- Go through the gate.
- Okay.
- Activate your system. Wonderful.
Do not leave with your helmet.
System activated.
- Whoa!
- Welcome... to Big Market!
- Hi!
- Yeah, sure, of course.
- Bill?
- Can I have my camera, please?
- Thank you.
- Say cheese.
- Thank you, Bill.
- You're good.
- Thanks.
- Hey.
♫ Come with me ♫
♫ Stand by me ♫
♫ Dance with.. ♫
- Good luck.
- What the hell are you doing, soldier?
- Sorry, sir.
- Keep an eye on the guy, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Please be careful down the stairs.
- Come on, everyone!
- Just think, baby, a million stores!
- Yeah.
Only stuff that we can carry, okay?
- I promise.
- All right.
- All right, drop in 12 minutes.
- Copy that.
- I found the suspect's store.
- Good. Sergeant Cooper will help you
get in and recover the stolen property.
- Major Valerian.
- Sergeant Cooper.
- As you read in the memo,
you need glasses to see the other dimension.
and a transmitter box to bring anything there.
- Especially a gun.
Authorized.
- Put this on.
Enter your genetic code on the front keypad.
To come back, enter your genetic code on the back keypad.
- Clear?
- Crystal.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- Hey, Tsûuri! Good to see you again.
Please sit down.
- Do you have what we asked for?
- Yeah, yeah.
But it was a toughie.
I lost a lot of personnel getting this for you.
But this... thing is priceless.
What can you give me in exchange?
Amazing.
I never thought I'd see one in my lifetime.
- You'll have hundreds of them.
Just as soon as you give us what we came for.
- Aw, that's where I have a slight problem, my friends.
If you're gonna knock out copies of this baby for me,
Why shouldn't I do it for myself?
Hey, easy, my little lambs.
- We absolutely need this converter.
You know we are fighting for a noble cause.
- I know. And I'm fighting for a noble cause too.
Mine.
You have ten seconds to drop your guns.
- Hmm?
- Show time.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Ooop.
- Federal Agent Valerian.
Sorry to interrupt this great deal,
but I'm also here for a noble cause.
It's called the law.
Hey, haven't I seen you guys somewhere before?
- Hey, I'm not running a tea room here.
What do you want from me?
- Igon Siruss, you stand accused of stealing a Mül converter
belonging to the Federation.
Before I drag your ass in, I have to recover the stolen property.
- All right, how we doing?
- Almost there.
- Valerian, I'll be to your left at three o'clock, three meters away.
- Got you.
Guys.
- Don't move.
Now, take it nice and easy, and push it into the box.
- Converter in the box.
- Copy.
- Undetected. Back to base.
- Good job.
- Copy that.
- Valerian, get out of here.
- I'm on my way.
- I'll find you, Federal Agent Valerian.
Wherever you are in the universe.
I'll find you.
And I will kill you.
- Good luck.
- Hmm.
- Valerian is in trouble.
- Mission takes priority. Keep going.
- Cooper, cover him.
- Copy that.
- Seek and destroy. Top priority.
Target's photograph to follow.
- Valerian, how we doing?
- Good. I think I lost them.
- Are you thirsty?
- No, thank you.
- I'm to your left, 200 feet away.
- My keypad is broken.
No, thank you.
Box is broken. Can't get my arm back.
Hey, do you need a lawyer?
- Federal Agent on duty. Leave me alone.
- Oh, no.
- Oh yeah.
- Valerian, what are you doing?
- Duh!
- Very funny.
What's your name?
- Duh.
- Duh?
- Come here. Come here. Try this.
It's way more fun.
- Duh!
- So long.
- Duh! Duh! Duh! Duh!
- Yeah, yeah, there's a time for everything, kid.
Don't you have homework to do?
All right, go get yourself cleaned up. Run to mommy.
- Mommy?
- Duh.
- Watch out!
Sorry!
- To retrieve your purchases,
please place your items in the transmitter box
and enter your DNA code. Thank you.
- Amazing. And so practical.
- Useless, you mean.
- You don't even know what you'll do with the darn thing.
- Don't be such a grouch. It's decorative.
Try to be civilized for once.
- Civilized. Yeah, sure.
- Sorry!
- Hey!
Hey, thanks a lot!
- Sorry!
- I didn't see the wall.
- Need some help?
- I just need you to fix my arm, thanks.
- I suppose since you asked for my hand,
you should probably get yours back first.
- Is that a yes?
- Don't move.
How can I help you if you keep moving?
- Will you just hurry up, please?
- Please keep still.
- Been detected.
- Uh...
Sorry to bother you.
I'm out of ammo and there is 3-headed my way.
- Give me one second.
- I don't have a second.
- Okay, you're good.
- Thanks.
- I don't know what I'd do without you.
To retrieve you purchases,
please place your items in the transmitter box
and enter your DNA code. Thank you.
- Fetch.
-You've been detected.
Keep moving. Don't change course.
- What are we supposed to do?
-Run.
- Zito, cover them.
- Yes, sir!
- Get in!
- Come on, let's go, go!
- I'm comin', I'm comin'!
- Zito, get that thing off our backs.
- I got it.
- Guys, take it out, take it out!
- Alex, we need you right now.
- Let's go.
- Shoot; you ruined my dress.
- Alex, I'm gonna take over on manual.
- Prepare to enter exospace.
- You know the coordinates for the rendezvous?
- Yeah, I'm just set...
- Alex, what was that?
We have a stowaway.
- Oh, great. Hold on.
Major Valerian, you're running nearly 20 minutes late.
- Yeah, well, time flies when you're havin' fun.
- We have the Mül converter.
- Excellent.
Now, perhaps you can tell me
what you're doing 17 light-years from your rendezvous?
- Yeah, it sounds pretty grim when you put it like that.
But when you say we'll be there in...
- nine minutes
- Does that sound better?
- I'll inform the commander that you're behind schedule.
and pass on your apology.
- Yeah, you do that.
Leaving exospace in five seconds.
- Somebody's gonna land with a bang.
- Okay. Let's have a look at you.
- Not at me, tiger. Come on.
Don't be scared.
I'll look after you.
Come on.
Hello.
Wow! You have the most incredible eyes.
Okay, you're a little scabby,
so, why don't we get you a nice treatment,
so you can get your mojo back?
Sound good?
Come on.
Some high-grade uranium, and you'll be good as new.
Hang on, tiger.
- Alex.
Analyze this, please.
Power: 20 megatons?
- Indeed. There's ten times more power in that pearl
than in our entire ship.
- Where does it come from?
- From Mül, a planet that was in the constellation QN34.
- Was?
- Yes.
The planet no longer exists. And hasn't for 30 years.
- Let's see what it looked like.
Abundant vegetation.
A few primal species, but of no particular interest.
- The one in my dream was pretty... interesting.
Zoom in.
User access codes.
- I'm afraid that won't be enough, Major.
Access is restricted.
- To what rank?
- General.
Five stars.
- The creature in my dream,
she had a pearl just like that on her neck.
- Noted, Major.
Leaving exospace in one minute.
- He's very cute, you know.
And a real charmer.
You may have some competition.
- I'm fine with competition.
Hey, I'm still waiting for your answer.
I know I can be full of myself sometimes.
But I'm dead serious about my proposal.
- We have to complete the mission, Major.
There's still the top secret part to attend to.
Or is your perfect memory failing you again?
Seat belt.
- You know what?
I'm gonna ask for ten days leave right now
and I'm gonna take you
to the most beautiful beach in the whole universe.
A real beach this time.
The perfect place for a honeymoon.
Ten seconds.
- The honeymoon comes after the wedding.
You know that, right?
- Really?
- Yup.
Three, two, one. Decelerating.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Alex, what are you doing?
Sorry. Too much traffic.
Do you want me to drive?
Nope! No, no, no, thank you.
Welcome to Alpha, the City of a Thousand Planets.
Alex, can you update us?
I'd be delighted to.
The Alpha Station has grown 7% this year.
And since it left the terrestrial orbit,
it has travelled almost 700 million miles.
- Population?
- Almost 30 million.
3236 species
from the four corners of the universe live on board.
Pooling their knowledge and cultures.
Over 5000 languages spoken.
Not counting the various computer languages.
Demographics?
To the south are the submerged parts
with 800 species living in all kinds of liquids.
Such as the peaceful Poulong Farmers
who grow cobalt.
To the north, we have gaseous lands
dominated by the Azin Mö
whose extreme sensitivity makes them specialists
in neurosciences and molecular components.
They can build cells of any kind.
To the east of them,
the large colony of Omelites.
They control information technology, finance, and banking.
Finally, to the west,
in a pressurized atmosphere,
we have nine million humans and compatible species.
Home sweet home.
The economy has been in shambles for a year.
Do you want a quick summary?
No. That's enough excitement for one day.
Intruder XB982
authorization to dock on Section One.
- VIP access.
- Oh, we're famous.
You're late, Major.
Sorry, sir. Things had been more complicated than we expected.
Prepare for the worst and you won't be disappointed.
And neither will I.
I'll keep that in mind, Sir.
And you, have you checked the converter?
He's in great shape.
May I ask what's going on?
Follow me.
Declassify.
A year ago, we discovered a radioactive zone
right in the middle of the station.
No signal of any kind can get through it.
We sent several probes, none came back.
So, we sent in a special unit.
Its mission was to get as close to the zone as possible.
And to find the nature of the threat.
And?
No one came back alive.
Any idea who attacked them?
No.
This is the situation today.
The air in the zone is unbreathable.
Highly contaminated.
And it continues to grow.
Like a tumor.
A tumor we have to cut out as soon as we can.
If we don't and the cancer keeps spreading,
it will destroy Alpha in less than a week.
Commander, who would have any reason to destroy Alpha?
Practically every living species is represented here.
This is a weapon of mass destruction.
And behind every weapon, there is a killer.
It doesn't matter who it is. It's a threat to us all.
It must be eliminated.
Through here.
- Commander.
- Minister.
The Council has given you the green light.
But we strongly recommend that international law
and the civil rights of all
concerned should be respected.
Of course. I shall see to it personally.
Agents Valerian and Laureline will be responsible
for your personal protection.
Sir, that won't be necessary.
I have a unit of K-Tron that are personally trained...
It's a direct order from the government, Commander.
The two agents need to report on the outcome of the operations.
As you wish.
Gentlemen, lady, good luck.
Since we have to be on the same team,
You mind giving us an update on the operation?
I'll be speaking to the Security Council in a few minutes.
You'll have all the details you need to know.
This is gonna be a lot of fun.
Hey, handsome. You're looking a lot better.
You know, I remember learning about you guys at school.
I'm dying to find out if what they say is true.
Wow.
I need to take you shopping with me.
Wait for me here.
- Anything?
- Not yet.
We haven't got a peep out of him.
But I'm trying something new.
One more hour.
If he hasn't talked, finish him off.
Yes, sir.
If anything goes wrong with this operation,
you know what you have to do.
Wow.
Looks like you're taking my protection very seriously.
His protection, actually. He's one of a kind.
You sure he needs to come along in such a dangerous mission?
The Mül converter is capable of reproducing
any conceivable product in record time.
It will come in very handy if we have to negotiate.
You have the K-Trons on your command
I'm surprised negotiating's on the table.
You take care of my security, Major.
I'll take care of any negotiations.
Give it to me.
I don't think that's a very good idea.
For your personal security,
why don't you let Agent Laureline look after
the little guy for safe keeping?
I don't think so, Major. It's against protocol.
I am the highest-ranking...
That animal is the last living specimen of its species.
The whole universe is after it.
That's why Major Valerian would rather I held on to it.
All right.
Just don't leave my sight.
Commander, the Council is waiting.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Stay here.
On route to the meeting.
Received, General.
You stay on back up.
I'll take the front line.
Yes, sir!
Delegates, thank you for answering the call so quickly.
As the elective representative of the Human Federation,
I have called this meeting of the Alpha Security Council
to update you regarding the state of emergency
we find ourselves in.
As you all know,
The heart of historic Alpha Station
has been contaminated by a force whose power
we do not know the origins of.
The Human Federation has launched
several small military attacks
in order to ascertain the severity of the threat.
But these have all ended in failure.
And with some significant losses among our troops.
In light of this alarming and growing threat to us all,
the Human Federation is seeking...
Everything okay?
You're missing out. I'm having a lot of fun.
Yeah, don't worry, we'll be on the beach soon.
I can now answer some questions you may have
about the details of the operation.
13th battalion, Special Assaults Division.
Ooh, there she is!
- I told you she's there.
- Yoohoo!
- Ugh, that's all I need.
- Agent Laureline!
- What?
- Doghan Daguis.
Oh.
- Nice to see you again.
- Agent Laureline.
Splendid as ever.
Just tell me what you want.
- We go where work calls.
- We speak over 5,000 languages.
- Which can be handy.
- In a party like this.
Need our services?
I have my own personal translator.
Now, move.
Ask them if they have Intel on Mül.
Planet Mül, ring any bells?
- A highly sensitive matter.
- Best person to speak to.
- Would be Major Samk.
- Alex?
- Major Samk died a year ago.
- Well, yes, a most curious demise.
- That was not fully explained.
- Murder, some might call it.
- Major Samk was an expert on Planet Mül.
- He took all that precious information.
- To the grave with him.
- What a waste.
- If you receive any Intel on this planet, we're interested.
- It would be a pleasure to work for you, Laureline.
- Mmhmm.
- Before we go,
- We would like to give you.
- Some info.
- For free.
- For free?
- Mmhmm.
- You guys must be sick.
- The converter is precious.
- And highly sought after.
- Mercenaries will come.
- To retrieve it.
- Sooner than you think.
What kind of mercenaries?
- The first tip was free.
- You must pay for more.
- You get a discount, of course.
General,
- We have an alert on section B.
- Alex, what's that?
A dozen individuals approaching.
- What kind of individuals?
- Undetectable for now.
- It appears your info just lost its value.
- Now get out of my face.
Move, pigeons.
- She just called us pigeons.
- What's a pigeon?
- I don't know.
- Where are they coming from?
Everywhere. They're going through the walls.
- Alex, I need to know the attackers' identity.
- Everyone, please evacuate.
- I cannot read their DNA.
- What?
- Sir,
The door's locked.
- We can't get out.
- Laureline.
- I'm coming.
- Evacuate the Commander.
- Copy that.
- General, secure that door.
- Commander...
...what's going on?
- We need to evacuate.
- Let's go.
- It's not working.
- What?
- Alex, open the door.
- What was that?
- The Pearls.
- They took the Commander.
- Here, take this. Free the General.
- Go to the command room and track 'em from there.
- Okay.
- Are we back to full power?
- Yes, sir, just now.
- Everybody, back to your posts!
- Status on Major Valerian. Level five emergency.
- Confirmed.
- Valerian, I've got you on visual.
- Okay, but I've lost track of 'em.
- Try to locate the Commander.
- Okay, I've got him.
- He's near the docking bay,
so he must be headed towards the vessel.
- Okay. What's the shortest way there?
- North-northeast, 113 degrees.
60... 70... 80... 90...
- That leads me straight into a wall.
- You said you wanted the shortest way.
- It may be the shortest way, but it's not the easiest.
- Keep going.
You're almost there.
- They've reached another ship.
- No tags. Unknown model.
- Valerian, they've boarded. Change of plan.
140 degrees east. Alex will pick you up.
- 81?
- That's it, 81, straight.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! 81, you're sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- Because I just went through, and I'm falling in space.
- Sorry, my mistake. It was number 18.
- That's okay. We all make mistakes.
Any idea to get me out of here?
- Alex, pick him up on 81.
- I'm in. Close it.
Ah. Bring on the beach.
I'm not sure where you come from.
But I know where I wanna send you.
- Valerian, hold still.
- We're analyzing its system of defense.
Major, their protective shield is too sophisticated.
You won't get through.
- I'm gonna try something bigger.
Shit.
- Laureline, which one has the Commander on board?
- Nine o'clock, lower level. Hurry up.
That's the one. Don't lose it.
Valerian, be careful.
- The Intruder's too big to follow him.
I'm gonna take the Skyjet.
- Okay.
Okay, Valerian. You're near the dead zone.
Reel them in before I lose you.
- I'm working on it.
- Valerian, you need to go faster.
Valerian, you've got ten seconds before I lose you.
- Take that!
Who's the clever one now?
- Valerian, you've got five seconds.
- Oh, no, not me.
- Valerian?
- I can't slow him down.
Come on.
Entering Red Zone.
- Valerian, do you hear me?
- Laureline!
I'm losing control!
Laureline!
- Valerian, answer me.
Valerian, answer me.
Major, respond.
- Alex, can you help?
There's too much interference.
I've lost the Major's signal.
- Valerian? Valerian?
Valerian, do you copy?
We've lost him.
- Sergeant, where are you going?
- To grab my Skyjet.
- You won't be going after him.
- Why not?
- That zone is under enemy control. It's too dangerous.
- An enemy that we don't know.
- An enemy that's just attacked us.
By putting us to sleep and not hurting a single one of us.
Why would they spare our lives?
Give me one good reason.
- I don't know.
Valerian has seen these creatures before.
They are from planet Mül.
- Planet Mül was destroyed 30 years ago.
You're not making any sense.
- It's our mission that doesn't make sense, Sir.
Someone is lying to us.
And while you find out who, I'm going to go save my partner.
General, Major Valerian is an invaluable agent.
You cannot afford to lose him.
- No, I can't afford to lose both of you in one day.
Restrain her.
Put us on high alert.
And find me the Commander.
- Yes, sir.
- Listen, I don't wanna tell you guys how to do your jobs,
but don't you think you should cuff me?
Firstly, because it's protocol.
But secondly, because I'm very tempted to escape.
Good job, boys.
We need to talk.
- Oh, it's dark in here.
- Not supposed to be here.
- Ow!
- Sorry.
- If you don't help me find Valerian,
then this bullet's gonna find you.
- You're up first.
- No, no, no, no.
- It's to avoid such situations.
- But all of our information.
- Is divided three ways.
- Kill one of us.
- And you kill the information.
- What a pity that would be.
- Okay, you're gonna have to give me credit, though.
beause I don't have much on me.
- Oh, how tiresome.
- If the Commander were here,
he could use the converter to pay us.
- But he is been abducted.
- Precisely, because he had the converter on him.
- Unless for security reasons.
- Someone else was carrying it on them.
- How in space did you get that info?
- It's not info.
- Just deduction.
- We know how humans work.
- They're all so predictable.
- Clearly, you've never met a woman.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Calm down.
- What do you want to know?
- Valerian's exact location.
- Hard to tell.
- But we know how to track him down.
- With complete precision.
- How much?
- 100 badools.
- Each.
- Forget about it.
- This is all I have.
- Diamonds are less valuable than badools.
- The negotiation is over.
- We trust you.
- And under the circumstances.
- We accept the deal.
- Good. Now, take me to Valerian. Now.
- Follow us.
- Phillips, head to the location where the Major disappeared.
Mylo, track down Agent Laureline and bring her in.
Neza, inform the Minister.
- Yes, sir.
Just give me a few minutes, please.
- Declassify.
I need all information on the planet Mül.
Well, who has authority over this file?
- Here we are.
- Do not like this place.
- Give it to me.
- Uh-huh.
- I've got a bad feeling about this idea of yours.
- Bingo.
- What do you want?
- We'd like to go fishing.
- For a cortex jellyfish.
- Male, if possible.
- Ah, it's not the season.
- Here.
- Males are harder to catch.
- And here.
- Welcome aboard.
- Uh, the thing, down.
- Down, the thing!
- This one?
- Down. Ay.
- There. Bromosaurs.
- Are they dangerous?
- Not really.
You just have to be careful they don't inhale you.
There. That one is a male.
- How can you tell?
- Oh, they're much smaller than the females.
- How do you know that that one has a jellyfish on it?
- All males do. The Bromosaurs blow out pure water
which the jellyfish can't do without.
That's why they live on them. All year round.
That's where they get their hypersensitivity from.
Soft as silk.
- Can I help? I'm a good driver.
- Shhh!
Mmm, Mmm, Ahh.
- Seat belt.
- What?
- Seat belt!
- I thought you said they weren't aggressive.
- Except when you take their little buddy.
- Great.
- I'm Bob, by the way.
- Hi.
- There's no time to lose.
- The cortex jellyfish is extremely fragile.
- Show it images of Valerian.
- And it will show you what it has seen.
- Sure, but how?
- You have to put it.
- On your head.
- Down to your shoulders.
- You're kidding.
- Never when we're working.
- Through a kind of osmosis.
- You'll be able to communicate.
- But be very careful.
- Not to stay under there.
- Longer than a minute.
- Because then, it starts to feed.
- On your memory.
- Great.
- Anything else I should know
before I voluntarily stick my head on his mouth?
Actually, it's not his mouth.
- You can begin.
- Good luck.
- Don't forget.
- One minute.
- Not a second more.
- I knew I had it in here somewhere.
- Ah.
- There we are.
- Pee-yew.
- Ah.
- There we go.
- This is so exciting.
Valerian?
I only work with my partner.
Valerian, answer me.
What can I do to make it up to you?
- 30 seconds.
Valerian, answer me.
Take that.
Laureline! I'm loosing control!
Valerian!
Valerian! Laureline!
- 40 seconds!
Valerian!
- 50 seconds!
- Get out!
- Now!
- 55 seconds!
Valerian!
- Careful!
- Incredible!
- One minute!
- And ten seconds!
- A record!
- Okay.
L.-630.-E.
S.U.L- DEACTIVATED.
Any idea what that means, guys?
- Level 630 east.
- Most likely a self bay pod.
- Deactivated, apparently.
Okay, okay, thanks.
- You need a detailed map?
- We biologically traced Sergeant Laureline to here.
- What's she doing out by the Galana Sea?
- No idea, sir.
- She stole a vehicle.
She headed into the Red Zone.
And we lost track of her.
She must've located the Major.
- General, there are 3 civilians here
who claim to have information that might interest you.
- Show them in.
- It's you three.
- Our humble respects, General.
- May you be healthy.
- And prosperous.
- What do you want?
- We have information of the utmost importance.
- That we're ready to sell.
- 100 badools.
- Each!
- Shoot.
- Valerian!
Move, lizard.
Valerian?
Valerian, do you hear me?
Valerian, wake up.
Valerian, please.
Stay with me, Valerian.
Come on, come on.
- What are you doing here?
- I came to get you.
You totaled your Skyjet, remember?
- Yeah.
I've lost it in the curve.
- You mean, you almost died. You're lucky I found you.
- What about the Commander. Do we know where he is?
- There's no sign of him.
Their spaceship went into a Red Zone.
- We gotta find him.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
Is that all?
- What do you mean?
- No «Thank you»? No «Well done»?
- I would've done the same for you.
- You little prick!
- Whoa, hey, hey, hey! Chill!
- I trusted you more than I trusted myself...
Isn't that what you wanted?
- No.
- You are an amazing woman, Laureline.
It's no wonder I wanna marry you.
- Why would I wanna marry an ungrateful, conceited...
- Because you can't live without him.
I mean look, whenever he wanders off, you go chasing after him.
- I was just doing my job, Major.
Now, will you please let me get back to the mission?
- Yeah... sure.
- Good.
- Sergeant.
- Captain, what's going on here?
- I report directly to the Commander Arun Filitt...
- I am General Okto-Bar!
In the absence of the Commander, I am in command on Alpha.
Arrest this man.
Now, release that one.
I apologize for your mistreatment.
We will take you to a jail,
but our doctors will take care of you.
- Help us.
- If you need my help,
you have to tell me everything you know.
But first of all, why are you attacking us?
- Because you have...
...what we need.
- Didn't you say that the girl in your dream
had a converter just like mine?
- That's right.
So, if the animals are native on their planet,
then surely it's understandable that they want to retrieve
the last living specimen.
- Yeah, and they probably kidnapped the Commander
because they thought he was carrying it.
- Yeah, once they find out he's not,
then I'll be at the top of their list.
- Don't worry, I'm not letting you go anywhere.
- No, I'm not letting you go anywhere.
- Pretty butterfly.
- Sure, but whatever you do, don't touch 'em.
- Why?
- Because some of them are...
- No!
- Valerian!
- Laureline!
I'm coming!
- Let me go, fatty. Come on, put me down!
- Sorry, I'm inedible.
- Valerian!
Major, I can read your signal now.
- Alex, any ideas?
The only way to get in without creating a
a severe diplomatic incident is to pass for one of them.
I suggest you try to find a Glamopod.
- Thanks, Alex.
- Have you run a DNA search?
- Yes.
- But it didn't match any of the 800 million species
we have in our database.
- Well, how is that possible?
- Either it belongs to a completely unknown species...
- Or?
- Or their species was deliberately deleted from the database.
- General,
the Major has resurfaced at the edge of the Red Zone.
- Which district is he in?
- Paradise Alley.
- Notify all units.
All units: Search Alert.
Major Valerian. Not dangerous.
Find and assist.
- Can I help you?
- Sure, you can. Move.
- Good. Now slide your gun into my holster.
Hold still.
It tastes its desires...
in Paradise Alley.
♫ We got the Refugee Allstars rub-a-dubbing in the club ♫
♫ Wyclef Jean ♫
♫ John Forte ♫
♫ Stayin' Alive ♫
♫ Praswell ♫
♫ Nah mean, the streets are getting ♫
♫ a little crazy ♫
- Hi, sugar!
♫ Looka looka looka here ♫
- Do you want a ride?
♫ Shorty got back ♫
♫ Should I ask her for a dance? ♫
♫ Hold on, there's too many in the wolf pack ♫
♫ And besides, Dirty Cash talking to her ♫
Hey, Err...
Hey, do you wanna fly?
I'm allergic to feathers.
My hero!
You've got the wrong guy.
♫ But it's all right cause it's Saturday night ♫
♫ So mister funkmaster, pump the Bee Gees ♫
♫ And all you college students, play your Ouijas ♫
Parisienne, Mon chéri
I... uh... I don't speak French.
♫ - E, get the CD from Sam Goody, hee hee! ♫
Hello.
It tastes its desires in Paradise Alley.
Come on, out! You pervert!
Hey! Cowboy!
You've come to the right spot.
This is the best damn club on the whole Space Station.
- Hey, Jolly!
- I'll be with you in a second.
I'm looking for something special.
Well, of course you are. Whatever it is you want,
I got it!
I'm not so sure...
Tell me. What is it you want?
What you looking for?
A Glamopod.
You are so lucky.
I got the best one in the whole universe. Come on.
- Jolly!
- Just...
Come on.
Hey, I work for the government.
If you wanna avoid a diplomatic incident,
you better let me go right now!
Look, listen, I didn't come here to get a makeover.
I need to leave. Do you understand?
I can't believe it.
I'm not here to try on a stupid dress!
Call your chief or a translator so we can at least communicate.
Do you understand what I am saying?
Okay.
This is where you lose the hardware, soldier boy.
Oh, I'd rather hold on to it. I'm on duty.
Yeah, well, unfortunately, rules are rules
and this is a place where we make love, not war.
Here's your ticket.
Don't lose it.
Could we make a deal?
Let's not talk about business.
Can we just talk pleasure?
What kinda music you into, huh?
You like Techno?, Macro?, Bio?, Nano?
- I'm more Retro.
- Ah, me too.
Oldies are goodies.
Sit down. Relax.
And enjoy the show.
♫ Hey! ♫
♫ La, la ♫
♫ La, la, la, la, la ♫
♫ Hey! ♫
♫ La, la ♫
♫ Lum bala la ho la ha ♫
♫ La ho la ho ho ho ♫
♫ Hey! ♫
♫ Oh-oh ♫
♫ Hey'a, hey'a ♫
♫ Hey! ♫
♫ Ta da da da da ♫
♫ Mmm ♫
♫ Yeah! Ragga, ragga ♫
♫ Hmm ♫
♫ Ragga, ragga ♫
♫ Hmm Yeah! ♫
♫ Hmm ♫
♫ Yeaaah! ♫
♫ Do you want, do you want we roll ♫
♫ Like you used to enjoy in control ♫
♫ Love me one, love me one, love me whole ♫
♫ I'm sure you can't control ♫
♫ Come, hey, control ♫
♫ Daddy, go ♫
I don't know how long I can keep this.
So, what'll it be, soldier?
Look, that was... really cool.
But not exactly what I'm looking for right now.
Well, I have a whole lot more in stock
if you just tell me what you have in mind.
I have a lot in mind.
And no time for this. I'll pass.
Listen, I have a problem and I really need your help.
You didn't like my performance?
No, no, yeah, I... I loved it.
Absolutely!
I started at age four.
Learning my trade in all the top schools.
I can play anyone or anything.
I'm sure you can.
I know all of Shakespeare by heart, if you want.
Poetry, maybe? You like poetry?
Uh, sure.
Rimbaud? Valerian?
Tough choice.
"I'm afraid of a kiss"
"Like the kiss of a bee"
"I suffer like this"
"And wake endlessly"
"I'm afraid of a kiss"
How 'bout I tell you
what I really have in mind?
Quit screaming!
Where'd you get a gun?
Major Valerian!
I advise you to put that gun down!
And I advise you to sit down.
Okay, okay, okay.
Please, no, don't shoot me!
What the hell is that?
That is you when you were ten.
You're not going to shoot yourself, are you?
Will you go back to normal, please?
Okay, okay.
No, not... this normal. The other one.
Thank you.
What's your name?
Whatever you want it to be, sweetie.
I don't have time for your games, sweetie.
Come on, tell me what's your name.
Bubble.
Look, Bubble, I lost my partner.
If you help me find her, I'll set you free.
What good is freedom when you're an
illegal immigrant far away from home?
I work for the government, okay?
You have an ID pass. You have my word.
If I leave, Jolly will kill me.
No, Jolly won't kill anybody ever again.
So, what do you say,
Bubble?
You really liked my performance?
Best I ever saw.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hm-hm.
So, ugh, I'm gonna take ten.
You two keep an eye on old soldier boy, huh?
He seems like a real freak to me.
Okay, Bubble, get off me.
All right, all right, I'm doing this.
Hey, you good?
Thanks.
You wanna go in there?
Yeah, but no foreigners are allowed.
The only way in is to look like one of them.
Oh, no, no, no!
I've never played a Boulan-Bathor before!
What? Are you an artist or not?
Yes, but, I need time to get into my role, and
capture my movements and behaviors, and
character's arc, we do a couple rehearsals,
you give me some notes...
Well, a little improve never hurt anyone.
- Let's go.
- All right.
- Turn around.
Ugh.
- This is not right.
- I need a manicure.
- Don't you think the hat might be a little bit over-the-top?
- Never mind.
- Hey, hey, hey! What are you doing?
- Give me a second to get the hang of it.
- Hurry, people are staring at us.
I told you I needed rehearsals.
This is a heavy role.
- Much better. You're doing good.
- General,
we picked up the Major's trail again.
- Finally. Where is he?
- In Boulan-Bathor territory.
- In the Bou... What...?
Nobody gets in there.
- And definitely not out of there.
- We need reinforcements. Inform the Minister.
- Yes, sir.
- So, how did you come to lose your partner?
- Because I'm stupid.
- What do you mean?
All I do is flirt and joke.
- Oh, trying to be cool rather than being honest.
- Story of my life.
How young were you when you lost your mom?
- Please don't go there right now.
- It's okay to be vulnerable sometimes.
- Can we stop this and go back to the mission, please?
And don't touch anything!
- Well, it wouldn't hurt you to show some weakness.
- I'm not good at that.
- It will make her feel important.
- Yeah, believe me,
she's already the most important thing in my life.
I think he wants us to join the group.
Uh, I'm not sure that's a good idea.
It doesn't look like he's giving us much choice.
- What's going on?
I guess it's lunchtime for Emperor Boulan III.
Ugh. Bussing tables? Every artist's worst nightmare.
Never mention this to anyone, okay?
Thank your lucky stars we're not the main course.
I'm gonna be sick.
There she is!
Wow, you're right. She's a 10.
Hi.
Something's wrong.
How 'bout I do a little dance to create a diversion?
No, thanks.
You guys are in big trouble!
I think we should go.
I think you should let me handle this.
Valerian!
I'm in here!
Hey!
You're gonna be a good boy, okay?
Down. Stay.
Laureline, it's me, Valerian.
What?
Bubble, get off me.
Yes, you're right. Let's go! Whoo!
Ah, excuse me, your highness.
Hey, baby.
I deserve that.
Watch out!
This is a lady. You can't fight her.
Let's talk about this. You're gonna hurt yourself.
I warned you.
Well, that's what I call a partner.
Woo-hoo!
Bravo! That was amazing.
I'm very impressed!
Hey.
Trust me on this.
3rd Regiment approaching, sir.
- Any news from our agents?
- None.
And the Commander, any ransom demands?
Negative. Minister online.
Okay.
- My respects, Minister.
- General.
You've been authorized by the Council
to assume command of this operation.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, sir.
But to fulfill my mission,
I will need full access to Commander Filitt's data.
According to regulations,
that isn't possible without his explicit agreement.
The Commander may well be dead.
If I am to succeed in my new assignment,
I need to know everything.
Access granted.
Thank you, sir.
Declassify.
Request file on the planet Mül.
Request authorized.
Huh, the conflict with the southern territories.
The war against Arysum-Kormn led to the destruction of planet Mül.
Tell me more about the planet.
The planet was uninhabited.
Who's in charge of this operation?
This does not smell good.
I told you there was a door.
Someone didn't look over the plans
before they came rushing in.
As usual.
You'd rather I show up after the main event?
I'd rather you took me someplace other than a giant trash can.
Bubble?
Bubble, where are you?
- Where is she?
- She was right behind us.
I'm here.
What's wrong?
I must've been injured during the fight.
Bubble, tell me what to do.
Nothing you could do.
Anyway, where I'm from...
Life is more painful than death.
Don't say that.
Unfortunately, it's true.
It's a drag when you don't have an identity to call your own.
You do have an identity.
You're the greatest artist I've ever seen.
I thank you.
It was my pleasure performing for you.
I leave you my kingdom.
Take good care of it.
I will.
- But most importantly...
- Yeah?
Take good care of her.
Love her without measure.
"There's beggary in love that can be reckoned."
Let's go.
All the battleships have docked, General.
Good. I want Section One operative as soon as possible.
What are these K-Tron doing there?
The Commander programmed them personally.
They can't be deactivated.
Great. That's all we need.
Do you have any idea where we're going?
Yeah, sure, I mean...
- I guess...
- You're sure, or you guess?
Look, I know it sounds strange, but it...
The Princess... she's guiding me.
The Princess? She's guiding you?
Yeah, the... Look, it's hard to explain, but...
It's like she's... been with me the whole time.
Wait.
You mean to tell me that you've had a woman
inside of you since the beginning?
Laureline, can we just keep going, please?
Sure.
Ladies first.
Ha. Hilarious.
- What you doin'?
- Villainy, villainy!
Captain Kris. Section One operational, General.
Proceed. A unit of K-Trons will join you.
- That won't be necessary.
- Commander's orders.
Not mine.
Copy that. Move on.
We've been manipulated from the start.
What do you mean?
We're in the middle of the dead zone
and we can breathe properly.
It seems there's no sign of contamination.
The Commander's fully aware of what's behind this
so-called absolute evil.
What?
Pearls.
My name is Tsûuri. I am the Emperor's son.
Great, how about you introduce us to daddy?
He is expecting you.
Try to contact the General. Get everyone down here.
I'll buy us some time.
How about you run for back up for a change?
Unbelievable.
Follow me.
I'd like you to meet my father.
The Emperor.
My name is Haban-Limaï
And this is my wife, Aloï
We're pleased to welcome you here.
My son sensed the presence of his sister,
Princess Lïho-Minaa in you.
It seems she chose you.
What do you mean?
At the moment of passing,
Pearls release all the energy left in their body
in the form of a wave
which travels through space and time.
Sometimes, it finds a benevolent host.
Lïho-Minaa chose you
to be the guardian of her soul.
Told you.
My daughter.
I'm so happy to see you.
Same here.
I mean... she is, too.
What exactly happened to you and your people?
Our planet was a true paradise
on which we lived in harmony
with the elements.
Our main activity was fishing for the pearls.
who possessed phenomenal energy.
They fertilized our lands.
Controlled the winds and tides.
Three time a year, we gave to the earth.
What the sea has given us.
We lived like this in harmony
for centuries and centuries.
Until the day of the apocalypse.
In the sky, over our planet
other people blindly fought out a brutal war.
A war between people we didn't even know.
Missiles loaded, sir.
Engage fusion missiles.
Do you confirm, sir?
Yes, I do.
At your command.
By the grace of God.
Your daughter died during the battle.
Yes, like six million others.
What happened after the explosion?
We drifted in space for many years.
Aboard a vessel we salvaged from the wreckage.
And that was half-destroyed.
Come back to your room.
This new environment was quite different from ours.
And at first, we needed time to understand it.
Absorbing the vast knowledge stored in its database.
We learned languages and mathematics.
Physics, chemistry, and philosophy.
We learned about the millions of planets and stars
and moons in a universe we never knew existed.
And we learned of the countless species who inhabit this universe.
Including humans, the ones who destroyed our planet.
Thank you.
Time has not dimmed the memories of our loss.
But it has allowed us to let go of our anger
toward those responsible.
Hey! Look.
Then one day, we were picked up by scrap dealers
travelling the galaxy.
After a few years, their hold was full.
And they went off to sell their cargo
on a huge construction site.
- Alpha.
- Yes.
The City of a Thousand Planets.
Where for hundreds of years,
so many species have shared their knowledge
and intelligence with each other.
In the shadows of Alpha, we lived undetected.
All the while watching and learning from each of them.
Until we acquired both the knowledge
and the materials to build a vessel of our own.
Our planet is gone forever.
But with what we have learned
we are now able to replicate and restore our lost world.
Amazing.
There are only two things that we lack.
A Mül converter.
And the pearl.
The only one Tsûuri managed to salvage.
We are survivors.
But that makes us witnesses.
Witnesses of a past humans want to erase
and forget forever.
We can forgive, but how can we forget?
So, we left you no choice but to steal the converter.
And Tsûuri hired a professional.
Igon Siruss.
Then Major Valerian intervenes and retrieves the converter.
Which left you with only one choice,
kidnap the Commander, force him to tell you the truth.
You know our story now.
Our destiny is in your hands.
Major,
arrest these creatures immediately.
They kidnapped me. They're extremely dangerous.
They're Pearls from the planet Mül.
I heard their ridiculous story. That's impossible.
Mül was uninhabited.
Their existence proves the contrary, doesn't it?
I am telling you, there was no life on the planet.
The detectors were categorical.
Arrest them.
How can you be so sure?
Because... I write the reports and...
And you were on board.
Yes. Yes, I was on board.
And we had much more serious things to worry about.
Our cruisers were being decimated.
We lost 500,000 soldiers in a day.
It was complete carnage!
You were so preoccupied, you didn't see the detectors
indicating signs of life on the planet.
Or even worse, perhaps you knew that planet was inhabited
and you sacrificed it.
Commander, the planet is inhabited.
By primitive lifeforms.
No, Commander.
I've detected a complex language and huge cerebral energy.
Major.
History is on the march.
And neither you nor a bunch of savages
are gonna stand in its way.
So, when you realized survivors from planet Mül
were living in the heart of Alpha,
you decided to erase any trace of your mistake.
Rather than accept the consequences.
I want no survivors.
And you destroyed all the evidence Major Samk had against you.
What did you expect me to do?!
It was the only way!
Admitting to an error on this scale
would've exposed our government to colossal damages
and compensation claims.
Our economy would never recover.
In one instance, we would've lost
our supremacy and our leadership.
There would've been immediate sanctions.
And it's a pretty good bet
that we would've been banished from Alpha.
And denied access to the greatest
market of knowledge and intelligence.
Is that what you would've wanted for your fellow citizens?
Leading them into ruin and degradation?
Forcing them to go backwards 1,000 years?
Our council saw fit to protect our citizens first and foremost.
Is that not its duty?
And mine?
And yours?!
Or would you rather risk
wrecking our economy for the sake of a bunch of...
Savages?
You are totally under the influence of these creatures.
Do not confuse the issue.
He's the threat.
He's the enemy.
You are your own worst enemy, Commander.
Unless you make peace with your past,
you won't have a future.
Major,
I order you to arrest this man.
Can we talk man-to-man for a second?
Major, what are you doing?
I taught him how to do that.
Nice talk.
Move on, move on, move on.
Section One is entering the Red Zone.
Prepare Section Two for an advance also.
Look, this was a lot of fun
but we gotta report back to our people.
Here, that's yours.
I'm gonna make this right. I promise.
Let's get this guy...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what are you doing?
I'm giving them back the converter.
No.
The pearl is useless without this.
Yeah, but...
- Will you give us a second, please?
- What?
That converter is government property.
Most likely the last one in the whole universe.
Oh, so, you buy into the Commander's
what's mine is mine and what's yours is mine philosophy?
No, I buy into my oath of allegiance.
We have no authority to hand it over.
The Federation messed up and must make amends.
Yeah, I agree, but that's not for us to decide.
Leave it to the courts.
They're 18 light-years away, Valerian.
Only we can make this right.
Laureline, I'm a soldier.
I play by the rules.
It's what makes me who I am.
You see...
That's why I don't wanna marry you
because you really don't know what love is.
Oh, come on, this has nothing to do with love.
That's where you're wrong.
Love is more powerful than anything else, Valerian.
It breaks all rules and laws.
And overpowers any army or government.
Just look at her.
For one second, put yourself in her position.
She lost all of her people and her child.
And she's willing to forgive.
That's real love.
It's the trust you place in someone else, and
I thought I could be that someone else for you.
- But clearly...
- You can.
You are.
I'd die for you.
I'm not asking you to die for me.
I'm asking you to trust me.
All right. Give it to 'em.
Thank you.
We are to blame for the loss of your planet.
And we'd be honored to help you get it back.
Here.
It means 'thank you'.
Spread out!. Spread out!.
Captain, we're locked on to you.
Any sign of contamination or radiation?
Zero trace of either.
It doesn't make any sense.
Didn't you say you wanted to go to the beach?
Our daughter made a good choice.
She can rest in peace now.
We must leave now.
May you and your people live in peace
wherever you may venture in space and time.
Explosives in place, General. We're operational.
Received. Evacuate the zone.
You have four minutes.
Copy that.
Father, there are hundreds of soldiers all around the spaceship.
We will be gone in a miunte.
The troops are in position, you don't have a minute.
You have no means of communication to the outside world?
If we stop jamming signals, we are defenseless.
If you don't allow me to communicate with them,
you'll be defenseless forever.
Just one call.
- Disarm the signal.
- Thank you.
The walls stopped moving.
Something's going on.
Maintain your position. We're analyzing the data.
I can't believe they'd do that.
The General would follow procedure.
Yeah, I hate procedure.
Captain, the data shows that they've built
some kind of vessel beyond the wall.
Contact with the enemy.
Give me a physical description.
Same creatures who kidnapped the Commander.
Are they showing any signs of hostility?
Not really.
- Are they armed?
- No.
General, we're picking up a signal from the 2005 Destiny module.
What?
Sounds like Major Valerian.
Patch him through.
Major, you're online with the General.
- Major.
- Yeah.
Major Valerian and Sergeant Laureline
We're alive and on the inside of the wall.
Call off the assault immediately.
Major, I can't read your DNA codes. You know the procedure.
I have to be certain it's you.
There is no time for dumbass procedures.
We are here with a whole species of people
you've already wiped out once.
The Pearls of Planet Mül.
So, tell your men to back off
before you commit a second genocide!
That's definitely her temper.
Planet Mül was uninhabited.
Come on, you know that's not true.
The Commander was there.
He gave the orders.
And then he organized this whole procedure
to eliminate any survivors.
The living proof of his mistake.
Stop the procedure.
Maybe that'll explain why the Commander
was interrogating that creature.
-Is the Commander with you?
Come on.
Woky-wooky.
- You're gonna call.
- What?
Ow!
Let's go, my friend. Time to confess.
Hello?
No DNA code. But voice waves match.
This is General Okto-Bar. Do you read me, Commander?
What's going on?
We are ready to activate the explosive device.
In accordance with the orders you gave.
Do you confirm those orders?
Or do you have anything to tell me
That would enable me to suspend the assault?
I'm a soldier.
A soldier will always choose death over humiliation.
Annihilate them all.
What the hell are you doing?
I didn't give the orders!
Captain, cease fire immediately!
It's not us, it's the K-Trons. They're shooting at us!
Come on, you...
I'm gonna get Tsûuri some back up.
Keep an eye on him.
Oh, he's not going anywhere.
Get down! Take cover!
Alex, load me up with all you've got.
- Copy that.
- Thanks.
Neza, stop this countdown now!
- Yes, sir.
Hurry, Neza!
How much time left?
Ten seconds!
- Hurry!
- Neza...
... check for survivors.
- Captain, status report.
Nothing's left.  Just a gaping hole.
They left with their spaceship.
Everything's vanished.
- And our agents, Valerian and Laureline?
- No, nothing.
- And the Commander?
- Anyone there?
- Wait, I hear something.
There's a body.
- Get me down from here, you children!
- It's the Commander.
- Is he alive?
- Affirmative.
Alive and kicking.
- Good.
Arrest him.
Help!
Do you have any idea what they left us?
- We're two hours away from vacation.
I fired the distress beacons.
- Two hours?
- Yeah, I know, two hours alone with me. What a drag.
- No kidding. It's basically an eternity.
- Hey...
Now that our mission's over,
Maybe we could finish our conversation.
- What conversation?
- We were talking about the future.
- Really?...
... and what does the future hold?
You.
Me.
Us.
«Happy birthday.»
- Thank you, Valerian.
That is so romantic.
Did you really think of this yourself?
- Yeah. You mean so much to me, you know.
Laureline...
... will you do me the honor of becoming my wife?
- For better or worse?
Uh, worse? Is that negotiable?
- No.
- All right, then.
- Is that a yes?
- It's a maybe.
- I'm confused. Is this how love works?
- No, this is how I work.
- You spent a day in a woman's body.
Did you not learn anything?
- Yeah.
I did learned something.
- What?
- I want only your name on my playlist.
Subtitled  by   TIEN SHEN LONG
♫ I gotta find myself, gonna find it now ♫
♫ I gotta be a man, I gotta find him now ♫
♫ I gotta be a man ♫
♫ They wanna take me down, wanna see me crawl ♫
♫ I gotta be a man, I gotta find him now ♫
♫ I gotta be a man ♫
♫ I gotta be the man ♫
♫ I gotta find myself, gonna find it now ♫
♫ I gotta be a man, I gotta find him now ♫
♫ I gotta be a man ♫
♫ I gotta be the man ♫
♫ When I come to town for the last time ♫
♫ Pull up in a fast car for the first time ♫
♫ I'm gonna say goodbye ♫
♫ You didn't see me cry ♫
♫ I got a million on my soul ♫
♫ I go build an army on my own ♫
♫ They put a bounty on my soul ♫
♫ Won't you leave me alone more ♫
♫ Oh, leave me alone more ♫
♫ I gotta be a man ♫
♫ Won't you leave me alone more ♫
♫ Oh, leave me alone more ♫
♫ I gotta be a man ♫
♫ Oh, hold my fire ♫
♫ Oh-oh ♫
♫ I gotta find myself, gonna find it now ♫
♫ I gotta be a man, I gotta find him now ♫
♫ I gotta be the man ♫
♫ Your stare makes me freeze but I can't stay still ♫
♫ Those eyes keep me up longer than any other pill ♫
♫ And I know, being together ♫
♫ We feel like forever ♫
♫ And now, more than ever ♫
♫ I feel everything (feeling everything) ♫
♫ You make me feel so crazy, I've never felt so sane ♫
♫ Beaten up by love but the feelings still remain ♫
♫ You should know, if you want it ♫
♫ It's yours So come and get it ♫
♫ Right now, more than ever ♫
♫ I feel everything (feeling everything) ♫
♫ All I got (I'm yours) ♫
♫ I'll give it to you (Be mine) ♫
♫ You're in my brain (I'm yours) ♫
♫ And my heart too (Be mine) ♫
♫ Because I am yours (I want you) ♫
♫ If you want me too (I want you) ♫
♫ Tell me you want me too (I want you) ♫
♫ 'Cos I'll give it all to you ♫
♫ I'm scared that I'm falling ♫
♫ Come catch me I'm falling ♫
♫ My heart is calling ♫
♫ You can't stop me roaring, I'm soaring, I'm sky high ♫
♫ I'm scared that I'm falling ♫
♫ I'm blind and I'm falling ♫
♫ My love is calling ♫
♫ You can't stop me roaring, I'm soaring ♫
♫ Come jump with me and fly ♫
♫ I never thought I'd fall like this ♫
♫ I've jumped right into this eternal bliss ♫
♫ And I know being together ♫
♫ We feel like forever ♫
♫ But now, more than ever ♫
♫ I feel everything (feeling everything) ♫
♫ All I got (I'm yours) ♫
♫ I'll give it to you (Be mine) ♫
♫ You're in my brain (I'm yours) ♫
♫ And my heart too (Be mine) ♫
♫ Because I am yours (I want you) ♫
♫ If you want me too (I want you, be mine) ♫
♫ Tell me you want me too (I want you, I'm yours) ♫
♫ 'Cuz I'll give it all to you ♫
♫ I'm scared that I'm falling ♫
♫ (Feeling everything) ♫
Subtitled  by   TIEN SHEN LONG