Captain!
Is that a trench?
It looks like there's more of them inside.
Echo 2-6 to command.
Colonel, we've got eyes on
three Kong in the north woods.
One of them is armed.
And our donkey
just spotted another trench.
Maybe the base is near.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir, copy. Over.
Hey, donkey.
Preacher.
The one with the gun.
As soon as the gunner's down,
you guys take out the trench.
Yes, sir.
Fire!
Come on!
Reload!
Fall back! Fall back!
Colonel, do you copy?
Colonel!
Who is this?
Preacher, sir!
It's Preacher!
Where are you, soldier?
I need your position.
I don't know!
What do you see?
I can't see anything, sir.
We lost a lot of men,
and the captain is dead, sir.
Okay, calm down.
You're in command now.
Command, sir?
I think it's just me
all by myself now.
Take control.
Colonel, I don't think I'm gonna make it, sir.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, sir.
Listen to me.
You kill as many as you can.
No! No, no!
Sixty-three dead.
You're him.
You're Caesar.
We've been searching for you for so long.
We heard you had
a hidden command base.
But we could never find it.
Some of us started to think
that you might be dead.
But Colonel McCullough said
you were out here somewhere.
Just kill us already.
Shut up, man!
What?
They're animals.
He's gonna slaughter us.
I did not start this war.
The ape who did is dead.
His name was Koba.
I killed him.
Now, I fight only,
to protect apes.
Yeah?
What about him?
We've got 10 more just like him.
I know these apes.
They follow Koba.
They tried to kill me.
They fear what I will do to them.
So now, they serve you.
Just to survive.
I don't fear you.
You must fear.
How long you think
woods can protect you?
Humans destroy you.
Their Kerna has all power.
For them, he more than just human.
He everything.
He say, First Caesar die,
then all of you die.
Winter! Take this traitor outside!
What should we do with the humans?
You're letting us go?
Tell your Colonel you have seen me now,
and I have a message for him.
Leave us the woods,
and the killing can stop.
Do you think they will
give him the message?
They are the message, Maurice.
He will see we are not savages.
The traitor attacked me!
He got away!
Koba,
still haunts us.
Why didn't I see,
that he could not forgive,
what humans did to him?
No one could have known how much
darkness, was living inside him.
Father.
Welcome home, Rocket.
You look tired.
It was a long journey.
Father, we found something!
Come.
Mother.
Cornelius.
Say hi to your brother!
Look who's here son.
Lake.
This is it, father.
We can start over. A new home.
What is beyond those mountains, son?
Show them Rocket.
A desert!
The journey is long.
But that is why humans will not find us.
We must leave tonight!
Tonight? That's impossible!
How long can we wait, Lake?
Soldiers getting closer!
Winter!
Your son's been gone, Caesar.
He doesn't know how hard it's been.
I know you are scared,
We all are.
But we are still planning.
Yes.
We must find a safe way 9:34 AM 07-Apr-18out of the woods.
There were only two of you.
But we are...
many.
We will find a way out of here.
Apes together,
strong.
Stay here, son!
Caesar! What's wrong?
How many on patrol?
Five? Six?
Get them!
Luca, get Rocket too.
Lima four to command.
Colonel, did you...
Rocket!
What happened?
I heard him talking!
The Colonel is here!
99, target acquired.
99, target acquired. Repeat.
King Kong is dead.
Let's go.
I can get out from here.
Caesar.
We can't find Winter!
He was scared!
I think he betrayed us!
Have you found Cornelius yet?
No.
We're still searching.
Let's go look for Caesar's little son.
Cornelius!
You're safe now.
Lake.
You loved my son.
Look after his brother,
until I return.
You're not coming with us to our new home?
No.
Go with Lake.
Caesar!
You're not going after them?
Not them. Him.
Caesar, you are our leader!
We can't leave without you!
You must.
The soldiers will be back soon.
Father!
When I find him,
the soldiers will all come after me.
That may give you the best chance,
to get out of the woods.
Where is he going?
Caesar! Caesar!
The soldiers' camp is always moving.
My guards think they know where it is.
Let me take you.
You need me to back you up!
No.
Please.
I know what it's like,
to lose a son.
I may not make it back.
That's why I'm coming.
To make sure you do.
Guards think soldiers here.
Always fires burning.
No one here.
Search the area.
I'm just gonna put this down.
What's he doing out here alone?
Maybe he's a deserter?
Look around.
Take what you can.
Something wrong with her.
I don't think she can speak.
Come.
She'll die out here alone.
We cannot take her, Maurice.
I understand.
But I cannot leave her.
Did you find the Colonel?
No.
Winter.
Where's the Colonel?
He's gone.
Gone?
He left this morning,
took many men with him.
More soldiers are coming
down from the North.
The Colonel is going to meet them,
at the border.
What border?
Why?
I don't know.
But the rest of us are going tomorrow.
The donkeys think the soldiers
from the North,
are coming to help finish
off the apes for good.
That day, after the battle on the hill.
The donkey we caught promised me
the Colonel would spare my life.
If I told them where you were hiding.
Forgive me!
My son.
My...
wife...
are dead.
Now what do we do?
Wait till the soldiers go.
Follow them to the Colonel.
Koba!
Ape...
not kill ape.
The soldiers are leaving!
They stopped.
Get down!
What are they shooting at?
I don't know.
Why did they shoot you?
Like her!
He cannot speak!
He will die of those wounds.
Luca.
Where did the soldiers go?
Winter said,
they were going to a border.
Yes, but which way is that?
Bad Ape!
Bad Ape.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I don't think he understands.
I don't recognize him.
He's not one of us.
Are you alone here?
Cold?
Cold.
I see girl, I think you human.
But you ape.
Like me.
No, put down.
How long have you been here?
Long time.
Long, long time.
Home.
Old home.
Are there more like you?
More apes from zoo.
Dead.
All dead.
Long time.
Human get sick.
Ape get smart.
Then human kill ape.
But not me.
I run.
You learn to speak.
Listen human.
Bad Ape!
Bad Ape.
No.
No touch.
That's mine.
I'm okay!
Amazing...
Always thought we were the only ones.
Wonder if there are more in the world?
More apes like us.
Eat! Eat.
New friends.
Special day.
Where did you get this?
Bad place.
I find long time ago.
After zoo, I look for food.
I find human zoo.
Zoo for sick.
Big walls.
Sick human climb.
Bad human kill.
And then, all get sick.
All dead now for a long time.
Long time.
Bad humans?
Soldiers?
Soldiers.
A deserted military camp!
On the border!
Maybe the Colonel
and the troops are going there?
Is it far?
Can you take us?
Human zoo?
No. No, no go back there.
I...
Everyone dead. I come here.
Very safe here.
Never go back.
Please, you must take us!
No! No! No!
No. Cannot take! Cannot take.
Cannot take. No! No!
Look! Look! Look! Look!
More snow. Cannot go.
Must stay.
You eat, you rest.
Stay here with me.
Here, you keep.
She keep.
Who is...
child?
I don't know.
But...
she with you.
She has no one else.
I see you look at her just now.
Look sad.
You have child?
One.
The other was killed by human.
Soldier?
I...
had...
child.
You think you will find him...
at human zoo?
With soldier?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Then...
maybe I take you.
Thirsty.
Luca, come.
Let's go closer.
Keep them safe.
What are they doing?
I don't know.
What's that? A patrol?
I don't see riders.
Hold it!
I saw them coming!
At least this time.
I was able to protect you.
Caesar.
This must stop.
It's not too late to join the other apes.
We cannot turn back!
Luca gave his life!
Please.
They must pay.
Now...
you sound like Koba.
It was a mistake bringing you all.
This is my fight.
I will finish this alone.
Go.
Now!
Join the others.
What happened?
They came out of nowhere.
Attacked us.
We thought they would kill us all.
But the Colonel stopped them!
There was madness in his eyes!
He said they would use us,
before we died!
And they brought us all here!
Use you?
They've been forcing us to work!
What.
What kind of work?
Wait.
My little son. Is he here?
Grant and Lee.
Wellington...
and Napoleon.
Custer...
and Sitting Bull.
You're probably not much of a reader.
But this is a big moment.
Where were you?
We came upon your herd.
We got lucky.
But I was surprised you weren't with them.
Hey, hey, hey!
I hope you don't come
to regret sparing his life.
He's quite a good shot.
Have you finally come to save your apes?
I came for you.
For me?
Who did I kill that night?
My wife.
My son.
I'm sorry.
I was there for you.
My God.
Look at your eyes.
Almost human.
How did you know I was here?
I was told you were coming.
That more soldiers from the North,
would be joining you here.
Joining me?
To finish us off.
For good.
Who told you that?
Okay.
Let's go.
Father!
Lake.
Forgive them.
We've been through much.
What have I done?
Battalion, halt!
Blood!
Makes the grass grow!
We!
Make the blood flow!
We are the beginning!
And the end!
We haven't had food or
water since we got here.
Why do they need a wall?
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Donkey!
Get him.
Okay, okay, okay.
Leave him!
Tell them to get back to work.
Apes need food and water.
Tell them.
Give them food...
and water.
Five...
Four.
Three.
Two.
Hurry! Back to work!
String him up, donkey.
Bad place.
Bad, bad place.
What you see?
Must save them!
But how?
Must think!
What would Caesar do?
Oh, no!
Why so small?
What did the Colonel promise you?
You really,
think he'll let you live,
after we are gone?
You let them call you donkey.
You are ape.
Kerna want see you.
Interfere with the work again,
and I'll begin slaughtering
the apes one by one.
Understand?
I need that wall.
Apes need food and water.
They'll get food and water
when they finish their work.
Give apes food and water,
or they cannot finish.
You know, you are very emotional.
What makes you think you're in
a position to make demands?
Okay, let's go.
The soldiers who are coming here,
they are not coming to join you, are they?
I saw men outside on the wall,
preparing for battle.
They told me you were smart,
but that's impressive.
No.
They won't be joining me.
They are against you?
They fear me.
Why?
Because you kill your own men?
We found bodies.
Something wrong,
with these men.
Jesus Christ, you are impressive.
Well, you paint quite a picture.
What you must think of me.
I think you have no mercy.
You came here to kill me.
Were you gonna show me mercy?
I showed you mercy,
when I spared your men.
I offered you peace,
and you killed my family.
Mercy.
You have any idea what
your mercy would do to us?
You're much stronger than we are.
You're smart as hell.
No matter what you say,
you'd eventually replace us.
That's the law of nature.
The irony is, we created you.
We tried to defy nature,
bend it to our will.
Nature has been punishing us,
for our arrogance ever since.
10 months ago,
I sent out recon units to look for your base.
My own son was a soldier
with one of the units.
One day he suddenly
stopped speaking.
He became primitive,
like an animal.
They contacted me
and said that they thought
he'd lost his mind.
That the war was too much for him.
Then the man who cared for him
stopped speaking too.
Their medic had a theory,
before he stopped speaking,
that the virus that almost wiped us out,
the virus that every human
survivor still carries,
had suddenly changed.
Mutated.
And that if it spread,
it would destroy humanity
for good this time.
Not by killing us but by...
robbing us of those things
that make us human.
Our speech, our higher thinking,
It would turn us into beasts.
You talk about mercy?
What would you have done?
It was a moment of clarity for me.
I realized that I would have
to sacrifice my only son,
so that humanity could be saved.
I held that gun in my hand,
for a long time.
I pointed it,
at my only child,
he looked at me,
trust in his eyes.
Even in his primitive gaze.
I felt his...
love.
I pulled the trigger.
It purified me.
It made my purpose clear.
I gave the orders
to kill the other infected.
All of them.
Burn their belongings and anything
that might spread contamination.
Some of the men questioned my judgment.
I was asking them to do what I had done.
Sacrifice their friends,
their family.
Of course, they refused.
So I had them killed too.
Others with children,
deserted into the woods.
One of those cowards fled
to my superiors up North.
They tried to convince me
this plague could be dealt with medically.
That's when I realized that
they had learned nothing...
from our past.
You killed them too?
What did I do, Preacher?
You severed their heads, sir.
Except for the one I spared,
so that he could return,
and deliver a message.
If they wanted to relieve me
of my command,
they would have to meet me here...
and do it themselves.
This used to be a weapons depot.
They turned it into a relocation camp
when the crisis was just beginning.
But the weapons are still here,
inside the mountain.
How many men,
will be coming?
Probably all of them.
But don't get any ideas.
The only thing they fear more
than me is you apes.
This is...
a holy war.
All of human history
has led to this moment.
If we lose...
we'll be the last of our kind.
It will be a planet of apes.
And we will become your cattle.
Look at you.
You think I'm sick, don't you?
I didn't mean to kill your son.
But if his destiny was to
inherit your unholy kingdom.
I'm glad I did it.
Hey! Hey!
Get back!
Donkey, hold him!
Hey!
So emotional!
I can see how conflicted you are.
You're confused in your purpose.
You are angry at me for something
I did that was an act of war.
But you're taking this all
much too personally.
What do you think...
my men would have done to your
apes if you had killed me?
Or is killing me more important?
Soldiers everywhere!
How will we get in?
Must get in somehow,
Must get in!
In? In?
No!
No go in! No...
Friends, friends!
No, no go in.
No go in...
Friend! Friend!
Thank you. Thank you.
Friend.
You saved our lives!
Sick humans,
must have escaped down here!
No! No! No!
No! No climb!
What?
What you see?
Wonder where we are?
Oh, no, friend!
No!
No! No!
No! Come! Come!
Come! Come back!
Come! Come!
No, come!
Come! Come! Come!
Come!
Koba!
Sleep.
You cannot save them.
Apes all die here.
No!
Yes.
Join me.
If he's still alive in the morning...
he goes to work like everyone else...
or you shoot him.
Come! Come, come.
She go in!
Thirsty?
Hide!
Quick!
Humans will kill her!
I know what to do! Go!
Arms up! Hey! Hey!
Arms up!
Watch it! Watch it!
Let's go!
Keep 'em up!
Follow him down.
Keep them up!
Are there others out there?
Sweep the area.
Put him in the pen.
Feeling better?
Good.
Then we can talk about...
Escape.
Apes together strong!
We are the beginning!
And the end!
Still alive.
Send him to the quarry, alone.
Hold on.
What is this?
How did this get in there?
Get him to work.
Thirty-seven.
Fifty-five.
Thirty-seven steps to the adult cage.
Fifty-five to the children.
You know,
Kerna shoot apes,
when war is done.
His war is madness.
It won't save him...
any more than it will save you.
I save myself.
Is there anything left...
of you to save?
I do.
Apes going back to the cage?
You.
Are very brave.
Brave?
Brave!
Ape?
Me?
You are...
Nova.
Come! Come!
Come see!
Come!
34, 35, 36, 37.
30...
37!
I do.
What now?
What?
Oh, no!
No, no!
No, no, no...
Okay.
This is the ape I told you about!
Thank you.
Bad Ape.
What's wrong?
We can't keep digging!
It will flood the whole tunnel!
If we don't, we can't reach the children!
We must keep looking down there.
Find another way to reach the children.
We must leave now!
More soldiers are coming!
Humans will destroy each other!
And us with them!
We'll have to get the
children out above ground!
How?
Hey!
You animals!
Who did that?
Who was it?
Was it you?
I love you, son.
Go, go, go, go.
Hurry! Let's go!
Caesar, what's wrong?
Hurry, you must go.
Without you?
No.
Maurice was right.
I am...
like Koba.
He could not...
escape his hate.
And I still cannot escape mine.
Move, go, go.
Go, go.
Fire!
Colonel! Colonel!
Where the hell is he?
Down! Down! Down! Down!
Get down!
Take him out!
Come on, donkey.
Let's go! Reload!
Colonel, are you in there?
Colonel!
Just break it down.
Donkey!
Grenade launcher!
God damn it, donkey!
Get me the launcher!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Don't worry.
Maurice.
You are all home now.
Apes are strong.
Withe...
or without me.
Son...
will know...
who...
was...
father.
And what...
Caesar...
did...
for us.
Caesar...
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections October 2017