[dramatic music]
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
♪ ♪
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
- [buzzing]
[footsteps scampering]
Help all kids learn
and grow with PBS Kids.
Thank you for supporting
our PBS station.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[pterosaurs squawking]
[dinosaurs roaring softly]
♪ ♪
- Huh?
[playful music]
[panting]
♪ ♪
[sniffing]
Hmm?
♪ ♪
[panting]
Ah!
[ground rumbling]
[gasps, sniffs]
[train wheels squeaking]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
Whoa.
[exciting music]
[train whistle toots]
- [roars]
- Hello.
[vocalizes]
[steam hissing]
[playful music]
♪ ♪
[footsteps thumping softly]
[upbeat country music]
- ♪ All aboard
the Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ It's comin' round the bend ♪
♪ It's always been
our favorite ♪
♪ Our true
and faithful friend ♪
Gilbert?
- Uncle Conductor.
[steam hisses]
[train whistle toots]
♪ All aboard,
we've got to say ♪
♪ It's never let us down ♪
♪ It won't complain
in snow or rain ♪
♪ The finest train around ♪
all: ♪ Your wheels,
your walls, your velvet seats ♪
♪ Your waggin' tail
in back ♪
[train whistle toots]
♪ The happy chuffin' sound
you make ♪
♪ When you're boomin'
down the track ♪
♪ All aboard
the Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ It's comin' round the bend ♪
♪ Big and long
and goin' strong ♪
♪ Our true
and faithful friend ♪
- ♪ All aboard ♪
all:
♪ All aboard ♪
♪ The Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ ♪
[train whistle toots]
- Well, if it isn't
the Pteranodon family.
Hello, Tiny.
- [squawks]
- Shiny.
- [giggles]
- Don.
- ♪ La-la-loo ♪
- And Buddy, my T. rex buddy.
- [giggles]
Rawr!
- And of course,
Mr. and Mrs. Pteranodon.
Ha, that's all of you.
We haven't a moment to lose.
All aboard!
all: Yeah!
[train whistle toots]
[upbeat banjo music]
♪ ♪
- [inhales deeply,
sighs heavily]
- Tickets.
Tickets, please.
- [giggles]
- Well, looks like
we're full to capacity,
just like I like it.
Now, where are we all going?
all:
Adventure Island!
[all cheering]
- I'm just so excited.
- I can't believe
it's finally open.
- And we're all going together!
- For a dream vacation!
It's gonna be
the best time ever!
♪ La-la-loo ♪
- Time--time?
Ooh, speaking of time,
it's time for a very special
Express Time Tunnel,
which will take us
directly there.
[all cheering]
Time Tunnel!
Express Time Tunnel
to Adventure Island!
[mystical music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
Oh, my.
all:
Ooh!
Ah!
- [sighs]
Yes.
We're headed
to the middle of the sea
in the middle
of the Jurassic time period
for the grand opening
of a theme park so brand-new,
even I haven't been to it.
And I'm as excited as you are
just to take you
to Adventure Island.
- Isn't there a brand-new song
about it?
- Oh, you mean
the "Adventure Island Song"?
[all gasp]
- Exactly.
Shall we sing it,
Uncle Conductor?
- D'oh, gee, Gilbert.
[laughs]
I'm not prepared.
Plus, we just sang a song.
I don't think these folks
want to hear another--
all: Sing it, sing it,
sing it, sing it!
- Ooh, ooh, ooh!
Ooh, sing it!
Pretty, pretty please!
- Well, if our passengers
demand it.
- ♪ How come we're singing' ♪
♪ How come we're smilin' ♪
- ♪ 'Cause everyone's goin'
to Adventure Island ♪
- ♪ Did you say
Adventure Island ♪
- ♪ Yes, I did,
both: ♪ Everyone's goin'
to Adventure Island ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ And what'll we do there ♪
all: ♪ Ride the rides ♪
- ♪ Swim and glide ♪
- ♪ Swoop and dive ♪
- ♪ Yes, and when
you ride these rides ♪
♪ You get to find out
what it's like inside ♪
♪ That particular species
of dinosaur ♪
- ♪ You mean I get
to stomp and roar ♪
- Yup!
both: ♪ Crawl, swim,
fly, or soar ♪
♪ Every kid can be ♪
♪ Any dinosaur ♪
- ♪ You mean I can swim ♪
- ♪ And I can fly ♪
- ♪ Yes, on wings
across the sky ♪
- ♪ Then I wanna fly
like a pterosaur ♪
both: A sauropod
that goes on all fours ♪
- ♪ You'll do all that
and then some more ♪
all:
♪ On Adventure Island ♪
♪ Adventure Island ♪
♪ Crawl, swim, fly, or soar ♪
♪ Every kid can be ♪
♪ Any dinosaur ♪
- ♪ So much fun ♪
♪ So many rides ♪
♪ What should I go on ♪
♪ I can't decide ♪
- ♪ Well, I'm gonna try
the T. rex ride ♪
♪ I wanna find out
what it's like to be ♪
♪ A T. rex who's
as tall as a tree ♪
♪ I get to romp
and stomp and roar ♪
♪ I'll roar
till my ears get sore ♪
♪ Today I'm gonna
finally see ♪
♪ Just what it's
really like to be ♪
♪ A giant grown-up T. rex ♪
Roar!
all:
♪ On Adventure Island ♪
♪ Adventure Island ♪
♪ Crawl, swim, fly, or soar ♪
♪ Every kid can be ♪
♪ Any dinosaur ♪
- Yeah!
[all cheering]
[light music]
♪ ♪
- Mom, Dad, can I go
on all the rides all by myself?
- All by yourself?
- You mean without us?
- Yeah, after all,
I'm gonna grow up
to be a giant T. rex someday,
and they're super brave.
This sounds like
great practice.
- I don't think so, Buddy.
- Hmm.
[gasps]
What if it was all of us kids
sticking together as a group?
- Hmm, I don't know.
We'll think about it
when we get there.
- D'oh, I hope so!
I can't wait to get there!
- All in good time, Buddy.
[pocket watch chiming]
Ooh, time.
Speaking of time,
it's Adventure Island time!
Next stop, Adventure Island!
[excited chatter]
all:
Ooh, Adventure Island.
[ethereal choral music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[both giggle]
- Oh, boy!
Oh, boy!
- Oh, boy, oh, boy!
I can't wait!
I can't wait.
Let's go!
[excited chatter]
- Hmm. [chuckles]
- Welcome to opening day...
- Whoa!
- On Adventure Island!
- [shouts]
- I'll take it
from here, sonny boy.
- [scoffs]
Hello, Thurston.
Good to see you, as always.
So you've been assigned to work
here on Adventure Island?
- [chuckling]
Oh, much more than that.
I had a hand in designing this
spectacular new theme park,
so I'm pretty much in charge
of the whole island.
- Oh, wonderful.
- Excuse me.
And now for
the Adventure Island tour!
Everyone ready to be amazed?
all: Yeah!
- [chuckles]
[whistle blows]
- All clear!
- Initiate...
♪ ♪
[all gasping]
[mechanical whirring]
- Wow, whoa!
[chuckles]
[excited chatter]
- Whoa, we're up in the air.
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
[lever cranks]
- [squawks]
What's going on, Mr. Thurston?
- Ah, you are now part
of Adventure Island's unique
suspended train system.
- [stammers]
But, Thurston,
I'm the conductor
of the Dinosaur Train.
I am supposed to stay with it!
- [chuckles]
We'll return you safely
to the Dinosaur Train
at the end of the tour,
Mr. Conductor.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Why don't we just take the
Dinosaur Train around the park?
- [laughs]
Because this special suspended
train has a better view
than if we stayed below on that
squeaky old Dinosaur Train.
- "Squeaky"?
Well, I just oiled it!
- And besides,
the Dinosaur Train
is a thing of the past.
Adventure Island
is the future!
- What do you mean,
"the future"?
- The future is...
robot dinosaurs!
- [yelps]
all: Robot dinosaurs?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Wow.
all:
Whoa, robot dinosaurs!
- Huh! Robot dinosaurs.
- Yes, robot dinosaurs...
rule.
♪ Why travel back and forth
in time ♪
♪ Who needs that anymore ♪
♪ What our patrons
really want ♪
♪ Is robot dinosaurs ♪
♪ Time travel takes
far too much time ♪
♪ A fact you can't ignore ♪
♪ My metal versions
are sublime ♪
♪ They're robot dinosaurs ♪
- ♪ So you built all
the different kinds ♪
- ♪ Like sauropods and all ♪
- ♪ Yes, my robot sauropods
have necks ♪
♪ That are every bit as tall ♪
- ♪ I see your robot theropods
still run on three-toed feet ♪
- ♪ But unlike
normal theropods ♪
♪ These never need to eat ♪
♪ Why visit actual dinosaurs ♪
♪ They truly make me snore ♪
♪ What Adventure Island has ♪
♪ Is robot dinosaurs ♪
all: ♪ Oh, what
Adventure Island has ♪
- ♪ Adventure Island has ♪
all: ♪ Is robot dinosaurs ♪
- ♪ Robot dinosaurs ♪
Everybody mambo!
♪ A-one, step,
and three, four ♪
♪ And one, step,
and three, four, and ♪
- ♪ One step,
and three, four ♪
♪ A-one, step,
♪ And one ♪
[giggles] This is fun!
- Robot dinosaurs.
[laughs sarcastically]
Real actual dinosaurs
are amazing and fascinating.
And so is time travel,
Thurston.
What do you say to that?
- I'm sorry.
Can't hear you.
I'm too busy dancing the mambo
into the future!
- Um, Mr. Thurston?
- ♪ Three, four, and ♪
Yes, Tiny?
- So the robot dinosaurs
don't eat any food.
- Good!
More fish-wiches for me!
- So if they don't eat food,
what makes them go?
- Yeah, where do
these robot things
get their power from?
- I have a hypothesis.
Maybe the power
that runs the robots
comes from something
on Adventure Island?
- Excellent hypothesis, Buddy!
I'll elucidate.
- Uh...
- That means I'll explain.
- Ah, good.
- The entire island is run
by geothermal steam power.
[music stops]
That's energy that comes from
deep in the earth as steam.
all: Whoa.
Steam power?
- Yes, the steam
is under great pressure,
enough to drive
the mighty gears
that run Adventure Island.
- [roars]
- Hey, you were right, Buddy.
- I have a question.
Are there no real dinosaurs
on Adventure Island,
besides us?
- Well, there are all
of the Troodon engineers
who work here
and run the rides.
They can be identified
by their name tags.
Most of the Troodons work
in Adventure Island's
Central Control
behind the scenes.
Ah, and here we are!
Central Control.
Hello, everyone.
And goodbye.
On with the tour!
- [giggles]
Whoa.
Look at that robot sauropod.
He's programmed to chew.
all:
Whoa, whoa!
- See?
Isn't it a triumph?
Everything is driven
by brilliant engineering
and powered by steam.
In fact, the whole island runs
like a steam-powered clock.
- But they're not
real dinosaurs.
They're robots.
- Yes.
Why robot dinosaurs, Thurston,
when there's a whole
actual Mesozoic Era
of real dinosaurs to meet?
- Here on Adventure Island,
every kid can be any dinosaur!
- Um, how exactly?
- By riding in a robot version
of one,
which is so much better than
trying to ride a real one.
all:
Whoa!
- But can you make friends
with a robot?
- They're robots.
You don't need
to make friends with them.
- [sighs]
Well, very impressive,
Thurston.
- Yes, it is.
Oh! I mean thank you.
[eerie music]
[ground rumbling]
♪ ♪
[panicked chatter]
- That was weird.
Felt like an earthquake.
- Wasn't it just giant
stomping robot dinosaur feet?
- Hmm, maybe.
Um, Mr. Thurston?
I have another hypothesis.
- Oh, oh, oh!
That's two hypotheses, Buddy.
You only get one.
That was a joke.
What's your other hypothesis?
- Well, what if there was
an earthquake
on Adventure Island?
Would that affect
the steam power
that runs everything?
- Oh, pfft, an extremely
unlikely hypothesis.
[mechanical whirring]
[groans]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, what's wrong?
What happened?
- Well, I hope you tested
everything thoroughly first
before you opened the park
to visitors.
- [cackles]
No.
Sheesh, what a fuddy-duddy.
After all, it is called
Adventure Island.
Lighten up, Mr. Conductor.
[scoffs]
[solemn music]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Ah, here we are
back where we started.
[all cheering]
Now your own Adventure Island
adventure can begin
when you experience the rides.
- Yeah!
- Yeah, let's get on the rides!
- I cannot wait.
- Well, have fun
on Adventure Island,
Pteranodon family.
I gotta stay on schedule.
There's lots more stops today
for the "old-fashioned"
Dinosaur Train.
all:
Okay. Bye, Mr. Conductor!
- All aboard...
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
[train whistle toots]
[solemn country music]
♪ All aboard
the Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ It's comin' round the bend ♪
♪ It may not quite be
up-to-date ♪
♪ But it's still
a faithful friend ♪
♪ All aboard ♪
- ♪ All aboard ♪
all:
♪ The Dinosaur Train ♪
- [chuckles]
Go experience the rides!
Have fun!
[all cheering]
- Okay.
Oh, be careful.
Don't run.
Okay, this is gonna be great.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
A Jurassic churro?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, can I have one?
- Mm-hmm.
- [crunches] Oh, boy.
- I'll have one of those.
- [gasps]
[inspiring music]
♪ ♪
Wow.
A tyrannosaurus just like me.
So can I ride the rides
by myself
if I ride
with Tiny, Shiny, and Don?
- Maybe after
we've had some time
to think about it, Buddy.
First you have to learn
to be patient.
- Okay, I'll be patient.
- Here's the Quetzalcoatlus
Coaster, Buddy.
Let's all ride it together
and see how you do.
all: Whoo-hoo, yay!
- Whoo-hoo, yeah!
all: Huh?
Oh.
- Why are we...
I don't understand.
- Hmm, looks like we'll all
have to be patient.
- It's okay.
Why don't we do the
Theropod Cheer while we wait?
- Yeah!
- Yes!
all: One, big legs
with three-toed feet.
Two, lots of teeth
for eating meat.
Three, long tail
for balancing well.
And four, theropods have
a great sense of smell.
One, big legs
with three-toed feet.
Two, lots of teeth...
[all screaming]
- Whoo-hoo!
[laughter]
- Whoa!
Oh, ah!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Pte-radical!
- [screams]
[all cheering]
[yelps]
- [giggling]
- [screams]
Oh.
[whimpers]
[all giggle]
- Yeah!
Whoo, this is fun!
- [panting]
I--you know, it just
doesn't make sense.
I fly all the time.
I am an expert flier.
- [squawks]
I know, hon.
- See how patient we were?
The line was long,
but we didn't complain once.
Now can we kids ride
the rides by ourselves?
- [squawks]
Yeah, can we?
- I kind of like having Mom
and Dad on the ride with us.
- Well, you did show us
you can be patient.
Now show us you can listen
and follow the instructions
and make good choices,
and then we'll consider
letting you ride by yourselves.
- Yes, okay!
We can't wait to show you
we can listen
and follow the instructions.
- And make good choices.
- Let's start
with the migrating dino
bumper cars ride.
Remember, listen
to the instructions.
- Welcome, welcome, welcome
to the Migrating Sauropod ride.
[stammering]
I...
all: Whoo!
[all giggling]
- Nothing!
Okay, you sauropods
stick together
in a migrating herd.
Meanwhile, the theropods,
you're gonna try
and herd these sauropods
into that corner
at the end of the course
while the sauropods are gonna
try to get to the other corner.
Okay?
The first team
to successfully migrate
to the other side wins.
- So how does this thingy work?
- Hmm, it's a robot,
so it must be programmed
to do what we do
with these controls.
I think you run the legs
and I run the neck and head?
- Sounds easy.
- Oh, pull that lever, Tiny,
and I bet it'll start to walk.
- [groans]
Hey, it worked, Shiny.
- Okay, now, here's
how to run the sauropods.
- Hmm.
both: Whoa!
[both giggling]
- Wait, I haven't given you
your instructions yet!
- Well, huh, their patience
didn't last too long, did it?
[playful music]
both:
Whee!
- Looks like they're programmed
to stick together.
This is so great!
♪ ♪
- ♪ La-la-loo ♪
What's this do?
- Not that one.
both: Whoa!
[both yelp]
- Buddy, watch
where you're going!
[squawks]
Buddy, we're all tangled up.
Let us go.
both: Faster, faster!
[laughing]
[laughter]
- Buddy, Don, untangle us.
- Look out!
Robot theropods coming through!
- Oh, they're all beating us.
Let's just race
to the finish line.
- Um, yeah, let's go.
both:
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
both: Whoo-hoo!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
♪ ♪
We made it!
Whoo-hoo!
both:
Wait for us!
- [gasps]
- Whoa!
[both scream]
- So how'd that go, Buddy?
- I think we came in last.
[chuckles weakly]
We forgot to wait and listen
to the instructions.
- Yeah.
- Don't worry, Dad.
I can remember
on the next ride.
I know we can do it.
- And make better choices.
[grunts]
- Well, here's
your chance, Buddy.
The next ride
is the Pterano-thopters.
- Pterano-thopters?
This should be easy!
- [squawks]
Okay, stick together, kids.
all: Yes, we will.
Whoo-hoo!
- We'll be flying with you
and watching to see
if you kids can listen
to the instructions.
Meet up at the exit
at the end of the ride, okay?
- Okay.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- These Pterano-thopter robots
are programmed to fly,
swoop, dive, and catch fish.
- Hey, that's
what we do already.
- [squawks]
This ride'll be a snap.
- [chuckles]
For you guys, maybe.
- You pull up on the stick
to fly higher
and push it down to dive.
See if you can time your dive
to grab these robot fish
as they jump out of the pond.
The Pterano-thopter
that catches the most fish...
[snorts]
Wins.
- I can't wait to try this.
[roars]
I finally get to find out
what it's like to fly.
- Yeah, and fish.
I know I'm a herbivore,
but I've always wanted
to try it.
- Okay, team, did you listen
to all the instructions?
- [squawks]
- [roars]
all: Yes!
- Do you have any questions?
- Yes, all this talk
about fake fishing
is making me hungry.
Does the cafeteria
have fish-wiches?
- [chuckles]
I think so.
But first rides,
and then we'll eat.
You kids ready?
all: Yes!
Go, Team Pteranodon!
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- [giggles]
Whoo!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Whoa, whoa!
♪ ♪
[whimpers]
Whoa!
- Pull up on the stick, Buddy,
like the Troodon engineer said.
- Got it.
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
I'm flying.
I'm flying!
- Look out below!
Whee, I'm flying!
♪ ♪
[both laugh]
- Wow--whoa!
[laughs, yelps]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
[mechanical whirring]
[all giggling]
- Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
[laughs]
Well, you are all too kind.
My friends,
the opening of the park
has been a monumental success,
and each and every one of you
played a vital role.
[chuckles]
Of course, none of your roles
were as vital as mine,
but, well, I'm sure
you all did your best.
- Mm-hmm.
[alarm blaring]
[all giggling]
♪ ♪
- Yes, I caught five!
♪ I'm in the lead ♪
♪ ♪
- That's five.
And six!
- Okay, that's all the fish.
All Pterano-thopters in!
♪ ♪
- Hmm...whoa.
No.
[gags]
Yup, they're fake.
- That was so fun!
Good job, Spikey!
You'd make a great Pteranodon.
- Wow, thanks, Shiny!
Best day ever!
[all giggling]
- We wait right here
at the exit for Mom and Dad.
- [sighs] Whew.
Flying a Pterano-thopter
is harder than I thought.
- Whoa, yeah.
I'm glad I don't have to swoop
and dive for fish all day.
Wait, I do swoop and dive
for fish all day.
Anyway, it's a lot harder
to do it in a Pterano-thopter.
[laughter]
Excellent job, kids.
You followed the instructions
perfectly.
- Mm-hmm, very grown-up
and responsible.
I think you kids
are ready for...
both:
The Theropod Tracker ride.
[all cheering]
- [panting]
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
[all scream]
- [roars]
- You know, hon,
maybe they're ready
to ride one by themselves.
- Do you really think so?
- Yes, they're really learning
how to listen
and make good choices.
Plus, I wouldn't mind
sitting down for a minute.
- Okay, team, you get to ride
this one by yourselves.
[all gasp, cheer]
- This means a lot.
I'll really show you
how grown-up I can be.
- Good, remember your mom and I
will meet you at the exit
when you're done.
- Stick together and wait
at the meeting place...
all: The exit!
Yay!
[both sigh]
- Okeydokes, you got all kinds
of giant robot theropods here.
You pick the one you think can
best track this little critter
and catch it before it reaches
the end of the course.
Choose the theropod
that can best do the job.
Some are faster
and more nimble.
Some are bigger
and more powerful.
So pick your ride
and saddle up!
[all giggling]
[laid-back country music]
♪ ♪
- Wow.
Cool!
[inspiring music]
Hello, T. rex.
[giggles]
- [squawks]
Hello, allosaurus.
- Nice to meet you,
Pinocchio rex.
My name is Tiny.
- And I'm gonna be
a daspletosaurus.
♪ La-la-loo ♪
- [chuckles]
All right.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
- Whoa, look at Buddy go.
[chuckles]
- Yay, Buddy!
Ride, ride like the wind!
- Whoa, wow, this thing
is hard to control.
Let me see
if I could slow it down.
- [roars]
- That didn't slow it down
at all.
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
[all giggling]
Whoa, whoa!
- Where'd it go?
I think it's
behind those bushes.
[playful music]
- Mine's a Pinocchio rex.
They have the best sense
of smell.
I bet this robot
has a robotic sniffer.
♪ ♪
[mechanical whirring]
And it's that way!
- Yeah!
Way to go, Tiny!
[footsteps stomping]
- Whoops!
Wrong way.
- [squawks]
How do you like it
so far, Buddy?
- I get to sit way up here
and see through its eyes.
I can't believe I get
to be this tall someday.
- [laughs] I know!
Me neither.
- But I don't think
I'm very good at it.
- Don't worry.
Take your time.
You'll figure it out.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Uh-oh.
- Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
We caught it!
Yay, giant robot theropod!
- Whoo-hoo!
both: Yeah!
- [chuckles nervously]
- Time for the Theropod Cheer!
Ready?
Okay.
all: One, big legs
with three-toed feet.
Two, lots of teeth
for eating meat.
Three, long tail
for balancing well.
And four, theropods have
a great sense of smell.
- [whimpers]
all: Whoa!
- Huh? Oh!
- Oh, dear.
- [chuckles nervously]
Oops, sorry.
My fault.
[bell rings]
- Well, that was
a right nice job, kids.
- Yeah, I guess.
- Ah, don't worry,
young theropod.
You'll make a great
grown-up T. rex someday.
Just keep at it.
- Yeah, okay.
[melancholy music]
- So what do you wanna do now?
Go find some fish-wiches?
Ooh, or Jurassic churros?
- No, Don.
We have to stick together
and wait at the exit.
- Oh, right.
Follow the instructions.
both: [squawk]
And wait for Mom and Dad!
- Oh, you kids did great.
You followed
all the instructions.
I'm so proud.
both: Whoo-hoo!
- Yeah!
- Thanks.
I guess I'm not really ready to
be a giant grown-up T. rex yet.
- Hey, kiddo, you tried.
Maybe you'll get another chance
to do it better.
- Really?
Thanks, Dad!
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
- [roars]
[music swells]
[both scream]
[water splashes]
- This is the one
that drops you
from way, way up high.
Right?
- [squawks]
Hey, look.
It's on the map.
Hmm, you get into a boat-sized
crocodilian Mastodonsaurus
that climbs to the very top
of the mountain...
- Then you float
down a long stream
that winds back and forth
and then...
- Plunges down
an epic waterfall into...
Boom!
This splash pool.
- Hmm, what happens
when your Mastodonsaurus boat
splashes into the pool?
[gasps]
[both screaming]
[ground rumbling]
[chuckles weakly]
- Boom!
- Okay, then.
- Hmm, sort of felt
like an earthquake.
[ground rumbling]
[suspenseful music]
- Uh, Tricia, would you
take a look at this?
The steam pressure
really jumped
after that weird rumbling.
- Let's see the readout.
[printer whirring]
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
- [whispering]
Do you think an earthquake
could be the cause
of the rumble that we felt?
- Could be.
Let's show this to Thurston.
And since the entire
island theme park
and all the robots
are driven by steam power,
maybe too much steam pressure
could cause problems.
- Yes, yes, but...
[scoffs]
That's highly unlikely.
- I don't know, Thurston.
I mean, look.
It seems to be
already happening.
- Eh, dah-dah-dah-dah-dah.
Everything will be fine.
I have to get back to work.
I'm coming up with a slogan
for Adventure Island.
What do you think of
"Adventure Island
runs perfectly like
a steam-powered clock"?
- Um...
- Don't you have robots
to watch?
- Yes, sir?
- Well, go on, then.
Scoot.
Scoot, scoot.
[upbeat music]
both: [screaming]
♪ ♪
[water splashes]
Whoo!
[giggling]
It sure is the ultimate plunge!
- [whimpers]
- Shiny, are you sure
you wanna ride this one?
- [whimpers]
[riders screaming]
[chuckles nervously]
[water splashes]
- Yeah, Shiny, your mom and I
were thinking
of riding something
a little slower and quieter.
- [gasps]
Ooh, look!
Moonlight Jurassic Swamp ride.
Seems nice and quiet.
- [chuckles, squawks]
Are you kidding?
I can't wait to ride
that waterfall.
We showed that we're
grown-up enough to do it,
so let's do it.
[riders screaming]
[gulps]
[water splashes]
[laughs nervously]
- Shiny is right, kids.
You have earned it.
Your dad and I are going
to go ride our own ride,
and you all get to ride
another ride all by yourselves.
all: [cheering]
Yay, we're so grown-up!
[whistle blows]
- But first, we need
to pick the meeting place
where we'll all get together
when we're done with our rides.
Hmm, your mom and I will ride
the Moonlight Jurassic
Swamp ride
while you ride
the amphibious water one.
And then we'll all meet up
at the visitor center.
all:
Yeah!
- Can't miss that tower
with a giant T. rex on it.
- So remember, stick together.
all: Okay.
both: What do you do?
all: Stick together!
both:
Right!
- ♪ Kids can get lost,
it happens ♪
♪ But there's no need to fear ♪
♪ We just come up
with a meeting place ♪
♪ And how to get there
from here ♪
- ♪ You can ask a Troodon
with a badge ♪
♪ There's plenty to be found ♪
both: ♪ Just remember
your name and species ♪
♪ And wait
till we come around ♪
- ♪ Stick together and wait
at the meeting place ♪
- ♪ And you'll come
looking for us ♪
- ♪ Right, remember
your name and species ♪
- Rawr!
♪ I'm Buddy Tyrannosaurus ♪
- ♪ We're Tiny ♪
- ♪ Shiny ♪
♪ And Don ♪
all: [squawk]
♪ We're all Pteranodons ♪
- Good!
♪ The Troodons
will help you find ♪
♪ Your dear old Dad and Mom ♪
both: ♪ So what do you do ♪
all: ♪ Stick together ♪
both: ♪ Say what ♪
all: ♪ 'Cause we're
Team Pteranodon ♪
both: ♪ So what do you do ♪
all: ♪ Stick together ♪
- ♪ One more time ♪
all: ♪ 'Cause we're
Team Pteranodon ♪
Stick together!
[squawk]
- Rawr!
[cheers and applause]
[chuckles]
I mean...[squawks]
- Wonderful.
- Okay, kids.
Remember, if anything
goes wrong, stay calm
and just use your senses
to find our meeting place.
- Wait, what are
our senses again?
- You know,
our seeing and hearing.
- And our smelling and tasting.
both: And touching.
- Ooh, ooh!
And digging holes?
- Well, digging holes does use
your sense of touch, Don.
- They mean like using
your sense of smell.
[all sniffing]
- Like, my sense of smell
tells me...
[sniffing]
That they sell Jurassic churros
over that way.
- Oh.
- [squawks]
Exactly, Buddy.
Now, where's the meeting place?
all:
The visitor center!
- Okay, this is big, kids.
You're gonna be on your own.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
- Ready?
Okay.
all:
Go, Team Pteranodon!
[all squawk]
- Rawr!
[all cheering]
[all laughing]
- Yeah.
all: Bye, Mom and Dad!
- Well, they're growing up.
So responsible.
[clears throat]
No, there's something
in my eye.
[soft music]
[dramatic music]
[riders screaming]
[water splashes]
[all gasp]
♪ ♪
[all screaming, cheering]
[all gasping]
- Whoa.
- [squawks]
I think I've got
the hang of it.
Wait.
What's happening now?
- Looks like we're going up
to the top.
all: Oh, boy,
oh, boy, oh, boy!
- Yeah.
Oh, boy.
[soft banjo music playing]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
This is romantic, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Hope the kids are okay.
- The kids are fine, hon.
Relax.
Here, have a churro.
- Oh, thanks.
[chomping]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
all:
Whoa!
[all gasping]
♪ ♪
[laughter]
[water rushing]
- What's that noise?
- Is it the waterfall?
all:
Whoa!
[all screaming, cheering]
[exciting music]
- [chuckles]
Guys, that wasn't so bad.
More like a water slide
than a waterfall.
all:
Whoa.
[all scream]
[ground rumbling]
- Oh, that's weird.
[mutters]
Something is a little...
- What is it, hon?
[rumbling continues]
- Huh, did you feel that?
Is it part of the ride?
- It's fine.
And the kids are fine.
- [sighs]
Right, yeah.
Kids are fine.
Any more churros?
[rumbling continues]
[suspenseful music]
[alarm blaring]
- [gasps]
It is an earthquake!
Look at the spike
in the pressure
from the steam power plant.
- I wonder how this will affect
the robot dinosaurs.
- Mm-hmm, I'd better
go get Thurston.
- "Adventure Island,
the unsinkable theme park"--
no, that's no good.
"Adventure Island,
the theme park where nothing
can possibly go wrong."
- Thurston,
something's gone wrong!
There was a big spike
in the steam pressure
at the power plant.
- And the problem is?
- Well, I'm worried that
with all of the earthquakes
we've been having
that the pressure at the plant
has become so overheated
that we run the risk
of massive malfunctions.
Some of the robots in the park
could already be affected.
- Well, tut-tut, Tricia.
The pressure is fine.
It'll never happen.
[chuckles]
[tense music]
[ground rumbling]
[steam hissing]
♪ ♪
[panicked chatter]
[robot dinosaurs roaring]
♪ ♪
[ground rumbling]
both:
Huh?
[mischievous music]
♪ ♪
both: Whee!
I'm flying!
♪ ♪
- [chuckles]
- [gasps]
[engines humming]
[water splashes]
Now I'm swimming?
- Wait, what?
- This isn't what the ride
is supposed to do.
- [chuckles]
Whoa.
- You're right, kid.
This isn't what
it's programmed to do.
- Uh, excuse me,
Mr. Troodon engineer?
I think our sauropod is broken.
- Broken?
- Well, they're supposed
to act like a herd...
- And move together
in a migration.
- Aren't they?
What are they doing now?
both:
Playing leapfrog.
[whimsical music]
♪ ♪
[soft banjo music playing]
- Huh, what?
- Hmm, what?
[both yelp]
- [squawks]
- Whoa!
Yikes, oh!
[both screaming]
- Whoa!
[both panting]
- Hmm, our reptilian boat seems
to have fallen asleep.
- And no more
Jurassic banjo music.
- Ride must be
temporarily stopped.
- Oh, well.
Now we can get
some real peace and quiet.
- Yeah, and to tell you
the truth,
that Jurassic banjo
was starting to annoy me.
- [chuckles]
Me too.
- [sighs]
[power clicks off]
[eerie music]
Hope the kids are okay.
all: [giggling]
Whoa!
[ground rumbling]
Whoo!
[all laughing, cheering]
[bubbles popping]
- Yeah!
- [squawks]
[suspenseful music]
[laughter]
[water bursting]
all: Whoa!
- Whoo-hoo!
- [squawks]
all: Whoa!
- Whoo-hoo!
both: Whee!
♪ ♪
all: Whoa!
- Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
♪ ♪
[squawks]
Wow, this ride is complicated.
- But I have to say it--
not very scary.
- Probably 'cause I'm doing
such a great job
piloting the robot.
[all giggle]
- Yeah.
- But I thought there was
gonna be a big waterfall.
- What's that noise?
[gasps]
[water slide rattling]
all: Whoa!
- Whoo-hoo!
[ground rumbling]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
all: Whee!
Whoa!
- Wait, why are we in a swamp?
This doesn't seem right.
- [squawks]
What happens now?
- We steer for shore?
- Something's wrong
with our Mastodonsaurus boat.
It's trying to swim on land.
[powers whirs down]
Guys, I think
this ride is broken.
- Wow, lucky we're real
dinosaurs and pterosaurs
and can just get out and walk.
- [squawks]
What's going on?
- Remember Buddy's hypothesis?
What if there was
an earthquake?
Would it affect the steam power
that runs everything?
- Yeah, I think
there was an earthquake.
That's what the rumbling was.
- And--
- That's why
our ride is broken.
- Your hypothesis
was right, Buddy.
- [gasps]
And now the robots won't do
what they're programmed to do.
[playful music]
♪ ♪
- So what should we do?
- Just like Mom and Dad said--
stick together.
One, two, three, four.
- That's all of us.
Good job, Team Pteranodon.
- And now we go
to the meeting place.
- The visitor center.
all:
And wait for Mom and Dad.
- The robot dinosaur vehicles
aren't working,
so I think we're
gonna have to walk.
- [squawks]
Shiny and Don and I
can fly there.
- But look,
the jungle is covered
by some kind of camouflage net.
I don't think
we can fly out of here.
- Besides, Mom and Dad would
want us to stick together.
We'll just have to use
our tracking skills
and all of our senses to find
a way to hike out of here.
- [squawks]
Buddy's right.
- Okay, let's find
the visitor center
and wait for Mom and Dad.
- I wonder
if their ride is broken.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- Aha!
- [giggles]
[dramatic music]
- Aha!
I knew we'd find
an emergency exit.
- My goodness!
The Troodons
think of everything.
- Okay, that earthquake
probably affected
other rides too,
just like Buddy's hypothesis.
- I hope the kids remember
to stick together
and get to the meeting place.
♪ ♪
- Let's go find them.
- [squawks]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
all: ♪ Oh, what
Adventure Island has ♪
♪ Is robot dinosaurs ♪
[music distorts, fades]
- [screams]
[panicked chatter]
- I said I'm busy.
What is it?
- Show Thurston
what's going on out there.
♪ ♪
- None of the robots
are behaving
like their species should.
The fliers are trying to swim.
- Uh-huh, so?
- The swimmers
are trying to fly!
- No big deal.
- And one carnivore is trying
to eat kale salad.
- [scoffs]
Kale salad?
That's ridiculous!
[groans]
Foolish, malfunctioning,
unreliable robots.
Whose idea was this?
[chatter stops]
- [clears throat]
Maybe you should've
tested your idea
before you opened the park?
- No, no!
It isn't my fault.
It's somebody else's!
Never mine, ever.
Ew, kale salad.
Ugh.
- Okay, we'll take it
from here, Thurston.
All right, grab some
hose clamps and tape,
and follow me.
We'll fix those broken pipes
and get the steam pressure
back where it needs to be.
- Yes, exactly!
Do...that.
[eerie music]
[footsteps stomping]
♪ ♪
all: Whoa!
Wow!
♪ ♪
[lively music playing]
- Okay, this way is no good.
We have to work our way
around these robot triceratops.
♪ ♪
[sniffing]
I smell churros!
- You do?
They're near
the visitor center.
- This way!
Come on!
♪ ♪
[all gasp, wail]
- Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
- Whoa!
[ground rumbling]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[train whistle toots]
[relaxed country music]
♪ ♪
- Almost time, Gilbert.
- You mean Time Tunnel time?
[pocket watch chiming]
- [gasps]
[ground rumbling]
Whoa!
all:
[panicked chatter]
- You know, I think
I'll switch tracks up ahead
and take us
to the nearest roundhouse.
- Huh?
- Better check up
on how things are going
back at Adventure Island.
That earthquake may have
caused some problems,
just like Buddy hypothesized.
- Aye, aye, Uncle Conductor.
[exciting music]
[bell dinging]
♪ ♪
[overlapping chatter]
- Now, now.
Nothing's wrong, folks.
[chuckles]
Just following a hunch.
We've had an earthquake,
and they may need our help
back in Adventure Island.
We apologize
for the inconvenience.
Oh, I just hope
we get there in time.
[upbeat country music]
both: ♪ All aboard
the Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ It's comin' round the bend ♪
♪ Never fear,
the train is here ♪
♪ We're gonna
save our friends ♪
- ♪ All aboard ♪
all:
♪ All aboard ♪
♪ The Dinosaur Train ♪
[footsteps stomping]
[mischievous music]
♪ ♪
- [sniffing]
I think the visitor center
is this way.
♪ ♪
[hopeful music]
I see it!
I see the tower!
- Ooh, ooh, what news
of the churro stand?
- Well, it's still there, Don,
but we need to meet Mom and Dad
at the visitor center.
Come on.
♪ ♪
[panicked chatter]
[playful music]
♪ ♪
- [vocalizes]
- [gasps]
[panting]
It's nuts out there!
Where's Thurston?
- Forget Thurston.
Help us fix everything.
[overlapping chatter]
- [chuckles]
Whew.
Oh, oh, ooh!
Thurston, you've done it again.
Nothing could go wrong now--
[screams]
- [roars]
- [panting, yelping]
[shouts]
[yelps]
- [roars]
- [screaming]
[whimpering]
Oh, dear.
Nature and machines
have fallen out of balance.
What in the Mesozoic
have I created?
[lively music]
♪ ♪
- Are you still sure
this is the right way?
- Not really.
I think it's this way
to the visitor center,
but look at all these giant
robot dinosaurs in our way.
I'm not sure
how to get past them.
[sighs]
Why did I think
we were grown-up enough
to do the ride by ourselves?
We should've stayed
with Mom and Dad.
Now we're stuck with a bunch
of robot dinosaurs
between us
and where we wanna go.
[sighs]
Maybe I'm not grown-up enough
to figure this out.
- Really?
'Cause I was just about to ask
you what we're gonna do next.
- [squawks]
Okay.
Everyone, take a deep breath
and remember all the things
we've learned about being
grown-up and responsible.
Right?
all: [breathe deeply]
Right.
Stay calm.
- Right, stay calm.
[breathes deeply]
- We'll find our way.
We just have to not get
stepped on while we do it.
We're all gonna be T. rexes
like you, Buddy,
and use your super
T. rex tracking skills
and find the visitor center
and Mom and Dad.
- [chuckles]
I'm not really that skilled.
- [squawks]
Are you kidding?
You're a T. rex!
You're a tyrannosaurus!
You're the biggest carnivore
in the Cretaceous forest!
Come on!
[rock music]
all: ♪ T. rex, roar,
I'm a tyrannosaurus ♪
♪ I'm the biggest carnivore
in the Cretaceous forest ♪
♪ Gonna romp and stomp around,
the biggest dinosaur in town ♪
♪ Gonna romp
and stomp all day ♪
♪ 'Cause nothing's standing
in my way ♪
♪ T. rex, roar,
I'm a tyrannosaurus ♪
♪ I'm the biggest carnivore
in the Cretaceous forest ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a T. rex,
yeah, I'm a T. rex ♪
♪ A roaring round the forest
tyrannosaurus rex ♪
♪ Roar ♪
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
- Yeah, let's do this.
The visitor center is just
past these robot sauropods.
[mischievous music]
[lively music playing]
- What are they doing?
- [squawks]
Dancing?
- [sighs]
Dancing sauropods?
Boy, did that earthquake
mess things up.
- I know what they're dancing.
It's the mambo.
both: The mambo?
- Yeah, remember?
Thurston and the Troodon
waiters showed it to us.
both:
Oh, yeah.
Everybody mambo!
- It's easy!
♪ A-one, step,
and three, four ♪
♪ And one, step,
♪ And one ♪
- Oh, that gives me an idea.
What if we move past the
sauropods every time they step
and make room for us
to get through their feet?
- Right, as long as
we're keeping in step,
no one steps on us.
- Come on!
♪ ♪
all: ♪ A one, step,
and three, four ♪
♪ And one, step,
and three, four, and one ♪
♪ ♪
[both sigh]
- We all made it.
Wait, hold up.
Where's Don?
♪ ♪
- [yelps]
- Help!
- Wait, did you hear that?
Sounds like someone
calling for help.
- [screaming]
Help!
all:
Thurston?
- Please rescue me
from these rampaging
robot sauropods.
They're out of control!
[wails]
- Okay, let's mambo dance
our way to him.
Ready?
- Hmm...
wait, now it look like
they're doing the cha-cha.
I think.
- You think?
Or are you sure?
- What?
Now we have to learn
another dance?
- [hums]
Yes.
It's definitely the cha-cha.
See?
♪ A-one and two and three,
cha-cha-cha ♪
♪ A-one, a-two, a-three,
♪ ♪
♪ A-one, a-two ♪
- Hmm, okay, team.
I think we can dance through
their legs at "cha-cha-cha."
What do you think?
- [squawks]
Let's do it!
- Everybody cha-cha!
♪ ♪
all: ♪ A-one, a-two, a-three ♪
- Uh, children, help!
I'm still up here!
- ♪ And one, two, three ♪
Wait, what's next?
- ♪ A-one, two, and three,
cha-cha-cha ♪
Come on!
- [wails]
Help!
I'm coming down now!
all: ♪ Two, three,
cha-cha, step ♪
♪ One, two, three,
cha-cha, grab him ♪
- Whoa!
[sighing]
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
No, no four.
Uh, well, step and cha.
Cha-cha, cha-cha.
There's three of those ones.
And step, step.
And two.
[laughs nervously]
- [squawks]
I see it!
This way, guys!
[all panting]
- [groans]
- [squawks]
Is everyone okay?
- Actually, everyone
is not okay.
Shiny, you were late.
Buddy, it's
"one and two and step."
And, Thurston...
[sighs]
I don't even know
where to start.
- Yes, well, it's a good thing
you found me, children.
- Okay, we're all together.
Good.
We're headed
for the visitor center.
That's the meeting place
where Mom and Dad
are going to wait for us,
which is right over
these giant cliffs.
all:
Aww.
- Hmm.
Let's take that boat
and ride it over the falls.
It should take us
straight there.
- Wait, over what falls?
Have you tested it yet?
- [giggles]
It is called Adventure Island
after all, Thurston.
[playful music]
Hmm.
[squawks]
Yup, the robot boat's
not working.
We can paddle it, though.
Grab some giant leaves
and come on.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- What's that roaring sound?
- Just the waterfall,
but there's nothing
to be scared about.
Shiny's a really good pilot.
- Oh, I'm not scared.
I didn't mean
that I was scared,
but I asked--no!
all: Oh, boy,
oh, boy, oh, boy!
- [laughing nervously,
screaming]
[all screaming]
♪ ♪
[water splashes]
[mystical music]
- [yawns]
Wow, we got
through the whole night.
♪ ♪
all: [gasp]
We made it!
[cheering]
- [squawks]
Look, a Troodon with a badge,
just like the song.
- Hello?
And who are you?
- I'm Buddy Tyrannosaurus!
- We're Tiny.
- Shiny!
- And Don!
- [squawks]
all: ♪ We're all Pteranodons ♪
- And this is
our meeting place.
We're supposed to wait here
for our mom and dad.
- Perfect, I'll wait here
with you.
all:
Thanks!
♪ ♪
- Thurston, are you
kind of lost too?
You wanna wait with us?
- [inhales, stammers]
Yes.
♪ ♪
[all sigh]
- So where are Mom and Dad?
- I don't know.
But we have to wait right here
until they come.
- Right.
- But how long will that take?
both: [squawk]
[gasp] Kids!
- And Thurston?
all: Mom and Dad!
Yay!
- You found your way
to the meeting place
and you waited here for us.
- I'm so proud of you.
You really are growing up.
- Yup, you are.
[whimpering]
So responsible.
- Wow, I guess we really are.
[ground rumbling]
- Wait, is that
another earthquake?
[lively music playing]
- Nope, it's that herd
of robot sauropods.
- It's crazy out here!
- And they're still
dancing the cha-cha.
Wait, now they're dancing
the mambo again.
No, it's some new dance
I've never heard of.
I'll call it "the robot."
Hmm.
- [squawks]
Come on, kids.
Let's get out of their way.
[percussive electronic music
playing]
- [yelps]
♪ ♪
- Come on, everybody.
Get in the elevator.
♪ ♪
- Hey, look.
Here come the robot theropods.
- They must be overheated too.
[steam hissing]
- How in the Mesozoic Era
are we going to round up
all these robot dinosaurs
and get them to a safe place
so we can fix them?
[cries]
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
- Hmm.
Robots overheated.
[gasps]
They're next to the water.
Hmm, I have a hypothesis!
- You do?
Finally! What is it?
- I think if we can get those
robot theropods under control,
we can use them to round up
those dancing sauropods
and get everyone to safety.
Quick, Tiny, Shiny,
lift me up
and carry me
to the robot T. rex.
And, Don, see if you can get
the rest of those
robot theropods
to follow my lead.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
both: [gasp]
all: Whoa!
♪ ♪
- Uh, are you sure
about this, Buddy?
- [laughs]
Don't worry.
I'm a tyrannosaurus.
I'm the biggest carnivore
in the Cretaceous forest.
I can do this!
Whoo-hoo!
[grunts]
Whoa!
Easy there, critter.
Whoa, okay.
Oh--oh, no, no, no, no!
That's not it!
♪ ♪
- [gibbering]
[all roar]
Uh-oh.
♪ ♪
- Easy, easy, easy!
[panting]
That's better.
Here goes--
Whoa, whoa!
[both gasp]
[stammers]
[grunts]
[both gasp]
- [squawks]
- [whimpers]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
[steam hissing]
I think it worked.
He's cooled down
and back to normal.
Yippee ti-i-yay!
Time to round up
some sauropods.
Whoo!
[exciting music]
- Said it before,
and I'll say it again.
That kid'll make a great
grown-up T. rex someday.
- Yay, Buddy!
- You go, son!
♪ ♪
- [roars]
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Huh?
Now what?
[lively music playing]
♪ ♪
Huh?
Oh, no.
Now the robot theropods
are doing it too.
- Whoa!
- [squawks]
- [gasps]
[foreboding music]
♪ ♪
Don, we've got
to lead them to water.
- [squawks]
Yeah, follow us.
[all roar]
♪ ♪
[tranquil music]
[lively music playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ A-one, step,
and three and ♪
Whoa!
♪ One, step ♪
♪ And three and four ♪
Oh!
♪ One, step ♪
[screams]
Rounding them up
is harder than I thought.
[ground rumbling]
♪ ♪
[all roar]
- [squawks]
We got this, Buddy!
- Whoo-hoo!
- It's a robot dinosaur
dance-off!
♪ La-la-loo ♪
♪ ♪
- [roars]
- Olé.
[giggles]
Look, they're running away.
They're no match for our mambo.
[footsteps stomping]
- There, we rounded them up.
Now let's fence them in.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- Whoa, guys, I think
it's safe to come out.
They did it!
- Yahoo!
- [chuckles]
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
[all cheering]
- Great job, kids.
That was pretty amazing.
[excited chatter]
[ground rumbling]
[all gasp]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Eek, they're coming back!
We're doomed!
Why did I ever create them?
If only someone or something
would arrive in the nick
of time to save us.
[train whistle tooting]
all: [gasp]
It's the Dinosaur Train!
- And the conductor!
Hoo!
- ♪ Hey, everybody,
no need to fear ♪
♪ Your day-saving pals
are finally here ♪
♪ If you're ever in danger,
in trouble or pain ♪
♪ Just listen for the whistle ♪
both:
♪ Of the Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ We're gonna ride
the Dinosaur Train ♪
- ♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
both: ♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
both:
♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
both: ♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
both: ♪ We're gonna ride ♪
all:
♪ Ride, ride, ride, ride ♪
♪ The Dinosaur Train ♪
- [roars]
[all cheering]
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[train whistle toots]
- All aboard!
♪ ♪
Oh, really?
I don't think so.
[train whistle toots]
♪ ♪
Whew.
Dinosaur families,
I am so relieved
to see all of you
together and safe.
- Oh, Mr. Conductor.
Thank goodness you're here.
My robot dinosaurs
are malfunctioning.
- Yes, they seem
to be dancing the mambo.
- Ooh, and sometimes
the cha-cha.
- Can you possibly
help us fix them?
- Well, my cha-cha
is kind of rusty, Thurston,
but I'm sure
we can fix anything.
Never fear.
The Dinosaur Train is here.
- Yes, I...
I said some terrible things
about the Dinosaur Train,
and, well, I'm--
I'm very sorry, Mr. Conductor.
- Mm-hmm, you didn't
actually test
your Adventure Island robots
before you opened the park
to all these dinosaur families,
did you?
- No, I didn't.
And I...
[stammers]
Apologize.
- Oh, it's all right, Thurston.
I forgive you.
[laughs]
Again.
- May I have a hug?
- Ah, sure.
Bring it in.
- Oh, I really am so sorry!
Why must I always do this?
When will I ever learn?
- Oh, there, there.
It's all right.
Oh, oh, we'll fix this
and get Adventure Island
up and running properly again.
[gasps]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- Well, hello, Tricia.
Good to see you.
So what do you think we
should do to fix these robots?
- Well, after the earthquake,
there's too much steam power.
The robots are too hot.
We need to cool down
the power plant first.
- Yes, yes,
but how will we do that?
- Hmm, wow.
I have another hypothesis.
both: Good.
What is it?
- Well, when my robot T. rex
fell in the water,
the temperature
cooled down quickly,
and it started working again.
So what if we move the water
from the amphibious water ride
to cool down the power plant?
- Yes, and once the power
plant has cooled down enough,
we can recharge the robots
with the correct temperature
steam power again.
- And everything'll
go back to normal?
- It's a pretty
complicated hypothesis.
- Hmm, it's a bold plan,
so bold, it just might work.
Let's do it!
- We're on it!
Come on, guys.
- Okay.
[overlapping chatter]
- Or, you know,
whatever you think is best.
[hopeful music]
♪ ♪
- Whoo-hoo!
- We got this, Buddy!
♪ ♪
- Yay, the steam temperature's
returning to normal.
[both sigh]
- Come on, team, let's go.
[all panting]
♪ ♪
[all cheering]
all: [chanting]
Buddy, Buddy, Buddy!
Buddy, Buddy,
Buddy!
- Wow, what a hypothesis.
T. rexes are so smart!
- [squawks]
We're so proud of all you kids.
- Yes, we're going to have
to enjoy every minute
of you still being kids.
You're growing up so fast.
[gentle music]
- Um, missed a spot, Thurston.
Ha, I'm kidding!
[sighs]
It actually has
never looked better.
It's as good as new.
- It is as good as new.
A wonderful, splendid,
perfect train, Mr. Conductor.
It is the greatest.
- What's that?
Once again in my good ear.
- I said it's the greatest.
[all giggle]
[train whistle toots]
Time traveling to visit
actual real dinosaurs
is--well, it is amazing
and fascinating.
And real, actual dinosaurs
are wonderful.
[all cheering]
- Yes, real dinosaurs rule!
[squawks]
- One, two, three, four.
Yup, that's all of you.
Everyone's together and safe.
Now what?
- Well, why not take
the Dinosaur Train
on a ride through
the whole Mesozoic Era
and go visit some
real, actual dinosaurs?
- [squawks]
Yes, best ride of all!
- Say, you can come too,
Thurston.
You might even learn something.
[upbeat country music]
♪ All aboard
the Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ It's comin' round the bend ♪
♪ Washed and waxed
and up-to-date ♪
♪ And still a faithful friend ♪
♪ Oh, all aboard,
we've got to say ♪
♪ It's never let us down ♪
♪ It won't complain
in snow or rain ♪
♪ The finest train around ♪
both: ♪ Who cares
what other people say ♪
♪ You always pass the test ♪
♪ And this is coming
from the ones ♪
♪ Who really know you best ♪
all: ♪ Your wheels,
your walls, your velvet seats ♪
♪ Your waggin' tail
in back ♪
♪ ♪
♪ The happy chuffin' sound
you make ♪
♪ When you're boomin'
down the track ♪
♪ All aboard
the Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ It's comin' round the bend ♪
♪ It's always been
our favorite ♪
♪ Our true
and faithful friend ♪
- ♪ All aboard ♪
all: ♪ All aboard ♪
♪ All aboard ♪
♪ The Dinosaur Train ♪
[pocket watch chiming]
- Time Tunnel!
Time Tunnel approaching!
[upbeat country music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
- ♪ I wanna ride ♪
♪ The Dinosaur Train ♪
- ♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
- [laughs]
[yelps]
[clears throat]
♪ ♪
all: [giggle]
Whee!
- Whoo-hoo!
[engine humming]
all: [gasp]
♪ ♪
Huh?
- [chuckles]
- ♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ ♪
- [yelps]
[laughs]
Whoo-hoo!
♪ ♪
- Whoa, oh!
[screams]
Oh, oh.
[chuckles, gags]
Guys?
[stammers]
Hold on, what?
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Dinosaur Train,
Dinosaur Train ♪
♪ ♪
- [yelps]
- [humming]
[giggles]
♪ ♪
[tapping]
[upbeat music playing]
all: ♪ Oh, what
Adventure Island has ♪
♪ Is robot dinosaurs ♪
[applause]
♪ ♪
- [chuckling]
[train whistle toots]
♪ ♪
[funky music]
all:
Whoa!
- [whimpers]
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
- Hmm?
Huh?
[sighs]
♪ ♪
- [roars]
- ♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
- ♪ I wanna ride ♪
♪ The Dinosaur Train ♪
- ♪ Dinosaur Train ♪
- ♪ We're gonna ride ♪
- ♪ Ride, ride, ride, ride ♪
- ♪ The Dinosaur Train ♪
Help all kids learn
and grow with PBS Kids.
Thank you for supporting
our PBS station.
- [buzzing]
[footsteps scampering]