File 82-712.
Agent Rick Dicker interrogating.
State your name, please.
Tony. Tony Rydinger.
Tell me about the incident.
Well, there's this girl in my class.
I saw her at the track meet.
You're Violet, right?
That's me.
I sort of knew her, but she'd changed.
Relaxed. She was more sure of herself.
Cool, cute.
I asked her out to a movie.
So, Friday?
- Friday.
And I went to watch the track meet.
Not long after,
this thing happened in the parking lot.
Behold! The Underminer!
I am always beneath you,
but nothing is beneath me!
As if things aren't weird enough,
I look over and I see these boots.
You two, stay here.
Wait. Should we be doing this?
It is still illegal.
They looked like superheroes.
- We're gonna lose him.
- Oh, all right.
One of you patrol the perimeter,
keep the crowds back and safe.
The other, watch after Jack-Jack.
- But I thought we were gonna go with...
- You heard your mother.
Trampoline me.
I call perimeter!
You're not going anywhere,
you little maggoty creep!
I see my chance to get out of there.
But there's something familiar
about one of the kids' voices.
The girl, she's upset
and she throws down her mask...
and it's her!
Tony!
Hi.
This isn't what you think it is.
It was just getting too freaky.
I couldn't handle it and ran off.
I feel kinda bad about it.
Maybe I should've said "hi" or something?
It's not her fault superheroes are illegal.
And it's not like I don't like strong girls.
I'm pretty secure manhood-wise.
What is that?
Have you told anyone else about this?
Your parents?
No, they'd only think I was hiding something.
You know what I mean?
Sure, kid.
I like this girl, Mr. Dicker.
I'm supposed to go out with her Friday night.
Now, things are just gonna be weird.
I wish I could forget
I ever saw her in that suit.
You will, kid.
You will.
Come on!
Consider yourself undermined!
Underminer! We meet again...
Oh, great! Now, he's on the agenda.
Incredible!
Meet Jack Hammer!
Buh-bye!
No, no, no! No, no, no!
Everybody, stay back! Okay? Stay back!
You're not sticking me with babysitting!
I can't steer it or stop it.
And the Underminer's escaped!
We'll have to stop it... Bob! The monorail!
Frozone! Yeah!
We have to stop this thing
before it gets to the overpass!
I'll try to keep it away from the buildings!
Hey, lady!
Thank you so much, young man!
What?
Violet!
Stop!
Everybody, stop!
- Heads up, Dad!
- Dash!
Violet!
Who's watching Jack-Jack?
Dash is watching him!
Violet, here, you take him!
It's headed for City Hall!
Mom needs help!
They're out in public again!
This is our chance!
Follow them, follow Frozone!
Bob! Help me with the boiler!
That should do it!
What are you kids doing? Get out of here!
This thing's gonna blow!
There's no time!
We did it!
Freeze, Supers!
What did we do?
Excuse me, Mr. Zone?
Sorry, but I'm not really
supposed to be here.
Which seems wrong...
doesn't it?
Perhaps you'd be interested in
changing that law?
Superheroes including
Frozone, Mr. Incredible, and Elastigirl...
caused further damage to the city.
The Underminer remains at large.
We didn't start this fight.
Well, you didn't finish it either!
Did you stop the Underminer
from inflicting more damage?
- No.
- Did you stop him from robbing the banks?
- Did you catch him?
No.
The banks were insured.
We have infrastructure in place
to deal with these matters.
If you had simply done nothing...
everything would now be proceeding
in an orderly fashion.
You'd have preferred we do nothing?
Without a doubt.
You weren't much help.
Do you want out of the hole?
First you gotta put down the shovel.
Well, that went poorly.
Dad, this is probably not the best time
to tell you about this...
but something else
happened today with a kid...
and my mask.
Hey, Rick. Violet thinks a friend of hers,
a kid named Tony...
might have seen her in the outfit,
without her mask.
- Talkative type?
- Don't know.
Last name is Rydinger.
Tony Rydinger.
I'll check it out.
Bob, Helen...
a word if you don't mind.
The program's been shut down.
What?
Politicians don't understand people...
who do good simply because it's right.
It makes 'em nervous.
They've been gunning for Supers for years.
Today was all they needed.
Anyway...
I'm done.
I'm afraid two more weeks in the motel
is the best I can do for ya.
It ain't much.
You've done plenty, Rick.
We won't forget.
Well, it has been a great honor
working with you good people.
Thanks for everything, and good luck.
Yeah. You, too.
Did you wash your hands?
With soap?
Did you dry them?
What?
Is this all vegetables?
Who ordered all vegetables?
I did. They're good
and you're going to have some.
- Are we going to talk about it?
- What?
The elephant in the room.
What elephant?
I guess not then.
You're referring to today.
Yeah, what's the deal with today?
We all made mistakes.
For example, you kids
were supposed to watch Jack-Jack.
Babysitting, while you guys
did the important stuff.
We talked about this.
You're not old enough to decide
about these things.
- We are old enough to help out.
- Yeah!
Isn't that what you tell us, Dad?
Yeah, well, "help out"
can mean many different things.
But we're supposed to help,
if there's trouble.
Well, yeah, but...
- Aren't you glad we helped today?
- Yeah, I know but...
You said that you were proud of us.
Well, yeah, I was. Am!
We wanna fight bad guys!
No, you don't!
You said things were different now.
And they were, on the island.
But I didn't mean that from now on...
So now, we've gotta go back to
never using our powers.
It defines who I am.
We're not saying you have...
- What?
- Someone on TV said it.
Can we just eat?
The dinner, while it's hot?
Did we do something wrong?
- Yes.
- No.
We didn't do anything wrong.
Superheroes are illegal.
Whether it's fair or not, that's the law.
The law should be fair.
What are we teaching our kids?
To respect the law!
Even when the law is disrespectful?
If laws are unjust, there are laws
to change them!
Otherwise, it's chaos!
Which is exactly what we have!
I just thought it was kinda cool.
What was?
Fighting crime as a family.
It was cool.
But it's over. The world is what it is.
We have to adapt.
Are things bad?
Things are fine.
May I be excused?
How much longer in the motel, Dad?
Not much longer, honey.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Maybe Dicker will find something?
Dicker is done, Bob.
Any thought we had
about being Supers again is fantasy.
One of us has gotta get a job.
One of us?
You did a long stint at Insuricare.
Hated every minute of it.
I know it was hard on you.
Maybe it's my turn in the private sector
and you take care of the kids...
No, I'm doing this. I need to do this.
You know where my suit and ties are?
Burned up when...
The jet destroyed our house.
Yeah.
We can't count on anyone else now, Bob.
It's just us. We can't wait for...
No lifeguard on duty!
Swim at your own risk.
Where'd you go today?
I noticed you missed all the fun.
Don't be mad because I know
when to leave a party.
I'm just as illegal as you guys.
Besides, I knew the cops would let you go.
Yeah, in spite of Bob's best efforts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I heard the program shut down.
How much longer are you in this motel?
Two weeks.
Now, you know the offer still stands.
You're very generous,
but there are five of us.
We wouldn't do that to you and Honey.
Well, door's always open.
You know, the news isn't all bad.
While you guys were being detained...
I was approached by a dude
who represents this tycoon.
- Winston Deavor.
- Wants to talk...
with me, with you two, about hero stuff.
I checked him out.
He's legit. Trained under Dicker.
He wants to meet.
Jeez! More superhero trouble.
We just came from the police station, Lucius.
When?
Tonight. I'm going there now.
You enjoy, I'm sitting this one out.
He wants all three of us.
Honey, let's just at least
hear what he has to say.
You got the address,
I'll meet you guys there.
Go in our Supersuits?
Yeah.
Might wanna wear the old Supersuits.
Got a feeling he's nostalgic.
Where are you going?
The fresh air is especially good tonight.
If Jack-Jack wakes up...
I know the drill.
Your security badges. Please, this way.
Hey, listen, you're my biggest fan.
Good to see you.
I'm your biggest fan.
Shoot!
I love superheroes!
The powers, the costumes...
the mythic struggles.
Winston Deavor. You can call me Win.
Genuine pleasure to meet you.
- Frozone!
- It's good to see you.
- Elastigirl.
- Nice to meet you.
- Mr. Incredible!
- Hello.
Mr. Incredible, Incredible
Incredible
Catching the bad guys
Pow, pow, pow
Who's the cat who's always chill
When survival odds are close to nil
Frozone
Yeah!
Can't tell you what a thrill this is.
And this...
Hello there, superheroes.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
...is my tardy sister, Evelyn.
And I'm scolding myself
so you don't have to, Winston!
Spectacular.
My father was so proud that I
was even remotely connected to you guys.
He used to call you the last line of defense.
He was your top supporter.
He donated to superhero causes.
He raised money
for the Dynaguy statue in Avery Park.
He got to know many Supers personally.
Even installed a phone with direct lines
to Gazerbeam and Fironic...
in case of emergencies.
He loved that, showed it off to everyone.
He was heartbroken when you
were all forced to go underground.
Father believed the world
would become more dangerous without you.
He didn't know how right he was.
There was a break-in.
My father called Gazerbeam. The direct line.
No answer.
He called Fironic, no answer.
Superheroes had just been made illegal...
The robbers discovered him on the phone...
and shot him.
So...
It must've been hard.
Especially for Mother.
She died a few months later. Heartbreak.
If superheroes
had not been forced underground...
it never would've happened.
Or Dad could've taken Mom to the safe room
as soon as he knew there was trouble.
I disagree strongly!
But we're not going into it right now.
The point is...
nobody expected us to be able to actually
run Dad's company.
But with Evelyn as designer,
and myself as operator...
we threw ourselves into
building DEVTECH into what it is today.
A world-class telecommunications company.
Bigger than ever.
Perfectly positioned
to make some wrong things right.
Hence, this meeting.
Let me ask you something.
What is the main reason
you were all forced underground?
- Ignorance.
- Perception.
Take today for example, with the Underminer.
Difficult situation.
You were faced with a lot of hard decisions.
Tell me about it.
I can't.
Because I didn't see it...
neither did anyone else.
So, when you fight bad guys like today...
people don't see the fight
or what led up to it.
They see what politicians tell them to see.
They see destruction and they see you.
So, if we wanna change
people's perceptions about superheroes...
we need you to share your perceptions
with the world.
- How do we do that?
- With cameras.
We need you to share your
perceptions with the world.
How do we do that?
We embed tiny cameras, like those,
into your Supersuits.
Wow, so small.
And the picture is outstanding.
Thanks! Designed 'em myself.
We've got resources, lobbyists,
worldwide connections...
and very important, insurance.
Insurance is key.
All we need now
are the super-est superheroes.
It needs you three. Come on!
Help me make all Supers legal again.
This sounds great!
Let's get this going.
What's my first assignment?
That enthusiasm is golden.
Now hold on to it. But for our first move...
Elastigirl is our best play.
Better than me?
I mean, she's good.
Really, a credit to her...
You know. You know.
With great respect...
let's not test the whole
"insurance-will-pay-for-everything" idea...
on the first go 'round, okay?
Wait a minute. You're saying what? I'm messy?
Well, Evelyn did a cost-benefit analysis...
comparing all your last five years
of crime fighting before going underground.
And Elastigirl's numbers
are self-explanatory.
Well, it's not a fair comparison!
Heavyweight problems
need heavyweight solutions.
Of course! We're gonna solve
all kinds of problems together.
After the perfect launch with Elastigirl!
So, what do you say?
What do I say?
I don't know.
What do you mean, you don't know?
A few hours ago,
you were saying it was over...
and being a superhero was a fantasy.
Now, you get the offer of a lifetime
and you don't know?
It's not that simple, Bob.
I wanna protect the kids!
So do I.
From jail, Bob!
And how do you do that?
By turning down a chance to change the law
that forces them to hide what they are?
They haven't decided what they are.
They're still kids.
Kids with powers, which makes them Supers...
whether they decide
to use those powers or not.
This will benefit them.
It's not a good time to be away.
Dash is having trouble with homework...
Vi is worried about her first date
with that boy she likes, Tony...
and Jack-Jack...
Jack-Jack? What's wrong with him?
Okay, nothing's wrong with Jack-Jack.
But even a normal baby
needs a lot of attention.
I'm just not sure I can leave.
Of course you can leave.
You've got to. So that I...
we can be Supers again,
so our kids can have that choice.
So you can have that choice.
All right, yes!
So I can have that choice.
And I would do a great job!
Regardless of what
Deavor's pie charts say or whatever...
But they want you.
And you'll do a great...
job...
too.
Well, that was excruciating to watch.
I can't lie to you.
It's nice to be wanted.
Flattering, you know, but...
But what's the choice?
One, do this right, get well paid,
we're out of the motel...
and things get better for all Supers,
including our kids.
Or two...
I find a job in two weeks or we're homeless.
You know it's crazy, right?
To help my family, I gotta leave it.
- To fix the law, I gotta break it.
- You'll be great.
I know I will.
But what about you? We have kids.
I'll watch the kids, no problem.
- Easy.
- Easy, huh?
You're adorable.
Well, if there is a problem,
I'll drop this thing and come right back.
You won't need to.
I got it, you go do this thing.
Do it so...
I can do it better.
Deavor here.
This is Elastigirl.
I'm in.
Mr. Deavor, it's wonderful...
but it's too generous.
Nonsense! That's the least we can do.
We're partners now!
Can't have my partners living in a motel.
But whose house? Is it a house?
It's my house. I have several.
I'm not using that one.
Stay as long as you need.
I don't know what to say.
How about "thanks"?
This is our new house?
Okay, easy, tiger. It's being loaned to us.
This is homey.
Look at this place. Deavor bought it
from an eccentric billionaire...
who liked to come and go
without being seen...
so the house has multiple hidden exits.
Good thing we won't stand out.
Wouldn't want to attract
any unnecessary attention.
It's got a big yard!
Isn't this a bit much?
Near a forest!
Would you rather be at the motel?
And a pool!
What exactly is Mom's new job?
The important thing is
we're out of the motel.
I like Mom's new job!
Well, check out the water features.
Wow.
Wicked cool!
Hey! Dash! Stop it!
- Not the couch! Stop it!
- No! Dash!
- Stop! Don't touch the buttons!
- The couch!
- Dash!
- No!
No, no!
Oh, no. Oh, boy.
This isn't me.
I'm not all dark and angsty.
I'm Elastigirl.
I'm, you know, flexible.
E designed this?
No, some guy named Alexander Galbaki.
Glad it's you and not me,
'cause you're gonna hear from her.
This note came with it.
What?
A new Elasticycle.
Elasticycle? I didn't know you had a bike.
Hey, I had a mohawk.
There's a lot about me you don't know.
Yeah, but... A mohawk?
You didn't miss anything.
Yeah! This one's electric.
What's that mean?
Means it's torque-y. I'll get the hang of it.
You will be great.
I will be great. And you will, too.
We will both be great.
Bye, sweetie.
- Wait a minute! Is that Elastigirl?
- I think that's Elastigirl.
Hey! Elastigirl!
Marry me, Elastigirl!
Here comes Elastigirl
Stretching her
No theme songs
or I'll turn this bus right around!
Look at that.
New Urbem. You wanna make
a big crime fighting statement...
you go where the crime is big.
Strange thing to be excited about, Winston.
It's like a superhero's playground!
No Sugar Bombs on my watch.
Where's Mom?
She's up and out.
She's at her new job doing hero work.
But I thought superheroes were still illegal.
They are, for now.
So Mom is getting paid to break the law?
She's not breaking...
She's an advocate for superheroes.
It's a new job.
So, Mom is going out illegally...
to explain why she shouldn't be illegal.
Hey...
The bus is here!
Grab your stuff quickly! Go on, get on the...
Put your homework in your pack!
Bye-bye!
We're gonna get along just fine...
'cause you don't ask any hard questions.
All right. All locations, we need to know
where you want us.
Stand by.
Seems strange to wait for crime.
Relax. You're smack in the middle...
of the worst crime area in the city.
It's perfect.
- It's a superhero's playground.
- "It's a superhero's playground." Right.
You know, after we went underground...
my husband used to listen
to a police scanner...
waiting for something to happen.
And I got mad at him for it.
I'm such a hypocrite.
- All units.
- Something's up.
We've been picking up some chatter
about potential disruptions...
to the hovertrain's opening ceremony.
- Disruption or threat?
- Both.
Station's at Fifty-Fourth and Nottingham.
A potential threat! Perfect!
Fifty-fourth and Nottingham. Go, go, go!
Hey, Vi! I want you back here by 10:30.
11-ish?
10-ish, heading for 9:30-ish.
10:30-ish it is.
Enjoy the movie.
"In the county of Noddoff...
"the Frubbers of Freep...
"are all giving in
to the sweet succor of sleep."
We will control the horizontal...
we will control the vertical.
That's not the way
you're supposed to do it, Dad.
They want us to do it this way.
I don't know that way!
Why would they change math?
- It's okay, Dad.
- Math is math!
I'll just wait for Mom to get back.
What?
She won't understand it
any better than I do...
The Outer Limits.
"All over Doozle-Dorf,
the Fribbers of Frupp are going to sleep...
"'cause they just can't keep up.
"All over Doozle-Dorf, Doozles are dozing.
"Eyelids so heavy, they're drooping.
"Closing! The point is:
Everyone, everyone's hitting the sack!
"Everyone's getting the sleep
that they lack."
Mayors often brag about their cities...
and I'm no exception.
And I'm willing to admit
that New Urbem is not the only city...
Are you sure the police are gonna be
okay with this?
Sure. You're making life easy for them.
They still haven't forgiven us for
the last time we made life easy for them.
I know the Chief of Police.
There won't be a problem.
With all due respect...
if you alone had handled the Underminer...
things would have been different.
I'm just saying.
...on budget and ahead of schedule...
to launch our magnificent new hovertrain.
It can get you where you need to go
at ridiculous speeds.
The future is open for business!
Wait. The train has stopped.
It's going the wrong direction.
It's going the wrong way.
I'm going after it.
This thing's really moving.
100 and climbing. How much track is built?
About 25 miles.
No one can shut this thing down?
They've tried. No-go.
Is that Elastigirl?
Overrides?
They're locked out of the system.
What about a fail-safe?
Not enough time.
Someone's calling! Switching over.
Hey, Mom. I can't find my high-tops
and Dad can't find them either.
But he won't call you and ask, so I am.
Do not call your mother!
Dash, honey. Can't talk right now.
Look under your bed, okay.
- How much time?
- Less than two minutes!
There's a shortcut.
Cut through the culvert up ahead.
I don't know if I can stay with it.
What the heck was that?
Is everybody all right? Is anybody injured?
Are you all right?
Your story better be good.
Hey. Hey!
What happened?
Honey, why are you...
Don't say anything.
It's Dad. Are you okay?
I'm fine. I don't wanna talk about it.
Tony didn't even call?
I don't wanna talk about it.
- Honey...
- Dad!
If you want me to feel better,
then leave me alone.
Please?
See, there's nothing a cop hates worse
than a missing child.
My kid brother's son.
Today is his first birthday.
But if anybody can find that child,
it's you, Roman.
Because you're a wonderful policeman.
This is a holdup.
All right, get your hands up, turn your back.
Put your hands behind your heads
and keep them there!
Don't move!
Drop that. All right, now get over there.
Watch the door.
You think I'm kiddin'?
Now.
I said now!
I got it! Come on, I tell you, come on!
You wanna get killed?
No, no, no!
No!
No, no, no.
No, no, no!
You have powers!
Yeah, baby, and there's not a scratch on you!
Did you go through the locked door?
Are those your powers?
Who can multiply like rabbits
and go right through any solid...
Oh, my God!
- Hello?
- Hey, honey.
- You weren't gonna call me?
- Oh, hey!
No. I mean, yes, yeah...
I just didn't wanna wake you.
The strangest thing just happened
out in the yard.
- Sounds like I just woke you up.
- No, no.
- It's just, Jack-Jack...
- He had an accident!
I knew it! I'm coming home right now!
I never should have...
No accident.
Stay there and finish your mission.
You never should...
What? You don't think I can do this?
No, no. Sorry. I misspoke.
Do you need me to come back?
No, no. No, I've got this.
Everything's great.
What happened with Jack-Jack?
Nothing. He's in excellent health.
Well, that's good.
How was Violet's date?
That was tonight, right?
Yes. Good.
All fine and good.
And Jack-Jack went down with no trouble?
Fine, yes, no trouble.
And Dash got his homework done?
All done.
So, things haven't spiraled out
of control the moment I left?
Amazing as it may seem,
it has been quite uneventful in fact.
How about you?
I saved a runaway train!
It was so great!
The mayor was there to cut the ribbon
on this new train.
Elastigirl pursued the train
and was able to successfully activate...
Blah, blah, blah.
He says a few words, cuts the ribbon...
and the train starts
pulling out of the station backwards...
- track of its brand new hovertrain...
- ...malfunctioned...
...thanking Elastigirl...
- Superhero Elastigirl...
- Elastigirl...
Boom! No casualties!
...specialized motorbike,
saving all of the passengers...
One thing leads to another
and suddenly, I go after it!
I'm telling you, honey, it was a saga!
That's fantastic, honey!
And on your first night!
I am so proud of you, really.
I'm proud of you, honey.
I know you want to get out there
and you will soon.
And you'll be amazing.
I couldn't have done this
if you hadn't taken over so well.
Thanks for handling everything.
It's nothing.
I love you, honey. I'll be back soon.
Sweet dreams.
Sweet dreams, honey.
"Hey, Dad, it's okay.
I'll just wait for Mom to get home."
As if she could... I know how to...
I can do math.
Oh, brother...
Wait for Mom!
What am I, a substitute parent?
It's not my fault they changed math.
Come on, buddy. Come on.
I think I understand your math assignment.
We still have some time to finish it
before your test.
So first, you wanna put all the numbers
by themselves on one side.
...you change the sign.
That means a plus becomes a minus
and a minus...
You got it?
Yeah, baby!
Hello.
We're in a new house.
I did write my address on your locker...
in permanent ink.
Is that what that is?
Did you forget?
Forget what?
That's funny.
Points for funny.
Was it the weird outfit?
Because there's a reason.
I'm in a drama class...
and they just wanna do Shakespeare...
but they're like,
"Try to make it relevant for the kids."
So, like, "Oh, superheroes!
Kids love superheroes."
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- You wanna wear one kind of tights...
and then they're like,
"No, wear these other kind of tights."
Do I know you?
Many say your speech today is critical.
Both sides just want the best
for their people.
We are so close to finally getting peace
in the region.
I haven't done this in a while.
This is good. The train gives us momentum.
Just go out there
and be your charming self...
and capitalize on it.
Ms. Elastigirl, they're ready for you.
Hey, stretch a leg.
Thank you, Chad. It was fun.
- Ambassador, your documents.
- We're moving to the rooftop.
Madame Ambassador, hello!
You are Elastigirl!
This is why now I'm shaking your hand.
It was so sad when you went underground.
I am glad to see
you back in your shiny outfit.
That means so much coming from you.
Good luck with your speech.
This way, Ambassador.
Bring lasting peace!
I will, when you defeat evil.
Okay.
Three, two...
For over 15 years,
superheroes have been in hiding.
Forced into it by a society
no longer willing to support them.
That may soon be changing...
due to a growing movement
to bring the Supers back.
Here, fresh on the heels of her own
heroic save of a runaway train...
and sporting a new look,
is the superhero, Elastigirl.
- Welcome!
- Hello, Chad.
All the polls are going in your direction.
That's true. Things are good...
Hello.
Hello?
Do I have your attention?
Yes, Chad.
Of course I do.
I'm appearing on your screen.
Reading the words I'm saying
off of another screen.
Screens are everywhere.
We are controlled by screens.
And screens are controlled by me...
Screenslaver.
Hey!
I control this broadcast...
and this idiotic anchorman
you see before you.
What's wrong with him?
The signal's been hijacked.
I'll check it out.
Don't look at any monitors.
I could hijack the ambassador's aerocade...
while it's still airborne.
Right, Elastigirl?
Nearest window! Where's the nearest window?
- What's going on?
- Where's Elastigirl?
Which one?
Elastigirl! What are you doing here?
The ambassador is in danger.
Which chopper is she...
Look out!
Follow them and get me close!
Get out of the sky, and touch down safely!
Stand down! It's Elastigirl.
Stay in your seat, ma'am!
We're under attack!
Quick, go! Protect the ambassador!
Open the door!
Do as she says!
Can you all swim?
- Yeah.
- No!
We're gonna have to slingshot! Hang on!
Are you all right, ma'am?
I'm perfectly fine...
Boys are jerks and superheroes suck.
Good morning!
He takes one look at me in that suit...
and decides to pretend
he doesn't even know me.
He's protecting himself.
If he really did see you,
it's best that he forget.
It's better for you, too.
I can't tell you how many memories
Dicker's had to erase over the years...
when someone figured out
your mother's or my identity.
It was Dicker! You told him about Tony!
- Honey...
- You had me erased from Tony's mind!
I hate superheroes!
And I renounce them!
I renounce them!
Is she having adolescence?
A new report out today shows that,
when it comes to decision-making...
people have more trust in
a monkey throwing darts than Congress.
What's going on, Tommy? A protest?
They're here in support.
Support? Support of what?
Well, in support of you.
Wow.
Oh, hey...
Thanks for coming out. Hi.
Oh, my goodness. Thanks so much.
Hello.
What does your sign say?
Ka-boom! Ka-pow! Supers should be legal now!
Talk to ya.
Oh, what do ya know!
Ellenwood.
Now you wanna return my calls
about superheroes, huh?
I'll have to call you back.
That felt good.
Felicia, hold my calls, please.
Hey! It's working!
The ambassador made a big speech
about superheroes today.
Turns out saving someone's life makes
a good impression on them. Who knew?
I'm getting calls from all over the world.
Media awareness is up 72%.
The push for superhero legalization
is becoming a worldwide movement!
I have big plans for our next move.
We're gonna have a summit at sea.
We'll use our ship...
we'll gather leaders and Supers...
- from all over the world.
- That's great.
I'm happy.
I'm happy the numbers are up.
I'm happy the ambassador is pro-superhero...
and I'm happy you're happy.
I'm hearing that you're happy,
but why am I not feeling it?
Because I didn't get him!
Screenslaver is still out there.
All I did was play his game
and win this round.
He's gonna want more
and as long as he gets to play, he wins.
One thing I've learned in business?
Smell the flowers.
They don't bloom that often.
What do you want on your tombstone?
"She worried a lot"?
All right, stop talking.
Show her.
This is just so exciting, isn't it?
Wow.
Wow! Elastigirl, there you are.
- Hello.
- I didn't...
Wow!
Come on, get yourself together, Karen.
Hi, my superhero name is Voyd.
I just wanna thank you, for being you!
Okay, what I can do is this.
Yeah.
That is impressive. Very interdimensional.
I felt like an outcast before.
But now, with you being you, I feel like...
Yay, me.
I flew them in from all over.
They've all been in hiding.
They have powers, secret identities...
and names they've given themselves.
I'm Screech. It's a pleasure.
I've always considered you
the gold standard for superheroes.
Thanks. You're too nice.
I am called Brick.
Nice to meet you, Brick. Where are you from?
Wisconsin.
Elastigirl. I assume your powers are...
You know, zapping things electrically...
charging things,
bolts of lightning, that kind of stuff.
Name's Reflux.
Medical condition or superpower, you decide.
That's a little line I say just to
put people at ease.
Hope I don't offend.
No, no, no. Reflux. Love it.
I do look forward to working with you.
Yes, that is impressive. Keep practicing.
Well, I'm beat. Congratulations. Big day.
Good night, ladies. I will see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Must be nice for you,
being out front after all this time.
Out front?
Well, it's been a while
since your superhero days...
and even then, you were kind of in
Mr. Incredible's shadow.
Nah, I beg to differ.
I'm not saying you weren't big.
No, you were, and are, a superstar...
but you have the stage to yourself now.
And people have to pay attention.
Oh, you mean, "It's a man's world"
and all that?
What world do you live in?
Your brother runs DEVTECH.
I don't want his job. I invent, he sells.
I ask you,
which of us has the greater influence?
Which side of me are you asking?
The believer or the cynic?
The cynic...
Would say selling is more important because
the best sellers have the most buyers.
Doesn't matter what you're selling.
It only matters what people buy.
This is true.
If I discovered the origin of the universe...
my brother would find a way
to market it as a foot massager.
So, what would the believer say?
The believer would tell you
to make your mark.
Don't wait for permission, assert yourself
and impose your will on the status quo.
- Sounds like my brother.
- What?
You sound like my brother.
Well, he's not wrong.
There is an art to getting a reaction...
I know how to get him.
- My brother?
- No. Screenslaver!
You're tech-savvy.
I need to lock onto a signal...
and trace its origin.
How fast can you slap something together
and meet me at the airport?
- Airport?
- Need to go out of town, pronto.
I can get your contraption together
by 5:00 a.m.
I need to get on TV. Chad!
I'll get my brother to set up an exclusive
with him tonight on the newscast.
- Finish our interview by phone!
- Promote the hell out of it.
Independence from Screenslavery!
Chad tonight.
Boom!
- Dicker.
- Yeah, hey, Rick.
You remember that kid I mentioned
to you? Tony Rydinger.
Mind wipe? Yeah, nice kid.
You also wiped out the Friday night date
my daughter had with him.
In fact, you wiped out my daughter.
Oops. Not an exact science, Bob.
Rick, you gotta help me here.
Violet hates me, and you, and superheroes.
I gotta fix this.
What do you know about Tony?
Not much.
Seems like a good kid.
Popular, plays sports, music.
Parents own The Happy Platter,
kid works there part time.
Happy Platter?
Why did we drive all the way
across town for The Happy Platter?
We'd like a booth over there,
near the philodendron.
Good, right? Near the philodendron.
This platter doesn't look all that happy
to me.
It looks bored.
The Bored Platter!
I thought Vi would want a change of pace
from drive-in food.
I like drive-in food.
Does this mean vegetables?
A balanced diet means vegetables, kiddo.
Get used to it.
Good evening, everyone.
Oh, no!
- Is she all right?
- Violet, are you okay?
- Nothing to see here.
- Yeah, more napkins would be good.
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
- It happens all the time here.
Mops it right up.
Normally, she doesn't ever drip like this.
- Would you like water, sir?
- Yes.
Yes, I would. This is my daughter...
- who you must know, right?
- God. Stop.
- Hello.
- Violet.
Hello, Violet.
Hey, Vi, say hi to...
Don't push it, Dad.
I'm Dash, her little brother.
Hello.
This is really good water.
It's very refreshing.
Spring water, is it?
I don't know, sir. I think it's tap.
Well, it is very good.
Excellent tap.
Excuse me.
Nice to meet you.
Where'd she go?
To find a good place to be angry?
Tonight, we go now
to a special remote interview...
with Elastigirl.
How you feeling, Chad? You doing all right?
I'm fine. The doctors checked me out.
I have no memory of the event.
I gotta tell you, it's pretty strange
to see a recording...
of yourself the night before
and have no recollection.
I don't think anyone needs to worry.
We've taken many precautions tonight though.
Where are you right now?
On a case, in a secure undisclosed location.
I wanna talk about you...
starting with your save of a runaway train.
Here's an exclusive unedited clip
from your own suit cam.
Roll the clip.
This thing's really moving.
100 and climbing. How much track is built?
About 25 miles.
The Screenslaver interrupts this program...
for an important announcement.
I'll be damned. She knew.
Let's see if your gadget works.
Don't bother watching the rest.
Gotcha!
Elastigirl doesn't save the day.
She only postpones her defeat.
And while she postpones her defeat...
you eat chips
and watch her confront problems...
that you are too lazy to deal with.
Superheroes
are part of your brainless desire...
to replace true experience with simulation.
You don't talk, you watch talk shows.
You don't play games, you watch game shows.
Travel, relationships, risk...
every meaningful experience
must be packaged...
and delivered to you to watch at a distance.
So that you can remain ever sheltered...
ever passive...
ever ravenous consumers...
who can't bring themselves
to rise from their couches...
break a sweat and participate in life.
You want superheroes to protect you...
and make yourselves ever more powerless
in the process.
While you tell yourselves
you're being looked after.
That your interests are being served.
And your rights are being upheld.
So that the system can keep stealing
from you...
smiling at you all the while.
Go ahead, send your Supers to stop me.
Grab your snacks, watch your screens,
and see what happens.
You are no longer in control.
I am.
Find anything?
Sorry!
What happened?
What happened is you destroyed my evidence.
What's going on? What did I do?
What did you guys do to me?
That's right, punk. Blame the system.
Your tracker worked like a charm, Evelyn.
You're a genius.
Aw, shucks!
I'm just the genius behind the genius.
Hey, Dad.
We're doing fractions and denismals
and percentages
and I don't get 'em.
Aren't you...
Didn't we get all caught up?
Yeah, we were caught up...
and now we're doing fractions
and percentages and demicels.
Decimals.
...the addition of the Incredibile,
the super car...
once driven by superhero, Mr. Incredible.
It's the kind of thing you buy
when you have everything else.
They said it was beyond repair.
It was in perfect condition.
You used to drive that?
They said it was destroyed.
Long thought lost or destroyed,
the famous car turned up at private auction.
They said it was...
That's my car!
Stupid water feature!
This car is just loaded with amazing gadgets.
Care to demonstrate?
I'd love to, but we haven't figured out
how to make them work yet.
Wow! It works?
What are you doing? This is not a toy!
That's a rocket launcher!
Sweet! Which one launches the rocket?
Hey! This is not your car!
It's not your car, either!
It is so! It's the Incredibile.
- Why's that guy have it?
- He shouldn't!
Launch the rockets! Launch the rockets!
Launch the rockets!
I'm not launching anything!
- I wanna blow it up!
- Do you think I want an angry rich guy...
coming after me right now...
- when I'm trying not to...
- I'm not sure
- what's happened here, Mark.
- ...distract your mother.
But everyone here has scattered
and I'm afraid I'll need
to move at any minute.
Rich guy got my car.
So, you're not gonna steal your car
back from the rich guy?
What the heck is that?
Jack-Jack has powers?
Yeah, but...
- You knew about this?
- Yeah.
- Why didn't you tell us?
- I don't know.
We're your kids.
We need to know these things.
- Did you tell Mom?
- No.
- Why not?
- Your mother is not...
- You'd want us to tell you, wouldn't you?
- Why would you not tell Mom?
- Because I didn't wanna...
- What?
- Come on, man.
- Because it's not the time.
- Why?
- Because...
- So uncool!
- Because I'm formulating, okay?
I'm taking in information, I'm processing!
I'm doing the math,
I'm fixing the boyfriend...
and keeping the baby
from turning into a flaming monster!
How do I do it?
By rolling with the punches, baby!
I eat thunder and crap lightning, okay?
'Cause I'm Mr. Incredible!
Not Mr. So-So or Mr. Mediocre-Guy.
Mr. Incredible!
We should call Lucius.
No. I can handle it.
There's no way I'm gonna...
Dada.
I'm calling Lucius.
Looks normal to me.
When did this start happening?
Since Helen got the job.
- I assume she knows?
- Are you kidding?
I can't tell her about this,
not while she's doing hero work!
Mama!
Girls, come on.
Leave the saving the world to the men?
- I don't think so.
- Mama!
I've got to succeed!
So she can succeed.
- So we can succeed!
- I get it, Bob!
I get it. When was the last time you slept?
Who keeps track of that?
Besides, he's a baby.
I can handle it, I got this handled.
So, you good then?
You got everything under control? Right?
What the...?
Cookie! Cha Cha want a cookie?
Num-num cookie? Cha Cha wanna num-num?
Num-num cookie! Cookie!
- You're not...
- Cookie!
- Oh, my God!
Dada! Dada. Dada.
Okay! Okay.
So, he can still hear you from the...
From the other dimension, yeah.
That is freaky. I mean, that's not like...
Not like our other kids. No, it is not.
Full powers, totally random.
So now, he's what? Is he good?
Yeah, you'd think so, right?
Obviously, I can't keep giving him cookies!
But if I stop...
He is freaking! Again, he is freaking!
No biting the daddy!
- What the...?
- No biting!
Okay.
I think I just need a little bit of me time.
Then I'll be good to go.
You need more than me time, Bob.
You need major life realignment
on a number of levels.
Starting with baby superfreak here!
You need some solid outside-the-box thinking.
Galbaki?
Elastigirl's supersuit is by Galbaki?
Explain yourself!
Oh, my God. You're worse than I thought.
It's the baby. I brought the baby.
Highly unusual.
You look ghastly, Robert.
I haven't been sleeping.
I broke my daughter,
they keep changing math...
we needed double-A batteries,
but I got triple-A's...
and now we still need double-A batteries.
I put one red thing in a load of whites
and now everything's pink.
And I think we need eggs.
Done properly, parenting is a heroic act.
Done properly.
I am fortunate that it has
never afflicted me.
But you do not come to me
for eggs and batteries, Robert.
I design herowear and Elastigirl
must have a new suit.
Actually, it's Jack-Jack.
You also wish a new suit for the baby?
I would hardly classify this as an emergency.
Well, he's a special case. Worth studying.
If I could just leave him with you
for a while...
Leave him? Here?
I am not a baby person, Robert.
I have no baby facilities. I am an artist.
I do not involve myself
in the prosaic day-to-day to...
day.
Fascinating!
Are you seeing this, Robert?
Dada.
Oh, my God.
Yes!
Of course you can leave the baby overnight.
I'm sure filling in for Helen
is challenging, and you are very tired...
and the other children need you
and miss you, and you must go to them.
Auntie Edna will take care of everything...
so, drive safely and goodbye.
I enjoy our visits.
"Auntie Edna"?
Attention. Attention.
I wanna thank everyone
that came out tonight...
in support of superheroes...
and bringing them back into society!
You all made it happen.
The need for this has been made
crystal clear in recent days...
with bad actors like the self-proclaimed
Screenslaver threatening our peace.
His reign was short, huh?
And thanks to this woman...
a great super. You love her. You missed her.
Welcome back, Elastigirl.
Come on up here. Don't be bashful.
Come on. Get up here.
I want you to have this.
A memento.
Thanks, Winston, Evelyn,
and everyone at DEVTECH.
I am forever in your debt.
And thanks to all of you, your pressure
changed all the right minds.
We've made amazing headway
in a very short time...
which leads me to an important announcement.
Just now, at a worldwide summit...
leaders from more than a hundred
of the world's top countries...
have agreed to make superheroes legal again!
We'll gather superheroes and leaders
from all over the planet...
on our boat, the Everjust...
for a televised signing ceremony at sea.
Now if you'll excuse us,
we got a ship to catch!
So good to see you. Thanks for coming out.
Hey. Hi, it's me, again.
There's something
I've always wanted to ask you.
Yeah, how do you balance the superhero stuff
with the life stuff?
I know I can handle the superhero stuff.
Would you please excuse me a moment?
Yeah, okay, see you later! Good talk!
Hey, Vi.
Hey.
Where's Jack-Jack?
E's taking him for a little bit.
Edna is babysitting?
Yeah.
And you're okay with this?
Yeah. I don't know why, but yeah.
I wanted to say something to you.
Sorry about Tony.
I didn't think about Dicker
erasing his memory...
or about you having to pay the price
for a choice...
you never made. It's not fair, I know.
And then, I made it worse at the restaurant
by trying to...
Anyway. Anyway...
I'm sorry.
I'm used to knowing
what the right thing to do is...
but now, I'm not sure anymore.
I just wanna be...
a good dad.
You're not good.
You're super.
Are superheroes allowed to drink on duty?
I'm definitely not on duty.
Ignore the costume.
I know I should be up there...
but I had to step away from the
grip and grins, you know?
Gotta get away to keep it pure. I know I do.
What are you getting away from?
You know, company stuff. My brother, mostly.
But you love him, you two
are this company. Yin and yang.
Yeah, I invent the stuff,
he's good at people.
Pleasing them, engaging them,
figuring out what they want.
I never know what people want.
What do you think they want?
Ease. People will trade quality
for ease every time.
It may be crap, but hey, it's convenient.
Yeah. Kind of like this case.
What? The Screenslaver?
Yeah, something's not sitting right.
It was too easy.
That was too easy? Wow.
- Funny.
- What?
Look at that.
One of Screenslaver's monitors
is tuned into my suit cam.
What?
Isn't the suit cam closed circuit?
It is.
Then how come Screenslaver has it?
Maybe he hacked it?
So, he's sophisticated enough to do that...
but he has simple locks on his doors?
Maybe he wanted you to find him.
He wanted to get caught?
He wanted you to win.
That makes no sense. He's a brilliant guy.
If he's smart enough to conceive
of technology like this...
he's smart enough to think
of something to do with it.
The guy we put in jail delivered pizzas.
So?
Einstein was a patent clerk.
Look, you won. You got the guy who...
Wait. All Screenslaver needs to do
to hypnotize someone...
is get a screen in front of their eyes.
But what if the screen doesn't
look like a screen?
What if the pizza guy
is really a pizza guy...
but he was controlled by the screens
built into his glasses...
You are good.
Look, the robot! It's taking off.
I'm not getting a reading yet.
- Press "fire"?
- Now!
More power.
I hope this works, Dad.
I thought it was best to just let you sleep.
Seventeen hours.
How do you feel?
Super.
- You got it, Dad.
- Hurray!
I can't tell you how much I appreciate
you watching Jack-Jack for me, E.
Yes, I'm sure your gratitude
is quite inexpressible.
Don't ask me to do it again, darling.
My rates are far too high.
I am joking, Robert.
I enjoyed the assignment.
He is bright and I am stimulating.
We deserve each other.
Your child is a polymorph.
Like all babies, he has enormous potential.
It is not unknown for supers
to have more than one power when young...
but this little one has many.
Yes, you have many powers.
I understand your lack of sleep
and coherency, Robert.
Babies can be anything,
and your child is no exception.
He has pure, unlimited potential, Robert.
He slept while I worked in a creative fever.
Auntie Edna stayed up all night...
making sure you look fabulous
in your many forms.
What are you... You're putting him in the...
In the chamber, Robert.
He is part of the demonstration
and will be fine.
Your challenge is to manage a baby
who has multiple powers...
and no control over them, yes?
That sums it up.
I often work to music and I noticed
the baby responds to it as well.
Specifically, Mozart.
I blended Kevlar with carbyne
for durability under duress...
and cotton for comfort.
Interwoven with these fabrics
are a mesh of tiny sensors...
that monitor the baby's physical properties.
Oh, Lord! What is he doing?
Well, it's Mozart, Robert. Can you blame him?
The important thing is that the suit
and tracker...
anticipated the change and alerted you.
Oh, no. Cookies. I gotta get cookies!
You do not need cookies.
As I learned quite painfully last night...
any solution involving cookies
will inevitably result in the demon baby.
"Combustion imminent"?
What does that mean?
It means fire, Robert, for which
the suit has countermeasures.
I suggest you extinguish the baby's flames
before he trips the sprinkler system.
The flame retardant
is blackberry lavender, darling.
Effective, edible, and delicious.
Well, what do you know? That is useful.
Although, I have doubtlessly exceeded your
expectations for a single night's work...
the suit and device contain
a few more features we need to discuss.
Thanks again, E, for everything.
How much do I owe you for...
Pish-posh, darling. Your bill
will be covered by my fee...
for being Mr. Incredible, Elastigirl,
and Frozone's exclusive designer...
throughout the known universe
and until the end of time.
But babysitting this one...
I do for free, darling.
I would resist the temptation to stretch.
The temperature around you
is well below freezing.
Try to stretch and you'll break.
So, you're the Screenslaver.
Yes and no.
Let's say, I created the character
and pre-recorded the messages.
Does Winston know?
That I'm the Screenslaver? Of course not.
Can you imagine what Mr. Free Enterprise
would do with my hypnosis technology?
Worse than what you're doing?
Hey, I'm using the technology
to destroy people's trust in it.
Like I'm using superheroes.
Who did I put in jail?
Pizza delivery guy.
Seemed the right height, build.
He gave you a pretty good fight.
I should say I gave you a pretty good fight
through him.
But it doesn't bother you
that an innocent man is in jail?
He was surly and the pizza was cold.
I counted on you.
That's why you failed.
What?
Why would you count on me?
Because I built you a bike?
Because my brother knows the words
to your theme song?
We don't know each other.
But you can count on me anyway.
I am supposed to, aren't I?
Because you have some strange abilities
and a shiny costume...
the rest of us are supposed
to put our lives into your gloved hands.
That's what my father believed.
When our home was broken into,
my mother wanted to hide.
Begged my father to use the safe room.
But Father insisted
they call his superhero friends.
He died, pointlessly, stupidly...
waiting for heroes to save the day.
- But why would you... Your brother...
- Is a child!
He remembers the time
when we had parents and superheroes.
So, like a child, Winston conflates the two.
Mommy and Daddy went away
because upers went away.
Our sweet parents were fools
to put their lives in anybody else's hands.
Superheroes keep us weak.
Are you gonna kill me?
Nah.
Using you is better.
You're gonna help me make supers illegal...
forever.
Dada. Dada.
Ready? Laser eyes.
Stop.
- Wow!
- Yeah!
Yay, Jack-Jack!
- Yeah, baby!
- And that's not all. Watch this.
Jack-Jack, blaster ready?
No way.
- That is crazy cool.
- My turn. I get to blast him first!
- Let me try. I want him. Give him to me.
- Hey, I'm just demonstrating.
No firing the baby around the house,
you understand?
This is potentially dangerous...
and we're trying to teach him
to control his powers, okay?
Stop. See the screen.
He vanished! That's really cool!
Okay, good. Use the thing.
That's the current readout. Click it.
See the readout?
Dimension four. See the shape?
That's the room. See where he is in relation?
So, where is he?
He's... there!
Okay. Come out. Num-num cookie?
- Yay, Jack-Jack!
- Yeah, Jack-Jack!
That's really cool.
Hello?
Elastigirl's in trouble.
What? What happened to her?
Sorry to tell you on the phone.
Meet me on our ship at DEVTECH.
The ship at DEVTECH.
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
What's at the ship at DEVTECH?
Lucius? Bob. Helen's in trouble.
I need someone to watch the kids.
Suit up. It might get weird.
I'll be there. ASAP. Fifteen tops.
Where are you going ASAP?
You better be back ASAP!
And leaving that suit.
I gotta go. I'll be home soon.
Lucius will be here sooner.
No firing the baby around the house, okay?
What's at the ship at DEVTECH?
And why are you in your Supersuit?
Is that Mom's supersuit?
She may need it. You never know.
What's going on?
I don't know, but Dad called Lucius
after getting a call about Mom...
and then left.
I thought you renounced superheroes.
Yeah, well, I renounce my renunciation.
Put that on.
Hello there, little fella.
Hello.
You kids aren't safe.
The Deavors sent us to take you...
Well, isn't that redundant?
The Deavors just sent me here
to guard the house.
'Cause the kids aren't safe.
I get it, managerial screw-up.
Tell Winston I handled it.
You understand, Ms...
Voyd.
Ms. Voyd.
Drive safely.
The thing is, he wants us to bring you, too.
Hey.
That isn't gonna hold them long.
Dash, grab the baby!
Spread out!
Whoa!
Dash!
We gotta get to my car.
What? What's going on?
Little fella!
It worked!
Incredibile, windows down!
Dive in!
Incredibile, set voice identification.
Loudly, say your names.
- Violet Parr.
- Dashiell Robert Parr.
Lucius!
Incredibile, escape!
Fill me in!
Good news and bad news. We found her.
She seems physically fine but
she's had an encounter with Screenslaver...
and she's acting kind of strange. In here.
Strange how?
Helen?
Helen, what are you...
Helen, it's me.
Incredibile, pull over.
We can't go to E's.
You saw those goggles they put on Lucius.
They were wearing them, too.
They're all under someone's control.
They've probably done the same to Mom.
Okay. Bad guys after us.
No Mom, no Dad.
No Lucius.
But we have our powers, this car...
and... what?
Incredibile, take us to DEVTECH.
The kids have escaped in a tricked-out car,
but we got Frozone.
Bring him to the ship at DEVTECH immediately.
We missed 'em!
I wish the Incredibile could
follow that boat.
- What did you do?
- I don't know.
- I didn't do anything!
Wow, this car does anything I say.
We didn't plan this well.
What do you mean? We're here, aren't we?
Yes, we're here.
We need to be up there.
Hey...
What if the Incredibile has ejector seats?
Wait, what? No.
- Yeah, baby!
- No, don't say any more...
Max power! Launch!
Come on.
Hello! Glad you could come.
Welcome to the conference.
Our stars, where are they?
The event's about to start.
They didn't want to upstage the others.
They'll join for the signing.
Welcome, guests! You're in for a treat.
This ship is the largest hydrofoil
on the planet.
So, hold onto something...
because we're going to open her up!
We need to find Mom and Dad. Stay here.
I'm gonna search for them.
Wait! Who's gonna watch Jack-Jack?
Suck it up. I won't be long.
Wait. Wait, but, but wait!
This is important. They are in trouble.
It's up to us. To us, understand?
Keep him amused but quiet!
Quiet!
Jack-Jack?
Jack-Jack? Jack-Jack!
Jack-Jack!
The mesmerized supers know we're here...
but I found Mom and Dad...
Where's Jack-Jack?
You lost him? I gave you one thing to do!
The tracker. Use the tracker.
He's going up?
- He's in an elevator.
- Let's go!
Hey, little baby. Where are your parents?
And here they are, folks!
The supers who started this whole thing.
I told you they'd be there in time.
Hey, did you make them new masks?
Yeah. Night vision, et cetera...
They look good, right?
So simple, even he can do it.
And we're back live in three, two, one...
This is a momentous occasion.
We've all managed to accomplish something
extraordinarily rare in today's world.
We agree on something.
We agree to undo a bad decision.
To make sure
a few extraordinarily gifted members...
of the world's many countries
are treated fairly.
To invite them once again
to use their gifts...
to benefit the world.
I thank all of you for representing
your nation's commitment to superheroes.
With special thanks to Ambassador Selick.
Yeah, it's okay. Let her hear you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you, Ambassador, for your early
and very crucial support.
I can't think of anyone
more deserving than you...
to be the first signature
on the International Superhero Accord.
There it is!
Holy cow!
I know he's on fire. Just put him out.
They're coming.
Is it okay to give him that?
I wasn't hearing any better ideas.
No!
Come on, Jack-Jack. We have to go.
Cookie num-num?
Mama, Mama.
I see him. He's getting away!
Stand back.
Darn it!
He's heading for Mom.
It is done. The world is super again.
Group photo. Come on. Group photo, everyone.
Squeeze in. That's it. Historic occasion.
Everyone, smile.
Go on phase two.
Years of mandated hiding and silence
have made us bitter.
You bring us out into the light...
only to clean up the messes
your lack of discipline creates.
Your bodies and your character are weak.
Your promises are empty,
and you will pay for it.
We no longer serve you.
We serve only us. May the fittest survive.
Some very alarming moments there...
before the technical difficulties.
Please bear with us.
What?
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
Hold! Let him talk.
Superheroes have forcibly
taken the bridge. Repeat.
Now.
A little further.
Little further. Stop.
What the... A baby?
Mom and Dad. Uncle Lucius?
- My mama.
- Jack-Jack, no!
A super baby?
No, no, no!
Put him down!
- Grab her!
- No!
Hold Jack-Jack.
No!
Hey, it's me!
Yeah, that's what I thought last time.
Kids, what are you...
You came for us?
Don't be mad.
Sweetie, how could I be mad?
I'm proud.
Not to break up a tender moment,
but where are we?
Is this DEVTECH's ship?
Evelyn Deavor controls the Screenslaver...
and until a second ago, us.
Where's the crew?
Collision detected. Correct course.
Uh-oh. Did I do that?
Mom, the suit? Try this.
Phase Three. Go on Phase Three!
Why are the kids here?
You didn't go to the house?
I went to the house.
You didn't escape? How did you not escape?
Hey! We just saved you!
Escape? Escape from who?
Those guys!
What the...? Jack-Jack has powers?
We know. Fight now, talk later.
Jack-Jack.
Laser eyes!
Come with me, Winston.
- Did I faint?
- You'll be safe here.
Safe? Safe from what?
Where are the diplomats? The supers?
Still hypnotized.
What have you done?
Evelyn, she's escaping.
Well, go after her. Finish your mission.
I can't just go! What about the kids?
Jack-Jack, who's gonna...
Mom!
Go. We've got this.
Voyd, come with me.
I'll go shut down the engine.
I'll try to slow the ship from the bow.
Wait, someone's missing.
Where's the crusher guy?
Strap in now!
It's for your own good.
No!
This is.
- We're too late.
- Get me up to the jet.
Hey, you did this. Can you undo it?
You want me to un-crush?
What? No one's ever asked for that?
No. To un-crush is silly. Why un-crush?
To get into the engine room.
Forget it. We don't have enough time.
What if I said to un-punch someone?
What do you do?
Welcome aboard, Elastigirl.
Although we haven't yet reached
our cruising altitude...
feel free to roam about the cabin.
Or just relax...
and let the cabin roam about you.
I can't get to the engine room!
We gotta do something!
Because trying to slow it down ain't working.
Hey! What about turning the boat?
The steering's been destroyed!
Dash means from the outside!
Yeah!
If we break off one of the foils
and turn the rudder...
we can veer the ship away from the city!
That might work.
I'll turn the front, you turn the rear.
Using the rudder? That's underwater.
How am I supposed to get...
All right. Come on, kids.
Dad, I know this is going to work.
But if it doesn't, and we crash...
my shields are probably better protection
than the ship.
I should stay here. With Jack-Jack.
That's my girl.
Remember, Bob, we're both turning right!
You know what's sad?
If it weren't for your core beliefs...
I think we could have been good friends.
At least...
I have core beliefs.
We have breaking news...
While there is still no radio contact,
the ship has changed direction...
and is heading towards land
at a high rate of speed.
So, Dash...
I am going to the rudder.
Once I turn the ship,
you hit the pull up button.
- Okay, Dad.
- Now lower me down...
The reputations of superheroes are ruined.
You will never become legal. Ever.
Never?
No.
- Ever?
- No.
Not even a little smidgee-widgee?
Hypoxia.
When you don't have enough oxygen,
things seem really silly.
Things get sillier and sillier
and then you die.
I don't wanna die.
Nobody does.
Really.
Not such a bad way to go.
Everyone, we need to get to the back
of the ship.
All supers, protect your ambassadors!
Follow.
Dad's been underwater for too long.
We gotta pull him up.
Wait. It's too soon.
I'm gonna press the button!
Not yet!
It's turning. It's working.
- Now!
- Dash, now!
Save yourself. Make a chute.
Make a chute. Make a chute.
Make a chute!
Helen! Brace yourselves!
Crash positions!
I missed Jack-Jack's first power?
Actually, you missed the first 17.
The fact that you saved me
doesn't make you right.
But it does make you alive.
And I'm grateful for that.
I'm sorry, but she'll go to prison.
Well, I'm sorry she's rich and will probably
get no more than a slap on the wrist.
First of all, Violet, I like you.
And who knows what the future may bring...
but I have a good feeling about all of you.
Good feeling. Should we be worried?
You guys got the next shift. I'm beat.
I saw what you did back there.
That was incredible!
No pun intended.
Sorry I had to punch you.
Yeah, baby! My sweet ride!
And in recognition of the extraordinary
service they have demonstrated...
the legal status of superheroes
is hereby restored.
You don't know me, do you?
No, I don't...
Wait.
Are you the girl with the water?
I'm Violet Parr.
- I'm Tony.
- Okay.
You split up into separate groups
and stuff...
- Tony, this is my mom.
- Pleased to meet you.
- This is my dad.
- We've met.
And this is embarrassing.
Charmed, I'm sure.
My little brother, Dash.
And the baby is Jack-Jack.
I tried to limit it to one parent.
We're all going to a movie, too, Tony.
Don't mind us.
We'll be sitting
on the other side of the theater.
Not watching you.
He's kidding. They are only
dropping us off at the theater.
They have other things to do.
So, you guys are close, I guess.
Yeah, I guess.
We can get closer.
Bob.
Stop! Let us out!
Here, large popcorn, small soda.
Save me a seat, center,
about eight rows back.
I'll be back before the previews are over.