Hello, everybody! And Happy Disney+ Day.
My name is Pete Docter,
and I'm the chief creative officer
at Pixar Animation Studios.
I directed Monsters, Inc.,
Up, Inside Out and Soul.
We have a lot of things cookin'
and a few sneak peeks for y'all today.
So, in honor of Disney+ Day,
let's go meet a few people
and take a look, huh?
Okay, we're walking into
the Steve Jobs building,
and I'm here
with my friends Luigi and Guido.
There they are.
I'm gonna let someone else
do the honors of our first announcement.
Somebody that we know very well as Mater,
also known as Larry the Cable Guy.
Take it away, Larry.
Hey, Pete, hey, everybody,
and happy Disney+ Day.
And I am, whoo-hoo, happier
than a tornado in a trailer park
to confirm that I will be playing
the lovable little tow truck,
Mater, in the new series,
Cars On The Road.
It is just a cross-country road trip
between McQueen and Mater.
Or should I say, Mater and McQueen?
And it's full of all the fun and laughs
that you've come to expect
from the world of Cars.
So, check us out next year on Disney+.
Can't wait. Whoo-hoo! Dadgum!
All right, Pete, back to you, buddy.
DOCTER: Yes, folks.
You heard it here first.
Both Owen Wilson and Larry the Cable Guy
will be reprising their roles
as McQueen and Mater in Cars On The Road
which streams next year on Disney+.
Okay, pretty cool.
All right, so now we are leaving
the Steve Jobs building,
which is where we do most
of our production work, in there.
We're gonna walk over to Brooklyn.
Brooklyn is another building
where we do a lot of our development work
on upcoming projects...
And oh, my gosh. Look, it's Domee Shi,
-the director of Turning Red.
-Hello.
-And Angus MacLane, director of Lightyear.
-How's it going?
-How's it going, guys?
-Is this Disney+ Day?
-This is Happy Disney+ Day!
-Happy Disney+ Day!
-Hey!
-Yay!
Actually, we're gonna go
to the main theatre...
Yeah.
...where we're finalizing
a whole sequence.
Yeah. We're super busy.
Got movies to finish.
Always busy, the life of a director.
I don't know if you've ever wondered
what the life of a director is like.
If you have, you're in luck
because we have two separate documentaries
exploring the making
of Turning Red and Lightyear.
Isn't that right, guys?
Wait, where'd they go?
Oh, they already went inside.
Okay, movin' on!
Okay, we are here in Brooklyn.
Brooklyn is where most
of our films begin their lives.
And, oh, some of you might recognize
this Vespa
from our most recent film, Luca.
Luca, of course,
is about Luca and Alberto,
two sea monsters who have a fun
filled summer on the Italian coast.
You know what, to tell you
about this next announcement,
let's call on the voice of Alberto,
Jack Dylan Grazer.
-Jack?
-Hey, Pete!
And Happy Disney+ Day, everybody!
Oh, my gosh! This is big.
Playing Alberto in Pixar's Luca
was like a dream come true for me.
Uh, I'm seriously so grateful for that.
And I'm even more grateful
and excited for a little short film.
A big, huge, massive, awesome short film
coming out today called Ciao Alberto.
It stars Alberto
and Giulia's father Massimo.
And basically what it does
is it reveals the story
about what happens
after Luca leaves for school.
I hope you love it as much as I do.
So, with that being said,
it's back to you, Pete.
All right, thanks, Jack. That was cool.
Hey, since we're here,
uh, let's take a little look
around Brooklyn.
See what else we can find.
Ooh, hey, look, it's Michael Yates
and Carrie Hobson.
-Oh! Oh, hey, Pete.
-DOCTER: Hi, you guys.
-We're so busy working like usual.
-DOCTER: I see.
I see. Yes, you're working very hard.
What are you working on?
-Oh, our show.
-Oh, our show for Disney+.
-Win Or Lose.
-Oh, yeah.
I just happen to be here
with Disney+ viewers.
Why don't you tell us a little about it?
Yeah. Win Or Lose follows
a middle school co-ed softball team
throughout one week leading up
to the big championship game.
Each episode follows a different character
as we go through the same week.
And each episode puts you into the shoes
of that character using animation.
So, we really feel
what it's like to experience life.
YATES: Yeah, like,
what it's like when you're coach Dad.
It's just, like,
the biggest thing in your whole world.
HOBSON: Or when you're up to bat
and, you know,
you're melting with anxiety.
YATES: Or you're the little brother
at the game
and you're just bored out of your mind.
You have to create your own world.
HOBSON: Or when you're the star player
and you make that game-winning catch,
you feel like you're on top of the world.
-That's our show.
-YATES: Super excited.
-Can't wait to show you guys more.
-HOBSON: 2023.
That about wraps it up from here.
Happy Disney+ Day.
Hope you enjoy the sneak peeks.
And maybe I'll just
take one of these for the road.
-Uh, thanks.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
-All right.
Good to see everybody.