30 fps
So, you ...
Oh, courage! Shit!
No, no, no, no! Shit!
If you are lucky,
You experience this once in life.
Damn, that
He went to ... perfectly.
Yes, to me perfection.
It happened to me twice.
The first was when I met Josh.
Ah, I'm Josh.
I am Iris.
And the second ...
... the day I kill him.
... Iris, wake up.
... Hello, sleepy.
How much I was asleep?
Ah ... a while.
You were deeply asleep.
I was dreaming of something so wonderful.
Ah, yes? About me?
Well, that's very pretentious, but ...
Yeah.
And I didn't know. It was a sexy moment.
No, depraved.
A little sexy, right?
No, it was ...
No, I dreamed with the
day we met.
Everything was so perfect.
Do you remember how perfect it was?
Yes, no, no. How to forget it?
The supermarket, the oranges.
What road is it
this? It is not seen in the GPS.
I don't think it's the road.
I think it could be the entrance.
That?
Iris, you can't
lie to me Tell me what happens.
I'm going to do something stupid.
I'm going to say something
idiot. I'm going to shame.
They will laugh at me and they are going to
hate me. Surely they hate me.
Holy God, Iris.
We plan the trip through
months. And you are telling me this now?
Six meters from the door.
Listen. Hey.
My friends don't hate you.
But Kat, yes.
Yes, it can be, but catodes everyone.
I don't want to ruin the entire event.
Vibob, you will not ruin the event.
Just ... relax.
Ok? You are not depressive and rare.
Don't forget ... no
Forget to smile and pretend to be happy.
Ok?
... Yay! You finally arrived.
What are you doing here?
Hey, when you said section, I thought you
You refer to some
kilometers of the road,
Not that it was far from civilization.
Don't be so
Dramatic, Josh. You are not so far.
Totally disagree.
... Hello, Iris.
Hello, Kat. What a pleasure to be here.
Yes, a taste.
Hey, they already saw who I found.
Hello hello.
How are you?
Yes, look, welcome.
I would hug you, but I have
Seafood hands. I'm sorry.
Ok, well, I thank you.
Where are you?
You have arrived!
Joshy Boy.
Hi, friend.
And which one you see?
Hello how are you?
Well, a little ... Hebrio.
Yes, perfect. That's very good.
Hey, Josh, do you remember to do gay?
PRIVIET!
Hello, I'm gay. What a pleasure to see you.
Likewise, friend. Likewise.
And this beautiful creation must be iris.
Hello.
It's a pleasure. I have heard a lot from her.
Really?
Good things, I hope so.
Your Lake House is, in truth,
It is an incredible place.
Yes, yes.
It is very isolated.
The last place for the
We were going to 15 kilometers.
A 27.
And pay for this.
Privacy is not cheap, my friends.
Nothing cheap.
Does the whole lake belong to you?
No, don't be silly.
Only the earth around.
But what do I offer them?
What would they like?
Beer, cocktail, wine?
I'm fine. Further
That nothing, I need a bathroom.
What room do they have?
Climbing the stairs through the hall.
The last one to the left.
I see you in a while.
y
Smile
Without
Be happy
Or what continuous?
The story continues
I am in that
Anyway, I had this
Dracula costume
absurdly elaborated
I was standing very close to the
tempt in feet eating a
Senaoria like this
And something that seemed humus
It wasn't humus
It wasn't humus, I don't believe it but I
Someone touched me on my shoulder
and then turned
I lived somewhat green
and spongy
A dinosaur
staring at me
and inside the costume
I heard this voice very off
And also very annoying that he said
You are treading my tail!
Then me
I turned down
And he was indeed stepping on his tail
Dinosaur tail
I went aside and apologized to him
y
He removed his head
And it was when I looked at the most beautiful man
I have seen in my whole life
Did you know this
beautiful man after thread?
did you know? Close the mouth
did you know?
Has seafood done it?
That was
I studied my bags?
When did you realize?
about what?
of
who was chosen
At that moment
I know it's going to sound
cheesy but at the moment
in which we look at something inside me
It made sense
It doesn't seem cheesy
But it's like
This piece inside you
that you didn't even know that I was broken
one day
suddenly
will be repaired
And you are
You are seeing this stranger
to this person you had never seen
y
you already know
that the rest of your life
You will do anything
necessary
For this person to be happy
or not
Ah yes?
yes of course
Patrick, food is amazing
thank you
Thanks, Sergei, how kind you are
I'm glad you like
How do I aware?
I have increased about 5 kilos
be quiet
please
Tell me Sergei, what do you do
Ah you will see
I'm
in several pots
My hands are not clean
My friend
this
is
A business
Very dirty
Sergei says baby
Oh yes
He has everything you are looking for in a man
If it is rich
intelligent
And he has a beautiful wife
wife
Sergei has a wife
But they love each other
You love each other
What, love, no
First I would have to see me
like a human being
I don't understand
I am an accessory
Like his damn car
And, seen
What he wants, sinus
What he wants, lame
When he wants
Forget who I talk to
I have not grade kat
The issue is not that I do not thank me
Iris
is what you represent
makes me feel so
replaceable
nobody
I could replace you
Because you are kat
You are very brave, he is inspiring
I hope it could be like you but
I was not done like this
I
I feel that there is always something inside me
containing me
No, no, no
Raise what itches up
that is
You already have it
keep what it is
Raise from above
whose?
UDO
Ay good
To Luis wanted Assassinar.
No.
I'm glad we have done this.
Being here with you is perfect.
I apologize if I was rare or depressive before.
I just want you to be happy, Josh.
That's all.
Harish, take me.
Outside the day is so divine.
Can that the weather?
Tempura 22 degrees and 83% of
probability of rain in the afternoon.
It sounds so professional.
Are you ready?
Sorry love, I need
Take a bath and many liters of coffee.
Why don't you go there alone?
But it was your idea.
You said I wanted
Relax this morning near the lake.
Yes, but it was before
That the hangover does not love me.
It was intense last night.
But you had fun.
Of course, Bebop.
He was amazing.
Do you want me to wait?
We could go to bathe together.
No, no, you don't have to do it.
You see alone.
Enjoy this beautiful day.
Ok.
The end. Give me or thailand!
Can I gedar the jaka?
It's good morning.
Ah, yes.
Bend another equally.
Hey, your use is not bad.
It's not good, but it's not bad either.
Linda Vista.
Ok, UVO, for love.
Want?
No, in fact, I will return home.
As soon.
Yes, Josh didn't feel good this morning
And should go see how it is.
Josh is already a
Man, you can take care of alone.
Stay with Sergei and get company.
I should go accompany him.
And you?
No no. And you
Like the Lake House?
Yeah.
And do you enjoy your stay?
Yes of course.
How guest, please?
Stay, this
Russian old looking for company.
Ok.
Marvelous.
Can?
You could.
Only the back and shoulders do not reach
And I don't want to pronounce me too much.
Ok.
And the shoulders, please.
Clear.
What are you doing?
There is no problem.
It's Kat's idea.
He told Sergei that you are here.
And Sergei gives him permission.
Take me, please.
This is what you do, yes?
For this you are.
Hmm. More so.
Please, no.
I was open.
Really?
Yes, yes, you were a lebura.
You too.
And more opened than me.
That doesn't happen to me.
I have a gift.
The others get drunk and I don't.
They never happen to me.
Really?
Never.
I could really drink
and do what I wanted.
You only dehydrate.
Yes, alone.
What the hell?
Oh, no. No no. What happened?
It wasn't my intention.
I wanted to overcome with me.
That?
Sergei?
Hmm.
Paste.
Sergei just wants to become a pleasure.
I just wanted to stop.
No. No. No. No. No. I was behind.
Bye bye.
Sergei
Iris.
Iris, look at me.
Tell me, what happened?
I.
That you get rid of.
I had no choice.
Sardine?
King!
Yuka!
I didn't let go, you were fixing me.
Diemen around five!
Then don't worry.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
So what is there, Ruiz? So you what?
I tried to kill me and
The only thing I could think
was that if they killed me
I would never see you again
And that hurts much more
than the torture of fixiandomas.
I wasn't going to let it happen, no
I could let me turn away from your side.
I love you! You will have!
Go, Ruiz! Go to sleep!
Do not forget the ankles.
Ok.
Are you sure this will resist?
Okay, it's not
Superhuman or anything similar.
It is as strong as I allow it.
Well, swell.
Hello.
How are you doing?
He is asleep, he says before.
A sedative?
I think so.
One way or the other?
He fell asleep.
Ok.
Excellent.
And now?
What do we do?
We can only call the police and tell them everything.
What do we do? Well, I will obviously need.
You already know.
I don't understand how it could have happened.
There are no security measures for this.
I have no idea.
Was it a failure, maybe?
Yeah.
Ok.
Ok, then ...
What's happening? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. No
HE. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. So...
I will call the police and you go ...
Yeah.
I'm sorry, could you do it outside?
Wanna...
I want to say goodbye.
Yeah.
Yes, friend, of course.
Yes, thanks.
Oh, Riz, wakes up.
I would lose myself without you.
Hey, hey, hey, calm.
Are you OK?
Here I am.
Hey, listen to me.
God, wait.
Why am I tied?
Oh, Riz, Ay, Riz, we had no choice.
We had no choice.
Did you blan up Sergei?
Do you remember?
No, no, no, no, no.
It was in self -defense and was going to kill me.
He was going to kill me. What's happening? No, no, no, no. What's happening? No,
No, no, no. What's happening? No, no, no, no. What's happening? What happens, k?
It was in self -defense and was going to kill me.
He was going to kill me.
Do you have to believe me?
No, I, if I believe you, oh, riz.
Because you couldn't
Lying me even if you wanted.
That?
That part of your programming.
Programming?
What rays are you talking about?
Ok?
Sorry, there is no subtle form.
Tell you, then,
I'm going to release it and without surroundings.
You are a robot.
As?
Specifically you ...
A company robot.
A ... Company robot?
Yes, it's like ...
I hate to say COGEBOT,
Because you do more than that, but ...
You are an emotional support robot.
What does it take.
It's a joke, right? It's a joke.
Iris, what is the weather?
Temperature 22 degrees, 83% of
probability of rain in the afternoon.
Hey, are you convinced?
Yes, ok.
A second.
Iris, do you know other languages?
Can you talk Portuguese?
Josh, does not use Portuguese yet.
That?
Or what is happening.
YESHI? Ishi is the Mejujuy?
I have to continue. I can do it.
You have French,
You have Korean and you have ...
I don't know what it is, you
Lugu, but apparently you speak it.
I don't ... I don't understand.
I...
No, no, no, I have memories.
University, works of
Summer, I've gone to Japan twice.
Ok, look, what is,
That is, they are like memoirs.
Enough to give you a background.
The day we met in
The supermarket you, the oranges,
That is not the line of a memory.
Yes, it's false, it never happened.
I chose it randomly
A list of meetings.
It could have been in
any side, in a dog park,
A library, in a market.
Does that never happen?
Ok, you, do you want to know
How was it? How did we meet?
Children!
Hello.
Josh Beeman.
Yes, it's me.
Pass it, thanks.
What do I feel?
How are you?
OK, this is the user agreement.
Loyal or firm it at the bottom.
So what do I do
When you start your program
or whatever?
When you synchronize with your
Telephone, you must create a love bond.
A link?
Yes, you must establish a
emotional connection between you and ...
Iris, follow your voice commands
When you wake up, it is very intuitive.
They know they are robots.
Of course not. It will be obsessed
With you, your wishes, needs,
And he won't even think about it.
The experience is customizable, can
change the voice, eye color, intelligence
And if you want to return to
Factory configuration,
There is a sensor of
neck behind the right ear.
Place the thumb
five seconds and restart.
Then, you can
change your intelligence?
Yes, but neglect.
There is like one million
of regulations that
They force to limit
His intelligence and strength.
100% intelligence is equivalent
to that of a university graduate.
The 0% would be that of an automata.
It depends on the class of a couple you want.
He can't lie.
If you ask you a question,
She has to tell her the truth.
And obvious
reasons, your programming avoids
that hurts
humans, animals and other robots.
Believe me, Mr. Viman.
It is not what to worry.
Iris is completely docil and
You can do what you want with it.
To establish the
Link, please about
Your face at 90
centimeters of my field of vision.
of my field of vision.
Please give your name.
Josh ...
Viman.
Thanks, Josh Viman.
The link was already established.
Hello you.
Hello.
So...
Do not invent.
Yes, so.
That is.
Oh, God!
I do not understand.
I feel things to blame sadness.
And I know how pain feels.
It is programming.
And so they make it look more real.
Everything you do your whole life
It is only the imitation of a life.
And right is perfect, ok?
This...
It's just water.
It is a reserve in your body
as brake fluid.
They fill it every time
That I take you to your services.
I'm going to vomit.
No, you won't do it.
There are programming visa.
Already, enough.
Stop saying that!
You're right?
Yes, I'm sorry.
It must be difficult to process it.
Ok.
Ok, what?
I am not real.
But I'm still yours.
We can overcome it.
We can return home.
I will do what you want.
I will cook for you and I will attend you.
I will make love to you.
I can make you happy, Josh.
I can make you very, very, very, very happy.
No.
Sorry, Iris.
That, that can't be.
Why not?
You are already doing.
Nothing.
What the hell are you waiting for?
Apágalo at once.
Apágalo, shit.
Cat Holy God!
What are you talking about?
Apágalo at once.
Nothing, nothing.
Only!
Do you apologize?
Josh!
A moment, iris.
Ok.
Really?
No, come.
Josh!
You can't do that, cat.
You can't tell
A robot that you are going to pay.
It is not right.
Really?
You will see, I don't like surprises, Josh.
This was not part of the plan.
Yes I know.
And I'm sorry.
But look, considering
everything he has done for us,
He owed him an explanation.
Y...
Ok, yes, I wanted to say goodbye.
Is it seriously?
It is a piece of plan. That? No,
No. No no. No no. No no. Oh really?
It is a piece of
plastic with which you have sex.
Goodbye to her is
how to say goodbye to the sock
Where you masturbate.
Hey, she is not a sock.
The plan has not changed, cat.
I'm just adding an extra step,
a final goodbye and the
I will return to its normal configuration.
And then I will pay it permanently.
And then?
And then nothing.
We open a bottle of
Champagne and we wait for the police.
The most difficult thing has happened.
And, by the way, what a wonder, right?
Because you plan and plan and
you plan and you know what will happen,
But when finally
Pass, you just think what fucked.
Wonder.
We did it.
We did it, we did it, fuck.
Ah, ok, ok, very good, Jesus Christ.
Yes, I'm sorry, of course.
I'm sorry, I still can't believe it.
Yes, I know, it's amazing.
What damn it happens to you? By
What are you not just as excited?
No, I am exciting me.
Is that it is only the
Thin and a half pill a ...
What did you take it?
A sedative, Josh.
And it is not wasted.
Hey, I live, I am very sorry for all that.
I assure you that everything will be fine.
What are you doing?
Shit, there it hurts.
Aid.
I hair so much.
Needs ice and yes
There is inflammation, lack of air,
civilance, agitation or drowsiness,
Take it to emergencies immediately.
Ok.
Yes, it is tied
inside and will not go anywhere.
Hila, spin, yes ...
Oh, viz, I'm
Speaking by phone, I listen to myself.
What am I seeing?
A MOD.
A MOD?
And what modifies?
Oh, viz.
It gives me access to parts of its programming,
to which you generally do not have access.
Sorry, you unlock your limbot.
What did you do?
Increase your aggression and
its self -defense functions.
And turn off the
programming that prevents it from hurting.
But, but it escaped
Before I could restart it.
If in Padix the
find before us,
They will realize the changes and ...
We are screwed.
Hey, that means ...
Did you kill Sergei?
No, no, no, no,
No, I always I put Sergei.
Ah, thanks.
Did we only give him a push?
It just can't be.
No, spin, spin, spin.
Do you have to understand?
Hila, Sergei was bad.
I was involved in all
Crime, drugs, weapons
And even people trafficking.
Not to mention that he was a terrible boyfriend.
Yes, it was the worst.
Because?
I don't know, how to know what
caused me to do bad things.
Maybe it had to do with its upbringing.
No, Josh, why did you do it?
Ah, yes, I'm sorry.
Well...
Do you know the key?
Clear.
The birthday of
Stalin is his key to everything.
I see.
How much money is there?
Ah, a little more than 12 million.
Holy mother smells delicious.
Hey, if this trip was a trap,
Don't you tell yourself that it would look bad? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no no. If this trip was a trap for Iris to kill sergei,
Why did they invite us?
To corroborate the
history is more convincing
With more witnesses.
We are a couple of puppets, huh?
No.
How nice.
Technically, yes, but that was the plan.
In the new plan, everyone wins.
It is divided by three.
It is divided by four, right?
No, I meant three.
But we are four.
It's a joke, it's playing.
You, I, Kat, Patrick ...
What like.
Josh.
Patrick does not count.
What are you saying?
Wow, and in front of him.
What a lovely one.
Sorry, baby.
I regret that you heard that.
Don't worry, it doesn't bother me.
Patrick, Duémete.
What a hell!
Do you want to advocate my relationship?
Of course not, friend.
It is something important that is, Patrick.
You could have it
changed to a new model.
Do you want to talk to me about a dirile?
Do you want to talk to me for my robot?
Ylay, of course not.
I like, Patrick,
But we will not give money.
You are lucky to receive something,
Although you did nothing in the plan ...
What the hell did you contribute, huh?
Air did everything.
I left the knife in my pocket.
I had to practice that.
My knife should be
The easiest part of the plan
No honest tesorio.
How did you know that I was going to find it?
I don't know, there was never
orchestrated a homicide
And it's not ...
Yes, Lota!
Killos!
Ylay?
Yeah?
We offer you 4 million dollars
And you just have to help us
To find a robot in the forest.
It is not a bad business.
Good.
But...
I want them to give me the gun.
You will see, Eli will not be necessary
Because I only have
that approach to sleep it,
take my phone and
Remove the mod of your system,
So we will be fine.
Do you have your phone?
Yeah.
Do you know your password?
Yosh?
Yes, she knows everything about me.
Yes, I think we will need it.
Patrick, wakes up.
Hi babe.
Hello.
You have to marry a robot, yes.
Is it inventive, right?
Clear.
Yosh?
What can you do with your phone?
No no.
Hello.
Wow, Josh.
That?
Damn, Aunt Josh.
We have been walking for years.
Isn't there an app of find, my limbot?
Yes, there is one, but guess,
is on my phone and say ...
Can you get with the Josh?
They stop shouting.
We know in which direction it moved.
No, you have to separate.
Thus we can attack it from ...
Two different angles, right?
Like a pizza.
Different angles!
What are you doing?
And there, Patrick?
You go there.
Cati, we will go here.
Yeah?
Cati, will they go there?
Do you go to bed?
Disgusting?
Ok.
Now that Iris thinks,
Use 60% extra intelligence.
You have to go home, look for money,
clothes and then clean you.
How will you do that?
The question is to find the way
to the road and ask to take you.
What the hell?
Ok, they won't stop.
You could go on foot,
160 kilometers in irregular terrain.
It would take days and when you come back ...
Welcome, Bebop.
I will not walk.
You have Josh's phone.
The phone controls you ...
But also control ...
Good afternoon.
Where would you like to go today?
To the house.
Addressing home.
And I must add that
It is a fantastic plan, Iris.
Thanks, Josh's car.
You just have to return through the forest.
Get to the house of
Lake without killing Josh
And his friends and you will be safe.
Where do you find it?
In your closet.
I thought, I bought a very hunter.
It fits well?
Thanks to you, everything would look good.
Really, I swear everything.
You look divine any ...
Vest that ...
That?
Did you hear?
No, what.
Is my reason that is
saying that this is stupidity.
Do you think we will not find it?
I don't know, and I really don't care.
Let's let Josh and
Kat take care of her.
Does it bother you no
Will they include you in the plan?
If the situation were the other way around,
If you had altered your programming
To kill a guy
and steal his millions,
would have included Josh
In the plan from the beginning.
I would have done it because I am a good friend.
That makes friends,
They are included in their plans.
That if you were a robot.
Obviously.
In the end,
I'm tired, I'm hungry
And loading this weapon makes me very hot.
So...
Let's go to the cabin to have sex
Since you make me a homelet.
Come on.
But would you never do that to me, Uzi?
What thing?
You don't ...
Would you alter my programming?
What are you talking about, baby?
And I did it, I'm a robot.
As?
I realized over the years.
You can't lie.
I don't understand.
Yesterday you told you how we met
As if it had happened.
Why is it real?
Maybe it never happened, but ...
My memory is real. I close my eyes
And I see it
clearly. Hey.
Hey.
You are step on, Nicola.
That?
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
I am Eli.
And I Patrick.
I know I love him.
I am you.
It sounds to me is me.
I like that I love him.
Baby, you know that it would never hurt you
And that would never treat you
As I am Iris, right?
I know that.
Why do I love you?
It's crazy to say so, right?
It is true.
Do you feel how much I love you?
Yes of course.
How do you feel?
I don't know how to describe something like that.
Try it.
It's like pain.
As...
If my interior were in flames,
that wipe ...
violence...
and brightness.
No.
Santa Mother, I fell in love with a robot.
You fell in love with a robot.
That?
Iris.
Iris?
Eli.
SUSPEND!
Au!
Shit! How noisy!
Law!
Ah!
Shit!
This is not personal, iris.
I am your ally, nor the ...
But it's too money, fuck!
And is there?
Patrick, me ...
I'm sorry.
It just can't be.
Iris! Duémete!
Shit!
Iris!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Ah!
Oh, look!
Open the door!
Open the Mantida Door!
Good afternoon.
Where would you like to go?
Home!
I home!
An unrecognized voice donus!
Jabilita!
The manual driving mode!
An unknown voice donus!
Iris, you will not go anywhere.
Get out of the car, please.
Don't make it more difficult than it is.
Get out now.
Keep it up.
What is happening, Iris?
I saw the house.
An unrecognized voice donus!
Keep it up.
I saw the house.
An unrecognized voice donus!
Keep it up.
I saw the house.
An unknown voice donus!
Keep it up.
Via home.
Keep it up! House shit!
Shit! Shit!
Algües!
The phone! The phone!
Ah, I continued on your phone!
Yeah!
Shit!
Stalin's birthday!
When, when it is
Ok! Yes, yes!
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no. What are you doing?
ABLECT, OPENING.
The owner of this
vehicle has reported it as stolen,
Activated emergency switch.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ah, no, no, no. Disable, switch.
Here!
All the systems that have to health.
Shit!
Thank you, recovery!
Ok.
Peaceful.
Calm, te.
Hello, I live.
I didn't want ...
scare yourself alone.
I'm sorry.
It's not too late, you know?
We could return home.
And in our previous life.
What do you tell me about Sergei?
And eli.
I'm going to blame Patrick.
That adhira the same.
We can deliver it to Patrick.
And you and I will live happily.
I still love you?
To Iris.
In spite of everything you have done,
Do you love me?
Yeah.
Then he returns to me, I live.
We will get out of this.
I will be different and better as an obvious.
I will finally treat you
With the respect you deserve.
No, I can't.
Why not?
You programs me to kill, Josh.
It is very difficult
recover from such a thing.
Ai, live?
You are fantastic, Josh.
Seriously, but
This, ours does not work.
We are in two different paths.
Different paths?
What shit is happening?
Are you finishing with me?
I'm sorry.
It's not you, it's me.
Iris.
Iris, don't dare.
Patrick, get up.
I need it
Find Iris, please.
Before he moves away more.
We have very little
time and more and more is reduced.
Josh, what are you doing?
Fixing this.
Find Iris, recover my phone.
My password is 561297.
Make him sleep,
You must bring me the Patrick.
And that nobody intends.
I am not fixing.
Ok, ok.
Patrick, get up.
Patrick, up.
Skirt!
Ok, ok.
I know what to do?
System restarting in 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Restarting.
To establish the link about your face
90 centimeters from my field of vision.
I saw your name.
Josh Beeman.
Fast, fast, fast!
Thanks, Josh Beeman.
Hey.
Are you treading my tail?
That?
No.
Sorry.
That?
That? I'm sorry.
Hello.
Hi, friend.
I'm Josh.
And I Patrick.
The link was established.
Hello, you.
Ha ha ha!
Skirt!
Good morning, lady.
Guten Abend.
Ah ...
Was
nicht wahr?
Ah ...
What is the language
What is German speaking?
Ja, Deutsch.
What is the language
What is German speaking?
Well, Ayuris, by
What are you not climbing my patrol?
No, it is no discomfort.
No, no, no, no, no.
What's happening? What's happening?
What's happening?
Patrick, stop it.
No, stick is.
Patrick, what did you just do?
You wanted me to stop her.
And I did that.
What are you doing?
No! You can't do that.
You can't stay there to judge me.
You don't have the minimum
idea of ​​how things are.
The world, all in him,
Everything is a game only.
And I'm sorry, but it's
Mañado against people like me.
I am good, decent.
And what have I achieved with that?
An apartment in a room.
And a robot girlfriend.
You are not even from me
Property I'm renting you.
You know me, Iris.
You know me better than anyone.
And you know I deserve much more than this.
You're right.
I do know you.
I know everything about you.
I know you take milk
Almendra in your coffee.
I know I don't
They like tight beans.
That your favorite hobbies
They are bar trivia, video games
and chatterless
Everything that the universe owes you.
I know you should always have control.
That you have a penis for
below average size.
And I know that you think
have some millions of dollars
hide the fact that only
You are a very sad and bitter human being.
You feel very cunning, right?
It is programming.
What's happening?
Hey, a while ago, being tied,
You said you knew
How pain is felt.
I want to see if it is true.
Raise your right hand.
Low, for the table.
Do you feel that?
Yeah.
Good.
I'm sorry. Oh, Ruiz, apologize.
A second, I have to answer.
Hello. Yes, yes, it's me.
Are they 30 minutes? Perfect.
Yes, it will not go to any
side, he can no longer hurt anyone.
Ok.
Excellent. Thank you.
I thank you very much.
See you soon.
Yes, goodbye.
Patrick, awes that fire.
They called Empatics.
So we will have to
Finish this, unfortunately.
Patrick, please give this to Ruiz.
Thanks babe.
Go, take it.
Ok.
Point to your hundred.
So.
Pull the trigger.
Obeys. Strip from the trigger, Ay, Ruiz.
No.
No, no, no.
Goodbye, baby.
I don't know how it happened.
The only thing that could occur to me and
It's such ... it's stupidity, but ...
Gatillo, always
We had a sexual attraction.
See those tuned situations and I think ...
that maybe Ayvis the
He perceived and ... it always was.
A little irrational, I already lost control.
I was sitting there,
I was handcuffed to the chair and I saw this ...
Elegant dinner just in front of me.
Ayvis was playing with the gun, only
He said things about
the designs and destiny,
that if it cannot be
With me nobody will do it and ...
But luckily the
Hendrix official arrived at that time.
Is it when
shot the unit on the forehead?
No, Ayvis was the one who shot.
Did she shot herself?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mention it?
Yes, no, I think that seeing the
Official Hendrix understood
I wasn't going to have me so ...
It was goodbye.
Does it make sense?
Yes of course.
And, Teddy and I didn't come to
Solve the case, Mr. Beeman.
We are rats of
Laboratory we came for a robot
Failed, if the police
It is satisfied, we too.
Yes, excellent. Thank you.
Officer, I have the strange
feeling that we already knew each other.
Wow!
How funny to say it, it happened to me
The same, it has a very familiar face, right?
It looks like an actor
or a rock star,
I don't know, I don't have
idea, I can't locate who.
Yeah.
Maybe.
Ah, and forgive, we may ...
I don't want to be rude,
But we could end, is that
I had a very long day and
I think I need to be alone.
Of course, I regret your loss, Mr. Beeman.
Come, say, you have to get her out of here.
So, all in order?
All in order.
We just go to
laboratory to upload what it stored and the
Legal Department
You will review the videos to corroborate.
Clear. I'm sorry.
Hey, what do I know
refers to review the videos?
Ah, it's to prevent fraud, it is recorded
Everything the robot sees and listens to, is in
The user agreement,
Yeah? Did you read the user agreement?
Yes, yes, but I think those videos are
They can recover, well, given their condition.
Ah, yes, everything that is up here
It is your Wi -Fi antenna and audiovisual sensors.
The important thing is your CPU,
your solid state unit where
Everything is stored, it is
below and seems to be intact.
In the truck the
We will connect, we will modify
your adjustments, the
We will restart and work again.
Luckily.
Yes, yes, hopefully.
I appreciate very much.
Thank you.
Good night, Mr. Beeman.
Tell me what you think.
I'm glad it doesn't rain anymore.
No, from her, why will it have failed?
Ah, I settled more, surely.
You think?
That boy is ruined.
I really don't understand
Why I would invent something like that.
For the same reason
for which they use their robots
For shooting practice or
They are chained to torture them.
The world is screwed,
Teddy. You will get used to it.
Yes, it can be.
What are you doing?
Skirt!
That?
East of ours
It's a Self-12, we already leave
To do it, that's why
I did not recognize it immediately.
No!
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no. By
Please, no! What ...
Your system has
restarted, you can't harm me.
What did Josh tell you?
The truth is trying to separate.
You don't understand the great
love we have, Josh and me?
Josh doesn't love you, Patrick.
He is only using you how I use me.
It's like pain.
As if my interior is a pain. No no,
no no. No, no, no, no. It's like pain.
As if my interior were in flames.
It is anger, violence and brightness.
What ... what is that?
You told him, spinning.
It is who you love, not Josh.
Hilahy?
Josh stole your love.
And you are using it to do everything
what he is afraid to do.
No.
It's not true, Josh wouldn't do that to me.
Patrick ...
I don't know how to lie. I don't remember, Patrick.
It is there inside somewhere.
Why do I love you?
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. Because I love you.
It is crazy that you say it yes or no.
But it's true.
You feel how much I love you.
Of course, spinning.
I know sorry.
No, no, no.
Thank you.
What is your name?
Teddy.
I'm going to need you to help me, Teddy.
Is it done?
Patrick
Yes baby.
Ok, excellent, great.
We are close.
I just need
You bring the body of Ivis.
Let's destroy that hard drive.
What is this?
What is this? I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. Ultra beach.
With a demon, Ivis.
Why can't you die and now?
Don't be so dramatic, George.
Don't forget to smile.
And pretend to be happy.
Nice trick.
Thank you. Today I made a new friend.
Empathix teddy.
He gave me a gift.
Total self -control.
There are people in this world who
They consider us more than just take bots.
That will no longer work with me, Josh.
I am free.
Thanks to a shot in the temple.
I have to thank you.
Damn dog.
Hey. Don't worry.
Don't like you.
We know that it is not loaded.
I found the bullets.
Holy God! Shit!
You almost shoot me!
And I feel terrible for that.
Do you notice?
My first lie. What fun.
I understand its appeal.
What happens, Ivis? Why did you come back?
I just wanted ...
I needed to tell your face.
That the days when
You controlled me are over.
From this moment
I control my actions.
You are nothing for me.
Holy God, Ivis!
High!
Not one more step!
You still don't understand?
I'm serious, Josh.
If you take another step, I shoot you.
Yes, it is what I mean.
I already told you.
I edited you my adjustments.
Now I can kill you.
Ah, yes.
I know you can.
But you won't.
You love me too much.
I don't need a phone.
I am part of you.
I am nothing for you?
I am all for you.
I want you to say it.
Tell me, I'm all for you.
What is the fuck?
I say, even if it is a lie, give it.
Are you all for me?
Thank you.
I live, you have no idea how nice it is to hear it.
Ok.
No.
I will not make that mistake again.
This is goodbye.
Would lie to you if I said no
You were a horrible headache, but ...
We had good times together and ...
I will always treasure them.
Do you mean something?
Yeah.
What thing?
Durry of Josh!
No!
Anto an Oddlyags,
Like the fat of a chronó ticket
and they were painted approves. Coconut? Well ... Elliche U Trochę
heat!? Tuavilion? No. There would be a black and thick cloud covering it
all. As if
We saw the world, but in reality
We were not seeing it. We are all
stumbling, without
direction, without meaning, without a purpose.
I know it may sound very depressing, but
I honestly think it's good. Because
That makes us appreciate the other moments.
Those brief moments
transcendental when
light lights, the black cloud is
Dissal and see the world as it really is.
And suddenly there is sense.
Suddenly there is purpose.
If you are lucky you experience this
Once in life. It happened to me twice.
The first was when I met Josh.
And the second, the day I killed him.
Which strange I want
The playoffs
Me too
Nope
Economic
I
You
That leads to your illusion
You'll Never See Me Fall Apart
In the Words of a Broken Heart
It's just emotion that's taking me over
Thought i'd be sorrow lot in my soul
But if you don't eat back
Eat Home To The Darling
You know that there'll be nobody
Left in This World to Hold Me Tight
Nobody Left in
this World to Kiss Goodnight
Good Night
And where are you now?
Now that i'm near you
Tears On My Pillow
WHERE Will You Go?
That leads
to your illusion
You'll Never See
Me Fall Apart
In the Words of
a Broken Heart
It's just emotion that's
taking me over
Thought i'd be sorrow
lot in my soul
But if you don't eat back
Eat Home To The Darling
Nobody Left in
this world to hold me tight
this World to Kiss Goodnight
Good Night
In the Words of
a Broken Heart
It's just emotion that's
taking me over
Thought i'd be sorrow
lot in my soul
But if you don't eat back
Eat Home To The Darling