Miss, we'll be landing soon.
Would you like a glass
of the same wine?
No, that's okay.
By the way,
I'm Korean.
Is that so? My apologies.
Have a comfortable flight.
The chairman's main
business is real estate.
He owns a ton of land in Korea
and has investments here too.
You know, he's one of those
people born into money.
The filthy rich ones.
How am I supposed to trust them?
You should have
considered my opinion too.
These are totally
different circumstances.
I don't get it.
Just do whatever you want.
We've calmed him
down with sedatives,
but he hasn't stopped
crying since birth.
All top doctors here
have examined him,
but he's medically sound.
So we've heard.
My apologies, but could we
have the room to ourselves?
Pardon?
There must be others with the
same condition in your family.
His father...
and his grandfather.
Is she talking about
Ji-yong and his father?
Those expressions...
Yes.
Changing from suspicion
to shock.
They live in the light and
look towards bright spaces.
Bright lights are needed
in the world for us to see.
And people only believe in
things they can see and touch.
A world with bright lights.
And the back side of it.
People have known of the beings
living in the darkness for a long time
and have called
them by many names.
Ghosts, devils,
goblins, ghouls...
These beings constantly
envy and long for the light,
and just occasionally
would cross the line.
That's when people ask for me.
Yin and Yang.
Science and superstition.
I exist between them.
I am Shaman Lee Hwa-rim.
My wife told me you'd be coming.
I'm Park Ji-yong.
My brother committed
suicide in the mental ward.
Then it began with me,
and now...
my newborn son.
When I close my eyes,
I hear screaming.
And a sensation of being choked.
Firstborns and tainted blood...
Normally, genetics
are initially blamed,
then the land their house is built on,
and finally, they move to a new place.
Shadow...
I saw a shadow here
as soon as I arrived.
It's pressing down
on its descendants.
It's likely the shadow
of your grandfather.
My grandfather?
We refer to it as
the Grave's Calling.
Simply put, it's one of your ancestors
throwing a tantrum in their grave.
Are you certain?
Yes, 100%.
Then what do I have to do?
You've got to spend
money and hire people.
I can't do this on my own.
We'll have to work with experts.
Damn it.
Why are they the only
ones I can think of?
- Exhumation!
How dare you stare at
your ancestor's awakening!
I'm sorry.
Come on, let's go.
- One, two, three!
- Three!
No sign of water.
I'm sorry for waking you up.
It's very clean.
Nice and fragrant.
This coffin is stuffed.
Man, oh man.
I told them not to put any
metals inside for her sake.
Chairman Kim.
I've settled on the plots for your
mother and ancestors, haven't I?
Yes, that's correct.
And you're all healthy
and business is good, yes?
Yes, thanks to you.
No matter how I look at it,
this is one of the finest plots
I've seen in my 40-year career.
It's got all the five
elements right here, see?
It really does, all right?
I really gave you a good deal.
Right, I'm sure.
So set aside your worry.
Do the right thing
and re-bury her.
It must be the right
call if you say so.
But why does she keep showing
up in my kids' dreams?
Even my wife said
she's been seeing her.
Mr. Ko!
What's taking so long?
I'm starving.
I'm hungry too, and so is she.
Look, someone shrouded
her without checking.
- Does the count look good?
- Yes.
Good.
Someone has the
old lady's teeth.
Who took the old
lady's dentures?
Did you take Grandma's teeth?
Sang-hyun.
The thing in your closet,
was that her teeth?
Why would you...
All her stuff was burned,
and now she's gone.
Dad.
I just wanted something
that was hers...
Kid, your grandma
says she's hungry.
Let's return it to her.
What about me then?
What do I remember her by?
There's nothing left of her.
Sang-hyun, right?
Sang-hyun, your grandma
will always be by your side.
Bloodline.
People that remain
tied even in death.
A group that shares the same genes
and physical and mental attributes.
When a person's body finishes its
cycle, it turns into dirt and earth.
As we drink from that dirt
and walk on that earth,
we live, die, and are
reborn in a cyclical nature.
In other words, the dirt and earth
connect and cycle everything.
All the skeptics can fuck off.
To the top 1%, feng shui
is a religion and science.
And I'm a feng shui expert.
I find and plot the land
for the dead and the living.
I am Geomancer Kim Sang-duk.
NOBLE FUNERAL HOME
Many domestic companies see
the current economic situation
as a prolonged downturn.
According to the findings...
Let it cook, will you?
I can't wait that long.
One grill is plenty.
Be honest, Mr. Kim.
Was that really a
pristine plot today?
Hey, watch what you say.
They're my regulars.
It looked like it was facing
the North quite awkwardly,
and the aura of the site
felt really quite off.
Why don't you become a
geomancer yourself, now?
If you think you know so well,
you should go on your own.
So I've been doing
some thinking.
An average of 250,000 people
die every year in our country,
and 30% of them get buried.
Imagine how many people have
been buried in good plots
since the Joseon era
in this tiny country.
So how can there still be so
many pristine plots around?
- It just doesn't make sense...
- That plot...
was a 65 out of 100.
Right, it wasn't a 100.
They're drying up.
There aren't any more.
Funeral directors like you
are hired by corporations,
and men like me who sell plots just
poke around construction sites.
It's all over. We're
the last ones standing.
Have a drink.
Hold on, they're here already.
You came so early.
It's been a while.
- Good evening.
- Hey, there.
Goodness, I could smell the pine
mushrooms all the way in Seoul.
- I just had to bring myself.
- He ate all of them.
What are you talking about?
- Have you been well?
- Come on in.
Sorry for not calling often.
It can't be helped
if you're busy.
By the way, Bong-gil. Your
looks have gotten better.
You really think so?
Don't even mention it.
The ladies all want him
around. It's inflating his ego.
How long has it
been? Three years?
Yes, time really flies.
How's business lately?
So-so, you know.
It's off-season.
Which is why I brought...
Wait a minute, I...
Mr. Ko, do you smell that?
What smell? Perhaps this?
That's right, I smell dough.
Jeez.
I tried my best to hide it.
You got me.
- Spill it already. What is it?
- We got you just right.
You gentlemen clue
in so quickly.
We visited a strange family in the US
upon a request from a doctor friend.
The family of Mr. Park Ji-yong.
The patriarch is
a Korean national,
but everyone else including
Mr. Park are American citizens.
- They're apparently...
- Filthy rich.
That's a good start.
All the firstborns are
haunted, including a newborn.
They held out long enough.
It isn't possession?
It's not at that stage yet,
but it's obviously
the Grave's Calling.
Are you really going to dig
up your grandfather's grave?
It's been almost 100 years.
I don't need your approval.
I've made up my mind.
You really believe
in such things?
And you think your aunt in
Korea will agree on this?
I'm the head of the family,
so I make the decisions.
I don't trust those people.
This could get out of hand.
The baby will get
better in time.
Let's pray together
and seek treatments.
We just have to live quietly
away from everything.
Who cares if her belly's
full during the wedding?
It's the best gift
you could ask for.
But even so, a grandchild? And
one with blonde hair, no less.
The baby will have blue eyes!
What an old fart.
Will she be staying in
Germany after the wedding?
Of course not. She has
to come back to Korea.
Anyway, I was worried about
the cost of her wedding.
We caught a big
game just in time.
Indeed.
Our Lord sends us pension
just when the time is right.
Amen.
How rich do you think this man is to
pay us 500 million won to relocate?
He probably paid more.
What? More?
You know how Hwa-rim can be.
You think she didn't take a cut?
Right, she wouldn't
hesitate to exploit us.
May I get your grandfather's
name and hometown first?
I normally check the family's reputation
and occupations before the job,
but since you're in a rush...
Shouldn't you earn the
trust of the employer first?
Trust?
Very well.
We can call this off if
you're not up for it.
Can you promise me two things?
From here on, keep
everything confidential.
And cremate him right away.
With the coffin.
With the coffin?
Don't bother opening it?
Does it matter?
I was told that it'd be either
relocation or cremation anyway.
Under normal circumstances,
we would first notify
the town office,
open the coffin, and have the mortician
check the status of the bones.
And then it would be
relocated or cremated.
Okay?
Let's go and check
out the plot first.
My parents and relatives
are against this adamantly.
- I would like it to be done as swiftly...
- So let's check the plot first.
Northern Gangwon...
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
I find it weird that he
doesn't want the coffin opened.
Shouldn't the bones
be checked regardless?
He'll skip the shrouding then?
Could there be something
inside the coffin?
BOGUK TEMPLE
NO ENTRY THIS IS
A PRIVATE PROPERTY
Ever seen a grave
at a mountain peak?
It's rare.
Do you know this mountain?
No, never heard of it.
You claim to know every
inch of this land.
How could you not?
I only seek pristine plots.
What an incredible view.
Very nice.
You can even see North Korea
from here. You see that?
The grave itself is quite
plain for such a grand plot.
Do you see something there?
There's no name.
Can you tell me who suggested this
plot for your grandfather's grave?
A famous monk at the time
found the most auspicious plot
because my grandfather made
a significant contribution
- to the country.
- A monk?
Yes, I heard they went by
the Buddhist name "Gisune."
"Gisune"?
That's a unique name.
The grave feels quite plain
despite what you've said.
I was told they decided
on a nondescript one
because of rampant grave
robberies at the time.
What do you think?
I'll settle on a date then.
What is it? Is something off?
Mr. Park.
I don't think I
can take this job.
He's screwing us again.
Mr. Kim!
- What is up with him?
- What is it?
Is it that bad?
Is there no way?
Why won't you tell us?
It's got a great view and
everything. What's the matter?
You know how much this job pays.
Come on, what's going on?
I'm sure you all understand
what happens if we mess
with the wrong grave.
I've been selling
plots for 40 years now,
but this one is a plot
I've never heard of.
It's vile.
No human should ever be
buried in a place like this.
Dealing with something like that
could get everyone involved killed.
Do you understand?
Hwa-rim, you saw the foxes, no?
Foxes at a gravesite
is an ominous sign.
It's the vilest plot.
That's the last time
I saw my son smile.
We conceived twice before him,
but they were miscarried
for unknown reasons.
We managed to give
birth to him at our age.
Do you have any
children, Mr. Kim?
Yes, I do.
I have a daughter who's
getting married soon.
Congratulations.
Don't even mention it.
Is your daughter in
the same line of work?
She majored in Aerospace Engineering
and works for an airline in Germany.
She's in a frenzy
preparing for her wedding.
Very interesting.
A geomancer father and an
aerospace engineer daughter.
The thing is, if you look
at both fields side-by-side,
they have quite a
lot of similarities.
Yin-yang and the five
elements are about studying
water, fire, metal, and wood
with earth as the basis.
It's about analyzing nature
under these conditions,
- and aerospace is about...
- Then...
can't you save my child?
You're hiding something
from us, Mr. Park.
What do you...
38.3417, 128.3189.
A longitude and a latitude.
They were engraved
behind the gravestone.
I don't know who
this Gisune was,
but it's absolutely clear that
they had some kind of intention.
I'm not sure what
you're talking about.
And I'm not hiding
anything from you two.
Let me make it clear.
Relocating a grave from
an unknown plot like that
is extremely dangerous.
It's like digging for
a mine with bare hands.
We could try a
withdrawal ritual.
I knew you'd say that.
We can do it while relocating.
You already know the solution.
I don't trust anything
that I haven't done before.
The combination will be a first, but
it's not theoretically impossible.
Wait.
Why are we waiting
for your permission?
You're not the only
geomancer in the country.
This is why it's tough
working with old geezers.
- Watch it.
- The child is in pain.
This hotel is on a good plot.
The Passing of Misfortune is
a type of deception ritual.
We'll get five diggers
with the pig zodiac sign
and five sacrificial
pigs tied together,
and we'll have the
men dig the grave.
The vile energy from the ground will
then be transferred to the pigs,
which I'll whisk away.
Your aunt is here.
Seems like your mother
shared what's happening.
Let's go!
Here we go!
All right!
Go for it!
- Appease the guardian!
Exhumation!
Appease the guardian!
Mountain guardian!
There it is.
Reveal!
- Reveal!
The chill is immense.
It's too old to
make anything out.
What's this?
It's a coffin made
of juniper tree.
Only the royal
families used this.
I can't believe I'm
seeing this here.
- Coffin removal!
Good, now let's move slowly.
- Lower the head!
- Take it easy.
Careful now.
Load the coffin straight
into the hearse.
We're heading to
the crematorium,
so bury the tombstone and make
sure to tidy up afterward.
Let's swap ropes.
- And remember not to eat meat today.
- Okay.
Thank you for everything.
Yes?
A soul that hasn't even been
shrouded is riding with you.
Let's be respectful, all right?
Come on.
I'm Ko Young-geun, the man who
shrouded the late president.
The job is done, so loosen up.
Let's see.
There's nothing there.
Let's go.
What is that?
Damn it.
What in the world?
Mr. Park.
We'll have to
delay the cremation
because of the
unexpected rainfall.
Why is that?
It's not like it's
done outdoors.
When cremation takes
place on a rainy day,
the soul cannot reach
a good afterlife.
It may sound
superstitious to you,
but I'm letting you know for
professional and ethical reasons.
This happens from time to time.
We can hold the body in
a nearby hospital morgue
and reschedule the cremation
when the weather improves.
Wouldn't we have to submit a funeral
report if we go to a hospital?
Mr. Kim!
I got confirmation!
We're good to go!
Don't worry about that.
We know these people.
Why the entire coffin
even after relocation?
The head mourner
won't let us open it.
Here.
Come on, there's no need.
Don't be that way, take it.
Jeez.
Well, the last group of the day did
just leave, so it's quiet inside.
That's good.
But having it pour
on cremation day,
he's got a long trip
to the afterlife.
They're rescheduling
the cremation?
Yes.
Are you sure you can
trust those people?
I paid them enough and spoke to
them on a need-to-know basis.
You don't need to worry.
Since we've gained some time,
let's consider moving him
to our family gravesite.
I'm still against the cremation.
He was my father, so
I get the say in this.
Go and get some rest.
Let's just leave it here
since we can't open it.
I'll take care of
the humidity level.
Thanks again.
Just look at that coffin.
He must've earned
some royal favors.
Good to see you.
The head mourner and his family
all headed back to Seoul.
But Hwa-rim told me that
she'll join us here.
It's a chilly day.
Go and have some hot soup.
I need to step out for a bit.
All right.
BOGUK TEMPLE
I don't think I've
seen you before.
Can I help you?
Pardon me for intruding.
I saw a sign on the
road while driving by.
Is that so?
It's just that I noticed
the geomancy symbol on it.
I wanted to ask about it.
Are you a geomancer?
Yes, I was a protégé
of Master Choi,
and I'm barely making ends meet
by selling plots on my own.
This place may look shabby now, but
it has existed for over 100 years.
The head monk who
established this temple
was renowned for his
geomancy expertise.
I see.
I can tell just by looking
at the site it's on.
Speaking of which,
was the head monk's name
Gisune by any chance?
Gisune?
No, he was called Wonbong.
May I ask why you're inquiring?
Oh, well...
There's a nameless grave at
the peak of that mountain.
Do you happen to know
anything about it?
Of course.
I'm not sure if
it's still there,
but I heard a lot of rumors
about it back in the day.
What kind of rumors?
Don't stay alone in
this eerie place,
and go have some hot
soup across the street.
Sure, don't worry.
- I'm off.
- Take care.
Why does everyone care
so much about my dinner?
There were rumors of
treasures buried in the grave.
Treasures?
People would say it was the grave
of the richest man in Joseon
or that of an unknown king.
So there were quite a lot of grave
robbers flocking to this area.
Grave robbers?
Some of them were arrested,
while others crossed the
border to North Korea.
So they never got
to rob the grave?
Probably never got a chance to.
I heard it belonged to
a high-ranking official,
so it was hard to
even approach it.
These were the tools
they left behind.
Can I ask why you're
asking about the grave?
Because I...
dug it up today.
So? Were there treasures inside?
Excuse me? What are you doing?
Hey!
Hwa-rim.
Hey, you!
Hwa-rim, are you okay?
What?
What do you mean, the
coffin's been opened?
Damn those sticky
fingers of his.
I paid him enough
to leave it alone.
I knew he felt off.
Hey, what happened?
Something flew past her.
What did?
Something came out of it.
Something very vicious.
Father...
My father.
Jong-soon.
My son.
Open the window.
Father...
Come inside.
Father?
My loyal little boy...
This is a land flowing
with milk and honey.
Your father is cold and hungry.
I'm sorry.
The spirit has got to be
flying wild everywhere.
The head mourner is in danger.
You leave for Seoul
immediately, Mr. Kim.
Meanwhile, we'll try to
summon the spirit back here.
You'll summon it from here?
It screamed to be let out for a century,
only to have nobody free itself.
Only resentment
remains in the spirit.
He'll pay a visit to every
one of his descendants.
What a mess we're in.
It's pouring out, the coffin's
open, and a ghost's on the loose...
I really didn't want to do this.
Tell me about it.
Will you two be okay doing
two rituals in a day?
We'll be fine.
Mr. Ko, make sure to
get the timing right.
- Hold the rope tight when it enters.
- Right.
Come forth.
Here he comes.
He's here.
Bong-gil!
Hold tight!
Hey, old man.
Who are you?
Huh?
Bong-gil, hang onto him!
What got you so riled up?
Talk to me.
Let it all out tonight.
Don't go off elsewhere.
I'm taking...
my children with me.
I can't allow that.
We lost him.
What do we do?
Hello?
Mr. Park, this is Kim
Sang-duk. Is everything okay?
Yes, what's going on?
Thank goodness.
It's just that
there's been a mishap,
so I'm on my way
to you right now.
I know it's late, but could
we talk when I arrive?
What?
What's going on?
You're still at the
same hotel, right?
I'm almost there.
I'll be right up.
One moment.
Who is it?
It's me, Kim Sang-duk.
Hello? What's going on?
Mr. Kim, are you
outside my room?
Excuse me, Mr. Park?
No, no!
That's not me.
Your grandfather's
coffin has been opened.
- What?
- Please open the door!
My grandfather's coffin?
My apologies, but
it was unsealed.
Is something going on inside?
Don't ever open the
door, and just stay put.
- I'm heading your way.
- Mr. Park!
Only listen to me
and act calmly.
Listen carefully, Mr. Park.
Walk away from the door
and get to the window.
Please open the door!
It's an urgent matter I
have to explain to you!
Don't answer, and don't listen.
Go to the window and open it.
Your grandfather will protect
you, so you must let him in.
Mr. Park!
Just listen to me and hurry!
I said, open the window!
Mr. Park!
Mr. Park?
Are you okay?
Proud young men
of the peninsula.
Do you hear the sound of hundreds
of airplanes and artillery?
Push forward, sons
of the Empire!
Raise your bayonets under
the Rising Sun flag!
Serve your devotion
to the Japanese Empire
for the unification
of Greater East Asia!
Ambulance...
Call an ambulance.
Please call an ambulance.
Call a damn ambulance!
I'm telling you, I saw
it with my own two eyes.
This could lead to a
series of funerals!
- We're going to the crematorium.
- All right, get going.
You get their permission to cremate,
and we'll stand by from there.
Your grandfather's coffin is...
The fox severed
the tiger's waist.
Pardon me?
The fox severed
the tiger's waist.
I said the fox severed
Mother, is everything okay?
She must be tired from the trip.
I need to get some rest.
Joseph's condition seems
to be better today.
Doesn't it?
Anyways, I cannot
reach anyone at home.
So I'll go back home and check.
Sure. I'll be here.
It's because this
is an urgent matter!
Have I ever asked for
a favor like this?
It's too late in the night.
We'll be there
soon. Please hurry!
Cremating in this
weather is nonsense.
What did the mourner say?
I told you, something
came out of the coffin!
You must know what that means.
The body needs to be
cremated immediately.
Please call his
family in the US.
Pardon? What do you mean?
You saw what happened.
The baby is next.
No one in the US is answering.
Then...
What's this?
You exhumed the coffin but
didn't shroud the body?
You'll cremate
the entire coffin?
Things will get messy if
the town office finds out.
My father's coffin?
I don't quite
understand it myself.
But he said it has to
be cremated immediately.
What do you mean?
Ma'am, we must hurry.
Your father's spirit is
headed to the baby in the US.
- I'll fire it up.
- One second.
The mourner hasn't
given us the go yet.
We're unable to reach
your family in the US.
Only you can give us the
permission to cremate the coffin.
Is this really the only way?
Very well.
Please proceed.
Yes, ma'am.
Burn it.
What a terrible fate.
Too bad he won't reach
a good afterlife.
Off on a journey
Beach rose of Myeongsasimni
Flowers bloom, leaves
fall Do not be saddened
Which saint led your bier?
- Why has the grim reaper appeared?
Re-routing to your destination.
Remember Chang-min, Mr. Kim?
He said he's fallen sick
after the exhumation.
Would you mind giving him a
visit when things cool down?
Make a left turn.
The hospital is clueless.
I just wasted money
on a bunch of tests.
I have nightmares
and hallucinations.
Mr. Kim...
I think I'm getting
punished by the gods.
I saw something while cleaning
up after the exhumation that day.
It looked so strange.
It was a snake...
What? A snake?
Damn it, I should've
just let it be.
Please do me a favor, Mr. Kim.
Find the snake I cut in half and
say a prayer to it, will you?
I really didn't want
to go there that day.
I really didn't want to.
That place felt weird to
begin with, didn't it?
Why was a grave there
in the first place?
Double interment.
Yes, I'm busy.
I'm doing a Bible study
with church friends.
Here's 50,000 won for you.
Go.
What?
A double interment?
Yes, just under the coffin.
By the way, Mr. Ko,
have you ever seen a
coffin buried vertically?
Yes?
Hwa-rim?
Here we go.
In two beats.
Coffins could go vertical
when the ground shifts...
but still, this is too big.
What the hell is this?
What's that about?
I think this chain...
is to prevent someone
from opening it.
- Or...
- Or what?
Or the opposite.
Let's pull it out
and examine it.
For what?
We should contact
the mourners first.
We've got the payment
left to discuss too.
Let's not mess with this.
Let's pull it out first.
I'm sure it belongs
to the family.
We can't just
leave it like this.
But how do we...
Let's pull it out.
Go get a rope.
Hurry, the sun's setting.
Pull hard on the count of three.
One, two, three!
How is that for a human?
Where is he going?
BOGUK TEMPLE
What's going on?
As I told you on the phone, we
had an emergency exhumation.
Please allow us
to stay overnight.
The mourner is on her way.
Is there space to store
the coffin in the meantime?
What...
exactly is that?
Could I trouble you for
some glutinous rice?
Bong-gil.
Get the horse
blood from the car.
You know this
isn't a good thing.
Double interment?
What does that mean?
Please tell us
everything you know.
I don't know.
I really don't know...
why that thing was buried there.
Nor do I know why my father
was buried in such a bad plot.
It was written on the tombstone.
"Vice Chairman of the
Central Advisory Committee."
Your father was quite a figure who
acted as a quisling for the country.
So I'm assuming the monk
intended to punish him...
Yes, I know.
That's why I don't understand.
That monk named Gisune...
he wasn't Korean,
but Japanese.
- Pardon?
- A Japanese?
His real name was
Murayama Junji.
I heard he knew every
inch of this country.
My father pledged
allegiance to them,
so why bury him in the
worst plot in the country?
I've received a call from
the US that the baby is fine.
I'll honor the payment
Ji-yong promised you all,
so please...
get rid of that
coffin as you see fit.
Let's burn it right away.
All right.
Let's burn it first
thing in the morning.
I agree. I'll feel
so much better.
Excuse me.
I made some noodles, so
come warm up for a bit.
Thank you.
- Shall we?
- This way.
I knew that grave was off. It
had a good view for nothing.
We haven't eaten
anything all day.
Please have a drink of this.
Thank you so much.
Thank you for the food.
- Cheers to our health.
- Cheers.
The flavor is...
This is really precious stuff.
Have a drink.
It's warming me up.
Is there any more of the...
Yes, Murayama Junji.
You don't remember? Master
mentioned him a few times.
He was a Fox Diviner in Japan.
That's right, Diviner Murayama.
Master met him once
a long time ago.
I remember hearing that his energy
was too intense to be a human.
That he was most
certainly a fox.
Why do you ask?
Where are you?
It's nothing. I remember now.
Thank you, Gwang-sim.
I'll call back soon.
Grandma.
Grandma...
I have a bad feeling.
My liver was taken, my liver.
My liver.
My liver was taken.
Someone took my liver.
Someone took it.
My liver was taken.
Where are my clothes?
My clothes.
Fuck.
Someone took my
liver and my clothes.
My liver.
Hwa-rim.
Damn it.
Fuck, what a stench.
It went through the roof
because of the seal.
This thing...
What the hell is it?
Say it.
I think this thing is
at the pigpen right now.
Go and wake everyone up.
The gate has been opened.
Is there a human?
I came for my helmet.
No, my lord, I am not a human.
I am your servant.
Very well.
Then have you brought me
the sweetfish and melons?
Do you not hear your lord?
I have brought the head
of the enemy general.
I'm sorry, my lord.
I will prepare the
sweetfish for you.
A human.
Run.
Bong-gil.
A pagoda.
Bong-gil!
Bong-gil, stay with me.
350,000 won and 750,000
for Kim Young-ja...
- Bong-gil, wake up!
- They owe me 200,000 won...
Mr. Kim, please help!
He needs help!
Please help!
He needs help.
Bong-gil, stay with us.
A wild bear attack
terrorizing the villagers...
Your temperatures aren't dropping,
so I'll give you something for that.
The local police found pigs
that were shredded to pieces,
as well as two human bodies in
the same condition near the scene.
The victims were found to be a local monk
and a migrant laborer who worked on-site.
Town officials are working in hand with
the military to track down the bear...
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have asked
to pull out the coffin.
I'm sorry about Bong-gil...
and the monk too.
When Bong-gil had to quit baseball
after being chosen by the spirits...
and when he came to us after
being abandoned by his family,
we all told him not
to become a shaman.
But he said he'd be okay
and that he had nothing to
fear as long as he was with me.
I panicked, and I froze.
It left footprints.
And casted shadows too.
There is an established
theory in shamanism.
Souls are only fragmentary, and
ghosts lack physical bodies,
meaning they can never
conquer us humans
with complete minds
and intact bodies.
But that thing we saw is
something completely different.
It's not a vengeful spirit
but rather an anima.
An anima?
It comes to be
when a human or animal soul
evolves with an object.
It's something that shouldn't
ever exist on this land.
I couldn't sense
anything from it.
What its identity is,
where it came from,
or why it was in the
Park family's grave...
He suffered damage to
his abdominal organs.
And he lost a lot of blood.
But the real problem is
the damage to the spine.
He needs to be sent
to a general hospital.
Since it was a wild
animal attack...
THE BACKBONE OF THE PENINSULA
THE BACKBONE
The fox severed
the tiger's waist.
I was told they decided
on a nondescript one
because of rampant grave
robberies at the time.
The grave robbers' tools are
still stored in the shed.
"Our land, my comrades."
"Iron Blood Alliance"?
We've prevented further
organ damage for now
and we'll need to
conduct more tests,
but he'll need to regain
consciousness for that.
I must say, his case
is quite unusual.
What in the world
is with all this?
Thankfully, he's out of the
woods but he injured his spine.
Will he be able to walk?
He'll have to work through
it, which I'm sure he will.
What have you been up to?
Spill it.
- Gwang-sim.
- Yes?
I smell a stench from him.
I know. That's why
I called you two.
It's been a while since we
played goblins, hasn't it?
Why are you standing
around, Ja-hye?
Go lock the door.
Bae Ji-dang, Lee Chung-gu,
Park Gil-ho, Shin Pal-gyun,
Kim Jung-bok, Song Jong-ik,
Min Geun-ho,
Jeon Tae-hwan, and Im Chung-sin.
I knew it.
They look too resolute
to be grave robbers.
Ladies, it's been so long.
Is everyone here?
I just got here.
The harvest is over, and
it's getting cold now.
Is everyone well?
With you all here, I
should've cooked something.
Don't you worry.
I brought rice cakes and
plenty of boiled pork.
I knew I smelled
something tasty.
Did you bring enough?
Of course, I brought plenty.
There's more than enough
for all three of us.
Should I get Mr. Jang over yonder
and the miss over at Jecheon too?
Why fetch those busy bees?
Let's just eat quietly
by ourselves...
Yes, let's not bring others.
Did you bring some sweetfish?
Who's that?
- I think Mr. Yoon is here.
- No way.
Didn't you hear what
happened to him?
Yes, there's no way he came.
What are you talking about?
Fill me in, will you?
Don't even mention it.
I heard he met something
really vicious.
How vicious was it for
him to be bedridden?
Haven't you heard?
He met someone in the
middle of the night.
What a load of shit.
Hey, Mr. Yoon.
What did you see
that scared you much?
He looks just fine.
Who was it?
The one you met.
Can you tell us?
The lord.
The lord?
Which one?
Spit it out, asshole.
My lord, the one who
cut down 10,000 foes.
Where...
is your lord now?
38.3417, 128.3189.
It's a Japanese ghost.
He's the general
who guards the site.
What the hell is that?
My lord, please look at me!
I'm right here.
I wish to be your vessel!
I'll offer him that meat.
Ja-hye.
Come closer.
Please help me, Ja-hye.
All of you bitches
are going to die.
Don't do this, Hwa-rim.
It's a Japanese ghost.
I know.
They kill anything and
everything just for being nearby.
You saw what happened in Japan.
Don't you dare even go near it.
Even with your grandma
protecting you, this isn't right.
Let's go, Ja-hye.
What about Bong-gil then?
I'll call you. Let's go.
So that thing was really
buried down there?
That means it's returned
to where it was.
But why did you go back
there in the first place?
Before Mr. Park died, he said,
"The fox severed
the tiger's waist."
What does it mean?
In geomancy, our peninsula is
metaphorically compared to a tiger,
one that is grasping
the continent.
So?
Remember the coordinates
written on the gravestone?
Where could it be?
That's right, that's the spot.
That's exactly where
the tiger's waist is.
That Fox Diviner
Hwa-rim mentioned,
that fox bastard...
put it there just like that!
He drove a stake
right on the spot.
What about Park's
coffin on top of it?
Since these resolute-looking men
were roaming about pulling them out,
they intentionally buried a
high-ranking official on top of it.
So that they couldn't
even go near it.
Then why is the ghost there?
He's the general
who guards the site.
38.3417, 128.3189.
I think...
that's what's guarding
the iron stake.
Hwa-rim.
I know we're based on a
business relationship,
but let me ask you a
favor aside from business.
Don't say anything
you'll regret later.
Do you still believe
in national spirit, or how Korea was
divided in half with iron stakes?
You know those stakes at the
temples are for land surveying.
You know they say
99% of them are fake.
What about the 1% then?
- Mr. Ko.
- What is it?
You know this isn't
just an ordinary grave.
This was planned meticulously.
You saw people die
because of that grave.
Do you really want to be next?
Mr. Kim.
Stake or not, we lived our lives
just fine without big trouble.
So why the change of heart?
You're right.
You and I lived prosperously,
selling land to rich pricks.
That's what bothers me.
This is about that same land!
The land that my unborn grandchild
will step on and live on.
The same land for all of us
and our future generations.
Hwa-rim, you said it's an anima.
If it really is an anima
attached to the iron,
we just have to pull
out that iron stake.
With that done, Bong-gil
will recover, no?
But that general or
whatever is guarding it.
How the hell are we
supposed to pull it out?
You saw the size of that thing.
Summon like a beast,
speak like an anima.
You really think it's doable?
There are things we can pull
off and things we can't.
I'm sorry to say that ghost
isn't something that
can be cast away.
Japanese ghosts don't need a reason
to kill anything in their path.
We may not be able
to get rid of it,
but I can distract it for a bit.
I can buy us time.
Bong-gil.
Pass me some more
antiseptic, please.
I'll wipe it with saline
and apply gauze over it.
Yes, ma'am.
Wait.
That bastard avoided the tattoo.
What kind of tattoo is that?
It's a Buddhist scripture.
My apologies,
but we had some reports of wild
animal activities in the area.
Where...
Where might you...
be headed?
We're here to weed out
graves in that mountain.
I see.
The soldiers are conducting a
search starting with that mountain.
We'll finish quickly
and come back down soon.
Very well.
Let them through.
Pull out and return to base.
We gave it what it wanted, so I
suppose it'll wake up at midnight.
If you can lure it to the yew tree,
I'll buy us as much time as I can.
It won't take us
long to pull it out.
Just get us 30 minutes.
When you pull out
the iron stake...
make sure to cleanse it
immediately with this horse blood.
Mr. Kim.
You're sure that iron stake
is really there, right?
I'm absolutely certain.
Gwang-sim, please look
after Bong-gil tonight.
If things go wrong,
he'll be in danger.
Stop staring.
She said it'll show
up at midnight.
Mr. Ko.
Thanks for coming with me.
"A person alone can be
attacked and defeated,
but two can stand
back-to-back and conquer."
"Three are even better,
for a triple-braided cord
is not easily broken."
Ecclesiastes 4:12.
Amen.
Gwang-sim.
I hope we won't have to kill it.
It would be dying in his place.
Plus, you like fried chicken,
so what's the matter?
Have you filled your stomach?
It has to be here.
Is someone there?
My mountain is being disturbed.
Does this mountain
belong to you?
Indeed, this is my mountain.
Goddamn old tree god.
How is it that I do not
hear any guns or bayonets?
You are mistaken.
The war ended a long time ago...
No!
Our war has not ended yet!
Why have you come here?
That fox brought me
here on the battlefield
instead of the Namsan shrine
when I was kept in Daitoku-ji.
I assume it was under
Katahito's order.
Or that of Makoto's.
This is a quaint land now.
You do not belong here anymore.
No, no.
We must continue heading North.
- Raise your bayonets and head North!
- And head North!
- Head North!
- A brave warrior never retreats.
I don't understand.
There's nothing here.
As the ruler of this
place, I will ask again.
Since when have you been here?
Retain your respect for me!
I am the embodiment of fear.
This is my land!
I will ask again.
What are you?
It's not here.
It's not here!
There's nothing here.
You said you were certain!
It has to be here.
Remember.
They took my head at Sekigahara,
but I transcended the mortal form.
I am the god of the battlefield.
My undecaying lord, you
are a burning sword!
38.3417, 128.3189.
The fox has put a curse on me.
I must protect this site.
Do you have someone captive?
Please free the human
you hold captive.
Now!
I beg of you!
A human.
Forward.
Cursed old hag.
Did you find it?
- There's nothing there.
- What do you mean?
We couldn't find anything.
We have to pull out...
Mr. Kim.
This can't be.
It has to be here somewhere.
38.3417, 128.3189.
My lord, please return.
38.3417, 128.3189!
Kim Sang-duk!
Mr. Kim! Get out of there!
Then why is the ghost there?
He said he's the general
guarding the site.
That means it's returned
to where it was.
Have you ever seen a
coffin buried vertically?
Fire.
The fire digs into the ground.
Get out!
Will you become my servant?
If not,
will you offer your liver to me?
It has been over 500
years since I memorized...
the scripture written on you.
The metal driven
into the ground,
and the fire that guards it.
Devour...
the liver, my lord.
A fresh liver.
The horse blood!
The blood of the white horse.
It's hot.
Please retreat.
You cannot have
them find you again.
It's an anima.
It comes to be
when a human or animal soul
evolves with an object.
Yes, it's the iron.
You are the burning metal.
Mr. Kim.
Pull yourself together!
Hurry, we have to carry him out.
Earth...
and wood.
Based on the energy of the earth,
fire, water, wood, and metal
form the four
cardinal directions.
Fire and water are
opposite poles,
and so are metal and wood.
That's it.
Burning metal.
The opposite of that...
is wet wood.
Water conquers fire...
and wet wood...
is tougher than metal.
Gwang-sim, wait.
His blood is dark.
One last blow.
Are you okay, Bong-gil?
Mr. Kim.
What do we do?
- Mr. Kim.
- What do we do?
What do we...
I'm dying.
Thankfully, it's
not that painful.
Hey, Kim Sang-duk!
Don't die on me!
I've always lived
so close to death.
I guess it's just my turn now.
Dying is about
returning to earth.
I'll leave in comfort...
Wait, my daughter's wedding...
Grant him the courage
to overcome the surgery.
Lord, please envelope him
with your precious blood.
Several people died, and a few
others were injured over a few days.
Upon inspection of
security cameras...
After several days of searching,
the soldiers captured a wild bear,
and the media is on an ongoing debate
on whether to kill this innocent bear.
For the safety of
the villagers...
He's awake.
Mr. Kim.
Are you awake?
Thankfully, Mr. Kim's recovery
was rapid despite his age.
As for Bong-gil,
well...
Speak of the devil.
Seriously?
This is our meal.
How could you eat without me?
- Here, eat.
- Give me a slice.
Is this a diner?
Why are you all
always eating here?
You think I'm eating
because I want to?
I'm stuffing myself
because it's so good.
It's good.
You have to fast, so
someone's got to eat these.
Think of it as a diet.
Winter passed and we all
went back to our lives...
as if nothing had happened.
- While I live briefly in this world,
- Always singing praises
- When the day fades away,
- I shall proceed in glory
- Through the gate of heaven...
I told you it has to
face the West, did I not?
Facing the South isn't
always a good thing.
What should we do then?
The bride and groom will
now bow to each other.
Bride and groom, please bow.
Family members, please step
forward for a group picture.
Hey, Mr. Ko.
Get over here.
It's a family photo. Why
would we be included?
Let's just join for one photo.
Let's just take one.
- We're practically family.
- Let's go.
But it's a family photo.
The tall gentleman in the
middle, please take a step up.
The gentleman in glasses,
please come closer.
Make sure you don't...
How do we have bellies
of the same size?
Goodness.
Here we go.
Father of the bride,
please look forward.
Looking great, everyone.
Let's all smile, all right?
One, two, three.