Do you think
I look like I'm from Sacramento?
You are from Sacramento.
You don't have to do that.
Well, it's nice to make things
neat and clean.
- You ready to go home?
- Ready.
Her hand moved
behind his head and supported it.
Her fingers moved
gently in his hair.
She looked up
and across the barn,
and her lips came together
and smiled mysteriously.
You've been listening to...
...The Grapes of Wrath,
by John Steinbeck. If you...
Our college trip
took 21 hours and five minutes.
Hey, wait. Let's just sit
with what we heard.
- Are you serious?
- Well, we don't have to constantly
be entertaining ourselves, do we?
I wish I could
live through something.
- Aren't you?
- Nope.
The only exciting thing about
2002 is that it's a palindrome.
Okay, fine. Well, yours is the
worst life of all, so you win.
- Oh, so now you're mad...
- No, it's just...
- because I wanted to listen to music?
- You're being ridiculous,
- because you have a great life.
- I'm sorry I'm not perfect.
No one's asking you to be perfect.
Just considerate would do.
I don't even want to go to
school in this state anyway.
I hate California.
I want to go to the East Coast.
Your dad and I will barely be
able to afford in-state tuition.
- There are loans, scholarships.
- Your very smart brother...
- he can't even find a job.
- He and Shelly work. They have jobs.
They bag at the grocery store.
That is not a career.
And they went to Berkeley.
Your father's company is laying
off people right and left.
Did you even know that?
No, of course you don't,
because you don't think
about anybody but yourself.
And Immaculate Heart
is already a luxury.
Immaculate Fart.
You wanted that, not me.
Miguel saw someone knifed
in front of him at Sac High.
Is that what you want?
So, you're telling me
that you want to see somebody
knifed right in front of you?
He barely saw that.
I wanna go where culture is,
- like New York, or at least Connecticut...
- How in the world
did I raise such a snob?
...or New Hampshire,
where writers live in the woods.
You couldn't get
into those schools, anyway.
- Mom!
- You can't even pass your driver's test.
Because you wouldn't
let me practice enough!
The way that you work...
or the way that you don't work...
you're not even worth
state tuition, Christine.
- My name is Lady Bird.
- Well, actually, it's not,
- and it's ridiculous...
- Call me Lady Bird,
- because your name is Christine.
- Like you said you would.
You should just go to city college.
You know, with your work ethic,
just go to city college, and then to
jail, and then back to city college,
and then maybe you'd learn to pull
yourself up and not expect everybody to...
In the name of the Father,
and the Son,
and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
- Let the Lord be with you.
- And also with you.
I want to welcome all of you back to
the start of the new school year,
all the Xavier boys
and Immaculate Heart girls.
TEACHER, STUDENTS:
Hail Mary, full of grace.
The Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou
amongst women...
Glory to you, O Lord.
TEACHER, STUDENTS:
I pledge allegiance to the Flag
of the United States of America,
and to the Republic
for which it stands,
one Nation under God, indivisible,
with liberty and justice for all.
A vote for Amanda is a vote for boys,
boys and healthy vending machines,
because no one wants a muffin
with that many calories.
Whoo!
Do not ask me, "Mr. Bruno,
is this gonna be on the finals,"
or, "Mr. Bruno, is this
gonna be on the midterm?"
Because I'm not gonna tell you.
That is none of your business.
Those aren't the rules. This is my house.
"A reading from
a letter of St. John."
We're afraid that we
will never escape our past,
and we're afraid
of what the future will bring.
We're afraid that we will not get
into the college of our choice.
We're afraid we won't be loved,
we won't be liked,
we won't succeed.
Here are the classics...
St. Augustine, of course,
Aquinas, my favorite,
Kierkegaard...
Oh, wait until
you hear his love story.
It will make you swoon.
And the coming
of our Savior, Jesus Christ.
For the kingdom, the power, and
the glory are yours, now and forever.
Amen.
Some of the students
were disturbed by your posters.
It's just a bird head
on a lady body, or vice versa.
I think it's a little upsetting.
It's my tradition
to run for office.
Don't worry. I won't win.
That's not what
I'm worried about.
This won't mess
with my scholarship, will it?
No. You're okay there.
You have a performative streak,
I think.
Yeah, I think that too.
Maybe you would enjoy
theater arts.
They're having auditions
for the fall musical.
Do we have that here?
It's a collaborative effort
with the men at Xavier.
How am I a senior
and not know we have that?
Perhaps you haven't always been
an active part of this community.
They do a fall musical and a spring play,
and from what I hear, it's a real blast.
What I'd really like
is to be on Math Olympiad.
But math isn't something
you're terribly strong in.
That we know of yet.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
"Julie" doesn't
need to be in quotes.
- But it's not my real name.
- It's not the same thing.
I'm not sure you're right.
I love this neighborhood.
Yeah, it's so beautiful.
If I lived here, I would
definitely have my wedding
in the backyard.
I'd have friends over all the
time to study and eat snacks.
I'd be like, "Mom, we're taking the
snacks upstairs to the TV room."
I'd have my own bathroom.
I can't stop you dicks
from hanging out here,
but quit wrinkling
all the magazines!
When I'm in this
store, I'm not your sister.
I'm a customer, Miguel.
I'm always right.
Ever since she moved in, your brother and
Shelly are becoming the same person.
No way.
Yeah, okay. Maybe.
See, why don't I look like that?
Yeah. Just once, I'd like to have
the song "New York Groove" playing
and feel like it
really applies to my life.
You've never even
been to New York.
That's why I'm applying
to New York colleges.
Do you know if Sarah Lawrence
is actually in the city?
- Your parents would pay for that?
- Scholarships, financial aid...
I'll figure it out. My mom thinks I can't
get in, but she is sorely mistaken.
- What about terrorism?
- Don't be a Republican.
Probably just gonna go to city college.
Put the magazine back!
Shit!
- You doing okay, mama?
- Oh, yeah, that was terrifying, wasn't it?
Thank God you were there. So I guess
we can't have pencils anymore.
Yeah, just gotta go back to
quill tipped markers. Crayola.
Right. Thank you. It's for you.
I got it for the baby.
- I couldn't resist it.
- She loves pink.
It's more for you and Andrea
than it is for the baby.
I'm sorry
I didn't have time to wrap it.
- No, it's perfect.
- Okay. Good.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Or, I mean, later.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
♪ It's hard to think ♪
♪ This eve of parting ♪
♪ Turns to sand of summer gone ♪
♪ When both our minds
are warped with parting ♪
♪ Break the thought of
nights alone ♪
♪ Maybe I should... ♪
Did you know toothpaste
is basically ineffective.
- It's like sucking on a mint.
- Mike Kelly died.
I didn't even know he was sick again.
How old was he?
Only 56.
- Can Shelly and I get in there?
- In a minute, honey.
- Dad and I are still in here.
- That's too young.
- Lady Bird, you better be dressed.
- I am dressed.
Yeah.
I'm gonna send them a note.
Do you think that Shelly and Miguel
have sex on the pullout couch?
Oh, yeah.
- Why can't I just make the eggs?
- Because you take too long,
you make a big mess, and I have
to clean the whole thing up.
Eggs aren't good
for the environment anyways.
- What?
- You heard her.
Eat quickly, please.
Look at all these pictures. Every
newspaper looks like USA Today.
Shelly and I are trying to be
vegan, hence the soy milk.
You wear leather jackets.
But they're vintage, so they
don't support the industry.
They aren't done.
There's white stuff.
You know how much
you love Brambles?
Pigs are smarter than him even.
I never thought Brambles
was a genius, okay?
- Mom, the eggs are not done.
- Fine. Make your own fucking eggs.
I wanted to.
You won't let me.
- Your sister doesn't like me.
- I'm hungry!
- She does.
- You had your chance. Going to bed.
Did you know
that Alanis Morissette
wrote this song
in only ten minutes?
I believe it.
So, I'm applying
to a couple East Coast schools.
I need you to help me with the financial
aid applications, but Mom can't know.
We...
Aren't they quite expensive?
First, yes.
That's why financial aid.
Second, I have to get in first.
Mom won't be happy about it.
Which is why I don't want to
fight about it before I have to.
- Just pull over here.
- Are you sure?
- I can drive you to the front.
- No. This is fine. I like to walk.
Well, I love you.
So,
what do you think about college?
- See what I can do.
- Thanks, Dad.
I love you too.
Have a good day at work.
Hey, I'm like Keith Richards.
I'm just happy to be anywhere.
♪ And what it all
comes down to ♪
♪ Is that I haven't got it all
Figured out just yet ♪
Hey, bitch.
- Hey.
- All right, girls.
- Hope you like pickles.
- Thanks, Uncle Matt.
- Sweet.
- He's not your uncle.
Just something I'm trying out.
Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
- Love you.
Bye. I love you.
- Your mom really likes you.
- Yeah.
- I just keep getting fatter.
- Me too.
- Matt's awesome.
- Yeah.
I hope he marries my mom.
That would be so nice.
He promised me his old car
when I turn 18.
Ugh! That car should be illegal.
Jenna Walton's not doing
any off-roading.
She just goes to Pavilions.
I heard Jenna Walton
has a tanning bed in her house.
She is so pretty.
Her skin is luminous.
Maybe we should try tanning.
Yeah.
...in the tub...
I scoot myself under,
just like now, like this,
and then the water just... whoop.
Schwoop.
Ooh, you're so gross!
I think I figured it out when I
was, like, three or something.
I take the showerhead...
Oh, my God...
Embarrassing, I use that.
I don't know if mine
is the right kind though.
Maybe it's different when you
actually have a penis in there.
Like, it's more intense.
Mine was pretty intense, I think.
You're not supposed to
eat the wafers.
They're not consecrated.
Being alive
Okay. Christine.
- Lady Bird.
- Is that your given name?
- Yeah.
- Why is it in quotes?
Well, I gave it to myself.
It's given to me, by me.
Okay. Take it away, Lady Bird.
Everybody says don't,
everybody says don't
it isn't right
Don't, it isn't nice
Everybody says don't,
everybody says don't
Everybody says
don't walk on the grass
Rolling along
Make me a channel of your peace
Where there is despair in life
Let me bring hope
Where there is darkness,
only light
And where there's sadness,
ever joy
There are giants in the sky
There are big, tall,
terrible giants in the sky
When you're way up high
And you look below
At the world you left
And the things you know
Little more than a glance
Is enough to show you
Just how small you are
I see light on in your
room. Go to bed.
- Congratulations.
- You too. We both got in.
Everyone who auditioned got in.
The part I got was basically
not getting in.
I don't even know
how I got cast in my part.
Me neither. I was the one who
had a dress and prepared a song.
- I know.
- Now you're gonna be all romantic
with Danny on stage.
It's probably my only shot at
that, you know?
- Do you have a pen?
- Yeah.
- Mom.
- We don't need to buy that.
It's only three dollars.
I'm having a hard week.
Well, if you wanna read it, we can
go down to the public library.
- I wanna read it in bed.
- That's something that rich people do.
We're not rich people.
Stop.
Stop it. Stop it.
Listen, stop.
Hey.
Hi.
Come here often?
Excuse me?
I'm Lady Bird. We're gonna be in
the musical together.
Oh, yeah. I remember you.
You were wearing that dress.
Well, I just wanted to say, "What's
up," and I'll see you in rehearsal.
Thanks. I'm super excited. You...
You live in the neighborhood?
No. I'm from the wrong side of
the tracks.
- Wh-What?
- Is that your family?
Yeah.
Wow. There's so many of you.
Irish Catholic. It's hard to find a
girl to date that's not my cousin.
Well, okay. You're gonna make
a great Franklin.
Oh, thanks. I want my hair... or
his hair... to be curly, though.
- Yeah.
- Like, um...
Like Jim Morrison. Very '70s.
- Like Jim Morrison. Exactly.
- Yeah.
- Danny!
- Oh, I gotta go.
Bye.
Who is Jim Morrison again?
He was in a rock band, moron.
The Doors.
- I knew that.
- This is with your employee discount?
Yeah. It's already included.
Oh, my... Okay.
- Ma.
- Mana.
- Manala.
Because it's not important to be right.
It's only important to be...
- True.
- Exactly!
Purple.
Two.
Yesterday is done
See the pretty countryside
To get our emotions going,
we're going to play
first one to cry wins
Starting... now.
I'm playing too.
So is Miss Patty.
Oh...
I'm sorry.
I heard that before he
became a priest, he was married,
and had a son named Etienne, who
died at 17 of a drug overdose,
which maybe was a suicide.
But my mom says same difference, if
you're that careless with your life.
Oh, that's her. Gotta go.
- Bye, guys.
- Bye.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I brought you these hot rollers...
for your Jim Morrison hair.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- You'll have to show me how to use them.
- It would be my pleasure.
They look like sperms.
I ju... I just remembered,
I had a dream about you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- What... What happened?
- Um, we were...
we were flying to Disneyland
on a giant carrot.
That's awesome.
- I love Disneyland.
- Yeah. Me too.
- I think it's kind of scary, but...
- Mm.
...I also love it.
So, everybody clear
on applying rules of exponents?
You guys with me?
Don't leave me hanging.
Give me a nod. That's good. Maybe
even a verbal confirmation.
Yes.
Aha! Thank you.
That's what I like to hear.
All right. So I'm gonna be passing
back your graded quizzes.
I urge you to find the problems where
you went wrong and work them out.
Good job, Jules.
I can tell from your work you even
understood the ones you missed.
Suck a dick.
I like "Jules."
I just don't get why I'm not good at math.
My dad is really good in math.
Even Miguel has a math degree.
Maybe it's your mom's fault.
- You lose! Point Julie!
- No. Look.
- Wish me luck.
- Luck.
Hey, wanna dance?
Hell, yeah.
Six inches for the Holy Spirit.
That's us.
- Oh, uh, no. My mom's coming.
- No, she's not.
- Yeah, she is.
- The plan was to sleep over at my house.
No. It's fine.
Okay. Bye.
Bye.
Hey, Matt.
Have you ever been
out of the country?
- When I was little.
- Mm.
My... My dad had a job
that took him to Brazil.
I remember from the pictures.
My dream to...
- Oh. Sorry.
- No. No, you go.
I've never been
out of the country.
It's, uh... It's my dream
to go to Paris.
Ohh. Paris.
That's why I'm taking French.
My mom said French
wasn't useful.
It is if you wanna go to Paris.
I still don't know how to use
those rollers that you gave me.
Oh...
Oh, it's so easy.
- Um, so, after they heat up...
- Mm-hmm?
...you... you take your hair
and you twist the hair like
this, and...
Larry,
how long will this hold us?
- I don't know.
- Well, somebody's gotta know.
I'm not sure.
What happens if somebody
gets in an accident?
Uh, the severance
package expires all at once.
Not within the calendar year.
- Is she home?
- Maybe just leave it tonight.
No, she knows better. She can't
sneak around like this.
Marion.
- You can't leave your room like this.
- I didn't.
None of these things were put
away right.
- They aren't nice. Christine, now.
- I put my clothes away.
- My name is Lady Bird.
- Don't lie to me.
This uniform... This is gonna
look like trash on Monday.
This isn't right. We can't treat
our clothes like this.
I don't know what
your wealthy friends do...
Why do you care
what I do to my clothes?
Your father doesn't have a job.
He lost his job.
Do you need him to come in here
and explain that to you?
Of course, he probably wouldn't
anyway. He's Mr. Nice Guy,
- and I always have to be the bad guy.
- Can we please just talk...
- It can't look like a rag,
- ...about this tomorrow?
Because that makes us
look like rags.
You wanna know the truth?
Here's the truth.
Some of your friends' fathers
could employ your father,
and they're not gonna do it if it
looks like his family is trash.
You understand?
Didn't you ever go to sleep without
putting all your clothes away perfectly?
Like even once?
And don't you wish your mom
hadn't gotten angry?
My mother was an
abusive alcoholic.
So, I understand you're not
interested in any Catholic colleges.
No way.
Sorry. But yes, no way.
Then you'll be applying to UCs
and state schools.
Yeah, but also those East Coast
liberal arts schools like Yale,
but not Yale, because I probably
couldn't get in.
You definitely couldn't get in.
Part of my job
is to help you be realistic.
Yeah. It seems like
everyone's job.
Your SAT scores are strangely
very good.
I had placed some calls to local alumni
of the schools you're interested in,
but unfortunately,
all the interviews are taken.
So what does that mean?
It means you'll have to get in
on how you look on paper.
Dreams don't die,
so keep an eye on your dream
And before you know where
you are, there you are
All right. Stop, stop, stop.
Should we go home?
My mom is always mad.
Doesn't matter if I get home late.
She'll be mad at me anyway.
- Your mom's hard on you.
- Yeah, well, she loves me a lot.
Pick a star for us.
That one. Right there.
Next to the bright one, and then
the dim one. You see it?
Yeah.
That's our star.
You know...
you can touch my boobs, right?
I know. It's just that
I respect you too much for that.
Cool. Awesome.
I totally get that. Thank you.
You're welcome.
If you had boobs,
I wouldn't touch them either.
I respect you so much...
because I love you.
I love you too.
- Let's name our star Claude.
- That's pretentious, don't you think?
It's French.
What should we name it?
Bruce.
- I love you!
- I love you.
Bruce.
It's normal
to not touch a penis.
I have to go to class.
- But I have free period.
- I need to pass history.
I think we're done with the
learning portion of high school.
- I'm gonna go.
- No.
- Mm-hmm.
- I hate being alone.
Bye! Love you!
Did Danny say whether his grandmother
has a formal Thanksgiving?
I don't know. There are a lot of
kids, but she lives in the Fab 40s.
Oh, well, your dad and I went to a
dinner party once in that neighborhood.
The CEO of ISC. That was pretty
formal.
You're not going to a funeral.
Well, I don't know. What says
"rich people Thanksgiving"?
I just think it's such a shame that
you're spending your last Thanksgiving
with a family you've never met
instead of us, but...
I know.
I guess you want it that way.
- Are you tired?
- No.
- Hey, Marion.
- Hey, Joyce. Hey, how's the baby?
- She's crawling.
- No! I wanna see a picture at checkout.
- Okay.
- 'Cause if you're tired, we can sit down.
- I'm not tired.
Oh, okay. I just couldn't tell
because you were dragging your feet.
Well, I just couldn't tell.
Why didn't you just say,
"Pick up your feet"?
I didn't know if you were tired.
- You were being passive-aggressive.
- No, I wasn't.
- You are so infuriating.
- Please stop yelling.
- I'm not yelling. Oh! Perfect!
- Honey, do you love it?
So, because my grade book has...
disappeared, here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna count on you
to reconstruct it, okay?
Now, I know you all know
your grades better than anybody.
I have a general idea, but this is
all about the honor code right now.
Hi. A-minus.
Pretty sure it was an A.
I'm not, but okay.
It was. Trust me,
I know talent when I see it.
You're welcome. Thank you.
Hey, I think B.
I thought it was more like B-minus,
maybe even C-plus territory?
No, because I did really well
on the last quiz.
Oh. I seem to remember you
doing only slightly better.
That brought my average
up to a B.
Okay. B it is.
It's your honor.
Lady Bird, your lover awaits!
- Hello, Danny! The famous Danny!
- Hi.
- Aw!
- Oh-ho-ho!
Aren't you adorable?
- Larry, isn't he adorable?
- He's adorable.
You're driving her and
everything. Wow.
Yeah, well, thank you
for letting Lady Bird come
to my grandmother's
Thanksgiving, Mrs. McPherson.
No. No more politeness.
Call me Marion.
Oh. Well, nice to meet you,
Mr. McPherson.
Please, call me
Mr. Larry McPherson.
Larry. Sit down,
Danny.
- Can I get you something to drink?
- Oh, no, I'm fine.
Hey, I'm Miguel, the brother. I think
Lady Bird wants to make an entrance.
She's mad we don't have
a spiral staircase.
- Shelly.
- What?
- Is my name.
- Oh. Hi.
Hi.
It's funny. On my way over here,
I went over the train tracks.
- Oh, you took H Street.
- Right. And so,
Lady Bird always says that she lives
on the wrong side of the tracks,
but I always thought
that was like a metaphor.
- Oh.
- But there are actual train tracks.
Oh, hi.
You look amazing!
- What the hell is in the duffel bag?
- Don't worry about it. Jeez.
- My grandmother will love that dress.
- Okay.
Wait.
- This is your grandma's house?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, Danny! You're late.
Oh, uh, well, thank you so much
for having us.
- This is Lady Bird.
- Hi.
Hi, honey.
Been anxious to meet you.
Your house is my favorite
- in all East Sacramento.
- Oh, thank you.
Oh, my God!
- Is this a joke?
- No.
- Pull these out...
- Oh...
Almost done. Do you like it?
Lovely. I love it. Would you mind
doing the whole table for me?
Okay.
Dreams that will explode
Waking up the countryside
- How do you know when it's working?
- You'll know.
- It's not working.
- It's not?
- No.
- My sister said this was premium.
- I'm working.
- I'm... I'm working too.
No.
I can't feel my arms.
You're working.
I'm no easy A
Quiet...
If Danny and I get married,
and then his grandma died,
I'd inherit the dream house.
Wouldn't his parents get it?
Oh, yeah.
We'd have to kill them,
and we'd have to kill
his older brothers too.
Yeah
- Whoo!
Where's Mr. Bruno's wife?
- How's it going?
- Okay.
Mom, we...
we can't really talk right now.
Well, happy Thanksgiving.
We missed you, Lady Bird.
Try to run, try to hide,
try to keep it inside
- Bye.
- Bye, Birdy.
- Bye, Shelly.
Why does that cigarette look
so weird?
Like, not like a cigarette?
'Cause it's a clove.
Lick your lips.
That's why they're sweet.
Your mom was really sad you weren't
here tonight for Thanksgiving.
Yeah, well, she hates me.
She has a big heart, your mom.
She took me in after my parents
freaked out about...
whatever, premarital sex.
I admire her.
Pray for us!
Save Jesus in our heart!
Forever!
Flying through the countryside
Merrily we roll along,
roll along
Catching a dream
Stop fighting! Stop fighting!
Hey!
Hey, old friends
How do we stay old friends
It started out like a song
Me and you
That's true. There she is.
- Hi.
- Jules. Wow.
- You were so good.
- Thank you.
I couldn't believe that.
This is my wife Becky.
Becky this is Jules. She's one
of my brightest students.
- It's so-so nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you too.
- How we doing? Feeling a little better?
- A little tired.
- Yeah.
- Okay. All right, I gotta get her home.
We got the little one, but that
was really great, Jules.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
He didn't understand it.
How long do you think you all will pee?
I drank so much soda.
- Fuck you.
- I just got my period.
- Goddammit.
- Where're you going?
There's never a line in the
men's room.
Uh, I...
Oh, my God.
♪ I'm so lost for you ♪
♪ You come crash... ♪
♪ Into me ♪
- ♪ Baby ♪
- ♪ Into me ♪
♪ I come into... ♪
♪ Touch your lips just so I know ♪
♪ In your eyes ♪
They're really nice socks.
They're expensive, actually.
They wick moisture away from
your feet.
My feet always have moisture.
Mom, I love them.
I'm sorry it's a small
Christmas. We wanted to...
It's just a little
small this year.
These are nice.
- Do you like it?
- Look.
- That's good.
- That's great.
I had to get it.
It makes me laugh.
Dad, come in.
How'd you know it was me?
Mom doesn't knock.
No, she doesn't.
Here they are. Your completed
financial aid applications.
Thank you!
- Merry Christmas.
- Thank you.
Do you need money
for the applications?
- I can help with that too.
- No. No.
I've got that.
Summer job's covered it.
This is why
we have computer shut off time.
- This is our room.
- Okay, okay.
Just can you drive me to the post office
on Jade? It should still be open.
Three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
So you pull the nozzle out. You
tip it in.
Hey.
I-I like your band.
Uh, with Jonah Ruiz,
- Lenfance New?
- L'enfance Nue.
Uh, well, I-I saw your
Thanksgiving show.
My name's Lady Bird.
That's weird. You shake hands.
Yeah.
I'm friends with Jenna and she's always
talking about how great your band is.
So I wanted to check it out.
- Yeah. Jenna's hella tight.
- Yeah.
Maybe I'll see you at the Deuce
or something, huh?
Sure. See you at the Deuce.
Hey.
I'm not paying you to flirt.
I wasn't flirting.
I wish you had been.
A reading from the book
of Genesis.
"The Lord took Abram outside
and said,
'Look up at the sky
and count the stars if you can.'
Just so, he added,
'Shall your descendants be.'
Abram put his faith in the Lord.
Who credited to him
as an act of righteousness."
Okay, the first time we did it, it
was at his lake house last summer.
- It was so funny.
- Oh, here you go.
From Uncle Matt.
I think he and my mom are fighting
so enjoy the lunches while you can.
Oh, no thanks. I'm trying to
lose weight.
Really?
Sex is not a big deal. It's just
my mom called me during it.
- Skirt check.
- Was on my cell phone.
The one she got me for
emergencies.
Did you pick up?
Yeah. I was like, "Um, Mom, I
can't really talk right now."
What was the emergency?
- What?
- Uh, what was the emergency?
- Oh, my great aunt died.
- I'm so sorry.
She kinda did it to herself.
Yeah. I don't know why you'd do
that if you're already so old.
Ladies.
Skirts.
I'm going to write you a
citation, Miss Walton.
No more short skirts.
Sarah Joan is all up in my junk.
She's a cunt.
Birdy, you like her.
Yeah, but she's a cunt.
I have an idea
of how to get Sarah Joan back.
- How?
- You'll see this afternoon.
No, we have auditions
this afternoon.
Oh, right. I mean, uh, I don't
think I want to do the play.
Meet me at the
teacher's parking lot at 3.
- I'll have the materials.
- Okay.
Wait, what was your name?
Lady Bird.
- Weird.
- Ladies.
We have a decision to make.
Prom themes. Top options so far,
cities of the world,
eternal flame, and movies.
Oh, where is Father Leviatch?
All right, let's have everyone
take a knee. Huh?
- What?
- Cozy sit.
Now, I know you all miss
Father Leviatch,
and I can tell you that
the brothers do too.
But I'm gonna give
this thing my best shot.
Uh, now, usually
I'm the JV football coach,
but from what I can see,
a play is a play.
Where's Lady Bird?
She's with her new best friend. She
thinks she's too cool for theater.
If you can pull out
your-your scripts,
I've assigned a number
to each of your roles.
And, uh, I'm gonna put the
blocking up here on the board,
and then if you guys can transcribe that
back in your play books, that'd be great.
Who's playing what part?
Uh, I had Miss Patty here assign
roles, since she knows you all.
So, uh, call them out,
Miss Patty.
Okay, uh, Prospero. Danny.
Danny. Nice. That's role one.
Wait. Where do you live?
Oh, um, The 40s.
That's where our
starter house was.
Which street?
Um, 44th.
It's the three-story blue one
with the white shutters and the
American flag in the front.
Yeah. I know that one.
Do you want to go over there
right now and eat?
I live in Granite Bay, otherwise
I'd say let's go there.
Actually, I was thinking maybe
we should go to the Deuce.
I was talking to Kyle about it,
and he was like,
"Whatever it's lame,
but maybe I'll see you there."
How do you know Kyle?
Oh, my mom made me get a job
at New Helvetia
to learn, like,
"responsibility."
Anyway, we hang out there.
Yeah. Kyle's awesome.
Let's Deuce it up.
Okay, guys. Now, look.
Role one, right?
You're gonna run, kind of,
a skinny post right up front.
I want you to look straight
at the audience, okay.
Don't be looking around and blabbing
at anybody if they walk by ya.
Eight, nine, ten. You're coming
in hard, right here.
'Cause these guys are
gonna love it.
Don't talk amongst yourselves. Now,
coming in slow, we're singing.
This is singing.
Wide lines are singing.
We're singing. We're singing.
Danny's not singing yet.
He's all alone.
Singing. Eight, nine, ten...
You come in hot!
- This is the Deuce?
- Yeah.
- It's a parking lot?
We were in one parking lot and
we went to another parking lot?
Hey, Kyle. Lady Bird and I just
decorated the Nun-mobile.
Like, just married to Jesus.
That's hella tight.
What you do is very baller.
- You're very anarchist.
- Yeah.
Fuck 'em.
Don't worry, I'm not gonna
snitch on you.
Well, I hope not 'cause I'd
fuckin' kill your family.
- What?
- Sorry.
I... That-That was
an exaggeration.
It's okay.
My dad has cancer, so
I guess God's doing that for us.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You work at New Helvetia, right?
Right.
Can I get your number? We were looking
to set up more gigs down there.
Definitely.
It's my parents number.
You don't have a cell phone?
- Nah.
- Good girl.
Government didn't have to
put tracking devices on us.
We bought them and put them on
ourselves.
I don't own a tracking device.
No, no, no. The cell phones.
- You see?
- Wow.
Yeah. I know.
I mean, you'll have one eventually.
Everyone's gonna have one.
And then,
it'll be a matter of time.
Before what?
Before they put them
in our brains.
What do you want from me?
Yes?
My-My grandma wanted me to tell you
that she missed you at Christmas.
Yeah. Well, I couldn't have gone anyway.
My mom was pissed about Thanksgiving.
Your mom is crazy.
I'm scared of her.
She's not crazy. She's just, you
know, she has a big heart.
She's very warm.
I don't find your mother warm.
- You don't?
- No. No, she's warm. Yeah.
- But she's also, kind of, scary.
- Well, you can't be scary and warm.
- I think you can. Your mom is.
- You're gay.
Fuck me.
Can you not tell anyone, please?
I'm so sorry about everything.
I'm so ashamed of all of it.
It's just... It's going to be bad and
I just need a little bit of time
to figure out how I'm going to
tell my mom and dad and...
Don't worry.
I won't tell.
It's okay.
And do you have a
support system?
What do you mean?
Who do you turn to when you feel
this way?
No one, I guess.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be sorry.
There's no wrong answer.
Please don't tell your daughter.
No. Of course not.
Of course not.
Remember that you are
dust and to dust you will return.
It's a new system. You just enter
your social security number and...
- Davis?
- Davis is good.
- Maybe you shoulda looked at it.
- It's only half an hour away.
- Less if you're driving fast.
- I went to graduate school there.
Lots of smart people
go to Davis.
I thought Berkeley had to
accept me.
You and Miguel went there.
I'm a legacy.
Uh, not if we don't give money.
- And you get bad grades.
- And what do you know about it?
- Meaning?
- Nothing.
- No. What are you implying?
- Nothing!
You fucking racist!
- I didn't say anything!
- I didn't put down my race!
Oh, yeah. I'm sure they had no
idea, Miguel!
You're actually fucking evil.
- What is wrong with you?
- Go. Go to your room.
- I'm not five!
- I didn't raise you like this.
I don't have to go anywhere.
I'm not going to a fucking
university
that's famous for
its fucking agricultural school!
And Miguel and Shelly, you'll never get
jobs with all that shit in your face.
♪ Cry me a river ♪
- ♪ Cry me a river ♪
- Hey.
Hi.
Um, help yourself to anything
in the fridge.
My parents are upstairs, but
they don't care if you drink.
Okay. Cool.
♪ It wasn't like you
only talked to him ♪
♪ And you know it ♪
♪ Don't act like
you don't know it ♪
♪ All of these things
people told me ♪
♪ Keep messing with my head ♪
♪ Messing with my head ♪
I hate that shit.
But you smoke.
I smoke hand-rolled cigarettes.
Never industrially produced.
Never cloves.
What's wrong with cloves?
Can't inhale cloves.
What's the point?
Oh.
You're not supposed to.
Well, cloves were what I first
smoked when I was young.
So, you know,
it's a force of habit.
It has fiberglass.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Rolling your own is best.
Also, like...
I'm trying as much as possible
not participate in our economy.
I don't like money.
So...
I'm trying to live
by bartering alone.
But doesn't Catholic school
cost money?
Yeah. The diocese we're in
are super into it.
It mattered to my dad that...
I go to Xavier, so
just trying to make him happy.
♪ The damage is done,
so I guess I be leaving ♪
♪ Oh! ♪
- ♪ The damage is done ♪
- I don't want to have sex yet.
- I haven't had sex yet.
- Me neither.
- With another person. Really?
- Nope. Me either. Yeah.
♪ You don't have to say
what you did ♪
- ♪ I already know ♪
♪ I found out from him ♪
- ♪ Now there's just no chance ♪
- LADY BIRD: Oh, my God.
It's the tanning bed.
Julie will love this.
Who's Julie?
♪ You can go on... ♪
Lady Bird. You can't lock the
door when we have one bathroom.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
It's just this is the only place
I can get any privacy.
You really need to use two
towels?
Uh, no.
- I guess no.
- If you need to use two towels,
you just have to say because
this affects my whole day.
Because I have to do laundry
before work
and I need to know if there's
more towels that I need to wash.
I just need one. Sorry.
Okay. Well, let me get to the
mirror, I've gotta get going.
When do you think
is a normal time to have sex?
- You're having sex?
- No.
Um, college is good.
I think college and use
protection like we talked about.
Okay.
Is Dad depressed?
Why do you ask that?
The pills. They have Dad's name
on them.
Dad's been struggling
with depression for years.
I didn't know that.
Money is not life's report card.
He's depressed about money?
Being successful doesn't mean
anything in and of itself.
It just means
that you're successful.
Yeah,
but then you're successful.
But that doesn't mean that
you're happy.
But he's not happy.
I have to get out of Sacramento.
Why?
Because it's soul killing.
It's the Midwest of California.
Isn't there a thing, like,
"Think globally, act locally"?
I feel that the person who said
that didn't live in Sacramento.
Ah!
I love it here.
I want to send my daughters
to Immaculate Heart.
I wanna... You know,
I wanna be a mom.
At least go to San Francisco.
I don't like hills.
Start simple with x
plus three times x plus two.
- Now if we use FOIL, where do we start?
- Julie?
Julie?
Julie. Hey.
What do you want from Julie?
Darlene, can you excuse us?
Darlene's staying.
Why aren't you in Algebra 2?
- I switched sections.
- Why?
Aren't Jenna and Kyle enough?
I'm sorry that you're jealous.
Jenna's a moron, you know.
She's not. She's in AP Calculus.
She's a moron in a deeper sense.
You don't even know her.
Miss Patty assigned you a role by the way,
you just never showed up to claim it!
- What role?
- The tempest!
- There is no role of the tempest!
- It is the titular role!
No, it's a made up thing
so we all can participate!
You can't do anything unless you're
the center of attention, can you?
Yeah. Well, you know your mom's
tits, they're fake. Totally fake!
She made one bad decision at 19!
Two bad decisions!
And at 15, this
girl was pregnant.
She decided that she was going
to get an abortion.
It made sense.
It was the right thing to do.
- She was sitting there...
- Let me guess, she didn't get it.
...and something deep inside of
her said,
- "No."
- Bingo.
Anyone want to guess who this
woman is?
The young lady right here.
- You?
- No. It was not me.
Um, your friend?
No.
The girl in the story was...
my mother.
I am that baby that
she decided not to abort.
That could have been me.
That could have been my fate.
Just because something looks ugly
doesn't mean it's morally wrong.
What did you say, ma'am?
- Nothing.
- Please. Share.
I said,
"Just because something looks ugly
doesn't mean that it's morally wrong."
You think dead children
aren't morally wrong?
No. I'm just saying that if you
took up close pictures of my vagina
while I was on my period, it would be
disturbing, but it doesn't make it wrong.
Excuse me?
Listen. If your mother had
had the abortion,
we wouldn't have to sit through
this stupid assembly.
Suspended? How does
this happen?
Everything we do is for you.
Everything.
Do you think
I like driving that car around?
- No.
- Do you?
- Do you think I like working double shifts
at the psych hospital?
- No.
- You needed to go to the Catholic school
because your brother saw somebody knifed
in front of him at the public school.
Is that what you want? Larry, what
are you doing on the computer?
- Nothing.
- You think your dad and I don't know
how ashamed that you are of us?
Your dad knows.
Your dad knows why you ask him to drop you
off a block away from school every day.
- Dad, I didn't mean to.
- You made him feel horrible!
- Horrible! You know that?
- I'm sorry.
- Marion, you didn't have to bring that up.
- No, Larry, you can't just be
the nice guy. She has to know.
She has to know how you feel.
Otherwise, she's just gonna think
she can say anything at all,
and nobody ever gets hurt.
Wrong side of the tracks!
- I didn't mean it that way.
- Yeah.
- It was a joke.
- Yeah. It's just a joke Mom and Dad.
They don't care. We didn't think
we'd be in this house for 25 years.
We thought we would've moved
some place better.
Whatever we give you,
it's never enough.
- It's never enough.
- It is enough.
Do you have any idea
what it costs to raise you?
And how much you're just
throwing away every day?
Give me a number.
What?
I don't understand.
You give me a number for how
much it cost to raise me.
And I'm going to get older
and make a lot of money,
and write you a check for what I
owe you.
So that I never have
to speak to you again.
Well I highly doubt that you will be able
to get a job good enough to do that.
So the attack on
Baghdad last night,
it was absolutely unbelievable.
That's right. Yeah,
the likes of which, uh, many US...
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me, Jenna.
Hey. Are you calling
me from school?
No. We got out early 'cause all the Irish
girls got totally sloshed by noon.
Oh, right.
Happy St. Patrick's Day.
Yeah. I guess they'd been
stockpiling mini liquor bottles
in the tampon machine,
and now they're all throwing up.
Everyone else got out early.
So, guess where I am.
I don't know. Where?
Ding dong. I'm outside.
- What?
- I'm standing outside.
No. Just leave.
Leave.
- Fuck!
- Hello.
Hi.
So this is your house?
Yeah.
That lady in the other house
was totally freaked out.
That's my friend's grandma.
That's her house.
Why did you say
it was your house?
I wished I lived in that house.
I don't even sort of understand why
somebody would lie about that.
I-I didn't lie.
You lied. You're a liar.
I hate dishonesty.
I'm sorry.
Apology accepted, I guess.
Are we still friends?
I mean, if you're still Kyle's girlfriend,
then yeah, I guess I'll see you around.
Mortar rounds fired at
the camp that will fly over them
if they are down below
on surface of the ground.
And that is hard work, indeed. Believe me.
We've had to do it...
I'm ready.
What?
I'm ready to have sex.
Oh. Okay.
Great.
You're so dexterous with that.
Thanks.
Oh.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Are you...
- Are you done?
- Yeah. Yes.
Sorry. I was confused.
- You have like...
- What?
- You have some sort of like blood.
Oh. Shit!
I get nosebleeds.
- Here.
- Thanks.
I'm sorry.
No. I'm good.
Remember when
tie-dye was an activity?
Oh, I didn't make that shirt. My
parents got it for me at Sea Ranch.
You can read Sea Ranch if you
look close.
Cut to ten years later.
What?
Like how ten years ago,
you were in first grade.
Now we cut to...
What does cut to mean to you?
Or like, you know,
little did he know.
Nothing you're saying is making
any sense.
How we're not virgins now.
We deflowered each other.
We have each other's flowers.
Sorry.
I'm just happy.
I didn't lose my
virginity to you.
Wait...
What?
I lost my virginity to
Cassy Duvall.
Excuse me?
You said you were a virgin.
No, I didn't. 'Cause I'm not.
- And I haven't lied in two years.
- Oh, Jesus.
Yeah. I probably slept with,
like, six people.
You don't even know if
it's six people?
I don't keep a list.
Why wouldn't you keep a list?
- We're in high school.
- Whoa. Why are you... What?
- Why are you getting so moody?
- You did say you were a virgin.
I think you might've
made an assumption.
I just had a whole experience
that was wrong.
- Look, you're deciding to be upset.
- No. I am upset.
Because you're deciding to be.
Don't be mad at me for this.
It's stupid. You can't be mad at me
for something I have no control over.
I just wanted it to be special.
Why? You're gonna have so much
unspecial sex in your life.
I was on top! Who the fuck is on
top their first time?
You have any, like, awareness of
how many civilians we've killed
- since the invasion in Iraq started...
- Shut up!
Shut up.
Different things can be sad.
It's not all war.
Are we still going to
prom together?
Sure.
I thought Miguel was gonna pick
me up.
Well, I was just arriving from
work and it was easier.
You okay?
Aww, honey.
He...
Oh. Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.
What's this sweater?
This is... My friend,
Jenna, gave it to me.
Who's Jenna?
My friend.
You wanna do our
favorite Sunday activity?
I don't have a second shift.
Yeah.
The attack came in waves,
cruise missiles, followed by
the F117 stealth bombers
with so-called
bunker buster bombs.
With target a bunker believed...
Lady Bird, a bunch of things
arrived for you.
Holy shit!
- Since when do you get mail?
- I get mail.
Whatever you're up to,
it's not gonna end well.
Yes!
These programmers nowadays
are like kids, man.
I know.
But that's why I think with me,
you'll find something different.
Yeah, but they're like babies.
I hear you. It's wild.
Which is why I went back to
school
and got my MBA at UC Davis
while still working at ISC.
Oh.
- Wow. That must've been a lot of work.
- It was.
I heard ISC's closing now
though.
I heard. Yes.
So the assholes who fired you
are now closing up shop.
- Feels good.
- Yeah.
Uh...
What else is supposed to happen?
Oh, I, uh, thought we'd...
talk about the position.
How'd it go?
Let's go buy a big bag of
Doritos and eat them in the car
- to celebrate your wait list.
- Okay.
But don't tell Mom about the
Doritos or the wait list.
- Hey.
- Hi, son.
Wait. What are you doing here?
Well, um...
I guess we're, uh,
going for the same job then.
Looks like it.
- Go get 'em.
- Thanks.
- This-This way? Okay.
- Yeah, yeah.
I know it was you
who did the just married thing.
It wasn't me.
I'm not going to punish you.
Oh. Why not?
It was funny.
Sister Gina and I drove all the way home
before we noticed people were honking.
Really?
To be fair, I wasn't just married to Jesus.
It's been 40 years.
Well, he's a lucky guy.
I read your college essay.
You clearly love Sacramento.
- I do?
- You write about Sacramento
so affectionately and with such
care.
Well, I was just describing it.
Well, it comes across as love.
Sure. I guess I pay attention.
Don't you think
they are maybe the same thing?
Love and attention?
Guess you won't be
going to any dances in college.
This is our last one.
You know Davis has a terrific
theater
if you're still interested in
theater.
- Are ya?
- I'm probably no good at acting.
Why don't I look like
the girls in the magazines?
It's too bad I can't meet
this Kyle before prom.
Well, he's not my boyfriend
anymore.
I mean, maybe he never even was.
Well, I'd still like to meet
him.
It's too tight. Fuck.
Well, I suggested you not have
that second helping of pasta.
- Mom.
- Honey, you seem upset about it
- and I'm trying to help.
- You're giving me an eating disorder.
I wish
I could get an eating disorder.
I love it.
Is it too pink?
What?
Why can't you say I look nice?
I thought you didn't even care
what I think.
- I still want you to think I look good.
- Okay. I'm sorry.
I was telling you the truth.
You want me to lie?
No. I mean, I just wish...
I just...
I wish that you liked me.
Of course I love you.
But do you like me?
I want you to be the very best
version of yourself that you can be.
What if this is the best
version?
You look really pretty.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You look like a badass girl
in a band.
Thanks.
Um...
I guess that's my date.
You aren't gonna get in a car
with a guy who honks, are ya?
I think, yes, I am.
Let me get your picture.
Your mom's pissed,
she had to work a double.
Even you deserve
better than this.
Have a good time.
Yeah. Good luck.
- See ya.
- I think she's weird.
- She is weird.
Hey, guys.
I guess I'll just sit shotgun.
Yeah.
- You look really nice, Kyle.
- You look good.
Thanks.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hey, what's going on, man?
Hey. Yeah. Okay,
that sounds great.
Okay.
Hey, do you guys wanna ditch prom
and just go to Mike's instead?
Yeah. I hate dances.
Yes.
Yeah. Okay. No prom.
♪ Baby ♪
♪ And I come into... ♪
- ♪ You ♪
- KYLE: I fucking hate this song.
I love it.
I actually want to go to prom.
Okay. Yeah. I mean...
I don't really want to do that.
Can you... Can you take me to my
friend, Julie's house, please?
Sure.
Who's Julie?
She's my best friend.
♪ Close to me ♪
♪ Oh, and you come crash ♪
♪ Into me ♪
♪ Baby ♪
Julie, honey?
There's someone here to see you.
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Fine. I'm fine.
What happened?
Nothing really. Nothing.
Why are you crying?
Just crying.
Some people aren't built happy,
you know.
Oh, my gosh.
We ate all the cheese.
It's okay. Lots of cheese vary
in size.
- This one was a small one.
- It's so small.
- It was tiny.
- That's not our fault.
What-What were we to do?
Fuck it! Let's just go to prom.
Doesn't your mom have a dress?
Let's be honest.
I've had a dress for months.
It's purple.
- It is?
- Uh-hmm, you're really gonna like it.
- Come and see it.
- Okay.
Cracker time. Dress time.
I hope it fits.
♪ You've got your ball,
you got your chain ♪
♪ Tied to me tight,
tie me up again ♪
♪ Who's got their claws
In you my friend? ♪
♪ Into your heart
I'll beat again ♪
♪ Sweet like candy to my soul ♪
♪ Sweet you rock,
and sweet you roll ♪
♪ Lost for you ♪
♪ I'm so lost, for you ♪
People make so much noise in the movies,
but it's really not a big thing.
You can totally
be quiet during it.
Was it amazing though?
I wanted it so badly,
but then I found that
when it happened...
I-I really like dry humping
much more.
You're not a virgin.
- I can't wait for state fair.
- Ah, I know.
Log ride.
- Shit.
- What?
I'm not gonna be here this summer,
like, all summer, basically.
- Why not?
- My dad, my real dad,
he resurfaced in Yellowstone,
and he wants me to come there
for the summer,
before I start SCC.
Oh.
I'm not going anywhere to college,
so it seemed like a good opportunity.
Yeah.
I'm gonna miss
the fuck out of you.
I probably won't get in, so
I'll go to Davis
and I'll see you every day.
Now, I want spirits to enforce,
and art to enchant,
and my ending is despair.
Unless I be relieved by prayer,
which pierces so that
it assaults mercy itself
and freeze all faults.
As you from crimes would
pardon thee.
Let your indulgence set me free.
Yes!
Ooh!
Christine "Lady Bird" McPherson.
Yeah!
Cheers.
To Miguel and his new job.
- Yay.
- Here, here. Yes.
- To Lady Bird going to Davis.
- To Davis.
- Congratulations.
- Good school.
Hey. So I talked to my manager and, um,
you could totally take over my old job.
- Great. Thanks, Miguel.
- I'm so proud of you, Lady Bird.
You walked weird across the
stage, but you did it!
- I didn't walk weird.
- Well, it seemed a little weird.
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Hey.
Aw, I missed you guys.
Oh, did you find out about the
wait list?
Oh, fuck.
What?
I'm not even in yet, so this
might not even be a problem.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have gone
behind your back.
I just... It's not like I'm
definitely going to New York.
Mom.
Aren't you, sort of, proud
that I'm so close to getting in?
Just a little?
I mean... yes, I know it was
probably easier
because 9-11 and less people applying
with terrorism and all that,
but still though, I'm sorry.
I know I can lie
and not be a good person, but...
please, Mom.
Please. I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I-I appreciate everything
you've done for me.
I'm ungrateful and I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry I wanted more.
Just... Please!
Talk to me.
I know I'm-I'm so bad!
I know I am.
But please just talk to me, Mom.
Mom, please talk to me.
Here.
Then next one.
That'll be three dollars.
You passed.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
Thanks.
It's not a thanking situation.
You either pass or
you don't pass.
Yay.
Come in.
Happy birthday to you
You remembered.
You're my only daughter.
Well, Shelly too. Kind of.
Thanks.
Make a wish.
Are you and Mom gonna
get a divorce over this?
No. We can't afford to.
Dad.
I'm kidding, no.
I love your mom.
Does Mom hate me?
You both have such
strong personalities.
She doesn't know how to help you
and it frustrates her.
I wish she'd talk to me.
She will. I know.
Happy 18.
Thanks.
Do you want some?
Yes.
One pack of Camel Lights please,
and a Scratcher,
and a Playgirl.
ID.
That'll be 10.87.
Oh, um, it's my birthday today.
I'm 18, which is why all these
things, I can buy them.
Okay. Happy birthday.
Thanks.
With her scholarships and then if we
refinance the house, then where are we?
♪ It's hard to think
this eve of parting ♪
♪ Turns to sand of summer... ♪
You're only supposed to use it
for emergencies.
It's my tracking device.
When both our minds
Are warped with parting
♪ Break the thought
of nights alone ♪
♪ Flesh cries out,
"Don't move don't leave me" ♪
♪ Conscience runs
till out of breath ♪
♪ Sunrise pregnant
with your leaving ♪
♪ Creeping in like
certain death ♪
- Thank you for driving.
- You're welcome.
You're not coming?
You can't walk up
to the gates anymore, anyway.
Yeah, but I'm going to college.
Well, Dad will walk
you to security.
Parking's too expensive here.
There it is.
Hello.
It's okay.
She'll be back.
She'll come back.
She was worried that there would
be errors or mistakes or something,
that you'd judge
her writing abilities.
I wouldn't do that.
I thought you should have them,
but I want you to know
how much she loves you,
but also don't tell her
I salvaged them, okay?
Okay.
♪ Won't somebody please ♪
♪ Help me with my miseries ♪
- Hey.
Do you believe in God?
- Uh, no.
- Why not?
Really?
Uh, it's ridiculous.
People call each other by names that
their parents made up for them,
but they won't believe in God.
What's your name?
Christine. My name is Christine.
Hey. I'm David.
You shake.
- I shake.
- Okay.
- Where you from?
- Sacramento.
Sorry. Where?
San Francisco.
Oh, cool. Yeah.
San Francisco's a great city.
Really.
♪ Can't somebody see, yeah ♪
♪ What this world
has done to me ♪
Bruce. Bruce.
No. My name is David.
Jesus Christ. You have really
bad music.
It's all greatest hits.
But they're the greatest.
What's wrong with that?
♪ Where you go, go ♪
♪ You will always see my face ♪
Oh, God!
I'm sorry.
What do you want us to do?
She's drunk.
Excuse me. What day is it?
Sunday.
Thank you.
Hi. You've reached
the McPherson family.
Please leave a message.
Thank you.
Hi, Mom and Dad.
It's me. Christine.
It's the name you gave me.
It's a good one.
Dad, this is more for Mom.
Hey, Mom.
Did you feel emotional the first
time that you drove in Sacramento?
I did, and I wanted to tell you,
but we weren't really talking
when it happened.
All those bends I've
known my whole life,
and stores and the whole thing.
But I wanted to tell you...
I love you.
Thank you. I'm...
Thank you.