♪♪♪
thunder rumbling
electricity zapping
police siren wailing
- Johnny cheers
- indistinct yelling
What's wrong with you?
Where did you even get that?
- screams
- Johnny, what are you doing?
♪♪♪
gate squeaking
- glass bottles rattling
- rats squealing
coroner grunts
♪♪♪
electricity zapping
groans
9-1-1 operator 9-1-1,
what is your emergency?
grunts
9-1-1 operator Hello? 9-1-1.
chokes
9-1-1 operator
Do you have an emergency?
Sir, can you speak?
chokes
9-1-1 operator
If you can't speak,
press any button on your phone.
Once for yes, twice for no.
coroner coughs
9-1-1 operator
Are you still there?
chokes
9-1-1 operator Sir,
I want you to stay on the line
for me, okay?
I'm gonna track your location.
Art snarls
9-1-1 operator
Are you still with me?
coroner coughing
- 9-1-1 operator Hello?
- coroner grunts
9-1-1 operator
Are you still there?
chokes
9-1-1 operator Okay.
129, Peterson Drive,
Miles County Morgue.
Sir, are you still with me?
coughs
9-1-1 operator Just sit tight
and remain calm.
Police and paramedics
are on their way...
coroner coughing, choking
- thuds
- groans
groans
chokes, screams
♪♪♪
chokes
groans, coughs
♪♪♪
police siren wailing
clattering
♪♪♪
coins rattles
snores
♪♪♪
electricity zapping
machine stops
♪♪♪
electricity zapping
♪ You're not alone ♪
♪♪♪
blows
♪ You're not alone ♪
Barbara Ma'am, I understand.
But I can't give you
that information.
Your husband's the only one
listed on the policy.
- Bitch!
- bacon sizzling
No, ma'am, not you. Not you.
Mom, don't we have
a tape measure?
I don't know.
Check the drawer
by the microwave.
Yes, ma'am!
I understand that,
but in the future,
your husband's going
to have to call the policy.
All I can tell you
is that it's still active.
Yes.
Mm hmm.
Can you wait five minutes,
and go get your brother, please?
Yes, ma'am.
My manager
is just gonna tell you
the same thing.
So, did you figure out
what you're dressing up
as tomorrow?
The Miles County clown.
- Don't do that.
- Why not?
Because that's beyond
disrespectful.
What are we talking about?
He wants to dress up
as a real guy
who murdered nine people
last year.
Do you have any idea
how insensitive that is?
Not to mention, sick.
- Oh, you're not doing that.
- It's just a costume.
How would you feel
if God forbid,
he attacked someone
in our family,
and people celebrated him?
That's basically
what you're doing.
You don't see people
dressing up as Jeffrey Dahmer
or Charles Manson.
I think
you're both overreacting.
Do you?
Charles Manson technically
never killed anyone.
All right, all right. Enough.
I said, "No," and that's it.
chomps
Did you know that Nazis used
to inject children's eyeballs
to see
if they would change color?
Barbara Jonathan!
Thank you.
♪♪♪
So, what are your plans
tomorrow?
Megan Melanie's throwing
a Halloween party.
That's nice.
Who are you going with, Allie?
And Brooke.
She's not driving, is she?
I'm gonna take an Uber.
Barbara
Why, so you can get shitfaced?
Who do you think I am,
stupid, Sienna?
Do we have to do this
every time I go out?
You know I don't drink.
So you say.
scoffs
box thuds
Your brother never closes
these goddamn boxes.
Give me that. I got it.
Mom, do you ever...
wonder about Jonathan?
What do you mean?
You know, he's...
- He's an oddball.
- So, what?
He was looking up serial killers
when I went in his room before.
Now, he's... he's talking
about Nazis and the Holocaust.
- I mean...
- It's just a phase, Sienna.
It'll pass.
You said that a year ago.
Yeah, well, he lost his father.
And I didn't?
You don't see me
crying out for attention.
Yeah, well, I wish you would
from time to time.
You keep everything bottled up.
It's not healthy.
All right.
Just don't be surprised if you
find a dead animal in his room.
You know what?
Watch your mouth, huh?
And what about you?
When Daddy took you fishing
for those midos or macos.
Minnows.
Barbara
Whatever they're called.
And he found you
cutting the heads off.
Didn't think I'd remember that,
did you?
I was a lot younger
than Jonathan.
Well, you were old enough
to know the difference
between right and wrong.
Your brother's fine.
♪♪♪
Do you have any Super Glue?
A little.
- Why, what happened?
- The string came off.
I thought you weren't gonna wear
this tomorrow.
I won't paint my face then.
- Jonathan.
- Come on.
It's too late
to get another costume.
Give me.
Jesus. What, did you grow
another foot since dinner?
Tallest kid in my class.
Yeah, well, I can still kick
your ass.
Not for long.
That is sick.
- How much do you have left?
- Just finishing up the skull.
It looks
just like Daddy's character.
You know?
You draw almost as good
as him now.
Thanks.
Is this a part
of your costume, too?
No. I could not walk out
in the streets with that thing.
I'd get arrested
in like two seconds.
Yeah. But nobody
would mess with you.
- That's for sure.
- Right.
Just be careful, please.
That blade's like razor sharp.
There. Should be good now.
Awesome.
You think
that guy's still out there?
Who?
The Miles County clown.
What's up with you
and this clown all of a sudden?
You're like obsessed.
They never found his body.
What if he decides
to come back here?
Is that why you wanna dress up
like him?
You think if he sees you
wearing his costume,
he'll be all cordial with you?
Cordial?
Friendly.
No.
Sienna
I wouldn't worry about it.
On the off chance
that he is still alive,
I'm sure he's gone far away
from here.
- Thanks again for the hat.
- You're welcome.
man on TV Tap lower down.
screams
woman on TV
Owen, I saw it again.
creature growling
Hmm?
- gunfire
- groans
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
♪ The club
is downright gruesome ♪
♪ But your appetite so big ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny,
food's a little funny ♪
♪ Food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
indistinct chatter
blows raspberry
♪ Drop on by the clown café,
your favorite meals on wheels ♪
♪ The menu is disgusting
and it's full of special deals ♪
♪ Nothing here is good for you,
so grab yourself a tray ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
♪ Double up your order quick
before it runs away ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪ Why not visit after school
and have yourselves a bite? ♪
♪ An appetizing appetizer
certain to delight ♪
♪ We haven't done a ride
♪ And thus,
it makes your tooth decay ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
♪ The grub
is downright gruesome ♪
♪ But your appetite so big ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
Food's a little funny ♪
♪ Food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
crowd laughs
nun Will you help this man?
You, over there!
Yeah! Feed this man.
How about you? He's hungry.
Will you feed this man?
He's not invisible. Feed him!
crowd laughs
commercial actor New Art
Crispies from Sugar Plum.
Fun, little surprises
in every bite.
cackling
commercial actor Glass,
insects, and razor blade.
There's no telling
what you may find!
Special prize included
in every box.
Wow! I wonder what I got!
Speaking of surprises, kids,
we have a very special guest
with us today.
Now, for a guy
who doesn't speak,
he sure makes a lot of noise.
All the way from Miles County,
please welcome Art the Clown.
crowd cheering
♪♪♪
carnival music playing
cycle horn honks
crowd chuckling
gasping
chuckling
Whoo! Whoo! Yeah!
shrieks
Yeah!
chomps
crowd laughing, cheering
laughing
crowd cheering, laughing
crowd laughing
nun Stop everything
you're doing now!
I see you feeding your faces.
Feed him! He's so hungry.
Feed this man!
- gunfire
- screams
gasps
groaning, screaming
- crowd clamoring
- gunfire
groans, chokes
screaming continues
- screams
- groans, pants
grunts, whimpers
thuds
♪♪♪
grunts, pants
screaming in distance
groaning, screaming
grunts, pants
commercial artist Special
prize included in every box.
grunts, whimpers
grunts, pants
groans, breathes heavily
groans
screams
gasps, pants
♪♪♪
grunts
Shit.
coughs
Jonathan What's going on?
- Mom!
- Get downstairs!
Jesus Christ!
Sienna Mom,
what are you doing? Come on!
Barbara Really, Sienna?
You left burning candles
on your dresser all night?
What are you, fucking stupid?
I didn't do anything.
They weren't lit.
Barbara
Then please explain to me
how your goddamn room
caught on fire.
- Sienna I have no idea.
- You have no idea.
So, it just spontaneously
combusted out of thin air?
- I guess so.
- Sienna...
Get back to bed.
You have school in the morning.
- You mean I still have to go?
- What did I say?
You know what, Sienna?
You are going to kill us
one of these days,
between your chemicals
and your heat guns,
and staying up until 4:00
in the fucking morning
doing God only knows what!
Oh, my God.
For the hundredth time,
I was not using chemicals
and I did not leave
burning candles on my dresser!
- Why can't you just believe me?
- Because...
Stay in my room tonight,
and I'll sleep on the couch.
I don't mind sleeping
on the couch.
Go to bed.
♪♪♪
sighs
Barbara I kept whatever
was in the bottom drawer.
Most of it's ruined.
Make sure you park
in the garage when you get home.
Those animals next door
are always throwing eggs
and shaving cream.
I don't want the car
getting scratched up.
You know the sword Daddy got me?
What about it?
It was on top of my dresser
last night.
Well, maybe it can be restored.
Is it bad?
It's fine.
There's not a mark on it.
That's good.
Can't say the same
for your clothes.
Jonathan, hurry up.
You have five minutes.
chomps
Art cackling
rattles
hammering
static on TV
Welcome back to the program.
If you're just tuning in,
I'm sitting here live
with the sole survivor
of the Miles County massacre,
which occurred
exactly one year ago today.
I've worked on the show
for many years,
and I've never sat across
from someone
who has a story to tell
quite like yours.
Thank you again
for taking the time to sit down
- and speak with me.
- It's my pleasure.
Monica Now, when we left off,
we were talking about the moment
you woke up from the coma.
Do you remember
your initial reaction
when you first saw your face?
Victoria Yes.
Monica Would you like
to share that with us?
I wished I was dead.
Monica Do you still feel
that way?
Victoria
People are frightened
by the way that I look,
especially children.
And it's really difficult for me
to deal with that,
so isolation is ideal.
Monica Now, what about
your attacker?
The man only identified
as Art the Clown.
Well, there's a lot
of controversy
surrounding his supposed death.
The authorities issued
a statement,
claiming that his body
disappeared
from the county coroner's office
the morning after the attack.
Victoria He's dead.
I saw it happen.
indistinct chatter
- What are you guys doing?
- Dude, look what Sean found.
It's the new mascot.
Jonathan Oh, man.
Right up your alley, huh, J man?
I wonder how it died.
Probably
had the school meatloaf.
chuckling
I think
you should leave it alone.
What for? He doesn't mind.
Eric It's so gross.
Dude, you should have been here.
Couple of birds
were eating his asshole.
Yeah.
Watch this. Stephanie!
Stephanie!
Come here for a minute.
Sean, come on.
chuckles
Sean It's gonna be awesome.
- What's up?
- Sean Check it out.
Some cat just gave birth
behind the dumpster.
- Really?
- Sean Yeah.
Go look at all the kittens.
Eric & Sean chuckling
Oh, my God!
What's wrong?
Maggots need love, too!
Stephanie!
- Can you?
- woman speaks indistinctly
chuckling
Ms. Principe What's going on?
Oh, shit. Ms. Principe.
What are you boys doing
back here?
Oh, Christ. Mr. Henderson.
- Nothing.
- Ms. Principe Really?
You go find
Mr. Curtis right now,
and you have him move that.
And you two, get to class.
Move it!
sighs
♪♪♪
Whalen Jonathan.
Keep your eyes
on your own paper.
Mr. Whalen.
- May I be excused?
- indistinct chatter
Wait. I think
I forgot my shorts.
I think I have an extra pair.
- Do you have an extra shirt?
- I might.
Stephanie's friend 1
We can go to the bathroom...
indistinct conversation
♪♪♪
door bangs in distance
whimpers
♪♪♪
Hey! No running in the hallways!
Jonathan, get back here!
door closes
principal Oh, my God.
- school bell ringing
- indistinct chatter
Happy Halloween, my pretty.
chuckles
- Little early for chocolate, no?
- Mm.
You're talking to someone
who eats Count Chocula
on a regular basis.
Can we not talk about cereal?
Please?
Okay.
Someone's in a mood
this morning.
Sorry.
Barely slept last night.
Let me guess.
You were up until 4:00
in the morning,
working
on that Halloween costume again.
Actually, it was more like 6:00.
Did you guys hear
about Monica Brown this morning?
Ugh! That bitchy talk show host?
Yeah, that bitchy talk show host
totally got her face torn off.
- Allie What?
- Brooke chuckling
Brooke Okay, get this.
So, she had that Miles County
survivor on.
Do you remember the one
who was in the coma
and her face was all mutilated?
What's her name?
It was like, I don't know,
Victoria or something.
- Victoria Heyes?
- Brooke Yes.
She had a meltdown
on the show, right?
And then backstage,
she went full-on psycho,
and mauled Monica Brown
with her bare hands.
- No way.
- Oh, my God.
Is she dead?
I mean, if she's lucky.
What? You ever see photos
of those transplant faces,
looking like Mr. Potato Head?
- Fuck that shit.
- God, is it really that bad?
Well, I haven't seen photos.
But from what I hear,
she kinda looks like
the inside of my cookie.
Her eyes are all gouged out.
And her nose was like
falling off of her face.
Oh, my God.
And I heard that her cheek
like a little bit, was found
at the bottom
of Victoria Heyes' shoe.
- breathes heavily
- You okay?
Sienna?
pants
Hey, you all right?
Brooke I really didn't mean
to freak you out
with that Monica Brown shit.
- I'm so sorry.
- No.
- Brooke You okay?
- I'm okay, I'm okay. I'm fine.
inhales sharply I just...
I just need a second I think.
breathing deeply
Hi. Excuse me.
Can you mind your own business,
please?
Thank you.
My God.
Sienna, talk to me.
What's going on?
We had... we had a fire
last night.
- What? Where?
- Sienna My room.
I must've fallen asleep
with the candles burning.
- It was pretty bad.
- Okay. How bad is "pretty bad"?
Like flames touching
the ceiling,
entire house
could have burned down bad.
- Jesus. Is everyone okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
No, my mom
put the flames out in time.
Wow. Fucking Barbara
to the rescue.
I swear
that woman's a superhero.
- Was she pissed?
- Livid.
Berated me for a good hour
and a half this morning.
Brooke I mean,
that's not so bad.
I mean, you did almost torch
the whole family
in their sleep.
Look. The important thing
is that nobody got hurt. Right?
Seriously, in a few weeks,
you'll be laughing
- about the whole thing.
- More like months.
- Okay. A couple months.
- Probably a year.
It wasn't just the fire.
inhales shakily
It...
Something really strange
happened last night.
What?
Nothing. Nothing. I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, no, come on. Um...
Let's... let's go back.
Now, that my food
is probably ice cold.
You want a piece
of my Monica Brown cookie?
- Brooke.
- Sorry.
Sienna chuckles I hate you.
Brooke laughs
Barbara Thank you, Officer.
I'm so sorry
to cause you trouble.
No problem.
Have a nice day, ma'am.
You, too.
- Get to your room.
- But mom, I...
Barbara Go to your room.
I don't wanna hear
another word out of you
until I say so.
sighs
creature laughing wickedly
I can't believe I'm reduced
to a pair
of cheap store-bought wings.
You think these are too small?
How big do you want 'em?
You're gonna be knocking
over people's drinks
and shit all night.
I think they're cute.
Well, they're not terrible.
You don't really have a choice.
sighs Ugh, it's my mom.
Where did you tell your mother
we were going tonight?
Megan Melanie's Halloween party.
chuckles softly
Okay. I'll catch you out front.
Okay.
Hey, Mom.
laughter in background
indistinct chatter
Allie Good.
No, I'm just in town
with Sienna.
What time are you gonna be home?
Because...
grunts Sorry.
I'm sorry. chuckles
Nice.
Nothing. I just ran into a man
wearing terrifying
clown costume.
♪♪♪
Sienna breathes shakily
creature laughing wickedly
♪♪♪
shop owner
Can I help you find anything?
Need any help?
Uh, find everything okay?
Yeah. Mm hmm.
I'm gonna need to scan those.
Oh. Um, right. Sorry.
It's all good.
Okay. That'll be 32.25.
Yeah, um...
I think
I left my bag downstairs.
inhales shakily
glasses jiggling
whirring
blowing horn
Sir.
If you're gonna put that
in your mouth,
you gotta pay for it.
Here you go.
Thanks.
You know what?
I'm gonna go get you a big bag.
Oh, no, no. I... I really...
- I don't... I don't need it.
- shop owner No, no, it's fine.
I got 'em right back here.
Okay.
breathes shakily
Please don't.
- honks
- gasps
honking
Stop. Please stop! Please!
shop owner Hey, buddy?
You wanna quit causin' trouble?
- Thank you.
- Happy Halloween.
- Sienna You, too.
Yo, we closin' up, man.
Can I help you find something?
8.99.
chain rattles
Are you serious right now?
Yo, can you pay for that or not?
Sir, what are you doing?
All right. Sir, you know what?
I'm gonna call the police.
Hey! Did you hear what I said?
Get the hell outta here
before I fuck you up.
- shatters
- groans
grunts
That's fucking crazy.
Sienna I'm telling you
it was him, Allie.
Right down
to the little black dot
on the tip of his nose.
grunts, groans
Sienna, you said it yourself.
I mean,
there are gonna be hundreds
of douche bags dressed up
as that psycho tonight.
Even your brother
was talking about going as him.
Not that I'm calling
your brother a douche bag.
screams, sobs
Allie It's just a coincidence.
Then how do you explain
the fire?
I dreamt it and it happened.
groans
Did you change medications
recently?
Jesus Christ. I'm not crazy!
Take a breath.
I... I'm just saying,
did you ever consider
the logical explanation
that maybe the fire
caused your nightmare,
not the other way around?
What?
♪♪♪
Allie I think that the fire
started while you were sleeping.
And it worked its way
into your nightmare.
I mean, your body must've felt
the flames.
You know shit like that
happens all the time.
Look, are you getting candy
or what?
I mean, what are...
What are we doing here?
Even if that is the case,
it doesn't explain
how the fire started.
Come on, honey.
Oh, my. They're closed.
- Wow.
- Oh.
shopping mother's son
Look at that, Mom.
shopping mother
Yeah, that's wonderful, honey.
Cool.
All right. Let's go. Let's go.
You're just gonna stay here
the whole time.
Come on.
We don't go direct
with our insurers.
Okay, but let me get
your zip code.
I'm gonna find a broker
in your area.
What are you doing home?
He's here, Sienna.
Who?
The Miles County clown.
What are you talking about?
I saw him today in my school.
Just like in the police photos.
Slow down.
It was him.
Something really bad
is gonna happen tonight.
Is that Daddy's sketchbook?
Look here.
How long have you had this?
Jonathan, answer me.
You know how long
we've been looking for this.
Read this.
I saw her today.
This exact girl.
Only she didn't look human.
There's some kinda connection
between her, the old carnival,
and the Miles County clown.
Something really
bad's gonna happen tonight.
I know it.
Did you put these in here?
No.
But look at this.
It's him!
Sienna Daddy drew this?
That's not all.
What if you're connected, too?
What?
Jonathan, you're acting crazy.
You're acting crazy. Okay?
Jonathan He created
this character for you.
He gave you that sword
right before he died.
It's like he saw this coming.
Daddy drew a lot of things
for me.
He bought me tons of shit.
Seriously,
what's wrong with you?
- Do you even hear yourself?
- What's going on in here?
Did he show you this?
She doesn't care.
She's just pissed,
'cause I might get suspended.
Suspended. For what?
Oh, you didn't tell her?
Your brother brought
a dead animal to school
this morning.
- What?
- Barbara Yeah.
A dead animal.
Can you believe it?
laughs
He vandalized the halls.
I almost
had a fucking heart attack
when they told me.
It wasn't me.
It was the clown.
The little girl brought it in.
I don't wanna hear another word
about this goddamn clown.
He was covered in blood
on his shirt and his hands
when he got here.
The principal literally
caught you red-handed.
That's 'cause he threw it at me.
chuckles
I should've listened to you.
You have been telling me
over and over again
about this kid.
I'm calling Dr. Schiffrin
on Monday.
I'm putting a stop to this now.
And put your goddamn bowl
in the sink.
I'm not telling you again.
It was him.
You gotta believe me.
Jonathan.
sighs It was...
It was probably just some kids
at school, messing around.
It's the one-year anniversary.
I mean, I already saw some...
jerk wearing that same costume
in Abracadabra an hour ago.
What about these drawings
and these articles then?
We both know what happened
to Daddy.
Okay, none of this
was his fault.
And all of these ugly things
in here,
that's not who he was.
He loved you...
very much.
It's gonna be okay.
- Stay home tonight.
- Jonathan.
Please. I'm begging you.
- Nothing's gonna happen.
- Jonathan Fine.
Just don't act surprised
when a bunch of people
get killed tonight.
Have you ever...
I believe him.
About what?
I don't think he vandalized
the school.
Barbara Oh, now,
you believe him?
Yesterday,
he was the Zodiac Killer.
What's changed?
door bell rings
Get the door.
news anchor Restaurants
on the East Coast
have recalled romaine lettuce
due to a recent
E. Coli outbreak.
At least 12 people
have been hospitalized
and two
are in critical condition.
- Hi.
- Trick or treat!
Happy Halloween.
Oh, I love your makeup.
Oh, she did it all herself.
Wow! Great job.
What do you say?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Bye.
♪♪♪
door bell rings
chuckles
Ah, aren't you a little old
to be trick or treating?
Wait a minute.
Aren't you that guy
from the costume shop?
You are?
What are you doing here? Oh.
Seriously, do you live
around here or something?
Hmm.
You're really weird,
you know that?
Yeah. Look, I get it, dude.
The whole creepy, silent
mime gimmick.
I mean, it's very effective.
And the blood
is a nice touch also.
Yeah.
I can't give you anything.
No, I'm sorry. Really.
No... no candy for grownups.
Come on.
door bell rings
- Go away.
- knocking on door
Seriously, asshole,
go bother somebody else.
banging on door
sighs
Are you kidding me right now?
I said, get out of here.
I mean it.
Wait. So, if I give you candy,
you'll leave?
Fine.
Here. Happy Halloween.
♪♪♪
children chattering
in distance
cellphone ringing
news anchor In other news,
talk show provocateur,
Monica Brown
is still in critical condition
this evening,
following a violent attack
which took place
at KLA Studios earlier today.
The TV host
was violently assaulted
in her dressing room
after a live broadcast
with guest Victoria Heyes.
Heyes is the sole survivor
of the Miles County massacre
of 2017, which left
eight people dead
and Heyes in critical condition.
The 20-year-old was arrested
at the crime scene,
and taken into custody
by authorities.
The interview sparked
controversy
upon its announcement
given Brown's
exploitative tendencies.
Heyes was released
from St. Michael's Hospital
yesterday evening
after months of rehabilitation
and psychoanalysis.
Like you, Sienna.
Halloween is officially here,
and thousands are lining up
for the parade
in New York City's East Village.
Weather conditions are expected
to be cold and rainy,
so dress warm
if you're planning to attend.
breathes heavily
breathes deeply
♪♪♪
thunder rumbles
electricity crackling
rain pattering
glass shatter in distance
♪♪♪
cellphone ringing
gasps
♪♪♪
No! No!
screams
groans, screams
No!
screams, groans
screams
No!
screaming continues
No, no!
screams
screams, groans
whimpers, groans
groans
cellphone ringing
grunts
screaming
actress Barbara on TV Johnny!
Johhny on TV
You're still afraid.
Stop it now. I mean it.
Johhny on TV They're coming
to get you, Barbara.
Well?
actress Barbara on TV
Stop it! You're ignorant.
Johhny on TV They're coming
for you, Barbara.
It's revealing.
actress Barbara on TV
Stop it.
Three months' worth of work,
and all you can say
is it's revealing?
Your tits are practically
popping out.
They are not!
They are! Turn around.
Johhny on TV
Here he comes now.
sighs
actress Barbara on TV
Johnny!
Sienna You know
what I was making?
It's Daddy's character.
Yes, but seeing it on paper
and seeing it on your daughter
are two different things.
You look like you're going
to a strip club.
Mom, this is how people dress
on Halloween these days.
Do you have any idea
how much work
I put into this?
You did an excellent job.
But when did Halloween
become synonymous with sex?
You're such a prude.
Okay. That's my ride. Later.
Sienna.
Dad would have loved it.
Bye.
Allie's mom Allie!
sighs
Have you been handing out candy?
That bowl is still filled
to the brim.
Allie!
Oh, my God.
Allie?
Allie? Allie, answer me.
pants
Where are you?
whimpers Allie?
gasps
whimpers, screams
Oh, no! No, no! No! No!
screams
whimpers
- Mom.
- whimpers
screams
♪♪♪
indistinct chatter
What'd I tell you?
I never doubted you
for a second.
Come on. Let's go get fucked up.
bartender
What can I get you guys?
Uh, vodka and coke, please.
What do you want?
Off your phone.
Uh, rum and coke. Mixed.
Also, can we have two shots
of whiskey, please? Thank you.
Has Allie texted you back yet?
No.
Well, can you check?
Brooke Negative.
You know this isn't like her.
Brooke It's fine.
Just relax.
And have a good time
for once in your life, okay?
Maybe if I just text her mom,
she will get back to me.
No. Off your phone.
- Phone down.
- Okay!
- Look, we're gonna have fun.
- Mm hmm.
- Stress-free environment.
- Yep.
- Take this.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- All right. Thank you.
Will you excuse me? Sorry.
- Oops!
- chuckles
- Let's go.
- Okay. Yep.
Okay.
To a great night with my girls.
- To a great night.
- Happy Halloween.
Sienna Oh, God. coughing
Oh, you're such an amateur.
I do not know
how you drink that shit.
Well, chase it.
- Jeff screams
- Brooke shrieks
Oh, you asshole!
Jeff Happy Halloween, baby.
smooches
You look hot.
Oh, yeah? You like my hair?
Jeff I do.
How long did that take?
Brooke You don't wanna know.
Ooh!
Yeah, nice shirt.
Wishful thinking.
I bet!
- grunts
- Brooke laughing
Oh, Jeff.
This is my best friend Sienna.
Hi.
Wow. That is a badass outfit.
- chuckles
- Thank you.
This girl
is unbelievably talented.
You have no idea.
She made this whole thing
herself, head to toe.
What did it take you,
like five months?
No. It didn't take that long.
Brooke Yes, it did.
You have no idea.
It took forever.
You are unbelievable.
You know, honestly,
I feel upstaged.
- chuckles
- Sienna Okay.
Could you guys please stop?
You're making me feel
a little self-conscious, so...
Brooke Oh. Well, a couple
of shots will help that.
- Oh! Shots! Shots! Shots! Shots!
- Shots! Shots! Shots! Shots!
No. No, no, no.
I cannot drink anymore tonight.
My mom will get so pissed
if I get fucked up.
No, she won't!
Your mom's gonna be asleep
in two hours.
I can't do it.
Okay, fine.
Take a picture of us.
camera shutter clicking
Okay.
Ooh, let's dance!
♪♪♪
children giggling
- Trick or treat!
- children gasp
- Kids, look how cool!
Oh my God!
So cool.
Ew. Why is mine so sticky?
trick or treat woman Don't
worry. It's just fake blood.
Just put it in the bag.
Ooh, I like it.
trick or treat boy 1 Ew.
children giggling
trick or treat woman
All right, thank you!
- Thank you!
Let's go. Happy Halloween!
- Happy Halloween!
♪♪♪
What are you doing in here?
You wanna watch a movie?
There is a lot of candy
leftover downstairs.
Come on.
I'll let you stay up late.
Go away.
Jonathan.
I am sorry that your plans
were ruined tonight.
I really am.
But you should've thought
about this
before you pulled that shit
in school today.
I mean, enough's enough.
I told you the truth.
- I'm not doing this again.
- Jonathan It wasn't me!
Well, if it wasn't you,
then I sincerely apologize.
But I just don't believe you
anymore.
What about this?
Again with this fucking book!
Why was Daddy collecting
these news articles?
"Slain girl found at carnival."
And this?
Look at these drawings!
This isn't like Daddy!
He was sick.
Why can't you understand?
He didn't know who he was,
or what he was doing
half the time.
And this.
This bullshit is nothing
but a fucking reminder.
No!
I want this out of my house.
You're such a bitch!
Don't you ever say that
to me again!
whimpers
Jonathan.
Jonathan, you get back here.
Jonathan!
Jonathan panting
indistinct chatter
♪♪♪
I'll be right back.
Wait. Where are you going?
I'm gonna grab a drink.
chuckles
club announcement
in background
- Yo, can I get a selfie?
- Sure.
Fuck, yeah, girl!
♪♪♪
breathes shakily
sobs
gasps
What?
sputters
Oh, my God.
indistinct chatter
indistinct announcement
Brooke Sienna!
- Hey!
- Hi!
both laugh
I missed you, girl.
laughs
Hi.
No, wait.
- Feel this.
- Oh.
Oh.
indistinct speech
laughs
- Oh, my God.
- No, no. Wait.
You don't understand.
I want it.
- I know.
- I wanna like...
live in it, you know?
laughs
- How are you feeling?
- Good.
Yeah?
- So good actually!
- Okay.
I feel like...
that shot's really starting
to hit me.
Well, whiskey will do that
to you.
- I needed this.
- Yeah.
You were right.
- You were so right.
- Yeah.
I needed to just, like get out,
and stop thinking,
worrying about every little
thing in my life.
Like... like this costume.
Yeah.
Sienna I mean,
it should be a happy thing.
- Yeah.
- Sienna You know?
It reminds me of my Dad.
He used to...
He used to draw this character
for me when I was a little girl.
He used to tell me
I was gonna grow up
to be like her one day.
And I really believed it.
Well, look at you now!
You are her.
I am nothing like her.
- scoffs
- Sienna I'm not courageous.
I'm not brave.
I mean, I literally
had a panic attack today
in school in front of everybody.
I put molly in your drink.
- chuckling
- Sienna What?
I did. I put a half a tablet
in your drink,
the other half in mine.
Not even really,
it was kind of nothing.
But it's fine,
'cause I'm also on it.
So, we're totally fine.
You and me.
And that is why you feel
like you're on molly.
chuckles
Brooke 'Cause you are.
Right now.
You fuckin' bitch! laughs
Brooke What the...
- That is so messed up!
- Brooke I did it.
I made you feel better,
didn't I?
I'm fucking pissed.
No, don't be pissed.
You're smiling.
You can't be pissed.
No, bitch. I'm not smiling.
laughs You're totally smiling.
laughs
So, we gotta go back out,
and we gotta dance.
pants
♪♪♪
horn honks
children screaming
radio static
indistinct radio chatter
horn honks
Barbara over radio Jonathan.
Jonathan, please get back.
Jonathan!
indistinct chatter
Brooke laughing
Oh, shit.
What?
My mom called me like six times.
- Ooh. Do not call her back.
- I'm gonna see...
- Don't call her back!
- Shh, shh, shh!
Sienna. Sienna.
- Sienna.
- Hey!
- Stop it.
- Barbara He's dead, Sienna!
speaking indistinctly
Wait. What?
Cut the call.
Barbara speaking indistinctly
over cellphone
Wait, mom.
Mom, I can't hear you.
Just...
sighs
Um, sorry.
Um, what'd you say?
Barbara He covered the entire
fucking car with shaving cream!
Sienna What?
Yeah! The whole fucking thing.
Shaving cream, toilet paper,
eggs. He's dead!
He...
Jonathan wouldn't do that.
Yeah. He didn't do this.
Just like he didn't vandalize
the school this morning!
Look at this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This... this is crazy now.
He's going to that psychiatrist
immediately.
I cannot deal with him anymore.
Sienna Really, mom?
You're gonna send him
to a shrink
because what, he put like
a little bit of shaving cream
on your car?
I'm glad you think
this is funny, Sienna.
Sienna
It's just shaving cream.
It's not like he took
a baseball bat
to your windshield.
It's Halloween. I mean...
Are you drunk?
- No.
- Barbara Yes, you are.
I can hear it in your voice.
How many drinks have you had?
I... I thought we were talking
about Jonathan.
Barbara Sienna, so help me,
if you come home plastered
on top of everything else
- I'm dealing with tonight...
- Sienna No.
I swear to God, I'm not drunk.
I'll even take a breathalyzer.
You're killing me.
You know that?
You and your brother both,
I have had it.
I love you.
Yeah, Sienna, I am warning you.
Sienna No. Really, mom.
I... I love you. I...
I don't say it enough.
I love you, too.
Go and enjoy your party.
I'm... I'm sorry to bother you.
And listen.
Everything will be okay
with Jonathan.
I promise.
Just remember what I said.
Be careful getting home,
all right?
Sienna I will. Bye.
DJ over mic Happy Halloween,
motherfuckers!
crowd cheering
- How'd it go?
- Fine.
All right.
Let me give you a little
molly etiquette here.
Rule number one, you never
ever call your mother
when you're rolling on molly.
Okay? Your mother, never.
All right?
Rule number two,
you don't fucking let it go
to waste. Come on.
♪♪♪
sighs
Barbara Look at this.
Did he really think
he was gonna get away with this?
He is in for a rude awakening.
Things are gonna change.
- gasps
- gunshot
indistinct chatter
♪ Pain, always pain ♪
♪ Pain makes the rhythm,
makes the rhythm ♪
♪ Makes the rhythm ♪
♪ Pain, pain makes the rhythm,
makes the rhythm ♪
♪ Makes the rhythm, pain ♪
Do you see that?
There. There.
That little girl.
What is she saying?
What are you talking about?
I... I... I swear to God.
She was right there.
I... I saw her.
She was...
She was... she was right there.
Okay. Come on.
It's bathroom time.
whimpers, screams
Brooke Sienna? Sienna?
Okay. Sienna, look at me.
It's okay. Shh, shh, shh.
Sienna, breathe. Breathe.
Breathe. You're gonna be okay.
Sienna breathes heavily
Sienna?
♪♪♪
Mom!
bell dinging
breathes heavily
whimpers
screams
Help me!
grunts
gasps, screams
whimpers, screams
grunts
I'm sorry you had to leave.
It's no problem.
You okay?
Sienna, what the fuck was that
back there?
Sienna I'm fine.
Are you fucking kidding me?
No! You're not fine.
You are so completely far
from fine right now.
You're just totally freaked out.
Gee, Brooke. I wonder why.
Oh! Don't blame this on me.
I'm on the same shit as you
right now, okay?
- I'm not freaking out.
- Jeff Whoa!
What are we talking
about here? What shit?
I put a pinch of molly
in her drink.
It was nothing.
- Sienna Plus Xanax.
- Jeff What?
I did not give you Xanax.
No, she was already on Xanax,
which I didn't know about, okay?
Let's make that perfectly
fucking clear.
You could've fucking killed me.
Brooke I was trying to do
something nice for you.
Jesus Christ!
You're like Ms. Morbid
all the time.
Thanks.
Just take me home.
Sienna, whatever happened
back there was not normal.
Okay?
You could have had like
a brain aneurysm,
or seizure, or something.
What if it happens again?
Wanna take her
to the emergency room?
I... I just...
I just wanna go home.
Just take me home.
cellphone ringing
If that's your mother,
do not answer it.
Hello.
demon girl Sienna,
I'm in trouble.
Oh, you think?
Mommy told me
what you did to her car,
you little asshole.
I mean, really?
demon girl No.
I need your help.
You have to come get me.
What do you mean?
Sienna What's wrong?
Where are you?
I'm at the old carnival.
Eric and Sean left me here.
I'm all alone.
Sienna What's wrong with you?
demon girl Please.
I'm really scared.
I don't know what else to do.
I can't call mommy.
Okay. Um, all right. Calm down.
I'll come get you, okay?
demon girl
Hurry, my phone is dying.
Sienna All right. Just wait
by the main entrance, okay?
Jonathan? Jonathan? J...
sighs Goddammit.
He's bullshitting you.
No, he's not.
Brooke Yes, he is.
It's Halloween.
Are you really telling me
right now
that it's beneath your brother
to do something twisted
like this?
Come on. The old carnival.
No. I... I know
when Jonathan's lying. Okay?
I... I could hear it
in his voice.
Something's... something's wrong.
Sienna! Like, dude...
It's only a few miles from here.
This is so stupid.
Great. Fine. Whatever.
I don't care.
It's not like this night
can get any worse.
♪♪♪
Well, where is he?
Sienna I told him
to wait in front.
- How old's your brother?
- 12.
Brooke Even the fact that
he's out here right now
should be telling you something.
Didn't like a little girl
get murdered out here
a couple years ago?
I'm gonna go look for him.
What? coughs
Sienna? Get back in the car.
Sienna!
sighs
She's crazy.
pants
Jonathan!
Maybe we should go with her.
Fuck that.
I guarantee you,
her brother's just gonna scare
the shit out of her.
He's turned
into a complete psycho
ever since his father
killed himself.
Ever since what?
Brooke No joke.
He had like
this giant brain tumor
that I don't know,
it just made him do
all this fucked-up shit.
And he was like seeing things.
And he got really abusive
towards the end.
Especially towards Sienna.
And then one day,
he drank a whole bottle of Jack,
and he got in his car,
and he drove straight
into one of those
transformer things.
And the car caught fire,
and he got trapped in the wreck.
And he burned to death.
You could hear him screaming
from a mile away.
Jeff Well, I've only known
your friend for a few hours,
but that explains a lot.
Brooke Yeah.
All things considered,
I think she's doing pretty well.
wind howling
pants
♪♪♪
Come on, answer me.
cellphone ringing
Where are you?
I'm searching
all over the place.
demon girl Help.
speaking indistinctly
Jonathan, can you hear me?
demon speaking indistinctly
over cellphone
I can't...
Listen.
I'm gonna wait for you
by the merry-go-round, okay?
demon speaking indistinctly
over cellphone
Did you hear what I said?
Meet me at the merry-go-round.
Hello?
Text me back.
♪♪♪
girl laughing wickedly
in distance
children wailing in distance
- What is that?
- Jeff chuckles
A little pick-me-up.
- Wow, Jeff. Okay.
- chuckles
Don't let Sienna see that shit.
Well, we'll just have to do it
before she comes back.
I'm not doing that.
You ever try it?
- Yeah. Once. I didn't like it.
- Jeff scoffs
Oh sure, impossible. Come on.
This will put us
right back in the club.
snorts, coughs
Fuck.
Trust me.
- Okay.
- chuckles
All right. Fuck it.
Um...
okay.
- snorts Ugh!
- chuckles
- groans
- Jeff chuckling
chuckles, sniffs
That tastes weird.
chuckles, smooches
♪♪♪
Sienna Jonathan?
monster growls
exclaims
♪♪♪
- What's wrong?
- groans, snorts
Where the hell is she?
Who cares?
chuckles
moans Wait.
All right.
Look, but, like, seriously,
what time did she leave?
- Well, who cares?
- Okay.
Okay. I'm gonna call her
really fast, okay?
- Just really quick.
- scoffs softly
Where are you going?
I have to go pee-pee.
You wanna hold it?
Ew. Leave.
door shuts
dialtone ringing
Sienna on voicemail
Hi. It's Sienna.
Leave a message,
and I'll get back to you.
operator
The mailbox is full...
Unbelievable.
operator ...and cannot accept
any messages at this time.
- Goodbye...
- gasps
screams, laughs
laughs Asshole!
That's twice!
snarls
Oh, it's so funny.
laughs mockingly
Yeah, you're so funny.
You know
what's actually really funny?
- Mm.
smacks lips
Let me see here. Oh.
- gasps
- Oh, hey. Don't fuck her up.
- Come on.
- Oh.
- Oh, you better say sorry.
- I'm sorry.
And I don't really know
if you can snort this
out of an ashtray.
It'd be kinda hard to snort
out of.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I won't do it again, I promise.
Are you actually sorry?
Hey.
- grunts
- Okay, fine.
- Jeff chuckles
- But you're a jerk.
chuckles
groans
Jeff?
Oh, my God!
screams
groans, screams
No! No, no! whimpers
screams, groans
screams
No! No, no!
screams, groans
screams
Oh, my God!
- engine starts
- screams
horn honking
screams, groans
screams
Oh, my God!
grunts
groans, sobs
groans, screams
screams Sienna!
screams
Brooke Oh, God!
Sienna!
screams
Brooke Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
screams, groans
grunts
sobs
pants, groans
screams
children wailing
Sienna Jonathan!
elephant trumpeting
lion roars
Can you hear me?
evil laughter
sobs
groans
Somebody, please!
sobs
Help me!
screams
pants
Sienna!
sobs, groans
Help!
sobs
Brooke!
pants
speaks indistinctly
grunts, pants
- roars
- screams
grunts, sobs
pants
sobs
bees buzzing
Oh, my God! No, please! No!
groans, screams
pants, sobs
Stay back. Stop. Please stop.
Stay away from me!
sobs Don't, please!
Wait, wait.
No! Please, please stop! No!
No, no, no, no!
Stop it. Stop. No. Please!
sobs, pants
Brooke No. Stay back.
Don't... don't come near me.
Please don't.
No, no, no!
groans, screams
sobs, screams
- thuds
- screams
screams
sobs
chokes
♪♪♪
heart beating
pants, gasps
Brooke!
pants
gasps, sobs
whimpers
Sienna Brooke.
sobs
gasps, pants
♪♪♪
gasps
breathes heavily
Jonathan?
Jonathan, run!
grunts
groans
roars
grunts, groans
whimpers, groans
grunts
chokes
♪♪♪
groans
Sienna whimpers
groans, pants
groans
pants
boards creaking
gasps, grunts
groans
grunts
pants, grunts
pants
Come on.
This way.
groans
♪♪♪
Sienna.
groans
- You're hurt bad.
- whimpers
I'm all right. I'm all right.
Let me... let me see you.
sniffles Are you okay?
Oh, my God.
You were right.
You were right about everything.
I was right about you, too.
About what?
They used me to get you here.
They need you in this place
for a reason.
What are you saying that?
It's what Daddy saw.
I think you're the only one
who can stop him.
Why?
I don't know.
Well, we gotta find a way
out of here.
pants
Okay, come on.
♪♪♪
Wait here.
breathes shakily
♪♪♪
Jonathan screams
grunts, groans
pants
grunts
thuds
Jonathan screams
sobs, groans
groans
Jonathan.
grunts
Sucker!
grunts, pants
grunts
breathes heavily
thuds
pants
Jonathan...
grunts
groans, chokes
Sienna grunts, chokes
panting
- gunshot
- thuds
Jonathan Sienna!
Sienna. Sienna, wake up.
Stay with me. Stay with me!
Please don't go.
Sienna.
Please don't leave me.
demon Sienna. Baby, wake up.
Mom?
Sweetie, it's okay.
You're safe.
Mom.
sobs softly
Oh, shh, shh, shh.
Everything's gonna be okay.
sobs
I thought
I was never gonna see you again.
Oh.
Jonathan told you...
didn't he?
What?
Jonathan Sienna!
Get away from her!
That's not Mommy!
sobs
pants
groaning
Jonathan!
groans, pants
No! No!
grunts
No! No, you tucker!
grunts, chokes
spits, pants
Fuck you.
spits
gasps
coughs
groans, coughs
indistinct voices
grunts
groans
screams
grunts
♪♪♪
host Speaking
of some prizes, kids,
we have a very special guest
with us today.
grunts
Let me out!
crowd laughing
screams
♪♪♪
- ♪ Come on by the clown café ♪
♪ The club
is downright gruesome ♪
♪ But your appetite so big ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
food's a little funny ♪
♪ Food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
screams
♪♪♪
screams, grunts
Sienna!
zapping
grunts, groans
screams
pants
grunts
screams
pants
Sienna.
sobs
You got him.
It's over now. Okay?
Okay.
sobs
pants
whimpers
breathes heavily
♪♪♪
thunder rumbling
Victoria coughs
retches
Please tell me
this is pumpkin spice.
Not a chance in hell.
chuckles softly
What is this?
security head Zombie platter.
My wife made it.
That's disgusting.
Creative, but disgusting.
security head I wouldn't say
that before you try it.
It's pretty tasty.
Mm. No, thanks.
As appealing
as that brain looks,
I don't really have the stomach
for it right now.
Everything okay?
I've been tending to our
celebrity patient all day.
Is that bad?
Let's just say her face
doesn't stimulate
one's appetite.
- What's she like?
- Tame.
Pretty cooperative actually.
It's kind of hard to imagine
she ripped that woman to pieces.
sobs
screams
Pass me one of those eyeballs.
Huh?
And, uh, put some
of that brain jelly on it, too.
And, Lola, don't be stingy.
Oh. There it is. There you go.
Little more.
Thank you.
Diet starts tomorrow, so...
screams
security officer slurps
security head Mm!
Mm.
hums
- What is that?
- Hmm?
security head That song
you're singing, what is it?
Oh.
I have no idea actually.
Victoria's been singing it
all day.
I can't get it out of my head.
Huh.
Victoria
♪ Come on by the clown café ♪
grunting, groaning
Victoria You fucking cunt!
laughing hysterically
Victoria
♪ Come on by the clown café ♪
Cunt! Cunt! Cunt! Cunt! Cunt!
munching
gasps
screams
Oh, God.
laughs
whimpers
laughs maniacally
screams, sobs
♪ Drop on by the clown café
your favorite meals on wheels ♪
♪ The menu is disgusting
and it's full of special deals ♪
♪ Nothing here is good for you
so grab yourself a tray ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪ Drop on by the clown café ♪
♪ Double up your order quick
before it runs away ♪
♪ 'Cause food's a little funny
at the clown café ♪
♪♪♪