Subtitle by Verdike
(szaszcsaba1968@gmail.com)
LONDON
- You like it?
- All right.
I need to go. My dad's here.
- I'll see you soon.
- Yeah.
This is the dress.
Do you like it?
We've got to hurry. Everyone's going.
There's only two left in my size.
Come on, Dad, let's go.
- When do I meet him?
- His name's Chappy.
- On the football team and very--
- Chubby?
Chappy.
You'll meet when he picks me up
for the dance.
- Not before?
- Dad, you really need to go faster.
- Will he drive you to the dance?
- He's rented a limo.
So he won't drive you?
Limos come with drivers.
So stop worrying.
It's a nice dress.
You'll be very pretty.
I want you to like it.
- I'm getting out.
- No-no-no. Wait until I park.
Everyone's already inside.
Fan, careful crossing the street.
You stupid--
- Metro desk, Ian Wood.
- Listen carefully.
An action wing of the Authentic UDI
has just exploded a bomb...
at the OBT Bank in Knightsbridge.
The code word is "Phoenix'.
Britain's banks are now
targets for the Authentic UDI.
The bombings will continue
as long as...
Britain's financial criminal
institutions persist in their support...
of the illegal occupation
of Northern Ireland.
A bomb just went off,
an OBT Bank in Knightsbridge.
A group called The Authentic UDI just
phoned it in. They're claiming credit.
Christ. There goes the Peace Accord
back in the shit.
... about the number
police officials
have current estimates
on the dead and injured.
but there have been
no further updates.
As you can see, it's a highly
fluid situation.
This is a major incident that they're
treating as a possible terrorist attack.
The bomb went off at exactly
4:15 GMT in Knightsbridge.
One theory on the cause
of the blast...
was that it may have been
a gasoline explosion underground.
How many?
How manny I get?
12 dead so far, three times
as many injured.
The explosion was centered at the
OBT Bank Branch in Knightsbridge.
There was no warning and police
were taken completely by surprise.
Fuck warnings.
That'll teach 'em.
Any problems?
- No.
- We should be moving.
That's the normal procedure.
Every cop, hotel, and landlady in London
is now looking for the Irishman.
This place is safe,
so long as we stay put.
BELFAST, NORTHERN IRELAND
Could I go to jail
if I murdered your phone?
Destruction of government
property?
Absolutely.
Too bad. What's the time?
Almost ten. Ten more minutes.
I'll miss my flight.
Let's stay here, door locked,
blinds down...
room service for a week.
Sound good?
And your work, Deputy Minister?
An acute case of food poisoning.
You need to work on your
excuses, darling.
Jesus Christ! There's been
a bombing in London.
Scores dead and injured.
Yes? - Jesus, Liam,
half the world's trying
to find you.
- Do you even know what's happened?
- Yes, yes, yes, I heard.
I've been trying you
for hours. Where've you been?
- Meetings. - Meetings?
- Aye.
And last night?
You didn't come home.
I was worried.
Came in late, left early.
Lot of work to catch up on.
- But the guest room wasn't slept in.
- Who said I slept?
Oh, cut the crap, Liam.
You didn't come home,
plain and simple.
And what if I didn't?
Look, I've got a lot
to deal with, okay?
So don't wait up,
and don't be worried.
Sunday is the 20th anniversary
of my brother's death.
Saint Mary's is dedicating
a mass to him, so--
I'll have Beth put it in the
calendar, okay? We'll talk later.
Oh, Jesus.
Yes, I understand the need
for swift action.
But until we can identify the threat,
there's not much we can do.
Well, you'll have finger on the pulse
over there, Liam. We're depending on you.
Anything you can provide, anything
at all, would be a tremendous help.
I'm meeting the Council now.
I'll shake the trees as hard
as I can and see what falls.
But there are new upstarts in the ranks,
pressing for the way things were.
I could use something now.
And you know what I'm refering to.
The Royal Pardons.
I remember your list,
the 40 „On-the-Runs”.
- Are we really back to that?
- My Cousin's on that list.
He hasn't even been convicted
of any paramilitary offenses.
These people are suspects
in many things, including murder.
These people are critical
to holding the peace together now.
A few letters of pardon
would be a small gesture.
We keep it quiet.
But knowing it's been considered
gives me the leeway...
to press certain men
for something in return.
As Irish Deputy Minister you have served
the British government honorably...
which hasn't always been easy.
But appeasement is a dangerous thing.
These are longstanding issues.
That if adressed now
would smack of appeasement.
I need something, Kate.
The newer members haven't lived
the bloodshed and are easily swayed.
I'm trying to hold this together.
A gesture is all.
It would make a difference.
I'll consider it.
But I want something first.
Something real.
Understood.
Hello?
We're closed.
We open at 12.
We're looking for the owner,
a Mr. Quin Minh?
Quan.
Upstairs.
They were found on site,
not far from your daughter's body.
Can you positively
identify them as hers?
Who did this?
As of now, Sir, we don't know,
but we're going to find out.
Why my daughter?
Is there someone we can call
to come and be with you, Mr. Quan?
I have no more family.
- These bombers, will you catch them?
- Yes.
- Will they be punished?
- Yes, they certainly will.
We'll let ourselves out.
- Good morning, Hugh. Thanks for coming.
- Been a long time, Liam.
It's been a long time, indeed.
Come, take a chair there.
- All right, Hugh?
- Now that we're all here,
does anyone know
who the Authentic UDI is?
Are they even part of the UDI?
Some new upstarts or
something else entirely?
They're trying to undermine everything
we've achieved over the last 19 years.
Well I won't have it.
They don't have the support of
the people who said no to the violence.
Our mandate's to uphold that choice
and maintain the Peace Accord,
no matter what.
Are we in agreement?
There's a lot of support for their
actions amongst the younger ranks.
Hotheads. Hotheads who don't
remember or know any better.
- You were one of those
hotheads, Liam. - Aye.
Long ago, when it was the only way.
And what did it give us?
More graves than
I care to remember.
This bombing rivals Omagh
with it's civilian deaths.
It's unacceptable,
anytime, anywhere!
And do you think the bombers
come from our ranks?
The Brits ID'd the explosive.
Czech-made Semtex
from our dumps.
They also used
our code word,
which means they have
a contact in our command.
Maybe someone in this room.
They're trying to divide us, put
the Brits back on the streets again,
stir up the Troubles all over
again. Well I won't have it!
I want a complete check of all
the arms dumps here and abroad,
everything verified, guns,
Semtex, the whole fuckin' lot.
- Jesus, you can't be serious.
- Never been more so, Patty.
We check 'em and if
something's missing,
we trace it back to those
who knew the location.
And then we deal with this
internally.
I want a complete list
of all the stocks within the week,
along with their locations and
everyone who knows where they are.
And no fuckin' exceptions!
SO15 COUNTER TERRORISM COMMAND,
LONDON
Show me.
We backtracked 47 minutes.
Clearly anticipated the CCTV.
He circled London for quite some time
prior to the bombing.
Now, this is the firstCC feed
we have on him.
Heading southbound on the A413
near Wendover at 10:53 AM.
We retrieved the serial number
from the bike's frame.
It was reported stolen in Reading
the night before.
The license plates were also stolen
from another bike in Reading.
What about phone calls?
Assuming that the bomb
was phone-activated,
we've dumped the five closest
towers to the blast zone,
trying to ID any call terminating
at the time of the incident.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Yup.
For you.
- Bromley.
- He's here again, Sir.
- The Chinese man.
- What?
The Chinaman.
It's five days in a row, now.
- Christ. Tell him I'm busy.
- I did, and he said he'd wait, again.
I assure you, this investigation
is our top priority, Mr Quan.
And we're doing all we can
and pursuing every possible lead...
to find those
who killed your daughter.
But they're a difficult
people to catch.
And it may take some time.
I need you to understand that.
You must catch these men,
Commander Bromley.
Again, it's our top priority.
20,000 pounds.
All I have for the names
of the bombers.
To be clear...
these are vicious men
who take pride in their attrocities.
Any attempt by you to contact them
is likely to end very badly.
This is our work, not yours.
You need to be patient.
How long have you been
in this country, Mr. Quan?
Since 1984. I'm a British citizen.
You were born in Guangxi, China.
Yes. I'm Chinese.
I live in Ho Chi Minh
after the war.
We escaped to Singapore.
Then we immigrated here.
You had two daughters before Fan.
Both killed during the escape.
And your wife?
Where is she now?
She died giving birth to Fan.
I'm truly sorry for your loss.
But you musn't keep coming
here on a daily basis.
It doesn't help,
and diverts time and resources
from our investigation.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Thank you for seeing me,
Commander Bromley.
After three weeks
of investigations,
there's little in the way
of solid leads that I'm aware of.
The public is looking
for reassurance.
One leading politician who
somberly may have answers...
lies uncomfortably at the
center of this storm.
We go now to an interview
I recorded earlier in Belfast...
with Deputy Minister
Liam Hennessey.
Deputy Minister Hennessey, you've
publically condemned the bombings.
What's the essential difference between
those acts you were involved in then...
and what's happened
in London recently?
Hope. We had none,
just years of vengeance.
I believe the men
behind this terrible act
never experienced
firsthand the troubles.
And for some they are more than happy
to resort to violence...
to upset the status quo.
Prepared for your signature.
They absolutely must be signed now.
What's the latest reaction
on social media?
The same as before.
Fear and anger.
- Anger directed at whom?
- From the Prime Minister on down.
CNN and the Irish Times
want interviews with you.
You can do tonight or
tomorrow morning at eight.
- Tomorrow morning by phone. What else?
- You've a call waitin' on line two.
- Waiting?
- For 30 minutes now.
A Mr Quan from London,
very insistent.
What does he want?
His daughter was killed
in the bombing.
I tried my best to console him, but
he really just wants to speak to you.
- He saw you on TV.
- Oh, Christ, Beth.
Civic duty. Take it and be done.
This is Liam Hennessey.
How may I help you?
Mr. Hennessey, tell me
who kill my daughter.
What on earth makes you think
I know who killed your daughter?
Because, you are
the First Deputy Minister
and advisor to Quinnshae,
and a former UDI member.
I am truly sad for your loss, Mr. Quan.
I have a daughter myself.
And I condemn these acts of violence,
but I can't help you.
Then please tell me someone who might
know the names of the bombers...
someone I can talk to.
I don't have any connections
to those sorts of people. I'm sorry.
I don't believe you, Mr. Hennessey.
You are a very powerful man.
Well, I work for the government
and our elected officials.
I do not work for terrorists.
Politics and terrorism are
different ends of the same snake.
Whichever end you grabe,
you still grab a snake.
It makes a great deal of difference which
end you grab, because one end will bite.
Again,
I'm sorry for your loss,
Mr. Quan. Good day.
Daughters slaughtered by Thai pirates.
An immigrant tragic story.
What are you doing?
You have to stop this.
This wasn't your fault.
I failed them.
What is this?
The restaurant is now yours.
You've been a good
friend to me, Lam.
No more of this talk.
Look at me.
I'm not going home. I'm staying
the night. I will sleep on the couch.
And on Monday I'm taking you
to see someone.
Someone who can help you.
But no more of this talk. Okay?
Quan!
I've been calling you all night.
Where were you?
What are you going to do?
When will you come back?
PORT OF LARNE,
NORTHERN IRELAND.
You have a room?
They are important documents
that we must have today.
Yes, I will keep
trying the sender,
because apparently
there's nothing else I can do.
which I find strange and certainly
not the service I've come to expect.
Yes, 329174-N for November.
You tell your supervisor
I'll be calling back. Good day.
Yes? May I help you?
Please, I would like
to speak to Mr. Hennessey.
- And your name?
- Ngoc Minh Quan.
- You are the one who's been phoning.
- Yes. I phoned many times.
I am afraid the Deputy Minister
is busy and won't be able to see you.
- I will wait.
- No, you must leave.
Best do as the lady says.
He's been phoning up
at all hours asking for Liam.
- He won't take no for an answer.
- Just groceries.
Go now,
before we make you.
- No. I'll wait.
- Right.
It's the man who's been
phoning you from London.
He's got a knife on him
One of those Swiss Army types.
Well, take it off him.
Jesus, how much damage can he do
with you two around?
Let him be.
As I explained before,
I don't know who the bombers are.
I realize that you're angry,
but there's not much I can do.
It's also very dangerous
for you to be here.
People in Belfast won't take
kindly to your accusations.
If you do not know who they are,
I would like you
to please find out.
DEPUTY MINISTER HENNESSEY
PROUD OF HIS UDI ROOTS
I haven't been affiliated
for 30 years.
When I was, I fought hard
against the violence.
I went to prison for what I did
and paid my debt.
Now I serve politics
of both sides...
trying to heal the wounds
and bridge the divide.
Again,
my sincere condolences,
but there's nothing I can do.
What if your wife and daughter
were killed by a bomb?
I'd do everything in my power
to get justice.
So, I've chosen you, Mr. Hennessey.
You will tell me
who killed my child.
Again,
I don't know.
You will change your mind.
Thank you for seeing me,
First Minister Hennessey.
I'm sorry, Liam.
He took me by surprise.
Are you okay, Beth?
You're okay--
Take her, take her.
- Murphy, have the boys
check the building. - Right.
Would you like a whiskey,
inspector?
No, thank you.
I suppose it would be a waste of time
asking who might've done this.
No one comes to mind.
Well...
it appears to have been
nothing more than a warning.
Fortunately, it wasn't
a serious bomb.
If it had been, we wouldn't
be here, would we?
Feel free to reach out,
should you have
the unexpected urge.
I'll feed the press
a gas leak story in the meantime.
Fair enough.
Thanks very much, inspector.
Hello?
It's him.
You come to my office
and plant a fucking bomb?
- Have you changed your mind?
- Changed my mind?
Are you out of your fuckin' tree?
You have no idea
who you're dealing with.
- But you'll soon find out.
- Give me the names.
I'll tell you what.
Let's meet face-to-face.
We'll settle--
That fuckin' wanker
threatened me and hung up.
Right. Let's check all the hotels and
guest houses. He won't be hard to find.
Fuckin' Chinaman.
Uncle Liam? What's up?
NEW YORK
I'll be there.
Stop! Hold it, hold it!
Don't move!
She's wired to blow!
NAMES
Two sets of wires
ten foot long...
soldered to that light bulb and
covered with ground-up match heads.
Gives an extra kick.
Not needed, but a nice touch.
Crude, effective, and easy to spot.
So he wanted us to see it.
Well it wasn't in the tank
so it wouldn't 've worked.
He just wants you to know
he can get to you.
Mickey.
We found him.
A B&B in Wellington Park.
- They found him.
- Grab him.
Drag him out of Belfast.
Discourage him from returning.
Wait for me. I'm on my way.
Hello.
I hear your office was bombed.
Hardly. It was the toilet
in the hall.
An Asian man in his 60's
with a grudge.
- It's all being taken care of.
- Why'd he do it?
His child died in the bank bombing.
He thinks I know who did it.
He's not the only one
of that mind.
So where are we
with the pardons?
Lots of resistance.
But if you give us something useful,
things might turn in your favor.
I have a lead.
I'm pursuing it.
Well, let's hope it bears fruit.
People here want heads.
The dogs won't stay leashed
much longer.
Top floor on the right.
Fuckin' get in!
Christ Almighty,
are you dumb and blind?
An old man making fools
out of the lot of you,
and he's still running around
out here, for God's sake.
You are four men. Four.
We had him cornered, then
he jumped off the roof,
- and slid down like some
fuckin' monkey. - What is goin' on?
Pack your bag.
You're going to the farm.
Go on. Get your things.
- You all right, Sean?
- Hi, Christy.
Go on through,
he's expecting you.
Beat ya up. Come on in
and have a drink, for God's sake.
Well, look at you.
- Jesus, the place looks well.
- It's not bad, is it?
- No.
- You're a sight for sore eyes.
- So how is New York treatin' you?
- Ah, it's cold.
Look, Murphy filled me in, there.
That bloody Chinaman.
He set off a bomb in my office,
put one in my Jag...
and beat the bejesus out
of Mick and Jimmy.
Do you want me to handle him?
No. That's Kavanagh's problem.
I need your help
with the London bombing.
Any idea who's behind it yet?
Not at all.
Well, the Yanks
aren't happy, Liam.
Dead women and kids all over the news.
Any fundraising now is impossible.
Yeah, this is not
about foundraising, Sean.
I need you to go to London
and meet someone.
A Richard Bromley in SO15.
- SO15? - He needs to know
the bombings aren't ours...
and that we're working the problem
hard, but we need his help.
Why me?
You're a decorated Ranger
in the Royal Irish Regiment.
Bromley will respect you as much as
he's capable of respecting any of us.
Should anyone find out that
we're talking to the Brits,
to go after one of our own,
rogue or not,
there'll be the devil to pay.
So, can I count on you, Sean...
to be discreet?
Of course.
- Right this way, sir.
- Thank you very much.
You took your time.
I just had to put out
the odd fire here and there.
- I'll be back in a minute.
- I'll be right here.
Jesus
I want the names.
ROYAL NAVAL COLLEGE, GREENWICH
Mr. Morrison.
Commander Bromley.
- We're not responsible.
- Really?
Forensic evidence and the use
of your code word suggests otherwise.
It's a renegade unit.
We don't know who they are yet.
You're telling me there's
an active UDI unit on the loose...
- you don't know nothing about?
- Yes I am.
- And the Semtex?
- They're raiding our dumps.
Dumps that were all given up
for the Accord?
And your code word?
They're being helped by someone
in our command.
- Belfast or Dublin.
- What do you want, Mr. Morrison?
We've a plan.
Different codes will be given
to each member of command.
When the bombers claim credit
for the next attack,
you'll tell us which word they use.
Then we'll know who gave the orders
- and then we end it.
- Who else is involved in this plan?
Liam Hennessey.
So you can appreciate
the need for discretion.
Only Liam knows who will be
given which word.
So Hennessey will personally work
with us to take out a UDI cell?
- A rogue cell.
- Your people, nonetheless.
I've one condition.
When Hennessey finds the bombers,
he tells me directly.
Then we take them down.
Not you.
This is non-negotiable.
We found some plastic bags
in his room.
Based on what I saw,
he's brewed up some nitroglycerin,
mixed it with weed killer, packed
into some plastic plumbing pipes.
I'm guessing he's made four bombs,
each enough to blow up a lorry.
- Jesus - When he surfaces
in Belfast, we'll find him.
You'll be safe here.
Aye.
I wouldn't count on it.
Benny.
Jesus. He roughed up
Benny and Sean.
They'll be fine.
Get more men from Belfast.
I've underestimated him.
It won't happen again.
It's another warning, Liam?
Aye.
Nothing I can't handle.
First Belfast, now here.
How in God's name
are you handling anything?
The problem's being dealt with.
He is destroying our farmhouse...
intent on God knows what,
and you calling it a problem?
God, you can be
so pompous sometimes.
I'm leaving for London.
Gonna stay at Keri's.
I'm not sure
that's a good idea.
Well, I wasn't asking
for your permission.
He's hardly likely to know about
our daughter's flat, and besides...
it's you he's after, not me.
Well, the point is, if he knows
about the farmhouse,
I assume he knows
about Keri's flat.
It's not worth the risk.
Well then, you're just gonna have
to handle it, like you said.
I remember a time when you would've
dealt with this, properly.
And other things too.
Those days are gone.
Weighs a bit more, but
shouldn't be noticeable.
All I'm adding is the Semtex,
a microchip and a few inches of wire.
It looks good.
Tricky part will be getting
it through the scanner, but...
- we'll find a way.
- And if it's turned on?
Shorter battery life,
but it'll work, no problem.
- Any idea which plane yet?
- No.
We don't want to hit a flight
with any Irish onboard.
One in the Queen's
fleet'd be best.
We just need the right mule.
Code word has changed.
As of tonight.
My news editor's
a complete twat.
Spends as much on a pair of shoes
as I get for eight hours
- writing crap like this.
- Makes perfect sense.
Who doesn't like
a new pair of sexy shoes?
You should try a real whiskey.
Two Jamesons, single malt.
"Wife attacks husband's
Transgender lover."
Some serious news
you're writing there.
Well, if it pays, I'll write it.
Beats being knee-deep
in a bloody bomb site.
- So what do you do?
- Wealth management.
- I'm Maggie.
- Ian.
Thanks, Mary.
Six more men are on
their way from Belfast.
When they get here they'll relieve
the fellas who've been up all night.
- Is it enough to secure the farm?
- Secure as it can be.
It's 20 total working two shifts.
All right. You're flying
to London today with Mary.
- Right, yeah - That's
completely unnecessary.
Get her into Keri's flat
then move them into a hotel.
- I can manage this, all right?
- I'll not be debating this.
Mick's gonna fill up the Jag.
You are leaving--
Take him to the hospital.
Get Mary to the airport.
- Right.
- Go.
Buried nitro bomb,
detonated by remote.
He needed a line of sight.
Those woods, that's where I'd be.
- Go.- Sean! Mick!
Get in the car!
Go, go, go!
Come on. Go, go, go!
You guys spread out.
I'll take the high ground.
Names!
Jesus Christ!
One old man running circles
around the lot of us.
Why is it so hard?
He's ahead of us
every step of the way.
- We need more men.
- We need 100 more men, at least.
And if we did that, we'd had
the whole Belfast against us.
Bring in a tracker,
someone who knows the woods...
and beat him at his own game.
- My nephew?
- Aye. If you can spare him.
Come on.
Oh, you--
Oh, you've gotta be kiddin'.
- Liam? - Tell Bromley,
I'll accept his terms.
I'll pass it on.
I've given out the code words.
Now we wait.
Quan hit us again.
The wee shitey
injured three more men.
Punji sticks,
if you can believe that.
Liam, it sounds
like he's trained,
Maybe Special Forces.
Which brings me to the point.
I need a tracker, Sean.
Can you give us a hand?
- I'll take a morning flight.
- Good man.
Hey.
How'd he sound?
Worried.
He's got a lot going on.
Well if he doesn't find
the bombers, the Accord's dead.
And politically, so's he.
Do you think he'll find them?
Yeah, if there's another blast.
The code word lead us
to who's running them.
He's finished.
The code word won't save him.
He's afraid to use his power.
He's just a washed-up-old man trying
to hold onto whatever he can.
I've never forgiven him
for my brother, Patrick.
Liam found out
who killed him.
A UVF death squad.
Four men.
I told Liam to kill them
before they got to court.
But he said no...
That the time for revenge
is past.
So my Patrick is dead
and buried...
and they're sitting in jail now.
All four of them...
taking classes
at the Open University.
It's not right.
It's not.
It's okay, baby.
Daddy.
Let them go.
Mom! Dad! Help!
Quan's daughters were
kidnapped, raped,
and believed by Quan
to have been murdered.
... was one of the most
deadliest fighters
Captured
Special UnitsProject Gamma
...was in a prison
Hugh McGrath's here.
I heard you're checking my dumps
We're checking everyone's.
No exceptions.
Four came up short.
Two were yours.
- Ten kilos of Semtex missing.
- What in God's are you doing?
My dumps were off-limits.
We were clear in that. Remember?
You were at the meeting.
If you knew that were short,
you should've handled it.
They were in perfect order.
I checked'em myself,
and that's a fact.
Christ, Liam, so the Committee
knows it's my Semtex?
Don't know who we can
trust anymore. Do we?
Trust or fear?
In your case, mostly fear.
Simple and brutal,
like my dad taught me.
Look, we have an opportunity here,
Liam, if you take the lead.
This Chinaman isn't helping matters, but
let me get some locals to hunt him down.
- How much do you know?
- Plenty.
Bomb in your office.
Your farm. Your car.
Mary and your daughter hiding out
in a London hotel. A bloody mess, it is.
And the men sense weakness,
as do the UVF.
You should be back in Belfast,
out in front, taking charge.
- Look, I'm no politician--
- What're you trying to say?
The bombing.
A few quiet words of encouragement
would soothe the ranks.
Encouragement?
- They kill civilians by the buckets.
- They went a bit far, I know,
but they have given us real momentum.
The Brits are on the ropes.
Jesus Christ, I said hit
a few financial targets. That's it.
No one gets hurt.
That's what we agreed to.
- You gave me your word.
- And by God, I kept it.
I don't know who they are,
don't even know who's controlling 'em.
And that's the way it has to be.
Because if something goes wrong,
they could trace'em straight back to us.
Go wrong? This wasn't
the fuckin' plan.
I needed this
to get our people back.
- You and I spent our whole lifetime--
- You don't give a shit about those men!
You needed the bombings
to shore up the election...
to prop up your weakness
in the ranks. Well, guess what?
In the fog o' war,
plans fuckin' change.
Now, I stood by you when
you put fire into the lads.
M62, Aldershot, Mountbatten.
You were calling for an escalation
then right enough.
Those days are long gone!
That's not what I heard
a few months ago.
I heard the old Liam,
a man back on track
with a plan.
You haven't forgotten what
we're fighting for, have you?
You question my loyalty?
I buried my brother-in-law,
before that my dad
and my two cousins.
We split our fair share of blood
struggling for a united Ireland...
not profiting off a divided one.
So don't fucking go asking me again if
I've forgotten what we're fighting for.
If there's anyone profiteering
around here, it's you...
sitting in your fancy houses,
cozying up to the Brits.
- You're not the Liam I once knew.
- You want the old me, huh?
The Butcher of the Bogside,
is that what you want?
Well then hear this.
You reel in those
fuckin' cunt and end it,
or by God, I'll bury
the lot of yas.
Right, I'm going now.
I'll be at my farm
if you need me.
And take care of that
Committee issue.
We don't want them jumping to the
wrong conclusion about that Semtex.
Do we?
Do you or any of the men know
where Mary's staying in London?
No. No one but Murphy.
McGrath knows where she's hiding.
I wanna know how.
What a day, Charlie.
What a day.
Come on now, let's go.
Come on, Charlie! Up you get.
Charlie!
You killed my dog.
Dog's fine. Just sleeping.
Sit.
I'm wearing a bomb.
Anyone comes in,
I touch it one, then we die.
- Now, give me the names.
- They claim to be UDI,
but I don't know
who they really are.
I'm doing everything I can
to find out who's responsible.
- You are lying! Who killed my daughter?
- I'm sorry. I truly don't know yet.
The explosives the bombers use,
it's Semtex-H?
Yes. Yes.
You know about Semtex?
I know Semtex-H.
During the war,
Czechs make for the army.
Good for bombs and traps.
- In Vietnam?
- Yes.
Many American people
died by Semtex-H.
Now, UDI use
to kill my daughter.
That's ironic.
I've read your history.
We both know what war is.
We've both tried to put it
behind us. You and me, we're alike.
We are nothing alike. You are nothing!
You kill women and children!
- Names!
- To Almighty God, I don't know.
Wait. Wait!
I've set a trap for them
when they use the next bomb.
When they claim the responsibility
to the next bombing,
they'll use a code word,
telling the police they're UDI.
I've changed that code word.
So when they use it, I'll know.
You have one day.
What if they don't set off
a bomb by then?
24 hours.
Oh, Jesus. Oh, Jesus.
Sweet Jesus.
We missed it the first time.
But ran a reconfiguration
through RAPTOR,
and the image's anomalies and
architecture became more apparent.
Now there, look,
the back of his hand.
Looks like a burn
or a birthmark.
We're running comparatives now.
So it's a bit more time,
but we'll get it.
- Morning, Sean. Thanks for coming.
- Are you all right?
- Oh, well, I've been better.
- There's been another bombing.
- Yeah. I just heard.
- Aye, a London bus.
- Has Bromley phoned?
- No, not yet.
McGrath's on his way
with some locals.
- They'll give you a hand.
- No, I don't need them.
- I'll handle it.
- Good man.
- Hennessey.
- They called.
But didn't give a code word.
What the hell's going on?
Maybe it wasn't them.
Press Association took the call.
A man with an Irish accent said
there'd be no more fuckin' cooperation...
with the Brits and
no more code words.
He knew exactly which bus and
how much explosive was used.
And it's been ID'd
as your Semtex again.
Either someone talked, warned
them out, or you're playing me.
Only two people knew
what was happening.
Myself and Morrison.
Like I said, one of you
can't be trusted.
Send me a number where
I can reach you day or night.
I'll call the moment
I have something.
It better be soon,
or you'll feel a backash the likes
of which you've never felt before.
A bus now.
For God's sake, 16 dead,
twice that injured.
I'm sorry.
I had a plan to nail
the bastards. Didn't work.
I've just come
from Downing Street.
The PM will consider
the pardons,
but only if you give up
the bombers immediately.
And how in God's name
do I do that?
Find a way.
Plans are afoot to put paratroops
back on your streets in 48 hours.
Belfast will erupt.
You'll give the bombers
exactly what they want.
Well, it's out of my hands now.
Call when you have something.
I'm heading for a conference
in Rome tomorrow.
I'll have my cell at all times.
How was London?
Is Mary okay?
You said to keep an eye on her,
and make sure she and Keri
were kept safe.
I spent some time
in her hotel lobby.
watching the comings
and goings, you know?
She had no idea I was there.
And your nephew turns up.
He spend two hours in her room.
- He spent two hours
in Mary's room? - Aye.
And after he goes,
Mary comes down,
and calls Hugh McGrath
on the lobby phone.
It's done.
Unless they take it apart, there's
no way to know it's been modified.
Fuckin' brilliant.
What'll set it off?
The internal clock.
I'll input the time
once we know the flight.
There's a security conference
in Rome tomorrow.
All the top MP's and security
people are flying there
- on three lunchtime flights.
- Perfect.
- What about our mule?
- Sara just confirmed he's going.
We then ran the burn-mark
through the database.
We got a positive hit on a
Patrick O'Reilly, age 29, from Belfast.
O'Reilly had one prior for domestic
abuse incident three years back.
Did two months in Hydebank.
We entered O'Reilly into
the facial rec bank for matches.
We got a hit.
That's him in a Dublin pub
with a UDI member four weeks ago.
It's a known UDI meeting place
we've had under surveillance for years.
- And the other two with him?
- I was about to get to them, Minister.
That and a woman we've just
ID'd at the bus explosion.
Yes.
Your mole's Hugh McGrath.
Did you hear me, Hennessey?
- Are you sure now?
- Quite.
We've ID'd Knightsbrid's bomber
as Patrick O'Reilly from Belfast.
Three weeks ago
Mr. O'Reilly was observed...
meeting Hugh McGrath
in a Dublin pub.
Where's McGrath and O'Reilly now?
I do not know O'Reilly.
- I haven't seen McGrath.
- Let me help you with McGrath.
His phone's GPS puts him
52 meters south of you.
I'm watching him
coming up your drive.
So let's cut the shit.
There's a Chinook airborne
right now with a 12-man team.
They'll land on your farm in
30 minutes to take McGrath into custody.
I needn't tell you
how that'll go...
now how your cozy relationship
with him will sink your career,
This time for good.
Or?
Question McGrath your way
and get what I need.
Names and locations of everyone.
You can't save him,
but maybe you can save yourself.
Thirty minutes. Get what I need,
I'll turn the around.
Jim.
Send McGrath's men
to the trailhead,
see if Sean needs any help.
Give me your phone.
- What the hell?
- Give me your phone.
Get your ass in that chair
there, you motherfucker.
- A London bus, for Chrissake!
- Now hold on.
Not even fuckin' warnings!
Sixteen dead.
You stabbed me in the back
and sanctioned this bloodbath...
- to get your war back on.
- The plan had no balls.
This wasn't a Bombing
Light campaign.
- We said hurt 'em, and hurt 'em we did.
- By killing women and children?
You can't restrain yourself.
You never could.
Well it's over.
- Their names, aliases and locations.
- You know I can't do that.
That's me being nice.
Now write and it better match
what I already know.
By God, I'll take you apart
joint by joint.
You used me.
You wanted the pardons
for your own political gain.
You're a disgrace to the cause.
Four men and a woman.
- Maggie Dunn?
- Aye.
You call her that.
Sara Mackay is her real name.
She works for you?
Bloody right.
Checks and balances.
An insurance policy,
if case you lose your nerve
which you have.
So now, if they take the lads,
she will lead them
straight back to you.
Not so easy anymore now, is it?
SO15 will be here
in 20 minutes to take you in.
We both know that can't happen.
You gave me up to the Brits?
You tout bastard!
You gave yourself up.
They've got surveillance of you
in a pub with a Pat O'Reilly,
who they ID'd as the
Knightsbridge bomber.
And thanks to your GPS phone,
they tracked you here.
You broke every rule, Hughie.
And now I'm left to clean up your mess,
as I have for the past 30 years.
A final thing.
My wife?
What about her?
She hates you because
of her brother.
So yes, I helped her...
and she helped me.
Oh shit, I'm late.
I've got to go.
Did you cum?
No. I'm not a three-second
wonder like you.
Well, keep wearing that shirt,
I'll be a two-second wonder.
You're gonna have
to get used to it.
Practise, practice, practice.
I'm close.
McGrath confessed.
It was his op all along.
I've got the bombers
names and location.
I'll text you the info.
You may need it.
The one who killed
Quan's daughter is Pat O'Reilly.
He's got a burn mark
on his right hand.
Either way, Sean,
you end this, now.
You hear me?
- Understood.
- Yes.
- Bromley.
I got your names.
You know why you're still alive?
You want the names?
They're in the phone.
The last text, code 7741.
Five names and their
location in London.
O'Reilly set the bomb
that killed your daughter.
He's got a burn mark
on his right hand.
You fought in the army.
Iraq.
Royal Irish Regiment.
Two tours, Special Forces.
You're Catholic, but
you fought for the British.
- Why?
- I fought for the regiment.
Out there religion didn't matter.
We are all the same. That's it.
Family?
A brother.
The rest have passed away.
Come in.
Take a seat, Sean.
Aye. You look like you've
been through the wars.
Aye.
Quan got the drop on me.
I gave him the names, he took
my things and let me go.
When the bombers called in
about the bus...
they didn't use a code word,
because someone
tipped them off.
Only two people knew the reason
for the code change.
You and me.
Liam, I didn't
tell anyone, I swear.
I spoke to Bromley,
and that was it.
What if I told you,
I had Murphy...
stay and watch Mary in London?
- My own flesh and blood.
- Liam, I'm so sorry.
I don't want to know
what happened in that room.
All I wanna know is,
what was discussed,
when your sweet aunt Mary
was with you.
Did she say she was involved
with McGrath and the bombers?
No. Never.
She was upset about her brothers
and kept on about that.
When you and I were
talking about the code word,
she asked about 'em but she
never let on about McGrath.
Oh, so she could
hear us on the phone?
No, it was only after our call
she mentioned the code word.
- She thought they wouldn't be at useful.
- So she steered the conversation?
Well, yes, I guess she did.
- A good manipulator, she is.
- So she told the bombers?
She told McGrath
and McGrath to them.
Thick as thieves, they were.
She tricked the information
out of you, Sean.
She used you.
- Liam, I--
- Shut up.
Bury that pig in the sow-pen.
And after that I have
one final task for you.
And when that's done,
go back to New York, son.
Thank you.
Zero, this is Alpha Two.
Echo One toward target house.
Zero. Echo One's towards
the target house. Copy.
Echo One has entered the
target house and unsighted to me.
Zero. Echo One is in the target house
and unsighted to you. Copy.
Thank Christ for that.
Sierra call signs. Confirm when
Echo One is complete in target house.
Sierra Two, Roger that.
Sierra Three, roger that.
X-Ray One on balcony.
Echo One approaching front door.
How'd it go?
It's done.
I have visual X-Ray One and
Echo One have left the room.
All other X-Rays remain.
Zero, this is Alpha Two.
One unknown Echo and two children
entering the target house.
Roger that.
Next.
X-Ray One entering living room.
All X-Rays now complete
in living room.
All call signs move to your
final rendezvous.
X-Rays and Echo complete
in living room.
We've lost visual.
Echo One has closed the blinds.
You have control.
Roger that. I have the control.
Standby. Standby.
Stop, stop, stop.
Wait!
Sierra call signs,
report what's going on.
I've two unknowns
at the front door. Wait.
Yeah?
Sorry for the bother, but
there's a gas leak in the building,
and the gas man needs
entry for an inspection.
Our gas works fine.
There's no problem.
He needs to inspect
all the flats, regardless.
He won't take a moment,
and it's an emergency.
It's quite important, Mr. Upton.
By law, I'm allowed
to use my own key.
All right.
Just a second.
Come down when you're done and
I'll take you to the next flat.
Thank you. I will be very fast.
This way.
Can I see the boiler, please?
Would you mind putting
your bag on the table?
Open it up.
All right.
All call signs,
standby, standbye.
Hold your positions,
wait for my order!
All call signs,
standby, standby, go!
Get down! Get down!
Get down!
- X-Ray down.
- What about Echo?
She's alive, under control.
Who has planned this?
Go fuck yourself.
What's this, eh?
Your next bomb?
Go fuck yourself.
Talk, you rotten slag!
It's too late.
Nine minutes it blows.
No time to land.
What's that?
A plane? Which plane?
Which plane?
Open her shirt.
That is how it works.
I ask the questions.
You answer.
That's right.
Flight 136 to Rome.
Passenger name Ian Wood.
Bomb is in his laptop.
Set to go off at 3:00 PM, exactly.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please be advised,
Flight 139 to Rome
has been further delayed.
We apologize
for the inconvenience.
Once again, flight 136
towards Rome...
Ian Wood!
Is there an Ian Wood here?
Ian Wood! Ian Wood?
Ian Wood? Ian Wood?
What is going on?
They're looking for someone
named Ian Wood.
That's me.
I'm Ian Wood.
Ian Wood?
- Is that your laptop?
- Yes.
Move! Move! Move!
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Move! Get down! Get out!
Get outta the way! Get out!
Move!
She sad a gas man turned up
with an assault gun, a Chinaman.
Started shooting, killed everyone
but her, and then walked out the door.
- She said it was a Chinaman?
- Affirmative. About 60 years old.
Just got word the
device is neutralised.
Good work. Fox Hunt
is now terminated.
No loose ends.
Understood.
It's Bromley. I need an AP out
to all city-disctrict units...
from Wapping High Street to A1203.
Suspect an Asian male, 61 years of age,
5 feet, 8 inches, 11 stone.
His name's Ngoc Minh Quan.
He's armed and has
U.S. Special Forces training.
Use extreme caution.
Yes.
I was on the flight they
targeted to blow up.
Because of your timely
information, we stopped it.
I wanted to thank you
personally.
Thank God you're okay.
The bombers were
neutralized, even Sara McKay,
whom you called "Maggie".
She gave a reporter the bomb that was
to have been put on my flight.
She also carried out
the bus carnage...
and is directly connected
to you... and McGrath.
We have call-pens going to
and from her off the cell towers...
by your farm and town homes. That's 250
precision locations and activitions...
- consistent with your mutual
activities. - Katherine--
I've spoken to the PM, he's agreed
to keep you in office for now.
I'm issuing pardons for five
"On-the-runs", one is your cousin,
but make no mistake Deputy First
Minister, you are now ours.
I say jump, you say where.
You're on the next flight
back to London.
Tomorrow, you'll brief SO15
and myself on everything you know.
All of it.
Evening, Sir.
How did you find me?
I gave you the names,
like I said.
This woman, she's a bomber.
You lie. You plan everything.
For whatever it's worth...
I never intended
to hurt your daughter.
Or any of those people.
Send.
Do it!
It's now on the internet,
you and your mistress.
The whole world will know
you are a terrorist.
Goodbye, Mr. Hennessey.
It's Landesman, Sir, in S-11.
I've got him.
He's returned.
The Happy Peacock Takeaway.
Do we shoot to kill?
Yes, Sir.
Sierra Two, roger that.
I believe we owe
this chap something.
This Chinese man
won't give up.
Keep back for now.
No point waking the dragon.
Yes, sir.
Subtitle by Verdike
(szaszcsaba1968@gmail.com)