Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Good morning.
Lovely day, is it not?
What can I do for you?
I know it's been quite some
time since you sold to anyone,
or traded for that matter.
I'm not selling.
But how about a trade?
I have some goods that
my wife put together.
I can't spare it.
You're not the
least bit curious?
I don't need
anything from you.
Please.
I have a family.
They're not my responsibility.
You're very luck out here.
So peaceful.
Miles away from anyone.
You should go.
Perhaps I'll see
you again sometime.
God bless.
Who's that?
He's a villain.
Why?
He steals girls like you,
takes them away from
their mother forever.
That's why they can
never know about you.
Look how radiant you skin is.
That feels good.
The others will be so impressed.
Why not help that man today?
He's dangerous.
Because he's desperate?
He said he has a family.
And if I helped him,
how could I refuse
the next person, right?
No exceptions.
I suppose.
Goodnight.
These are dire times, indeed.
To lose a life at
such a young age,
is a tragedy no parent
should ever endure.
Liam was my grandson,
so this is an
especially hard day.
But there is not a
single soul among us
who could fathom
the depths of pain
that the boys parents are
feeling at this very moment.
Bridget,
Colm, my son,
I am so sorry for your loss.
It might feel like this pain
will never pass, but it does.
It will.
And we will be here
for you both all of us.
We will not allow
this time of darkness
to extinguish the
everlasting light we have
in our Lord Jesus Christ.
Amen.
How's your
William doing?
No, Colm, don't.
Colm.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, stand.
- Stand.
- Go home.
- Forgive me.
- You must truly
regard us as lower than dirt.
- I beg your pardon.
- You see that?
My wife and I buried
our son today.
Well, then my
condolences to you both.
You don't give a damn
about anybody at all!
- Don't touch me.
- Or what?
Or what, or what?
Speak up, speak up!
Speak up!
You come through here
parading your abundance
on the day of my son's funeral!
I wasn't aware of the funeral.
Flaunt it in front of
all these starving people!
That was not my intent.
We are the faithful ones.
Yet, God smiles upon
you why is that?
God's got nothing
to do with it.
Everyone knows
what you are, Devil.
Everyone knows what you are.
- You creature.
- Please go!
- Everyone knows.
- Keep away from there!
Keep them, get away!
Get away all of you!
Get away, get away, get away!
Get off, get off there!
- Get off there!
- That's enough!
Return those to Miss Earnshaw.
Are you all right?
Thank you.
You heard
what the man said?
Colm Dwyer?
He cursed her out
then he hit her.
Despicable.
I want to help.
Make him regret it.
He deserves it.
But keep it secret.
I wouldn't know how.
Well, Darling,
what you have to do
is you go to Colm's house,
and you get something
from his son.
We'll use it in the ingathering
for our little
ceremony, all right.
Don't tell your mom.
Thank you.
What was that all about?
Nothing.
Come on, let's go.
- What is it?
- I have to pee.
Hurry up or you'll have to
hold it the rest of the way.
Otherwise you'll force
me back into the box?
That's right.
Would you say that to me
if I was the man who hit you?
What do you want?
I want to help, I'm ready.
This is not the time
for that conversation...
Both of those men threatened
you because they're unlucky.
They think you're the villain.
Who do you trust, them or me?
Pardon my intrusion.
It's Mr. Buckley, isn't it?
Yes.
Here.
Here please take this.
Uh.
Please, sir, this
does not concern you.
You're welcome to it all.
What, everything?
Everything.
Just as long as you forget
what you have seen here today.
It's settled then.
Please, sir, this is
not as it appears.
Oh, no, what is
it then, exactly?
Sir, please take it.
Let us be.
Please.
Here.
No, no, that's enough.
No.
No, no that's enough I said!
Goddamn you.
I never seen you.
Thank you.
He'll talk.
No matter his
promises, it'll spread.
That's how it works
with these people.
Audrey?
Listen.
I got you, Love.
You're safe now.
Come here.
Now watch.
You.
Okay.
Bridget, love.
Bridget.
Goodnight then.
We must keep our voices low.
My wife she's asleep upstairs.
Your wife?
Yeah.
- Bridget.
- Bridget?
What's your name?
I'm Colm Dwyer.
And you?
Audrey.
What were you doing out there?
Who's Liam?
Our son.
What age is he?
He.
Passed.
What happened?
Fell ill.
It was his breathing.
The funeral must
have been very hard for you.
That's how we'll be known now,
the parents who
lost their child.
It'll be our legacy.
Your legacy?
Perhaps it's strange
for me to put it that way.
Maybe not, I don't know.
At least you
still have Bridget.
I don't know what I'd
do if I lost her too.
Why were you out there?
Where'd you come from?
Right.
It's late.
You can sleep there tonight.
Colm.
Yes.
Thank you for letting me in.
Goodnight then.
Bridget.
What the bloody
hell is wrong with her?
And how
was she afterwards?
Oh, she fell to sleep
once I had her back inside.
You know how she is.
She's always been
a tad agitated.
Good morning.
Bridget, love.
Of course I've been agitated.
He was our little boy.
I'll step out for a moment.
Why'd you do it?
Why not ask Burke if you
wish to discuss my well being.
I brought him here
to come and help you.
You're not helping me!
It wasn't normal what you...
God.
Bridget?
Okay?
Eh, Burke!
Burke!
Where were you?
- Nowhere.
- Don't do that.
We don't do that to each other.
- What?
- Where did you go?
I took a walk.
To the Dwyer's house.
What, no.
I heard you yesterday.
You spoke of him.
I said you were attacked
and took it like a dog.
How long have you
been feeling this way?
Not long.
And have you
noticed anything else
that's at all out
of the ordinary?
I don't believe so.
I'm sure it's been a
difficult time for you both,
so it does make sense
that you've missed this.
But,
you're with child.
With child?
It wasn't like this with Liam.
It felt different.
Every pregnancy is different.
It's the reason for
your unusual cravings.
Stick to proper food,
and have a cup of tea if
you have any other urgings.
But I'll come back in a week
or so, and we can talk more.
I'll see myself out.
Goodbye, Burke.
I mean it.
Something feels off.
That's
just shock of it all.
We'll take it day-by-day.
Come here, Love.
It'll be okay.
This one's done.
What do you see out there?
It's getting colder.
All the more reason
for us to make haste.
Hand me another.
Christ, Audrey!
I know it's all been
for my protection,
everything you've done.
I've tried.
I know.
But you need to
trust me now too.
I'm ready.
If that's the case,
then you'll understand
the importance of sacrifice.
Let me see.
Mm.
No.
What happened here?
I cannot say for certain.
Fettered from the inside.
It's not good.
Yeah, Lochlan's horses he's
sentimental about these things.
They're not supposed
to cross species.
How's our girl keeping?
Oh, she's good, she's healthy.
Aren't you girl?
You best keep her separate
till the slaughter.
Mm.
What, what's wrong?
- Perfectly good.
- No good.
No good.
Bless us, O' Lord,
with these thy gifts
which we're about to
receive from thy bounty
through Christ, our Lord, amen.
Amen.
Where did this come from?
Eat up before it gets cold.
Mm.
Mm-mm.
Come now, Mauve.
Is everything all right?
What?
No, no.
What is it?
I know Bernard better
than he knows himself.
There's something wrong.
Ten days ago now he came home
with some fresh milk and bread.
Where would he get that from?
He wouldn't say
where he'd found it.
That can't be all.
He's been fondling himself.
I caught him in the act.
There's something
wrong with him.
This deep sadness
I can't help him.
Please, Seamus.
Give us a minute.
May I?
It's not as she
tells it, not at all.
Why don't you take
it from the beginning.
What brought this on.
Well, you remember
how Claudia Baron died?
How she grew so sick
and with the nightmares,
and she blamed it
on Agatha Earnshaw.
Of course.
That she had a
daughter, Agatha did,
a daughter that no one
had ever seen before.
I questioned Agatha myself.
That poor girl
withered away terrified,
and not one soul
of us believed her.
Well, I do.
I do.
Well, no, don't tell
Deirdre for God sake.
Promise me that.
What happened, exactly?
Well, I was coming
home from a job,
and it was the day
after Liam's funeral.
And I passed them on the road.
And I had words with Agatha.
And then I seen her.
I seen her.
She could have
been an acquaintance?
It was her
daughter I know that.
I know that from the
moment I saw her,
and from that same moment
when she looked at me,
I had a feeling that
I never had before.
Suddenly empty.
What are you saying?
I don't think I can
go on living like I was.
Not now.
She was the most
beautiful creature
I've ever laid eyes upon.
It's just the wind.
Yes.
What would
you do if he came back?
Well,
I'd protect you.
But what if it was the
Dwyer man from the funeral?
Oh, that
wouldn't change anything.
- But at the funeral...
- That was different.
There was a crowd.
You were in the cart.
What's you legacy?
Well, I'd say you are.
Is one's legacy
always their child?
No, sometimes it can be
if someone does
something important.
Then perhaps one's legacy
is how people remember you.
Possibly, yes.
And that could mean sacrifice?
Maybe.
Does that mean you'd
sacrifice yourself for me?
What?
- What have you done?
- Nothing.
Get in!
No, let me out!
Get me out!
I want out!
Hello?
Lochlan?
Mary?
Hello?
God.
We need to talk.
We need to speak, Seamus.
We need to have words.
It's not normal.
One, two good luck..
We're going to be late.
I'm coming!
♪ Savior from all of our fears ♪
♪ May angels guard
us while we sleep ♪
♪ Till morning light appears ♪
You may be seated.
Before we get to today's sermon,
I'd like to make
an announcement.
Colm and Bridget are
expecting a child.
I thought we should start with
a short verse from I John,
chapter four verse one.
"We love because
he first loved us."
Short and simple,
- but perhaps something...
- That's enough!
How?
How can you keep
saying these things
and maintain a straight face?
- Pardon me?
- We love.
We love because
God loved us first.
Is that it?
It's not merely a lie.
It's a great load of horse shit.
You best
mind that language.
No, no we're gonna
talk right now!
Failed crops, sickly children,
how much graver must
our circumstance become?
A calf was born with
two bloody heads,
and not one person
uttered a word.
We're bedeviled by something
unnatural out there.
And what are we doing?
It's not normal.
This is not normal!
I'm well aware of how perverse
- these tragedies have become!
- These tragedy is
that we've become so complacent.
We just bend over and take it.
There's a
difference between complacency,
and maintaining one's faith...
- Faith!
- in the face of...
This is not about faith!
Bernard, what's going on?
- Shut up!
- Put it down, Bernard.
I only wish you knew
what I felt with her.
I truly do.
It's a strange comfort to know
how truly insignificant you are.
- We can talk.
- Bernard, stop.
Let's step outside.
- No, no!
- No, no, no, no, no, don't!
What do you want?
I can't be seen.
Get inside.
Hello?
Anybody in there?
What
happened to your family?
We just couldn't
survive anymore.
I had to do it.
How do you do it?
Do what?
You have the only farm
producing for miles.
I don't know.
That's not what I've heard.
What have you heard?
They think it's
your heathen ways.
A pact with the devil
for all that out there.
Silly superstitions, I suppose.
All ye had to do was
help me that day,
and they'd still be here.
I know you chose to insult me.
I'm sorry.
You knew
I was desperate.
I don't want any trouble.
Don't speak.
Now I'm gonna take as much
as I can carry then leave.
If you mention this to anyone,
I'll come back for you.
I swear to fucking God I will.
Do you understand?
Very good.
We can handle this.
Well, I
could've handled it myself.
He had you against the wall!
He was a villain
just like you've said
- about everyone!
- That's enough!
They think you're weak.
- And they're right!
- Watch your mouth!
They will come looking for him,
and sooner or later
they will find him.
I saved your life.
I was a fool to
think I could be the mother.
Come on.
What's wrong?
Look.
When'd that happen?
I was brushing my teeth.
- Let me see.
- No.
- Come on let me see.
- No!
I need to tell you something.
I can't have this baby.
What?
There are ways to end a pregnancy
before it comes to term.
Remedies and such.
There's no way!
You want to kill our child!
- Colm.
- I won't allow it.
- Colm, wait!
- I won't allow it!
Wait!
Colm, wait.
No wait.
Stop, listen to me I'm sorry.
I wasn't aware.
- You weren't aware!
- I wasn't aware!
- Don't fucking touch me!
- I'm sorry please.
You weren't aware
that I'd be disgusted
by such a heinous proposal.
The soil's not yet
settled on Liam's grave,
and you're ready
to bury another!
I'm sorry.
- Don't touch me.
- Please don't go.
Where are you going.
Anywhere away from you.
But you can't go, please.
Please don't leave me.
I can't be alone right now.
Colm!
Please!
Come here, love.
Deirdre.
What did
Bernard say to you that day?
- You know I can't.
- What was it?
I just can't.
Look something pushed
him over the edge,
and I have a right to
know what that was.
Look I understand
your confusion.
Is there someone else?
It wasn't anything like that.
"What I felt with her,"
he obviously wasn't
referring to me.
Trust me, I'm working on it.
Have you sent for help?
There has to be
an investigation.
- What help?
- From the cities.
They can deduce his
reasoning with science.
You know Bernard was
your brother-in-law.
He's not just another
entry in your catalog.
You want to know what
Bernard said to me?
He claimed to have seen the
daughter of Agatha Earnshaw.
What if he did?
Have you spoken to Agatha?
This requires tact.
Bernard killed himself.
Deirdre, please.
Trust me to do the right thing.
You'd better.
We all deserve better than this.
Bernard deserves
better than this.
Hello, Agatha.
May I come in?
What's this about?
It's important.
I'll make it brief.
What is it?
I know it's strange,
my being here.
Yes.
A man from my
congregation passed.
It was a suicide.
Oh.
It happened during service
in front of everyone.
He had come to me a few
weeks prior he said...
He said he had seen
you and another,
a girl he believed
to be your daughter.
I've heard this rumor before.
I remember,
but this is not...
No, you don't get to
do this to me again.
No.
It's only due diligence
for his widow's sake.
He referenced her, this girl,
before he pulled the trigger.
Your man was sick in the head.
I will to be held accountable.
Have you had another threat?
Uh, no, why?
There's another man.
Poisoned his family.
Just.
Just be careful.
Mr. Buckley killed himself.
He saw something in you.
Bridget.
Bridget, love.
Bridget!
Bridget.
What are you doing?
Shh.
You'll wake him.
What is this?
We're leaving.
I told you word would spread.
Seamus wasn't
looking for the man.
About you, Audrey.
And, yes, sooner or later,
they'll come looking
for the body.
I can handle it if they do.
It's too much.
This is our home.
We're going, at
least for a while.
I'm not going anywhere.
This isn't up for negotiation.
Do you hear me?
I can't believe
how weak you are!
It's sickening!
You'd let them walk all over you
before standing your ground!
What happened
to my sweet child?
One of us has to do something.
Audrey.
Audrey, stop it?
Stop it, that's enough.
That's enough!
You've made your point.
Bridget!
Bridget?
Bridget, what have you done?
Huh?
You didn't.
What have you done?
Okay, okay.
Just a wee while longer,
and we'll be done.
Will she be well?
Yes,
but she'll need
to be very careful
while the stitches are in.
And the child?
She was very lucky.
What's this?
No, you don't have to do this.
No, Burke, I swear I'll be
fine, no, don't do this.
It's for your own good, Love.
Colm, please don't.
Promise I don't need this.
Please, God, please don't.
I'm sure it's for
your own good, Love.
Colm, please don't
just stand there!
I promise I don't
need this, Colm.
It's only to calm
your nerves, Bridget.
Please don't.
Where are you going?
To the others.
They deserve to know
what's happened.
At least they haven't
forgotten why I'm here.
You'll need to keep here in
there for at least a few days.
What the bloody hell
is wrong with her?
I don't know.
- Her temperature...
- That was not
her temperature!
She's gone stark-raving mad.
Her heart is racing!
Bridget, breathe!
You need to calm down now!
Well, think, damn you!
That's not grieving
what she's done.
What do you want me to say?
She's been acting
strange for days
since before we knew
she was carrying child.
That's all I thought it was.
Everything changed after Liam.
It's been a rash of
awful business lately.
Liam,
now this,
Lochlan and his family.
Bernard.
What about Bernard?
You're not to utter
a word of this to anyone.
Of course.
He swore to me that he'd seen
the daughter of Agatha Earnshaw.
He passed them on the road
the day after Liam's funeral.
After the funeral.
He called her the most beautiful
creature he'd ever seen.
I saw her too.
I brought her here.
I heard a scream, and then I
found her laying in the grass.
Why didn't
you say something.
I didn't say
anything to anyone.
Not even Bridget I was so drunk.
I hardly recall any of it.
It all started after
that night, the sickness.
She said her name was Audrey.
Here.
What's this.
Every affliction
the village has seen.
Oh, god.
Everything can be traced
back to the eclipse 17 years.
If Agatha's her mother,
then who's the father?
God, help us.
Why are you doing this?
What's your purpose?
My purpose?
You've corrupted
my daughter-in-law.
You've propelled a man from
my congregation to suicide.
Why did your mother
keep you secret?
Answer me.
I need to understand.
I could explain, but it's
easier if I just show you.
No.
I can't.
You can.
Hello, Agatha.
You frightened
me half to death.
Where are you running off to?
I was coming to find you.
What are you doing here?
We're
going to go and see Audrey.
I wasn't running away.
That's not what I was doing.
I know how hard
it can be to let go.
Deirdre.
What are you doing here?
Of course, I'm here.
Tonight's the?
Eh?
- Eh?
- It's the ingathering.
Yes, exactly.
Where were you
earlier before this?
Home.
What?
You mean you weren't out there?
No.
Let me take your coat.
No, it's fine I'll
keep it, it's cold.
This will be over soon.
I promise.
We are pilgrims,
absolute in our conviction.
We endure ridicule from
our fellow countrymen.
Persecution even for our loyalty
to the rights of
our forefathers.
But we know this is your will
that our standard is
the most righteous path.
God makes the sun rise and set.
And is faithful
from generation to generation.
God makes summer and
winter come and go.
DEIRDRE AND
COLM: He is faithful
from generation to generation
God makes the plants
grow and flowers bloom.
DEIRDRE AND
COLM: He is faithful
from generation to generation.
God gives us...
Um?
He grants us...
No.
God gives.
God gives us food to
eat and people to love.
He is faithful from
generation to generation.
God is always with us.
DEIRDRE AND
SEAMUS: He's faithful
from generation to generation.
Oh, Lord God,
Father of all mercies,
We yield thee praise and
thanksgiving for our deliverance
from those great
and apparent dangers
wherewith we were compassed.
Please deliver my Bridget
from this sickness.
Spare this famine
from another death
through Christ, our Lord.
Bridget.
Bridget, Bridget.
Hey, hey, hey!
Come on.
Hey.
Bridget, don't do this.
Listen, listen to
me, listen to me.
I'm sorry for how things
were after Liam, okay.
Okay, I know I could
be a better husband.
Bridget.
Please, Love, please
don't leave me too.
Don't
die on me please.
I need you.
Please.
Should we go check on them?
He'll
need some space.
What about Bridget?
- No.
- What?
We should prepare
for the worst.
What has gotten into you?
You couldn't recall
the prayers earlier.
We've all been under a tremendous
amount of stress lately.
No, Dad, that's not it.
Not for you.
What are you suggesting?
I saw you earlier.
You were with the Earnshaw girl.
That, that belonged to Lochlan.
They stashed his body in
the fucking wood shed.
Why were you with her?
She appeared before me.
Do you know what
happened to Bernard?
Yes.
I know only too well.
Colm!
Colm, get down here immediately!
- What happened?
- Look at him.
What, what is it?
He was with the Earnshaw girl.
She was here?
I saw them both together.
Hand me the gun.
Something's wrong, believe me.
Deirdre?
The Earnshaws killed Lochlan.
She's right.
- Look at him.
- Give me bloody gun.
Deirdre's right.
She's here.
What?
Audrey.
Bridget's gone.
And I need to die too.
What are you saying?
We'll find Audrey!
We'll settle this!
Just fucking do it!
I can't bear it!
I can't bear it one fucking...
What have you done?
- What have you done, you?
- I don't know.
Fucking fool!
I brought you into our home!
I took care of you, why?
What did we do to deserve this?
I was in the cart the day
you threatened my mother.
What did she do to deserve that?
It was my son's funeral.
What is it?
What is this?
Do you know how many
girls died trying?
I carry you to term.
They'll tell you.
The jealousy was so awful.
They weren't so strong.
They couldn't do what I did.
Say something.
Thank you.
No, goddamn you, Audrey!
No!
Please no!
Do you enjoy the struggle?
Pouring sweat over fields
that'll never sprout.
No, please don't do this.
- Anything you want.
- Please.
Anything it's yours.
I promise you.
Don't do this.
Who's the father?
There's no father.
I'm still a virgin.
No, please.
Please have mercy on me!
Don't do this!
No!
No, no, don't!
No.
Please no.
No, no!
Please, no!
I beg you please don't do this!
No!
No.
No, no, please!
Please don't do this.
He's faithful from
generation to generation.
No, please.
Colm.
It's coming.
- One last push.
- Come on.
- Push.
Come on, Love.
What is it?
Boy or girl?
Come on what is it?
- Oh, god.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong?
Christ.
What, what's wrong?
No, no.
- What's happening?
- Don't look!
Kill it!
Colm, please come back!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ I saw you for sure ♪
♪ When the clouds passed over ♪
♪ Casting long shadows ♪
♪ On your face ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Are nearer ♪
♪ And blood is housed inside ♪
♪ The blood moon ♪
♪ Yes, dew it's cloudy ♪
♪ And the clouds passed over ♪
♪ Hiding your face ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ Are nearer ♪
♪ And the blood
is housed inside ♪
♪ The blood moon ♪