Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Where's my primer?
Vada, we're late!
- Vada.
- Mmm.
♪ Timing, timing, timing ♪
- ♪ All about timing Timing, timing ♪
- God...
♪ Sit back in my chair
Relaxin' and reclinin' ♪
♪ He has not A care in the world
No, I'm lyin' ♪
♪ Takin'
all these meds To the face ♪
- ♪ Got me flyin' ♪
♪ Takin' all these meds
To the face ♪
♪ Got me dyin' ♪
♪ Smoke 'til my mind fryin' ♪
♪ Eyes red, high and cryin' ♪
♪ Numb the pain
With Oxy and Dior ♪
- ♪ Yeah, I'm pricey ♪
♪ Juice like Tupac Shakur
No iced tea ♪
♪ Givenchy, Louis V,
Double V, icy ♪
Dude,
we are so fucking late!
Are the cake pops
different flavors
or are they just
different colors?
Different flavors.
What are
the flavor differences?
♪ Timing, timing, timing ♪
♪ All about timing
Timing, timing ♪
♪ Sit back in my chair
I'm relaxin' ♪
- ♪ And reclinin' ♪
- ♪ Reclinin' ♪
♪ He has not a care
In the world, no, I'm lyin' ♪
Honestly, it is a miracle
that we made it on time.
Dude, we are killing it!
Per ushe, yes.
Also, is it just me
or does coffee
immediately make you
have to shit?
- Oh, immediately, yeah.
- Like I smell coffee and I'm shitting my pants.
Pause the shit-talking
till Justin Dragonas passes.
Oh, my God, I want him.
We need to come up with a code
for shitting.
You're right!
Alright, let's think.
- Okay, like...
- We can say like I need to talk to my boss.
- What are you talking about?
- Are you picking what I'm putting down?
It's like, "Okay, I need to
have a long call with my boss
and he's mad."
Oh my God,
my boss is so mad at me
that I got a penis call
this morning.
Oh, and then when you...
It could be like you're texting
your boss.
You're texting
your boss. I love it.
- We love that.
- You have to keep it fancy.
We love to keep it
fancy, that's what we do.
Now that's also a concern because
most of that water is paleo water.
Dating back to the most rec...
Yes, Vada?
Does the kind of rock affect
how long the aquifer last
or how quickly it recharges?
Oh, that's a great question,
but that depends on
many factors.
Anybody wanna guess
what the next biggest
aquifer is?
So we have to think about
what we know
about the aquifers, right?
So the Ogallala Aquifer is one
of the largest eight
in the world,
not to... Yes?
I'm sorry,
can I use the restroom?
Yes.
It dates back
to the recent ice age.
So when we think about that
we have to say, "Wow,
this is one of the largest
in the world."
Are you okay?
- No.
- What happened?
I don't want anyone to hear me.
Dude, literally just tell me,
you're freaking me out.
I got my...
What? I can't hear you.
I'll just text it to you.
Jesus, Amelia!
You don't text 911
when you get your period!
You scared the shit
out of me. Oh my God!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Wait, haven't you been dyin' to
get your period for like a year?
I thought you'd be stoked.
It's different than I thought.
Oh, you mean shitty as hell?
Yeah, I know.
You're the worst.
I'm hanging up now.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Do you, um...
have everything you need?
Yeah, I stole it from your room
a few months ago.
It's in my backpack.
Just in case.
I was just gonna tell you
to stuff a bunch of toilet paper
in your pants till
you get home,
but that...
That's some pro-level shit.
Nice move!
Oh, my God.
How about this?
Let's go to dinner tonight,
just you and I, okay?
And I will fill you in
on all the bloody, chunky,
gooey, goopy details.
Ew, shut up.
I love ya.
Congratulations.
Don't say congrats, you freak.
I love you, too.
Photo day.
Better get my shit together.
You don't even need
to wear makeup.
Sorry, what?
I just said, "You don't even
need to wear makeup."
I...
What was that?
Come on, come on!
- Was that a gun?
- Get down!
Take 'em off!
No! Oh!
We're gonna die.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Oh my God. Oh my God.
Is it over?
Who's in there?
I'm not the shooter.
It's Matt Corgan, I saw him.
Do you know where he is now?
I don't know, I don't know.
My brother.
Come, come under. Just...
Oh, fuck, are you shot?
My brother.
You! Drop your weapon!
Drop your weapon now!
Down on the ground!
Maybe we should
wake her up.
She needs to rest.
I just wanna
talk to her.
Did you know him?
He follows you on Instagram,
so he knew you.
It's like on every channel.
Like CNN was interviewing
your friend Melody.
So crazy.
Did you know anyone who died?
- Amelia.
- What?
Is there like a list
or something?
Sometimes, I'm just like,
"What year are we living in?"
I'm literally gonna Amazon
a bulletproof backpack.
Amelia!
What?
Please don't cry, Mom.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Do you need something?
Was just gonna take a bath.
Okay
Okay.
Fuck.
I'm glad
you're going to see Nick.
How's he holding up?
I think okay.
Good!
Good.
What about you?
How... How are you feeling?
Better.
That's good,
so good.
I'm really so glad
to hear that.
I literally thought
it was a drill
'cause Cambie had us locked in,
shades over the window
in like two seconds,
so I was like, "Okay, clearly,
this is a drill."
- Right?
- Yeah.
And Olivia Metis is
like talking,
you know, being annoying,
and Cambie goes
- "Olivia, be fucking quiet."
- No.
And we're all like, "Oh shit.
Like this is real deal,
no joke."
It's just so...
It's so fucked.
I can't stop hearing
the sound of it.
So last night,
I was like, "Okay,
why did I survive?
Like out of everyone,
like why me?
Is it so that
I can do something
to like make this
never happen again?"
Hmm.
So, I set up this Zoom
with Everytown
and we're gonna talk
about like
how to be more reactive,
how to start a movement,
how to get
a fuckin' bill passed.
Like something.
Why do you think he did it?
I don't know,
is there like ever a reason?
After initial reports
of a shooter,
officers surrounded
the campus,
directing the evacuation
of hundreds
of students from the scene.
This tragedy is.
I think Anderson Cooper
is cute.
We've been
on the scene.
He is. Don't get too attached.
♪ Who should I be ♪
♪ What is it you want
When you come for me ♪
♪ Every time
You're another evil ♪
♪ Waiting for an angel
that you bring to hell ♪
♪ Oh, my God
Who should I be ♪
♪ You're so regular
I am no short of spectacular ♪
♪ Break it up, break it up
Break it up ♪
♪ All of the cash
Stackin' up fast ♪
♪ See me, I set it up
Set it up, set it up ♪
♪ Look at my bag
Look at my hair ♪
♪ One for Japan
One for your man ♪
♪ I do what I want
With no conscience ♪
♪ Name on my neck
And I'm ballin' ♪
♪ Mindin' my business
As always ♪
♪ People don't get it
I'm awesome ♪
♪ Talkin', they want me
To fail ♪
♪ I am too busy to care... ♪
Disturbing
videos from the students' cellphones
In the video, gunshots can be
heard in the hall,
answered by children screaming
in their classrooms...
I'm gonna go to Nick's.
Uh, okay.
...during the escape,
children fled the building.
Hey.
Wanna come in?
Thank you.
Want some water or somethin'?
Okay.
You have a really nice house.
Thanks.
Really nice, it's a cool vibe,
with the wood and uh...
You have a lot
of cool art here, too.
Yeah, uh, my dads
are artists, so...
- Your parents are artists?
- Yeah.
That is so cool.
It all makes sense now.
Do you know
when they'll be back?
I'm actually not really sure.
Yeah, they're gone
like all the time.
Uh, I have to be honest
with you,
'cause if I'm not then
I'll probably feel really bad
about it.
But I watched some of...
Thank you.
Some of your dance videos
on Instagram.
In the videos, you come off
like, so like hard.
And whatever.
What I'm tryin' to say is you're
a completely different person
when you're dancing
and in real life,
you're like so different.
Yeah, I don't know why
I'm like that.
It's like... Yeah.
It's cool though that you're
able to like just switch into
a different mode.
Like I could never
do something like that.
It's dope.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Is that...
Is that wine okay for you?
Oh, yeah, no, it's so good.
Are you sure?
I have like a couple of others...
No, it's... Yeah...
That's like the best one
I've ever had, so.
Okay.
- I'm sorry, I'm gonna...
- Oh.
I'll turn this off,
my mom keeps checking in on me.
Okay.
Nick told me that
Quinton's brother's service
is tomorrow.
Already? That's...
- Yeah, I...
- That's great.
I guess some religions
do them fast.
I was thinkin' about going.
Do you think
that would be weird?
No. No, I don't...
I don't think so.
Okay.
I mean, I can, like,
come with you if you want.
Yeah, no, I...
- Yeah, I want... Yeah.
- Yeah, if you...
Um, yeah.
If that's cool with you, so...
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Cool.
Can I ask you a question?
Mmm-hmm.
Did you have like
the craziest nightmares
last night?
You have to be able to sleep
to have nightmares.
Hey.
- Hey.
Uh, thank you for coming.
Of course.
♪ Hold my hand ♪
♪ 'Cause the thought of harm ♪
♪ Brings a chill ♪
♪ Across my arms ♪
♪ If I can run ♪
♪ If I can hide ♪
♪ I'm gone ♪
♪ Burning down ♪
♪ Feelin' fire ♪
♪ Like where water ♪
♪ Meets the water ♪
♪ If I can breathe ♪
♪ If I sit tight ♪
♪ I'm gone ♪
Do you wanna go to Starbucks?
No.
Do you want a Starbucks?
Mmm, no.
Okay.
I'm literally gonna make Mom get me
something with caffeine.
I only do that when
I play with my little dinosaur.
Do the cat pitch.
Never again.
I only do that when I play
with my little dinosaur.
Do the cat pitch.
Never again.
Are you hungry?
- That's really good.
- Mmm.
I'm spilling it everywhere.
It is really good.
Are your dads really chill?
They travel a lot though, huh?
Mostly, Europe.
For like fun?
Work.
Do they send people
to spy on you
or they trust you just to not
throw a bunch of ragers.
I mean, they know I'm not
like a rager person, so.
Who do you hang out
with at school?
Like...
Like different people.
Like a bunch
of different people, so.
I'm gone a lot with dance.
How often do you dance?
Every day.
Like classes?
Mmm-hmm.
But I haven't gone
since the thing.
Are your parents chill?
My dad more than my mom,
for sure.
My mom's like very white and anxious.
I don't really tell 'em
anything though, 'cause like
they worry.
I feel kinda bad for it.
They're actually really good parents.
I see you're packing
for a trip.
What's your favorite
country to visit?
Paris.
What's the last country
you visited?
Europe.
What country
do you wish to visit?
Persia.
What's the weirdest word
in the English language?
Moist. Yuck.
When was
the last time you cried?
Can you stay?
It's late.
Just till I fall asleep.
Okay.
Thanks.
What's your
favorite movie?
Mmm, Pizza.
Favorite TV show?
Um, I would have to
say my pilot with Kate Berlant
that was passed on by every major
network and streaming platform.
Meanwhile, rapists everywhere
continue to freely make up 10.
What up, bitch?
Dude, I'm so sorry I missed
the march.
I mean, it's fine.
I was just, like, legit worried about you.
It was cool, though.
They let me speak.
I wish you'd been there,
but it's fine, I'll send you a link.
I know, I'm sorry.
I just...
It's a long story,
but I ended up goin' to Mia's house and...
Wait, lol, Mia Reed?
What?
Yeah.
She... She's just been alone
and I feel bad.
- So I just...
- No, no, no, I mean, it's fine. It's just like random.
Is she okay?
I mean, she will be.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Just tired.
We wanna know
how a 16-year-old can have access
to a military assault rifle
and that's considered okay?
It's not okay!
We want change.
We deserve to feel safe going
to our own school every day...
It feels like so soon.
It's been like two weeks.
No, I hear you.
It's... It's intense,
but I just...
I don't want us to be ruled
by fear, you know?
I feel like it'll be less scary
if we were together.
I gotta go.
Okay, love you. Call me later.
Hey! Honey, can I come in?
You don't have to ask
to come in, Mom.
Okay.
So it sounds like Nick's going
back today, huh?
Yup. He is.
Well...
Well, as long
as you wanna stay home,
you know,
your dad and I support that.
Thank you.
There's just one thing.
Were you tired a lot
before the incident?
LOL.
You called it "the incident".
Um...
No, I guess I'm just
always tired.
I mean, I guess, that's what
caffeine is for.
Right?
What do you do
when you get tired?
Sleep for like
14 hours straight.
Ooh, I really like watching
early seasons
of the Kardashians.
The OG Hidden Hills shit.
That is my vibe!
What's this, you're just
gonna fax that to my mom or...
- Fax?
- Yes. Fax.
What are you, a time traveler
from the '80s?
I mean, I had my suspicions
when I saw those sneakers,
but now I'm pretty convinced.
Touche.
Look, I know this whole
therapy thing is weird
and can be uncomfortable.
But everything that you say
in here is confidential.
And, side note, I actually do
really like your shoes.
They're very cool.
No, I know. Thank you.
Are there things that you don't
feel comfortable talking
to your parents about that
maybe you wanna share with me?
Yeah.
My porn addiction.
Okay.
I'm so sorry. I'm...
When I get nervous,
I make really inappropriate
jokes, so, my bad.
You don't have to be sorry.
And you don't
have to be nervous.
Well, I know that my parents
are worried about me
and they think I need help.
But I get it,
and that's fine,
but I personally am fine.
Like I feel like I'm really
good at managing my emotions.
It's...
What do you mean by that?
I'm just very chill.
Like a very low-key person.
So when it comes to emotional
stuff or drama I'm like
"Okay, is this
really productive?"
Yeah. I get it.
But you know, just because...
It doesn't necessarily mean
that someone's being dramatic
because they're emotional.
You know, for a lot of people,
they need to fully experience
their emotions,
in order to process
what they've been through,
so that they can begin to heal.
It's actually really healthy
to show your emotion.
I know most people
come in here crying
about their cheating husbands.
Vada, I wanna talk about you.
I wanna know how that
shooting at your school
has made you feel.
I feel...
It's okay.
I mean, it makes sense.
I want you to track
how you're feeling
using this worksheet.
So there's questions on there
that'll guide you.
You don't have to overthink it,
it's just basically there to
hold space for you to...
To understand whatever
emotions may come up.
All you have to do
is try and feel.
That's it.
No matter what
those feelings are.
Then you can bring it back next
session and we'll go through it.
Or you know,
you can fax it to me!
If that's easier for you.
She said you were incredibly
bright, and smart, and funny.
Wait,
is she in love with me?
Oh, what's the point of
goin' to therapy,
if they're just gonna tell their
parents everything they said after?
Honey, she didn't
tell me anything.
She gave me a general assessment
of how the session went.
- That's all.
- She thought you were doing really well,
considering what you
went through.
- Excuse me?
- Amelia!
She was on speakerphone.
It's not like I was trying to listen.
I'm sorry.
Whatever. Do I need
to go again?
Because it sounds like
she thinks everything is fine.
Well,
I don't know, honey.
I mean, do you think you're
ready to go back to school?
- Aren't you coming with us?
- No.
Well,
I don't know what you want.
- I don't know, turkey.
- Toasted?
I don't care, Mom!
♪ Tap, tap, tap in ♪
♪ Wrist on glitter, aye
Waist on thinner, aye ♪
♪ I'mma show you how to bag
A eight-figure nigga, hoo ♪
♪ Face on zaddy, sheesh
Pockets on jigga, hoo ♪
♪ You better get the card
And make it swipe like Tinder ♪
♪ Phew ♪
♪ Tap, tap, tap in ♪
♪ Wrist on glitter, aye
Waist on thinner, aye ♪
♪ I'mma show you how to bag
A eight-figure nigga, hoo ♪
♪ Tap ♪
♪ Tap, tap, tap in ♪
♪ Wrist on glitter, aye
Waist on thinner, aye ♪
♪ I'mma show you how to bag
A eight-figure nigga, hoo ♪
♪ Face on zaddy, sheesh
Pockets on jigga, hoo ♪
♪ You better get the card
And make it swipe like Tinder ♪
♪ Tap, tap, tap in ♪
♪ Wrist on glitter, aye
Waist on thinner, aye ♪
♪ I'mma show you how to bag
A eight-fig... ♪
♪ Tap, tap, tap in ♪
♪ Wrist on glitter, aye
Waist on thinner... ♪
We won't live our lives scared
to go to school every day.
We can't accept a world
in which the federal government
thinks American high school
students getting gunned down
in their classrooms
isn't a priority.
We won't accept that our leaders
have NRA money in their pockets
and our blood
on their hands.
We want real change.
We want real leadership,
honest politics that make
our schools a safe place
for us to learn and grow.
And we want it
before it's too late.
Can I have some wine?
That was Nick Feinstein,
one of the several
surviving students.
Does it get stuck
on your fingers?
Yeah.
I don't know,
it's gonna be good, you know?
- You just gotta get in it, you know?
- Yeah, like that?
- It's the shoulders.
- It's all in the shoulders.
- Like you can't do it without the shoulders.
- Okay, my bad.
I feel like that felt right.
- Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
- Like now it feels ready.
- I think if you did it anymore, it'd be overkill.
- Okay. Okay.
Oh, where did it go?
It wasn't enough.
No, you definitely have to
grind it way more.
I need more?
Little more.
Ooh, yeah.
Stoner vibes.
It's gonna be good.
- So good?
- So good.
Can't wait?
Can't wait.
Are you getting pumped?
Go! Go! Go! Go!
This is it.
- Ooh.
- Look at us.
- Who'd have thought?
That is fat.
Why do you trust me?
'Cause you've smoked before.
- Okay. Not like too much.
- It's so thick.
Is it ever too much?
- We'll find out.
- Stoner thoughts.
- Hey, did you just say "stoner thoughts"?
- Yes, I did!
Oh!
It's kinda thick.
- Curvy queen. So beautiful!
- She has curves.
- Holy, how do I?...
- Do the honors.
- No, just... Just... No.
- Do I...
Is this cigarette
or is it like this?
- Cigarette? Weed?
- You choose.
- Weed? Cigarette? Weed?
- You choose. You choose.
Wait, other...
Oh!
Okay. This is it.
Yo, it has gotten so bad
though, like so bad,
to the point where they're
cutting the elephant tusks off
before they release them,
so like the poachers
can't kill them.
So, it's like,
"Okay, they don't have tusks,
but like at least,
they're alive." You know?
It's so messed up!
No, and then it makes me think
about the uh, what's his name?
The Jimmy John's founder?
Apparently, he's like
some trophy hunter.
But the thing about that one is
like I don't know
if I have the right to be mad
about that,
'cause I don't know
if it's true or not.
So every time I see it,
I'm like, "Is this real?
Or is it like this fake news?"
Like, "Can I trust this meme?"
Can you be honest with me
for like 2.5 seconds?
- Am I being annoying?
- ♪ Salivatin' over me, sir ♪
Because personally for me,
I feel like this weed
is making me
a little bit chatty.
Like I don't even feel sad
at this point, I'm just chatty.
I don't know, is that bad?
What about you, what do you feel?
♪ Cut him off, cedar ♪
I feel chill.
You always feel chill.
♪ I go red hot like a demon ♪
♪ I go ghost
For no damn reason ♪
♪ Stupid boy think
That I need him ♪
I feel nothing.
♪ Stupid boy think
That I need him ♪
- Fuck!
- ♪ Stupid boy think That I need him ♪
♪ I go red hot like a demon ♪
♪ I go ghost
For no damn reason ♪
♪ Stupid boy think
That I need him ♪
♪ Stupid, stupid ♪
♪ Stupid boy think
That I need him ♪
- I hate weed.
- ♪ Stupid boy think That I need him ♪
♪ I go red hot like a demon ♪
♪ Stupid boy think that I... ♪
I hope that's not your dinner.
Yup.
Ew, Vada.
Where's your sister?
Um, filming a nighttime routine
for her YouTube channel.
Don't ask.
Do you think we should take her
phone away?
No, but you should probably get that app where
you can see everything she does online.
That exists?
Who knew!
Wow, where we'd be without you?
So Vada, honey, I was um...
I wanted to talk to you
about school.
What's up?
Well,
I don't want you to fall too far behind.
I won't.
Well,
you can't stay home forever.
Why not?
Sure, I just think that
the longer you stay home,
the harder it's gonna be
for you to go back.
All...
All I want is what's best
for you.
I wanna see that sparkle back.
You know,
Amelia got her period.
What?
- When?
- Forever ago.
Guess she just didn't
want you to know.
My mom's tryin' to make me go
back to school.
Fuck.
When are you gonna go back?
I don't know.
My dads said I could do
homeschooling as long as I want.
Lucky you.
I'm gonna try
and get some sleep.
Goodnight.
Night!
Get out of the building
and far away from it as you can.
Next, you need to find...
Always remember
these three things.
That should
be enough for today.
You can basically just review
your notes for the test.
Again, if I've talked about it,
it'll be on the test.
And guys, remember, I said,
"No phones
during classes, please."
Shit.
Oh, you bitch.
You dumb fucking bitch.
It was a fucking soda can!
Dumb fucking stupid...
So today at PE,
Jack Booth was whopping the beanbag
and one hit me in the forearm,
and the PE teacher saw it,
and didn't say one word.
And I was like, "Okay, you're
terrible at about your job."
I'm sure he's not terrible
at his job, Amelia.
Dad, he's protected
by union and tenure.
That's the only reason
he's still there.
How about you, Vada?
How was...
How was your first day back?
Just low-key.
So, is everyone
settling in okay?
I don't know, it's...
It's heavy, but I think everybody's
just tryin' to move on.
Good. That's good.
I'm so glad.
Yeah, it's amazing.
Ugh, I'm so full.
Finish your salad.
It's wilted.
It's good for you.
Finish it.
I just can't do arugula, Dad.
It's the texture!
Hey.
Uh, hey.
Do you have any E?
Uh, what?
How much do you want?
♪ Love ♪
♪ You're my Brooklyn love ♪
♪ Walk me to the deli for ♪
♪ Late-night candy runs ♪
♪ What we have is good
So fun ♪
♪ You're my Brooklyn love ♪
♪ Love, love ♪
- ♪ Love ♪
♪ You're my Brooklyn love ♪
♪ Love, love ♪
- ♪ Love ♪
♪ Love ♪
♪ Ooh la la
Je suis chaude pour toi ♪
♪ Chaude pour toi ♪
♪ Oh my God
Pourquoi je suis comme ca ♪
♪ Pourquoi je suis comme ca ♪
♪ Ooh la la
Je suis chaude pour toi ♪
♪ Chaude pour toi ♪
♪ Oh my God, oh my God ♪
♪ Walk me to the deli for ♪
♪ Late-night candy runs ♪
♪ What we have is good
So fun ♪
♪ You're my Brooklyn love ♪
♪ Love, love ♪
- ♪ Love ♪
♪ You're my Brooklyn love ♪
♪ Love, love ♪
There's gonna be
a quiz, okay? Um...
May I go to the restroom?
Sure.
Okay,
so make sure that you are studying.
You have to know the difference
I'm not gonna help you on this
when you have a pop...
quiz for this on Friday.
♪ Come winter, we shop, shop ♪
♪ In the light
Now the block hot ♪
♪ Get it, don't get got
Switched on like a hotspot ♪
- ♪ Low in the low ride ♪
- Nick.
♪ Low ride ♪
♪ Why else
Would they call it that ♪
♪ High in the daytime ♪
♪ How else could you laugh
in times like these ♪
♪ Current bet, bayonet ♪
♪ Last breath
Really stunk of treason ♪
♪ Off with his head quickly ♪
♪ Get this pussy hole
From 'round me ♪
♪ First flight back to LA ♪
♪ World shown too many ways ♪
♪ Sunshine
where grandmama stay ♪
♪ Sunshine where my dad died ♪
♪ Sunshine
and that summer wind ♪
♪ Sunshine without
Showing rays ♪
♪ Shine bright
Over shallow graves ♪
♪ Pray my body
Don't float away ♪
♪ Pray move swift
When you down ♪
♪ Buy some land
And grow trees on it ♪
♪ Purify what
You breathe on it ♪
♪ See me hidin' in the leaves ♪
Vada, Vada!
Oh my God, Vada! Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Vada, what'd you take?
I hate it here.
Vada, what're you doing?
Hey, what'd you take?
Hey, what's on your face?
Vada, come on!
Spaghetti.
No.
Hey, you need
to get your shit together
before someone sees you.
Come on!
Ready? We're going.
We're going!
We're going, okay.
Is it at least a good high?
Is that an elbow?
Why's your mouth
all blue?
Jesus, Millie,
what do you want?
A pen exploded in my mouth.
Oh, that happened
to me once, too,
but like it was a marker.
Good story, what do you want?
Nothing.
Mmm.
Ugh.
Motherfucker.
Shit.
Oh, okay,
so I guess you weren't playing.
What does that mean?
Let me read you this text.
"Uh, Q, I did drugs,"
with a Z, by the way.
That was the Z
on the drugs.
Uh, "And I'm YOLOing hard.
Hit me up, honey.
Let's party."
And then you did this emoji,
and then this emoji,
and then a hockey stick.
You just spammed, uh,
spammed emojis.
No, I did not.
Yeah,
yeah, you did.
But uh, now why'd you do the
drugs, uh, with the Z?
Dude, I literally don't know,
so what had happened was...
Is, um...
I was walking past Dan
Bonavure, and I was like, "Okay,
I know he's a dealer.
I know he has E.
I'm gonna take some like
right now."
Oh shit, okay.
Uh, and how're...
How're you feelin' now?
To be determined.
Well, I'm here if you need me.
Um...
What are you doing later?
'Cause I was just
gonna be low-key
and like watch a movie
or something.
You should come by.
Okay. And I'll
bring the acid.
Goodbye.
So is he
your boyfriend?
What are you making?
Slime. And don't
avoid the question.
This is way too juicy.
You've literally never
had a boy over
that was straight before.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I shouldn't assume
his sexual orientation.
So like how does he identify?
You're asking
way too many questions.
Vada, you are gonna stay
in the living room, right?
No, I was thinking we're gonna
snuggle in the dark in my room.
Yes, Mom!
I was just asking.
Please don't embarrass me.
I'm serious, Amelia.
Oh my God.
No!
No, no, no, don't go in the river!
- Why is he going in the river?
- I don't know.
This is the saddest shit
I have ever seen in my life.
This is terrible!
This is so bad!
Why would they let kids watch this?
Yeah, you said
you wanted to watch this.
- I cannot... You picked this.
- You said this was your fa...
I gave you options.
I gave you options...
- Come on.
- And you chose this one.
What are you guys
laughing at?
Amelia!
Sorry, sorry!
I just wanted to let you guys know
that the slime is almost ready.
If you wanna try it,
I'll allow it.
I love slime. I wanna try.
Okay! Do you want blue or red?
Blue, please.
Vada?
I don't...
Red. I don't care.
Coming right up!
I am so sorry.
She's so cute.
Do you wanna watch
The Staircase?
- Do you know what that is?
- No, what's The Staircase?
It's this white guy,
who murders his second wife,
and probably his first wife,
and gets away with both.
Oh, a tale as old as time.
Tale as old as time, really?
Yeah.
Wait, no, have you seen
the memes of like you know,
all these women are obsessed
with these murder docs,
people have like taken these
photos of the Stepford Wives
you know, with the smile,
with the knife?
- It's like...
- Nah, I haven't seen...
Uh, and it says,
"Murder me, Daddy."
Nah, I haven't seen that.
You've never seen that?
It's everywhere.
Check your timeline, dude.
It's really funny.
Everything okay?
Is everything alright?
Yeah, uh, I'm sorry.
I just have to go home
right now.
I'm sorry, but you know, uh,
family stuff.
Yeah, don't even apologize.
That's totally fine.
Yeah, um, honestly,
I just can't believe that
you're gonna leave alone to watch this
cat flow down the river all by myself.
Oh, you're actually
gonna finish it?
I have to!
I have to see what happens!
Okay, well, uh, text me
and let me know,
you know, what happens.
I hope everything's okay
at home.
You know how it is.
Yeah.
I'll see you.
No, no, no, no, no
- You don't trust me?
- No!
- No, mom!
- You don't trust me?
- Oh my God.
- Stop! Stop!
No, now let me see
which one you have.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- Stop!
Stop.
- But this one, I heard this would be better.
- That smells like strawberries.
No, that's too...
No, smell, smell.
Smell, smell. Smell.
Oh! Ew!
- Disgusting, I know. Oh God!
- You're so bad.
This one does
smell good, though.
Just take a little sniff.
Come on.
Ow, Jesus!
- V!
- What?
- Let me in!
- No.
You never lock the door.
What are you doing in there?
None of your business!
Are you wearing my lipstick?
What? No.
Can you tell Mom I don't need a ride?
Nick's gonna take me.
Only if you tell me why you're
wearing my lipstick.
I think those fake glasses are
messing with your vision, dude.
Well, you know, everyone wears
fake glasses now.
It's socially acceptable!
Okay, wait,
serious question.
Okay.
Now Drake?
Degrassi Drake? Choose.
I like wheelchair Drake.
Wheelchair Jimmy!
- Jimmy!
Jimmy!
♪ Jimmy ♪
You're, like, yodeling.
You probably
didn't know this about me,
but I'm the best yodeler
in my family.
Prove it!
You can't put me
on the spot like that,
'cause then that's just like,
you know...
This is like
a little preview.
- Yeah, this is like warm-up.
- Okay.
You know, but I'm gonna get you
when you're not even ready.
And you're gonna
be like...
Hey, you know,
this might sound weird,
'cause like I haven't known you
for that long,
but, like, I feel
so comfortable with you.
Like we're bonded
or something.
Same.
When'd you lose your virginity?
I haven't.
You haven't had sex?
No.
Do you mean
you haven't had today?
- What?
- You dance like such a fuck princess!
What? No, I do not!
- Yes, you do!
- What does that even mean?
It means exactly what it sounds
like it means!
You know, th...
The fuck princess!
- Nah. no.
- Okay, I get...
Okay, that's on me.
- Never assume.
- You never...
Wait, like, have you?
What?
Obviously not!
I am so awkward
and like embarra...
Like, no!
Like, oh my God!
I will say this.
I feel like high school sex
is very '90s.
Okay.
And waiting until college
is more now.
I mean, I feel like I'm probably
gonna wait until I'm like in love.
Oh.
Oh, that's really sweet.
Or when you go on tour with
Drake one day.
You just let him have it.
What's wheelchair Jimmy
like in bed?
♪ I broke in ♪
♪ To our home ♪
♪ Had we even been ♪
♪ Living here all along ♪
♪ And your face ♪
♪ That I know ♪
♪ Says night falls ♪
What are you
thinkin' about?
Hmm?
Okay, I know you're a
woman of very little words,
but I know you got
some deep shit happening
in this nice little head of yours.
Beep.
God.
Anything?
Okay.
Let's say this.
Let's say you die tomorrow.
Okay?
And what if you die sad, 'cause you
regret not saying what you wanted to say?
Then what?
I can't say it.
Why?
Is this okay?
Where have you been?
We've been freaking out!
I was at Nick's.
Nick's been calling all morning
wondering where you are.
Vada, your phone was dead.
We didn't know if something
terrible had happened to you or...
I'm sorry. I'm fine.
The perfect child
tells a fat one.
She better lose screen time
for that one, Dad.
Vada, come back here!
Vada!
I told you,
you don't have to know!
- Vada
- Vada, don't be rude.
Vada, what were you doing
last night?
Nothing, Jesus!
Are you...
Are you seeing someone?
LOL, seeing someone. No!
Uh, I'll do it...
I'll do it.
If you're gonna be
spending the night
at someone's house, Vada...
I'm not
having sex, Mom!
- Okay.
- Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
Last night, I slept over
at my friend Mia's house
- and I got drunk.
- You got drunk?
Yeah, Mom, I got drunk.
I am 16 years old
and I drink alcohol,
and here's the thing,
I don't even like drinking.
I was just tryin' to live
in the moment,
and feel shit, and YOLO
or something, okay?
Now if you excuse me,
I am hungover as shit
and I'm gonna go barf
in the shower.
Who's Mia?
I'm not even tryin' to be rude,
I'm just...
I'm super busy
and I don't have the time.
So.
Okay.
I'm sorry
I never called you back,
but you didn't have
to get me in trouble, dude.
Vada, I was just
worried about you.
When I didn't hear back
from you,
I felt like I had to call
your mom,
'cause the last time
I had seen you,
you had literally done drugs
at school.
So I was like, "Okay, cool.
Maybe she's like having
a serotonin drop from hell
and she's like suicidal
on a bridge somewhere and...
Then to hear like how freaked
your family was all night,
I just...
I don't know, I hoped that
whatever you went and did was worth
everything you put them through.
But, you know what?
I'm guessing uh, it's more likely
you were with Mia Reed somewhere,
acting like nothing happened.
Why're you being like this?
Because I've
waited for you, Vada.
For a month,
I've given you space and love to heal.
But I've been dealing with this
my own way!
You haven't dealt with
anything, that's the problem!
All I wanna do is try
my hardest to stop this
from ever happening again.
Like why is that so hard
for you to understand?
That's not fucking fair, Nick.
None of this is fair, Vada.
Yeah, yeah.
Mmm-hmm, go be with Mia.
She's gonna save the world
with her hot ass.
Fuck you, Nick.
Wow.
Nice.
He's just hurtin',
I think we all are.
He was so cruel about it!
Yeah, but you know,
he's under a lot of pressure.
He has to be the face of this,
just act brave, but, well,
he's scared, too.
You know,
fear makes people act crazy.
Okay, I...
Like I'm sorry for like
calling you and dumping
all of this on you,
especially, because it's
been the hardest on you.
It's hard on everyone.
I think for me, you know,
when it hurts too much,
I think about
how this can't be for nothing.
Like, oh, we won't even let
this be for not... Like, it...
It can't be for nothing,
you know?
Fuck. Yeah.
Tell me about your brother.
I just wanna know
more about him.
He was, uh, real quiet
when you first met him.
He watched everything now,
you know.
Like, he'd be like,
"Oh, that girl is gonna go home
with that guy
and that guy is gonna go home
with that girl and..."
Like, he was always right.
He was funny.
Like always making me laugh.
He, uh...
He sounds dope.
I feel him.
Now I know this sounds crazy
to say like...
I just...
I know he's still with me.
He's not gonna let me
go back and be sad,
he's not gonna let me go
forward and freak out.
He keeps me here.
He keeps me calm.
I think he's definitely
still here.
Lot of people
don't ask me about him.
They think I'mma like
cry or somethin'.
Um, well, thank you.
You can always talk
about him around me.
Wait, wait.
I'm sorry, I...
What's wrong?
I'm just going through a lot
right now, it's just...
I just don't know if I'm in
the right headspace right now.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, my God.
- I am so sorry!
- No, you're okay.
I'm... No, of course, you are.
I'm so sorry.
You're perfect, I like you,
it's just...
- I'm so sorry.
- V, I swear, you didn't do anything wrong.
I am so sorry, okay?
No, don't be sorry, it's...
It's not like that.
I am so sorry. I am so sorry.
I can't sleep.
You know, I can always see
where you are on Find A Friend
when your phone isn't dead.
You better delete me
off of that.
Like tomorrow,
so I don't tell Mom
about your Finsta.
Fine!
Why do you care where I am?
I don't.
You're always at a house
in North Bay.
Why?
It's where my friend Mia lives.
Hmm.
V, I'm scared.
Of what?
What if...
What if a shooter comes
to my school next?
It won't happen.
How do you know?
Sorry, I almost got you
killed in a shooting.
What're you talking about?
If I hadn't texted you
about my stupid period,
you wouldn't have
left the classroom.
You would've been safe.
- You could've died.
- That's not true.
Yes, it is!
Quinton's brother died,
'cause he was walking
in the same hallway.
It wasn't safe anywhere
Definitely wasn't your fault.
Then why have you been
so mad at me?
I haven't been mad at you.
Why do you keep thinking that?
Because...
You're never home anymore.
You never talk to me.
We never went to dinner
to talk about...
periods.
I'm sorry, but I'm definitely
not mad at you.
Can I tell you something that
I've not told anybody before?
We were in the bathroom.
And the stall where we hid,
there was a moment where I...
really thought
I was gonna die.
And it was
the scariest moment of my life.
And the only person
I could think of was you.
Do you remember when I sent you
that "I love you, too"?
I thought I only had time
to text one person,
so I texted you.
I didn't know that.
You're my favorite person
on Earth, Millie.
Even if you get married
one day?
No, fuck a husband.
You're my number one.
Don't let go.
I don't know
what's wrong with me.
Nothing is wrong with you.
Oh, Dad, I...
I feel so...
empty.
Vada, you went
through something
no one should ever have
to go through.
I can't imagine
how scared you feel.
Life's fuckin' hard.
I'm sorry
for saying "fucking".
No, you're right.
Life's fucking hard!
Dad.
What? No one's around.
Try it, it feels good.
Life is fucking crazy!
Yeah!
Fuck!
Life's fucking confusing!
I can't fucking feel anything!
Good one.
Fuck you, Matt Corgan!
Yeah, fuck you!
I'm scared to go to school
every day!
I'm scared to take my children
to school!
I'm scared to sleep!
I'm scared of...
time!
We're not even
swearing anymore, Dad.
Still feels good.
I'm incredibly proud
of how smart and amazing
my daughter is!
Dad, don't be fucking cheesy!
Please!
Never again.
Ah!
Mia?
♪ Just hit the belly
Poppin' up at the party ♪
♪ When I'm ready, I'm ready ♪
Oh, my god!
♪ Big bowl of spaghetti
Puffin' on somethin' smelly ♪
Mia?
♪ She only got the vision
When she saw me on the telly ♪
- Mia?
- ♪ Realest to the core ♪
♪ Strong drink
Said she feel it in her jaw ♪
My God.
♪ Rock bottom we were sittin'
On the floor ♪
I'm just sweating out.
I thought you were
fucking dead, dude.
Don't scare me like that.
Ah...
Come on.
Do you hate me?
No. Why would I hate you?
Just scared the shit out of me.
And I don't regret it.
Just scared it was gonna like
ruin our friendship or something.
Yeah, I was scared
of that, too.
Then let's not ruin anything?
Okay.
I think I'm gonna go back to
dance tomorrow.
Even though, I'm like literally
scared to leave my house,
I know I need to do it.
That's amazing.
You totally should.
Well, what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go with you.
No, you're not.
We never discussed this.
Stop trying to get rid of me!
I am Postmate-ing us
frozen yogurt.
I think I actually want some.
Okay, then push.
I like the doodles.
Who's that guy?
Is that Harry Potter?
That's Paul Dano.
He's my celebrity crush.
How was this?
Processing through
all these emotions?
Good.
I had a lot of ups and downs,
but I feel like
I felt everything.
So that's...
It's good, I guess.
I noticed that you used
the word "scared" a few times.
When did you feel
the most scared?
Being at school.
I don't feel comfortable
being back there.
Can you tell me more
about that?
You know,
all these kids from my school,
specifically one of
my closest friends, Nick,
who I love so much, um...
they've been able to take
what happened, and...
are literally using it
to change the world.
Like, they're doing so much
amazing stuff and...
For some reason, I feel like
I'm unable to do that.
I feel like it has kind
of ended our friendship.
Sucks.
'Cause I really,
really miss him.
What are you feeling right now?
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
I feel...
mad.
Mad about what?
I feel mad,
because I had no idea
one guy with a gun
could fuck up my life so hard
in six minutes.
Fuck up so many lives!
Then I think I should be
grateful to be alive.
I feel like, I don't know,
maybe there's some
weird fucked up reason why
I made it
and other people didn't.
Um, but then when you sit back
and you think about it,
you realize, "No!
There isn't.
There's no fucking reason."
None of us should've died.
I'm having a really hard time
moving on.
Oh, hi.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Sweetheart, I love you, too.
I'm gonna try to be more honest
with you about my life.
You know what?
I would really,
really like that.
I've been really struggling.
Mmm-hmm.
And I don't know why it's been
so hard to tell you like,
'cause I just didn't
want you to worry.
And you're right, I was acting
funny that time I was drunk,
because I did have sex
with someone.
And I was a little bit stoned,
but not as stoned
as I was when I was on E.
Jesus, that was rough.
And the person I was having sex
with wasn't the person
that I thought I was maybe
gonna be having sex with,
but I'm...
I'm telling you all of this,
because I want you to know
that I'm...
I'm never gonna do any of that
stuff ever again.
You know, the bad...
The bad stuff.
Mmm-hmm.
Okay. Well,
thank you for uh...
For trusting me.
With this information.
Was that too much?
No! I am...
I'm processing.
Don't worry,
it was with a girl.
Hmm?
The sex stuff.
It was with a girl,
so it's not
like I'm gonna get pregnant.
That's a bonus, right?
Yeah.
Bonus.
Okay.
I'm... I'm ready
to talk about it more now.
♪ The day is over
Come to an end ♪
♪ I know your eyes are ready ♪
♪ You can't close them ♪
♪ The world is heavy ♪
♪ So you'll need your rest ♪
♪ Good night ♪
♪ Sleep tight, my friend ♪
♪ And I'll sing ♪
♪ While you sleep ♪
♪ I'll cover your feet ♪
♪ So out of reach ♪
♪ I'll breathe
When you breathe ♪
♪ Whatever you need ♪
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ I know it feels ♪
♪ Like you're fightin'
The wind ♪
♪ Waitin' for one of you ♪
♪ To give in ♪
♪ The truth is
You're stronger ♪
♪ Than you've ever been ♪
♪ But there's nothing wrong ♪
♪ With holding my hand ♪
♪ So I'll sing ♪
♪ While you sleep ♪
♪ I'll cover your feet ♪
♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ So very out of reach ♪
♪ I'll breathe
When you breathe ♪
♪ Whatever you need ♪
♪ Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm
Mmm, mmm, mmm ♪