Subtitles by explosiveskull
Hello?
Are you still in bed?
No. I've been up for a while.
Hey, man.
Hey. We brought you
some groceries.
- Thanks.
- Jesus.
I know. It's not me.
So, what's new?
Your, uh, mom's biopsy
came back benign.
Really? Cool.
You should go get your moles
checked out too.
Yeah, definitely.
How are your finances?
They're okay.
- Credit card?
- It could be worse.
Because you know we're not
bailing you out again.
I had a big case last week.
Really? What was it?
You know I'm not supposed
to talk about that stuff.
This gay guy wanted me to find
out whether another guy was gay.
Was he?
Yeah, a little bit.
Oh, that's nice.
What's on your mind, Abe?
Should I be worried
if my pee smells like fish?
Yeah, maybe.
You know Rory Beans is
in the back, right?
So what?
Just leave, man.
We're not gonna judge you.
I used to be loved.
I used to be a kid detective.
When I was 13,
I solved the case
of the missing
fundraiser money.
It was Rory Beans,
the neighborhood knucklehead.
Get him, Rory.
In the beginning, I ran
my trade out of a tree house.
Somebody stole the
basketball magazines from my desk.
Can you remember
what else was in the cubby?
My pencils, erasers,
some peanut butter cups,
a photo of my bird.
But nothing else was taken?
- It was Clive Cunningham.
- How do you know?
- He's allergic to peanuts.
- Wow, thanks, Abe.
Whenever we watched movies
as a family,
I would always spot
the bad guy.
It was the bald man.
And guess the ending
in the second act.
She poisoned his drink.
This isn't mine.
Mine was bourbon.
It is. You saw me pour it.
Seth used to be
nice, but now he's mean.
I need you
to find out what happened.
Somebody keeps borrowing
my bicycle
- without asking permission.
- I found this in the park.
I need to know what it is.
I noticed some blood
on my dad's car.
I want you to find out
what happened.
Are you sure?
I saw that Constable Cleary was
in the yard again.
He wanted to catch me up
on some of the latest cases.
Oh, that's so cute.
Son, we want you to know
how impressed we are.
I've never seen a young person
take such initiative
for the sake
of their community.
I was 12 when someone
finally chopped down
my tree house.
The town raised enough money
to set me up with a real office
in the middle of Main Street.
The mayor's daughter, Gracie,
was my secretary.
I used to pay her in soda pop.
Abe Applebaum's office.
Oh, hi, Daddy.
He's in with Principal Erwin.
Want me to take a message?
Somebody stole a cashbox
from the school fundraiser.
- What was it for?
- Animal rescue.
Rory Beans was bit
by a dog last summer.
Someone's been sneaking up the
clock tower, changing the time.
Sounds like the Red Shoe Gang.
Don't you have
a boy on the inside?
Not anymore.
He kept getting grounded.
I was often
in one of those situations
where you're looking
for evidence in a house,
and then you hear the owner
come home so you have to hide.
And it keeps seeming like
they're gonna open the closet,
but they don't.
And then you sneeze
and give yourself away.
Oh, my God, that's adorable.
Bill, come and look at this!
One day,
while taking a stroll,
it suddenly occurred to me
who had robbed
Mr. Hepburn's candy store.
I was awarded
free ice cream for life.
- Here you go, Abe.
- Thanks, Mr. H.
Good morning, Abe.
Hi, Abe.
As a reward for
all my hard work,
I was invited to play drums
for Sharkwater
at the annual fall barbecue.
Sometimes I would lie awake
all night...
and wonder if I was the
smartest person in the world.
Oh, my God, I met
this super cute boy
at the record store
last weekend.
You're always
meeting cute boys.
It's driving me
up the wall.
- See you later.
It's been nearly
two weeks since the abduction
of 14-year-old Gracie Gulliver,
and the local anxiety
continues to mount.
I can't believe it. She comes
in my store all the time.
Things like this
aren't supposed to happen here.
The mayor and his wife released
this emotional statement...
- Hello?
- Hey, Abe.
It's Mindy Martingrove.
Oh, hi.
I was wondering,
how much longer do you think
it'll take you
to find Gracie?
Mmm...
Mm, I'm not sure.
My mom told me
not to tell you this,
but we're all
really counting on you.
I know you can do it.
Constable Cleary
still hasn't called me back.
Try and get some sleep,
sweetheart.
You have to stop
torturing yourself.
She knows
you're thinking about her.
Hello?
Where the hell are you?
It's Sunday.
No. It's not.
Fuck!
Morning, Mr. Ackerman.
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Who did that?
Some idiot I got suspended
20 years ago.
He stole fundraiser money
from the principal's office.
And he's still pissed?
His parents were about
to buy him a hunting kit.
The widow Gulliver was here,
but she got tired of waiting.
Is she coming back?
- Didn't I just find him?
- That was a year ago.
So you're worried
he's been hit by a car?
If it was a simple accident,
someone would've called,
wouldn't they?
- He's wearing his tags.
- We're coming up on Halloween.
It's possible he was used
in some kind of satanic ritual.
- What?
- This is Willowbrook.
And you know
what kids are like these days.
This guy in homeroom,
Henry Hooper,
claims he was in New York
over the summer
and practiced with the Mets.
I need to know if he's lying.
He's lying.
I have a $50 bill.
Let me see it.
Uh, butter pecan, please.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Oh, good, you got my text.
Nothing worse
than walking home
with just toilet paper.
Everybody knows you need
to take a shit.
- I'll get it next time.
- Yeah, sure.
Hi, is this Mrs. Hooper?
This will sound strange,
but did your son play baseball
with the Mets last summer?
He didn't? Okay.
Thank you very much.
There's a girl in your office.
- What? Who is she?
- I don't know.
What's the matter?
I forgot
to brush my teeth today.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
- I was out on a case.
- It's okay.
I stole a magazine
from reception.
Some cool stories in there.
- Lucy forgot to get your name.
- Caroline.
- Can I fix you a drink?
- Uh...
no, thank you.
How about some water?
It gets pretty hot in here.
Sure.
Yeah?
Could you bring Caroline
a bottle of water?
From where?
The store.
Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- It's okay, really.
It's no trouble at all.
So when's the last time
you solved a case?
I solve them all the time.
They just... stopped putting
my picture in the paper.
Who's that?
That's me
and Mayor Gulliver.
Isn't he the one
who hung himself?
He also founded
the potato festival.
- I've actually been here before.
- Oh, yeah?
About five years ago.
Someone stole a silver broach
at my 11th birthday party.
You solved it
in less than an hour.
Probably why I don't remember.
You asked which of my friends
had the most cake.
It's an old trick. When you
answer a question like that,
your memory becomes
extremely selective.
You're telling me
who you trust the least
- without even knowing it.
- Cool.
It only fails if you have
a really fat friend.
Jesus.
So, what can I help you
with today?
I have another case I was hoping
you might consider.
Of course.
Somebody murdered
my boyfriend.
- Seriously?
- Pretty seriously.
He was stabbed 17 times.
Um...
- That's him.
- Hi. Sorry I'm late.
- Your face looks better.
- Why? What happened?
- He was in a bar fight.
- It wasn't like that. Here.
It's an occupational hazard.
When he was in high school,
kids used to throw bottles
at the house.
Oh, that's awful.
You reek of alcohol.
How's the sleuthing?
- Uh, not bad.
- You know, we really admire
that you're still doing that,
sticking it out.
It takes a lot of courage.
You always knew what you wanted
to do and you're not giving up.
You're living your truth.
- Thanks.
- What are you working on?
He's, uh, not supposed
to talk about his cases.
Actually, I got
a pretty big one today.
- Oh, yeah? What was it?
- You hear about that kid?
The one they found in the river
a couple weeks ago?
Uh, we were
telling them earlier.
The police are getting nowhere
with the local youth
so his girlfriend hired me
to find out what happened.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
I did some work for her
a few years back.
- What'd you tell her?
- I told her I'd think about it.
You can't take that case.
- Why not?
- It wouldn't be fair.
- You don't have the experience.
- I've solved over 200 mysteries.
How many of them
have been murders?
You're taking advantage
of this girl's naivety.
- She's not even paying me.
- Then what are you doing it for?
Isn't this your job? Or are
you still working for quarters?
It's like you've forgotten
who I am.
- Who are you?
- Abe Applebaum!
I solved the case of the missing
time capsule when I was 12!
The mayor gave me the key
to the fucking city!
Finally,
after all this time,
somebody trusts me
with a real case.
A chance to prove myself.
You're telling me
I shouldn't take it?
- Good for you, Abe.
- Stop, please.
It is inadvertently
patronizing.
I know you don't
mean it to be, but it is.
- Heard of the Red Shoe Gang?
- Of course.
Everyone knows not
to go near the Boiler Room.
- What's the Boiler Room?
- Biker bar where they hang out.
Oh, right, ahem. It used
to be called the Steamer.
What does this
have to do with Patrick?
Well, he was stabbed 17 times.
Usually when that happens,
it's because you've pissed off
the wrong people.
Is it possible he was involved
in something dangerous?
- Such as?
- Drugs.
No, he would never do drugs.
- Gambling?
- No, he would never gamble.
- Demon worship?
- He would never worship a demon.
Tell me about his home life.
His parents
were super strict.
He had the highest grades
in our year.
Is it possible the pressure
was too much for him?
He was a good person.
He wanted to do well.
In this line of work,
you learn one thing quickly:
Everybody has secrets.
No matter
how simple a case may seem,
it's always shocking
what you find.
I just want you to be prepared.
Where do you wanna start?
Shouldn't we
talk to his parents?
I don't know.
That's a bit heavy, isn't it?
Why don't we get
warmed up first?
His friend Billy
works a few blocks away.
His family runs
the butcher shop?
Yeah. Why?
I was working a case here
the other week.
Really? What was it?
Nothing that serious.
His dad might be a homosexual.
- Holy smokes.
- Don't say anything.
Hey, Billy.
Hi, Caroline.
Who's this guy?
Uh, He's a really
awesome detective.
He's gonna help me find out
who killed Patrick.
How many murders
have you solved?
I have to ask you
some questions.
I need you to be
completely honest.
I know what it's like
at that school,
drugs are more popular
than milk.
To the best of your knowledge,
did Patrick have any contact
with the kids on the stoop
or the Wild Geese?
This guy has no idea
what he's doing.
Yeah, well,
your dad is gay.
Who else lives around here?
Can I offer you
something to drink?
Are those cupcakes
I smell?
Sorry, they're for
my sister's class.
My mom counted them.
- Is it her birthday?
- No. She's just not very popular.
Calvin?
Come upstairs, please!
Sorry. Be right back.
What are you doing?
It's an old trick.
Always open a window
wherever you're invited.
Why?
In case you need
to sneak back in.
What's the matter?
Would it be easier
if she left the room?
No, it's okay.
Caroline, I know you think
Patrick was
this perfect boyfriend,
but he was
a lot more complicated
than he allowed you
to believe.
- What do you mean?
- Give us an example.
He used to collect
bottle caps.
- So?
- He had thousands.
It was compulsive.
Anything else?
Yeah. He lied...
about movies
he hadn't actually seen
or books
he hadn't actually read.
Everybody does that.
He was very impatient
with handicapped people.
Was he cheating on her
or something?
- Why?
- You seem pretty determined
to shit on his grave.
I'm sorry, Caroline.
You shouldn't have
found out this way.
What are you talking about?
He had a concubine.
- What's that?
- Sort of like
a second girlfriend.
- Who?
- I don't know,
but she sounded kind of wild.
- What does that mean?
- He would brag
- about the stuff she did.
- Such as?
Uh...
Put her hands on his penis.
That's not so bad.
What else?
Put his penis in her mouth.
There are euphemisms
for these things.
Yeah,
but I didn't wanna sound vulgar.
How do you know
he wasn't making it up?
He had a picture
in his locker.
- But you didn't recognize her?
- She was wearing a tiger mask.
That's... all she was wearing.
I don't believe you.
I'm sorry, Caroline.
I wouldn't say it
if I wasn't sure.
God, those cupcakes
were killing me.
So how long were you together?
Three months.
But that's high-school time.
So like six?
I don't know. I...
I thought he was different
from the others.
Because he was a geek?
He was cultured.
I kept finding these
origami roses in my locker...
on days when I had
a test or something.
How'd you know
they were from him?
He was the only Asian
in our school.
I remember when girls still went
for the star quarterback.
Nobody cares about football.
God, this town got cynical.
Did it?
Look at this place.
On Saturday night, this was
the center of the universe.
They used to serve
breakfast for dinner
and dinner for breakfast.
Why?
To be funny.
Are you sure
you want to continue?
Yeah.
It won't feel real
until I understand.
Then we gotta break
into the school.
Why?
I wanna look
for that photograph.
Shit.
What?
They replaced the vent.
There might be a window
open on the other side.
- Why is that?
- Art class has been oil painting.
- So?
- Mrs. August is pregnant.
She might be more sensitive
to the fumes.
Are you making fun of me
or something?
What's that noise?
Must be the overnighters.
Who?
You know,
the kids who hide out
at the school
over the weekend.
Good fucking God.
This was his locker.
- Shit.
- What?
The cops already cleared it.
Just a bunch
of fucking bottle caps.
I still have his jacket.
Here.
Oh, gross.
Oh, Jesus!
Sorry.
Oh, thank God.
Huh.
What the hell?
Yeah?
How did you know it was me?
I didn't.
Put me in touch
with your drug dealer.
What? No.
I wanna ask
about these pills I found.
Why don't you ask
your drug dealer?
We have a special relationship.
I don't wanna ruin that.
So go talk to the kids
on the stoop.
No.
Why? Are you afraid
they'll make fun of you?
Yeah, right.
So that's the stoop?
Technically,
it's a concrete divider.
Check it out.
What's up, Apple Bum?
You know what these are?
- Holy shit.
- Yeah?
Answer my questions,
I'll give you some.
They're called
Ego Boosters.
- What do they do?
- Give you that extra nudge,
if you wanna ask out a girl
or do some stand-up.
They improve
your self-esteem.
Looks like you guys
could use some.
They also get you
super jacked.
Why don't I feel anything?
They take a while to kick in,
depending on how insecure
you normally are.
How much is this bottle worth?
Like a grand.
Great, now he's not gonna
give us any.
Tell me who the supplier is,
I'll give you the whole bottle.
Candy store.
- Is that code for something?
- No. It's a candy store.
Hepburn's candy store?
Yeah. He's been selling
for years.
- It's the truth.
- Just go in there
and, uh, tell him you have
a headache. You'll see.
What happened?
Nothing. I told him
I had a headache.
Okay, what happened next?
I bought this ice cream.
It was too awkward.
Here, I got you this.
Thanks.
I think maybe
those kids lied to you.
Here comes
the kid detective.
Let me go!
Abe, stop!
Who is the supplier?
The Red Shoe Gang! How long have
you lived in this fucking town?
Make you feel big
to beat up a kid?
Yes! These pills are awesome.
Be careful.
They're super addictive.
- What now?
- Take me to the Steamer.
It's time to talk
to some adults.
I'm here to see
Clive Cunningham.
No peanut products.
Right, sorry.
Go ahead.
We need to talk
about Patrick Chang.
No.
He wasn't there.
What does that mean?
We'll just have to work it
from another angle.
Have those drugs worn off?
Yeah, I think so.
I don't know,
maybe we should call it a day.
What's the matter?
You realize
if I go in there,
we're really gonna
have to solve this thing.
Of course.
It's just...
I find that kind of pressure
can be counterproductive.
I'm very sorry
to have disturbed you.
I know how...
devastating and... And... And...
And deeply confusing these
past few weeks must have been.
It's, um...
It's beyond awful.
Do you have kids?
What? No.
So, uh, you don't
really understand
what we're dealing with.
You're right. I'm sorry.
It's been two weeks
and the police haven't
offered any clarity.
They're so preoccupied
with the physical evidence
that they sometimes
can overlook
the more complex,
psychological integers.
- What does that mean?
- Uh...
Do you keep a lot of fruit
in your kitchen?
We used to.
What did Patrick favor?
When he was a kid,
he loved peaches.
And in the weeks
before his death?
He ate a lot of bananas.
They're dry,
which means no mess.
No plate,
no paper towels.
You don't have to cut them up
or even wash them.
You see where I'm going
with this?
No.
I think
he may have been depressed.
Our son wasn't depressed.
I found these
in his jacket.
Open them up.
They're called
Ego Boosters.
Basically a mixture of coke
and who knows what.
Someone must have planted them.
To make it look like
a drug killing after the fact?
It hadn't occurred to you?
I'm open
to all possibilities.
I realize
it's probably easier
to solve the murder
of a drug dealer
than a mild-mannered
honor student.
But these
do not belong to our boy!
Patrick was cheating
on his girlfriend.
- With who?
- I don't know.
- I haven't found her yet.
- How can you be sure?
- His friend told me.
- His friend told you,
and you treat it as fact?
No, Patrick had a picture
in his locker.
Which you saw?
No.
Are you a detective
or just some idiot
who believes
whatever he's told?
I've closed
over 200 cases.
How many of them murders?
Three.
Then don't let me
discourage you.
He was a very private boy.
We didn't even know
about Caroline
until she called us
after his death.
It's difficult to accept...
that you didn't know
everything
when you've loved someone
so thoroughly.
I promise you, I will not rest
until this case is solved...
and your family finds
some source of peace.
Don't promise that.
It's silly.
Can I hang on to this?
- What?
- I think I found that tiger.
Really? How?
Social media. I keep telling you
to get with the times.
Oh.
Nice work.
Hi, I'm looking
for Melody Miller.
A little old,
aren't you?
I'm a private detective. I need
to ask her some questions.
Spare me the theatrics. She's
in the basement with her sister.
Your mom seems nice.
She's getting to that age
where she thinks
she's too cool for me.
- Who's Paul?
- Just some guy.
Paid 50 bucks
to write his name on my face.
Not bad.
I can wash it off
in a week.
How much was Patrick
paying you?
It wasn't like that.
Patrick and I had
very deep conversations.
Oh, yeah?
What was perplexing him?
He was concerned
about the environment
and whether or not our distinct
identities are just an illusion.
Impressive.
Ever have any arguments?
No.
So you weren't jealous
of his real girlfriend?
She's just a kid.
Cute but uncomplicated.
Did Patrick know
his life was in danger?
Red Shoe Gang had
no reason to hurt him
as long as he
kept his grades up.
I'm not sure I follow.
Everyone had to submit
their locker codes
as a result of drugs
in the school.
The principal could open them
at any time.
So the suppliers had to recruit
kids who were above suspicion.
So the nerds became
the new dealers.
Whoever had the highest marks
in each grade.
That's awesome.
Everyone knows smart kids
have no spine.
It doesn't take much
to intimidate them.
- Have the police found you yet?
- No.
Figures.
Thank you very much, ladies.
Thanks for waiting.
I know this is weird.
- What's the matter?
- That car.
It was with us
at Patrick's house.
No way.
Do you think
they're following us?
Let's find out.
What the hell?
- Try going faster.
- Okay.
Okay, this is stupid.
Okay, pull over here.
Are you gonna do something?
What?
I mean, someone's
obviously following us.
Isn't it safer
to know who?
Yeah, I guess so.
No way.
- What the hell are you doing?
- We were worried about you.
- Whose car is this?
- Your uncle's.
- You're unbelievable.
- Are you out of your mind?
We saw you walk into
the Boiler Room.
How long have you been
following me?
Since this morning.
Get the fuck out of here.
I am working.
Do you not understand
how humiliating this is?
Wait...
- I told you.
- What was I...
You should have backed up.
Why would I back up?
Well, who was it?
Reporters
for the local paper.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- What'd they want?
- Just to follow our crumbs
and break the case
before we can.
- It happens all the time.
- That's so cool.
It's irresponsible
journalism.
Oh.
Um, I won't be able
to help much tomorrow.
- Why not?
- It's a school day.
The principal always calls
if I miss class.
Your parents
seem pretty cool...
about letting you
drive the car at least.
That's because they're dead.
I live with my grandparents.
- Sorry. I didn't realize.
- I was really young.
- How did they die?
- Downhill skiing.
Oh.
Both of them?
Yeah.
It was a very blustery day.
In some ways, you're lucky.
My parents
are always on my ass.
Sorry. That was
really insensitive.
I love my grandparents.
It's just not the same.
They're pretty old.
Must be lonely.
I don't know.
I've always felt like
there was this...
other presence
watching over me.
Do you believe
in that sort of thing?
Yeah. Sure.
Why not?
Good luck tomorrow.
Let me know what you find.
Sure thing.
What are you doing here, Abe?
You know you're not allowed
on school property.
A man
just walked into your office.
I know.
I have the same problem.
What do you want?
To talk about Patrick Chang.
- You can't be serious.
- His girlfriend hired me.
Is she okay?
All things considered.
I don't think
it's really hit her yet.
I'll help you with yours
if you'll help me with mine.
One of the custodians found
some broken beakers
in the science lab
this morning.
Mrs. Hersholt noticed
some footprints
on the floor of the gym.
- What?
- Overnighters.
Excuse me?
Kids who stay at the school
over the weekend.
How long has this
been going on?
I don't know.
Seems like
a pretty established subculture.
So...
what can you tell me
about Patrick?
He was a quiet kid.
Used to mouth
the national anthem,
heh, as if we couldn't tell.
- Is that it?
- No. Um...
I was warned that he might
be mixed up in something...
about a week
before his death.
By who?
One of his friends. Uh...
I'm too old
to keep the names straight.
Was he tall and ugly
or portly and pathetic?
He was a bit heavy, yes.
- Calvin?
- Uh-huh.
I, uh, checked
Patrick's locker.
I couldn't find anything.
Another fight
in the girls' restroom.
Who is it this time?
Both Beckys.
What am I supposed to do, Abe?
These kids have
no concept of authority.
I don't know, dude.
Maybe there's more nobility
in just giving up.
Maybe.
Oh, wicked.
"I only get one life, one body,
and I'm trapped in a teapot.
"A harmless shell
with no hard edges.
No one can see how much love and
violence I have inside my soul."
Jesus Christ.
"How to make her understand
"I'm the one
who really sees her,
"who knows what she's worth.
"Who would never
mock her innocence
or take advantage
of her trust."
That's motive, motherfucker.
Hey.
Can you turn
the music down, please?
- What are you doing home already?
- Last period spare.
- You want me to fix you a snack?
- No, thanks. I'm not hungry.
Fuck.
- Mom wants you to set the table.
- I'm doing homework.
No, you're not.
- I set it last night.
- Okay.
Calvin, come down here, please.
Little bitch.
Where are you going?
I need to pee.
- Jackie?
- Yeah?
You haven't finished
your potatoes.
I'm full.
What did she say?
But I thought she liked Jake.
- Time for bed.
- Okay, five minutes.
Benji's an idiot.
He didn't even know
what a kayak was.
Mom, I'm scared.
Of what?
I think I heard
something in the closet.
Come on, Jackie.
I thought we were past this.
Too old for all this
monster nonsense.
- Sorry.
- Go to sleep.
That kid is traumatized.
The family is furious.
Did you explain?
What the hell
was I supposed to say?
That you're some
wandering mental patient?
A private detective.
She's 9 years old.
I was investigating
the older brother.
I got trapped
in the house.
In connection to what?
The Patrick Chang
murder.
Who hired you
for a homicide?
His girlfriend.
- I hope you're not charging her.
- What have you found so far?
I can't talk about that.
It's an active
investigation.
Why didn't you
call me back...
after Gracie got kidnapped?
Because you were 12.
So?
I'd helped you before.
How would it have looked?
The police chief consulting
with a child
in the middle
of our town's greatest crisis.
- You weren't the chief back then.
- Lucky for you, I am now.
I'll see what I can work out
with the family.
Convince them
to drop criminal charges.
Thank you.
This has to stop, Abe.
Gracie was not
your responsibility...
and neither is this.
You can't run around
calling yourself a detective
and expect everyone else
to play along.
You know
I've always liked you.
But at a certain point,
we've all gotta grow up.
Maybe this is
that opportunity.
Your parents
posted your bail.
Hello?
You finally made
the paper again.
What does it say?
That you were found masturbating
in a little girl's bedroom.
I wasn't masturbating.
I believe you.
I'm really sorry, man.
My friend really needs
to get in there.
I believe you've been informed
by telephone.
My brother has been murdered.
It was the maid.
When I'm investigating a crime,
I'm not a man.
I'm a bloodhound.
Thanks for coming, man.
I've just been drinking
too much, you know?
Hey. What are you doing here?
I'm sorry, but you weren't
answering my calls.
Uh, yeah, I've been busy.
And you're not paying me,
so I had to prioritize.
I found another paper flower
in my locker.
- Okay.
- What do you think it means?
That they were
never coming from Patrick.
- What?
- Origami is Japanese.
He probably just took credit
because you started
talking to him.
Oh, my God.
I'm such a racist.
Well, relax.
It's not that bad.
Well, then who's making them?
Probably Calvin.
He's in love with you.
What? How do you know that?
I'm sorry. I gotta go.
Are you, uh,
ever gonna get dressed?
- Why?
- I have people coming over.
In the middle of the week?
It's fucking Friday, man.
For real?
What the hell?
What?
- Caroline?
- Where are you?
- I'm outside your place.
- You are?
You called me
at midnight, remember?
I did?
You might have
to refresh my memory.
You said you wouldn't rest
until this case is solved
and my family found
some sort of peace.
Remember?
- Are these your parents?
- Yeah.
- They're very photogenic.
- I know.
- And these are your grandparents?
- Mm-hm.
Where are they right now?
Um, probably out
feeding pigeons.
Thanks.
I need to apologize
for the other day.
It's okay.
I'm sorry you had
to see me like that.
I was in a bad place.
I got arrested.
I know.
- You saw the paper?
- I went to your office.
Your secretary showed me.
What a cunt.
The people in this town
used to look up to me.
Even the adults.
I was so far ahead
of the game, and then...
one day
I just woke up behind.
What do you mean?
A few years ago, I heard
my roommate talking about me
when he thought
I wasn't home.
He called me a "detective,"
in quotes.
I could hear him doing this
with his fingers.
It's difficult to accept...
the difference between
who you are in your head...
and who you are
in the world.
I know what you mean.
You do?
People act like I've never
seen a restricted movie before
or stayed up
past midnight.
Even my own boyfriend
saw me as this little girl.
Don't blame yourself
for what that kid did to you.
Experience is overrated.
The world has
enough assholes.
It's been a while since
I've known anyone like you.
Reminds me
why I got into this business.
Your clothes are ready.
What the hell happened?
I had some friends over.
The door's unlocked.
What if a client came in?
I wouldn't worry about that now
that you're the town pedophile.
The phone's off the hook.
I wanted to make sure
you were okay.
Wow.
What is this thing?
That girl left it for you
the other day.
It's from her dead boyfriend.
Poor Calvin.
I need the key to the garage.
Wow.
Hello?
I need you
to stay home tomorrow.
- What? Why?
- It isn't safe.
They're not coming from Calvin.
Have you found my cat yet?
No. I actually
completely forgot about that.
I'm here to talk
about your daughter.
You preserved her bedroom.
The house hasn't been touched
since Burt died.
My parents just redid mine.
Do you know
where this came from?
She never said anything
about a secret admirer?
Who could keep track?
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Nothing to worry about.
Find my cat, Abe.
I'm lonely.
Everything all right, Abe?
Yeah. Why?
Nobody real
comes in before 5.
My mind's running races.
I, uh...
I need to relax.
What happened the other week
with Rory Beans?
He beat the shit out of me.
- Why don't you just apologize?
- For what?
No one forced him
to steal the fundraiser money.
He didn't do it, man.
What?
Why do you think
he hates you so much?
He stole the fundraiser money.
- What was it for?
- Animal rescue.
Rory Beans was bit
by a dog last summer.
- Who did that?
- Some idiot
- I got suspended 20 years ago.
- He's still pissed?
Everyone had to submit their
locker codes to the office.
I found another paper flower
in my locker.
She never said anything
about a secret admirer?
I've always felt like
there was this other presence
watching over me.
- Yeah?
- Hey.
I need you to check the date
on the first Rory Beans case.
Are you serious?
There's a chance he was set up.
I might know who's
really making those flowers.
What the fuck?
Abe?
I know you're in the closet.
I'm under the bed.
Why aren't you at school?
It's Sunday.
What are you
doing here, Abe?
Do you remember the first case
you ever brought me?
No.
Somebody stole the cashbox
from the school fundraiser.
That was the last year
we had one.
I think I might have
made a mistake,
implicated the wrong kid.
Who cares?
Wasn't this years ago?
You found it
in his desk the next day.
I don't understand.
You were just testing me,
weren't you?
Trying to see
how my head worked...
if I was really as smart
as everyone said.
Why would I care
to do that?
Gracie was kidnapped
a week later.
What are you asking me?
Are you the bad guy?
I'm an educator, Abe.
I hope you understand
how even
the most outlandish claim
could tarnish my career...
stir doubts
about my character.
I found the picture you stole
from Patrick's locker.
You thought
it was Caroline, didn't you?
In the tiger mask.
It wasn't?
Are you sure?
I know about
the paper flowers.
You killed her boyfriend.
You wanted someone innocent,
untouched, just like Gracie.
You thought
he'd ruined her for you.
Gracie wasn't innocent.
She used to stop by my office
just to show me her outfits.
She was 14.
Of all people...
you should appreciate
the relativity of age.
That girl got
what she always wanted.
She would have loved
to see this place.
Her face
on every telephone pole.
People marching through
the marshes, arm in arm.
For a month, the whole country
knew her name.
I should have seen it.
I could have saved her.
You were just a kid.
No one expected you
to find her.
She did.
Abe,
I watched you grow up
with the weight
of the entire town
on your conscience.
I always felt
a little sorry for you.
No child
could survive that.
What happened to her?
She didn't last long.
Her spirit went soft...
after I gave
our daughter away.
What?
Everyone knows me here.
I can't have a newborn
suddenly appear out of nowhere.
It wasn't easy,
leaving Caroline on the steps
for those decrepit
church mice.
But I knew they wouldn't ask
any questions.
My only consolation was
watching her mature
with such grace
and sensibility.
I took something beautiful...
but I gave something back.
Something better.
Balance was restored.
I was relieved when I first
heard they were dating.
He seemed sort of...
sexless and irrelevant.
Congratulations, Abe.
You've solved
your first murder.
What now?
I'm not afraid of you.
Nobody is.
There's a reason
I always obliged you, Abe.
We both know how it feels
when nobody takes you seriously.
Now they'll know
what we were capable of.
Abe?
I found her.
What are you talking about?
My cat is a boy.
I found her.
What?
She's too scared
to talk to me.
When I was 32,
I solved the case
of the Willowbrook kidnapper.
It was Ellis Erwin...
the evil principal.
Gracie's discovery remained
a national news story
for weeks.
I was the kid detective
who never gave up.
The governor presented me
with a medal.
Rory Beans accepted
a handshake.
The widow Gulliver called me
a hero.
I think her cat is
probably dead though.
It was like the whole town
returned to color overnight.
People came out
for the potato festival
for the first time
in 18 years.
Morning, Abe.
Even Lucy started
looking at me differently.
Wait.
She's in there.
Caroline.
How are you?
I'm okay.
What happened to your office?
I had to take
the old headlines down.
Looked too stupid.
Feels pretty empty.
Are you back at school?
Not yet.
That's good.
You should take your time.
No one really knows
what to say to me.
And your grandparents?
They're still
pretty confused.
They thought
I was a gift from Jesus,
not some pedophile rapist.
I'm sorry.
It's not like
you didn't warn me.
No matter how simple
a case may seem,
it's always shocking
what you find.
I was just being pretentious.
Still...
isn't it better
to know the truth?
Well, at least
you saved Gracie.
Yeah, sort of.
Has she reached out
to you yet?
She's just a kid.
Hi.
Can I get you
a tea or something?
Oh, no, thank you.
We're okay.
How are you enjoying
the extra space?
It's great.
Not a little lonely
without Corey?
- He was kind of a deadbeat.
- Oh.
It's so tidy.
- Yeah, I hired a cleaning lady.
- Oh.
Oh, did you see
you were in another magazine?
It's a story
that touches people.
Getting any money
out of that?
It's good for business.
You, um...
You seem tired.
Yeah, I've been having
a little trouble sleeping.
Why? What's wrong?
It's nothing.
The floor creaks at night.
You know, they, um...
They called us for a quote.
I hope you don't mind.
Are you all right?
Abe.
What's the matter?
Subtitles by explosiveskull