Your Fault
NOAH'S 18th BIRTHDAY
\an8MOM
MOBILE
\an8Hello, Freckles.
NICK
MOBILE
YES, FRECKLES
YOU ARE MINE
LION
MOBILE
ANIMAL SHELTER
Mr. Nick Leister. I love you, my love.
I love you too.
Yes. Yes.
YOUR ABSENCE WILL FOLLOW ME WHILE I SLEEP
\an8THE PLAINTIFF ANABEL GRASON SEEKS
TOTAL CUSTODY
\an8OF NICHOLAS LEISTER
AGAINST MISTER WILLIAM LEISTER.
LETTER OF WITHDRAWAL OF SHARED CUSTODY
PHOTO
YOU ARE MINE
Are you still in the apartme
Are you still
in my grandfather's apartment?
Yes
Take care of N
REJECT - MESSAGE - ACCEPT
\an8INCOMING CALL - FRECKLES - MOBILE
CALL ENDED
LION
MOBILE
INCOMING CALL
FRECKLES - MOBILE
50 - YEARS - ANNIVERSARY
LEISTER
Forgive me.
I know you only wanted to help me.
I love you
\an8SLIDE TO TURN OFF
EMERGENCY CALL
YOUR ABSENCE WILL FOLLOW ME WHILE I SLEEP
ALWAYS
NOAH, I WILL ALWAYS BE YOUR
\an8NOAH, I WILL ALWAYS BE
YOUR LIGHT IN THE DARKNESS - NICK