Hey. How you doin' in there?
You sitting comfortably?
All settled in? Okay, good.
Now, listen.
I'm gonna tell you a story.
It's all about the time
we escaped from a chicken farm.
There was this farmer, see?
And she absolutely hated chickens.
Kept them locked up
like prisoners.
I guess you could say
she had a real axe to grind.
Got herself a machine
that turned chickens into pies.
We mustn't panic!
But what she didn't plan on
was going toe to toe
with a certain freedom-fighting chick.
She was fierce, fearless,
and wanted one thing and one thing only.
Freedom.
She pulled us all together...
...and gave us the wings
to fly right outta that hen-hole.
She got every chicken out of there.
And got rid of that wicked farmer
to boot.
Huh?
Bye-bye.
And you know
who that freedom-fighting chicken was?
Your very own mom.
Rocky, don't you think bedtime stories
might be a bit premature?
Well... I mean, you're never too young
to learn where you came from.
But those days are over, thank goodness.
We've got our happy ending.
We're living in it.
Your way, Mac.
More fruit coming, Bunty.
Oh! Oh, thanks, Mac,
'cause I'm working up a thirst here.
Good work, Bunty. Keep it up.
You know what?
I think it's time
to put the past behind us.
- Turned out nice again.
- Ooh, yeah. Lovely.
Past?
What past?
That past, behind us.
But these,
these are our glory days.
That's who we are.
It's who we were.
We went through all that
so our baby doesn't have to.
Y'know, you are right.
From now on,
our only mission is to keep our baby safe.
Don't you worry.
Ol' Rocky here is on the case.
What do I do? What do I do?
- Whoo-hoo!
- It's hopping!
Just grab it!
Whee!
Oh no!
Whoops!
Egg's up!
Good grief. A live shell.
Clear the area!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Oh! Get it!
- Watch out!
- Huh?
No!
Would you look at that.
We've got ourselves a family.
Huh?
Oh, look at her, Rocky.
She's perfect.
Welcome to the world.
- Molly.
- Mm.
Ah, what a bonny wee hen.
Oh, she's got
her father's spindly little legs.
We need to build them up, what, what.
When I was in the RAF,
we did 50 squats before breakfast.
Ah. Oh.
That's gone.
- I made her a bicycle.
- Really?
Mm-hmm.
Oh. You knitted one.
What a lovely... thought.
Thank you, Babs.
Y'know, I'd say our little island paradise
just got a little more
"paradisier."
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
- Boo-boo!
- ♪ Let me tell you all about my baby ♪
Coochie-coo.
- Ooh.
- ♪ You will never find her misbehavin' ♪
♪ Oh, she's such a diamond... ♪
Huh?
Whoops.
Molly! No, no, no, no!
Stop that pram!
♪ Everybody tells me she's a charmer ♪
♪ Never gets in trouble ♪
♪ She's the apple of my eye ♪
- ♪ She's so sweet... ♪
- No!
- That's my brave little girl.
- Yes! You're doing great!
- Ooh. No, no, no, no.
- No, no, no!
Molly, that's a bit too brave.
Careful up there, sweetheart.
Hold on to the sides.
- Hold on to it.
- Ah.
Huh?
- Whee!
- Oh no! No, no, no!
- Outrageous!
- ♪ Cherry pie, buttercup ♪
- Oh!
- ♪ Sugar, little honeybee ♪
Aw.
♪ Never thought
That I would love another... ♪
Mm.
- Anyone for tea?
- Ooh, yeah. Cuppa tea.
Mm-hmm.
♪ All the way up ♪
- Huh?
- ♪ Can't get enough, I know ♪
♪ Sometimes she drives me crazy ♪
- Huh?
- ♪ I never could get mad at my baby... ♪
Hey, boys. Welcome back.
We have got some quality old junk
for you today, Rocky, mate.
- Here you go.
- Molly, hold on to this for Daddy.
- All right. Well, nice to see ya.
- See you next month.
- Hiya, hen.
- Huh?
Mm, bye-bye.
♪ I know ♪
- Mm.
- ♪ One day, she'll have to go ♪
♪ And leave me behind... ♪
- Mutt.
- Ah.
♪ 'Cause she's so sweet ♪
No, you cheater! Cheater!
See you later.
- ♪ To keep her to myself... ♪
- Hmm? Hmm.
- Hello!
- Morning.
- Hello! Morning!
- Morning!
- Hiya!
- Morning, pet!
♪ Without my sweet ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Cherry pie, buttercup ♪
♪ She's still got the world to see ♪
Hmm.
Hi, Mum.
- Oh. Hello, darling.
- Hi, Dad!
Uncle Nick! Uncle Fetcher!
She just called me "uncle."
Steady, mate. Steady.
But I've never had
a family of me own.
Me neither.
Mum, I was thinking. Can we go over there?
Where, love?
The other side of the water.
Oh, we've spoken about this, Molly.
There's nothing over there for us.
What about stuff Uncle Nick
and Fetch bring?
Isn't that for us?
Hey. What's up, Ginge?
Rocky.
Molly's asking about going off the island.
Oh, right.
Hey, Molly.
Do you wanna see
the world's coolest invention?
Hmm.
Okay.
What is it, Dad?
Only the answer to all of life's problems.
Popcorn.
Mm!
Is that the best thing ever or what?
- Mm! It is good.
- "Good"?
This is great!
Life, my girl,
doesn't get better than this.
- Mum, what is it?
- It's nothing to worry about, Molly.
Nothing at all.
Well, it was only a matter of time
before the humans showed up.
It looks like they're taking them
to some kind of chicken farm.
Uh-oh.
I haven't seen that look in a long while.
You can't right
all the world's wrongs, duck.
Meeting tonight. Spread the word.
Here we go again.
What's going on, Mum?
Why can't I go up my tree anymore?
What's this meeting about?
It's nothing, Molly.
It's, um, just...
There's some quite big wasps
up there this year.
Really?
Besides, I need someone to stay here
and look after your dad.
Don't worry. I'm good.
Okay.
Maybe while you're out,
he can tell me a story.
Good idea.
Good night, my big, brave girl.
Good night, Ginge. Good luck.
Okay, Mollypod. What do you wanna do?
Well, I thought
you could tell me about... this.
Oh!
Uh, uh, uh, that... that is... not me.
Okay. Yes, it's me.
But it was a long time ago.
And?
And,
actually,
it's a... it's a pretty good story.
It's not just eggs
they want from us.
Ginger has that look about her.
I reckon she'll have us charging
right into the fray.
I don't want to charge into any frays.
I... I'm fray-phobic.
- All right, everyone! Please, quiet!
- Wait. She's starting.
- Quiet!
- Shut your beak.
Now, we all know about the new road.
And the trucks taking chickens
to what looks like some kind of farm.
A farm?
No, it's all right, Beryl. Listen. Listen.
We know from experience
what that can mean.
It's something we just can't ignore.
We really only have one choice.
I don't want to hear it.
We've got to do something.
We have to hide.
- Ah?
- Huh?
Hide?
Yes. Hide!
You mean, pretend we're not here?
Exactly.
Operation Lie Low. Jolly good.
Ooh! I like lilos.
Especially the stripy ones.
She's right, you know.
- It's really not our problem.
- Oh, you!
Are you all right, hen?
It's not like you to shy away from danger.
I know, but I have Molly
to think about now.
And I...
We can't risk our freedom
by venturing into a world
that finds chickens so...
delicious.
Lift!
Right.
All we have to do now is keep quiet
and not draw attention to ourselves.
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Rocky!
Um, given our new situation,
maybe you shouldn't crow anymore.
Don't crow?
What?
But that's, like, my thing.
Maybe you could do a different thing.
A quieter one?
Wow! Look at this!
Molly! Get away from that.
- Ginge, can we talk about the whole...
- She's right, you know.
Careless squawks cost lives.
We have to lie low.
I'm running a camouflage lesson at noon.
If you can find me.
Ooh.
What's it for, Mum?
Oh! What is that?
It's got a chicken sitting
in a bucket on it.
It's doing this.
Oh, that's so funny.
Uh, let's go home.
Where are they going?
Can we go with them?
- It looks like a lot of fun.
- I'm sorry, Molly.
- You're not ready to go off the island.
- But I...
Uh, Rocky? Little help?
Maybe I could crow on weekends. Y'know?
Why am I not ready?
I'm a big, brave girl.
- You always say so.
- I know.
But you're still a child.
Says who?
Says me and your dad.
Right, Rocky?
Yeah, that's right. That's right. Yes.
Listen to your mom, kiddo.
Oh! Oh. How about just half a crow?
Like a "cock-a" or "doodle-doo"?
Something that's a little shorter.
Well, I'm going over to see those trucks
because I am a Lone Free Ranger.
Like Dad was.
I've seen his poster.
Ah.
He used to live over there,
and you did too.
Did I say that? I don't... I don't remember.
That's it.
Molly, you are not leaving this island.
You can't make me stay here.
You're not the boss of me.
Actually, I am.
Look, Molly, you've got
everything you want right here.
Except for one thing.
And what's that?
Freedom.
You know, she is a lot like you.
Mm.
Your daughter
is going to be delicious!
Not the face! Not the face!
- Huh?
- Molly?
Molly?
- Come out, Molly!
- Molly!
- Molly?
Come out, Molly.
No!
She's left the island.
This isn't so bad.
Don't know what Mum was worried about.
I'm big and I'm brave.
Yeah, course I am.
I'm big...
And...
...not very brave.
Huh?
Hmm?
What were you doin'?
Have you got a death wish?
No.
Wait, what's a death wish?
Isn't it a bit late
for you to be out, baby girl?
I'm not a baby girl.
I'm a... I'm a big, brave girl.
And isn't it a bit late
for you to be out too?
Okay, I like it.
Give as good as you get, eh?
Well, I'm Frizzle.
And you are?
Molly.
Although,
it's kind of a goofy name.
So I'm thinking of changing it to...
Zip it, kidda.
It's stoppin'. Now's our chance.
- Are you comin' or not?
- Coming where?
To the happy chicken truck.
You've seen them too?
Right.
Wherever that truck's goin',
it's gonna be cooler
than a penguin's toenails.
Uh, what's a toenail?
What's a penguin?
Oh! You have got so much to learn.
Come on.
Wait for me!
I mean, so she found my poster,
and I told her a story.
I don't think that's such a big deal.
Oh no. It was perfectly sensible
to encourage our daughter
to be a Lone Free Ranger.
You know, if you had it your way,
she'd still be in her shell.
Well, better in her shell
than out on the open road.
So, do you live on an island too?
Nah. I was stuck on a boring old farm.
Then the trucks came,
and they said I was too small to go.
But that's not gonna stop me.
You get to sit in a bucket.
What chicken doesn't want
their own bucket?
I want a bucket.
The thing about us, Mol,
is that we wanna go
where we wanna go whenever we want.
Yeah. With nobody telling us
what we can and can't do.
Me and you, kidda. All the way.
Holy moly.
Hear that? It's like a party in there.
Oh!
What is that?
You've never seen a human before?
We had them back at the farm.
They're kinda stupid.
They fed us and tidied up after us.
They're basically like waitin' staff.
Oi!
- Oi, you!
- Huh?
How did you two get out here?
- What do you say, Molly?
- Uh...
Do you want to come
on the adventure of a lifetime or not?
Uh...
- Oh no!
Molly!
Ginger!
Huh?
Molly!
I know what you're thinking.
Where are the buckets?
I bet they give 'em to us
when we get there.
- Are we nearly there yet?
- Molly!
Huh?
Hello.
There go the goujons!
- Hang on, Fowler!
- What do you think I'm doing?
Molly!
Well, hey. That doesn't look so bad.
Oh, that looks so bad.
Right. Stop here.
Let's have a look.
- Okay, all clear.
- On your way.
We mustn't panic.
- No. No panicking.
- I don't like it.
It's a perfect time to panic.
The enemy has the upper hand.
We must keep our heads!
- Where should we keep them?
- I'm trying to think here.
No panicking. No. I said no panicking!
- Ginger, what do you say?
- What did I say?
I say, last time,
we broke out of a chicken farm.
Well, this time, we're breaking in.
Ooh!
- It smells funny.
- This is not what I expected.
This is, uh... cool, isn't it?
That's it, my lovelies.
Come on down.
Ah.
I don't fancy that.
- Come on.
- Huh?
Over here.
- Ooh!
- Huh?
Huh?
Wow.
Did I promise you
the adventure of a lifetime or what?
Come on. Let's play.
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Let's go in the pool.
Listen, everyone. We can do this.
- We just need a really clever plan.
- Ooh. Ooh.
Okay. I've got this. I've got this.
I'm gonna go in there,
and I'm gonna bust Molly out.
And just how the bloomin' heck
are you going to do that?
Well, by, uh... uh, y'know, going in there
and then... busting her out.
That's not a plan.
That's just saying
what you wish would happen.
Aye, and 12 herrings and a bagpipe
are just a pile of mince
if you havnae kent the rules.
You know,
that sounded a little negative to me.
Mac's right. We need more details.
We only get one shot at this,
so we need to make sure
that every move we make
is carefully thought through.
We can't just rush in and...
Uh, Rocky?
What are you doing?
Sometimes you just gotta take a leap,
Ginger.
- You ready, Fowler?
- Ready.
- Fire.
- Rocky.
Cock-a-doodle...
Huh?
Whoa!
Ooh, that went well.
Well, one good thing.
At least now we've got the details.
Right.
We're gonna need some backup.
No way. That place is impenetrable.
Yeah, and you can't get in neither.
It's an impossible mission.
Uh, shouldn't it be the other way around?
Don't be a 'nana, Fetch.
I know it looks
like a million-to-one shot,
but we know the layout,
and Mac thinks there's a way in.
This is Fun Land Farm.
Oh!
It's much smaller than I expected.
Uh, thanks, Babs.
There's a wee side door in a blind spot.
With a cheeky wee trick to open it.
So, only the small matter
of this electric fence.
All these guards.
The camera-driven gun-toting moles.
And the laser-guided exploding ducks.
Please. You've got to help us.
Rocky's in there.
Ah, shame. I quite liked him.
And so is Molly.
Molly? Our little niece?
Steady, mate.
Stay strong.
- So you're in?
- Just tell us what you need.
Anything for our little Molly!
We can do this, everyone.
Bunty, with your strength, my love,
we can move mountains.
Mac, you're the brains.
Babs, you're our... wool specialist.
Ah.
Nick and Fetch,
you're the sneakiest little toerags
this side of the Dales.
Oh.
- You're too kind.
- Flatterer.
And, Fowler, with your wisdom
and vigilance...
Fowler?
Ooh. And then the second wave
of bombers approach the target,
and that's where I come in.
Actually, Fowler,
we need to find something special for you.
Ah, right.
How about... getaway man?
Getaway man, eh?
Hmm. Sounds important.
I like it.
Right. Let's gather what we need
and hurry.
Who knows what horrors
Molly is dealing with in there.
Whoo-hoo!
- Wow!
- This place is fun!
It's the most amazin' place ever.
And my mum said that's where we live.
Yeah, right.
Are the streets paved
with marshmallows where you live?
Can ya bounce on them?
No! They're paved with dirt.
Can you lie around doin' nothin' all day?
Actually, my dad can.
Well, everyone can do that here.
Wow.
I've heard of this,
but I never knew it actually existed.
Cool. What is it?
All-you-can-eat buffet.
Hey!
Cooler than a penguin's toenails.
Right?
Mm!
Whee!
It's just, back home, I had jobs to do.
I helped Mac with the harvester,
helped Bunty pick carrots,
made yarn with Babs.
But here, it's just play.
And then more play.
I wonder if they're missing me.
It's great, innit?
We're free to do whatever we want.
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
Come on!
Whee!
Yay!
Sorry.
Hmm?
Whee!
- Ooh!
- Ah!
Huh?
Whee!
Hmm?
Ah.
Oh! Uh-oh!
Uh... Um...
Uh... Frizzle!
There's actually something strange
about this place.
I'll say.
Ever seen anything like this before?
Oh no, what's this?
You aren't supposed to be back there,
number...
Hmm.
You don't have a number?
We don't want chickens
making any trouble here.
Especially not today.
Okay, everyone. It's go time.
It's all right. I went before we left.
Hmm.
Mm!
What the... Huh?
Huh?
Oh!
No, you mug.
It's upside down.
Oh right.
Mm.
Go! Go! Go!
Yup?
All clear.
Ah.
Let's go.
Oh!
Perfect landin'.
Right on the button.
Right on the button?
Mm. Okay.
Let me out!
The camera!
I've got it.
Huh?
Hmm?
Mm.
Huh?
- Hmm?
- Hmm.
"Getaway man," she said.
More like taxi driver
for a couple of rats.
There. Textbook landing.
Ah, oh.
At ease, soldier.
I reckon they think
I'm too old for this caper.
Some rambling old rooster
who's easily distracted.
Hm. Oh, actually,
there's quite an amusing story about that.
One time, I was out rambling...
Well, on maneuvers, and...
All right.
I'm inside.
Huh?
Get off of me.
Oh. Uh, ooh.
Nick, uh, I don't wanna worry you,
but I think your bum just spoke.
Huh?
Guys? What are you doin' here?
Rocky!
We're with Ginger.
Uh, we've come to rescue ya.
Rescue me?
No, no. I'm doing the rescuing.
I'm not being rescued.
I am rescuing Molly.
How's that going, then?
Well...
Look, don't take this the wrong way,
but you guys are just gonna hold me back.
I tend to work alone.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, the Lone Free Ranger.
Right? And I am close.
I can feel it.
I'm gettin' warm, boys.
Really warm, actually.
Can anyone smell roast chicken?
I said you'd hold me back!
Whoa!
Huh?
Oh dear.
We actually planned that.
Did we?
Okay. I've gotta go find Molly.
Molly?
Hold it back, son. Hold it back.
Ah.
Look at them.
- It's like they're all a bit... brainless.
- Ah.
Erm. I don't think I like it here.
Yeah. It's not as much fun
as it looked on the poster, is it?
Hey, Frizzle.
Maybe we should try and find out
what's going on in this place.
Now, that sounds like
a real adventure.
Come on.
Let's investigate.
Ah!
Come on, now,
you naughty little thing.
I'm just your big chicken friend
who only wants you to be happy.
Frizzle!
What was that?
Hello.
Who are you?
What?
It's me. Molly.
Happy to meet you.
Frizzle, what's this?
Huh?
Come on, Frizzle.
We've got to go.
But I've never been so happy.
Whee!
No.
I'm big...
...and I'm brave.
Frizzle.
Listen. I'm going to find out
what's going on here.
Then I will be back.
I promise.
Huh?
Whoa.
Dr. Fry, your guest has arrived.
Sir Eat-a-Lot.
Right.
It's showtime.
Ah, Sir Eat-a-Lot! Welcome.
What an honor
to have a knight of the realm with us.
Actually, Sir Eat-a-Lot
is just the name of the restaurant.
My name is... Oh.
Oh.
Here at Fun Land Farms,
we do everything we can
to make our chickens feel right at home.
Well, I must say, I've never seen
a farm like this before, Dr. Fry.
Is all this security really necessary?
Oh yes.
Molly.
You see, behind these doors are secrets
that will change
the world of poultry technology forever.
Come on.
No!
Oi, what are you lot doing?
Attack!
This place is a maze.
How am I ever gonna find Molly in here?
- There she is.
- Huh?
Molly?
Molly! Molly!
And, um,
how's the restaurant business?
Actually, a little slow.
Oh well,
I think we can help you with that.
Molly!
No! No!
Molly! Molly! Molly!
Ah. Ginger?
Right. I'm gone.
Well, can't we just take the lift?
All I can say, Dr. Fry,
is this had better be...
good.
My, uh, partner
will be joining us shortly.
In the meantime, we've prepared
a little presentation.
Please, be seated.
This is an ordinary chicken.
Plain, dull, and easily frightened.
Like any simpleminded creature,
its natural instincts,
when faced with processing,
is fear and panic.
When this occurs,
the muscles tense,
which cause the connective tissues
to form knots.
The result?
Meat that is tough, dry, and flavorless.
Mummy, this meat is tough,
dry, and flavorless.
- I hate you, Mummy.
- Oh!
Molly.
Fear not,
underappreciated mother.
For what if science could change all that?
For what if science could alter
a chicken's response to fear?
What if it could make
a chicken happy to be processed?
Then you'd say,
"Well done, science."
Because a happy chicken
is a tasty chicken.
This is the most delicious chicken
in the whole wide world.
I love you, Mummy.
Thank you, science.
Molly.
That's a clever little cartoon, Dr. Fry.
But will you be able to do it?
We already have.
That voice.
Allow me to introduce my wife.
Melisha Tweedy.
Welcome to the future.
It's her.
Darling, this is Sir Eat-a-Lot.
The name is Reginald Smith.
Sir Eat-a-Lot
is just the name of the restaurant chain.
Hello, Reginald.
I see you've met
my current husband, Dr. Fry.
Was I attracted to his large inheritance
and vast acres of land?
No, it was his mind.
You probably can't tell
by looking at him, but he's a genius.
You flatter me, darling.
With degrees from Oxford
and Cambridge in clinical neurology,
behavioral psychology,
genetic engineering...
And drama!
Now you've had the appetizer,
time for the main course.
Come.
Molly, no. Get back.
Let me go!
Right. Try and find Molly.
Oh, look.
Rocky and the rats are on telly.
Looks like a real cliffhanger.
Where is she?
Oh.
Oh, look.
They like the new egg cup ride.
Frizzle.
Mum?
Oh, Mollypod.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Promise never to run away again.
- Did they hurt you?
- I'm fine, but I think they eat...
- Come on. Get on with it.
- Shh.
Right you are, pumpkin.
Behold.
The remote control.
And the other remote controls.
Why three?
Nobody knows.
Let's go with...
that one.
Huh?
- Why am I playing golf?
- Where am I?
- What am I doing?
- Molly? Where are you, Molly?
What's going on?
No, no, no.
Wrong one, my angel.
That's the off button.
Ah!
Allow me.
It's me.
Whoa!
Ah!
Ooh!
She's won the prize.
Oh wow.
What a lucky ducky!
Ooh!
No. Stop.
Run, chicken! Run!
Bye!
Have a nice time!
Look at me, and do not look away.
Behold,
the dawn of the nugget.
Mm!
I love you, Mummy.
Um... Um, I... I... I mean, it's delicious.
Picture it.
On every street, in every town.
People on the go.
Modern people in a modern world.
They want their food,
and they want it fast.
And we will give it to them
by the bucketful.
Fast food.
I like it. This could be big.
No. It will be huge.
And Melisha Tweedy will have her revenge.
Revenge?
Revenue. That's what I meant.
I'll send a truck to collect
the first batch at dawn tomorrow.
With my nuggets
and your chain of restaurants,
this is going to be
a beautiful partnership.
Ah.
Uh, shall I see you to your car,
Your Sirness?
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
No, wait. We can't go without Frizzle.
Frizzle? Who's Frizzle?
She's my friend. I can't just leave her.
I promised I'd come back.
Please, Molly. You don't understand.
But you saw what happens. She'll die.
And if we don't leave here now,
then we will die too.
I don't care. I'm not leaving her here.
You are just a child,
and you have no idea
who you're dealing with.
Uh...
Bye-bye.
You!
Huh?
Come back here!
Well now, the little escape artist.
You won't ruin this.
Not again.
Come back immediately, Doctor.
And bring a collar.
We've an unexpected guest.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Stop.
You're pushin' us too hard, cuz.
I ain't been this knackered
since I took that hamster wheel
for a test-drive.
- Here she is.
- Shh. Listen.
The miserable,
malcontented chicken
that escaped Tweedy's Farm
and ruined my life.
What is this bloomin' place?
Molly, where are you?
Ooh! He's laddered me knitting.
Run!
I gave you
all a hen could want.
A warm hut,
all the feed you could eat.
But you still weren't happy.
Well, I'm gonna make ya happy now.
Mum.
I've gotta get in there.
Ah, I've got an idea.
- You're the Lone Free Ranger, right?
- Yeah.
You used to get shot
out of a cannon, right?
That is all... Why?
Huh? Ah?
It's not working. Turn up the power.
The equipment's in good order, my love.
I've just never seen a chicken
so strong-willed.
You don't know
the half of it.
Turn it up to full power.
Full power?
But we've never tested it
at that.
Must I do everything myself?
Husbands and chickens,
the bane of my life.
Huh?
Sure you can make this work?
Oh yeah. There is nothing
Fetch don't know about electrics.
He could chew through wiring
before he could walk.
- Ready.
- Great work, boys.
I'm ready to fly.
Goodbye, cuz.
Or should I say, "au revoir."
It's more likely goodbye, to be honest.
Hmm?
Let's go.
Come on, Mum.
Mum? Who's Mum?
You are. And we have to get out of here.
Why? I love it here.
I'm so happy.
No.
Huh?
Dad?
Molly.
Hmm.
Right.
Whoo!
Huh?
He's got some moves.
Mum, wait.
Ha!
♪ We can't fly, we are chickens! ♪
Ow!
Get him.
- Come here, you.
- Oi!
Hey! Get him.
Ow!
Find those chickens!
♪ I'm H-A-P-P-Y! ♪
♪ I know I am! I'm sure I am! ♪
- Come on!
- Shush, Mum. We have to be quiet.
- But I want to sing!
- Shh!
- Just follow me.
- Oh, goody.
Are we going on holiday?
No, we have to find Frizzle
and Dad and get out of here.
But why?
Because I say so.
Well, you're not the boss of me.
I can see my feet.
Where'd they go?
- Come on, Mum.
- Come on!
- This way!
- Cooee!
Huh?
Wait up!
Come on. Let's get a shimmy on.
Ginger. Oh, thank heavens you escaped.
I can't believe we're back up
against that horrible woman.
What? Mrs. Tweedy's the best.
- I love her.
- Bunty.
- Mac. It's this collar.
- She's the loveliest.
- It's making Mum act weird.
- The bestest.
Molly!
- Ooh!
- Cooee!
Huh?
- Ha. Got him.
- Uncle Nick?
Uncle Fetch.
How did you find us?
- We just fell down the air vent.
- Love, Molly.
Love showed us the way.
Going up.
- Cooee!
- Ginger!
Mum!
♪ I'm H-A-P-P-Y ♪
♪ I know I am ♪
- ♪ I'm sure I am ♪
- It won't budge.
- ♪ I'm H-A-P-P-Y ♪
- Ooh. Babs, what's in your bag?
Uh, not much, I'm afraid.
Magic.
The very dab.
That tickles.
Oh.
It's like being
inside a giant biscuit tin.
But without any biscuits.
I've lost my specs.
I cannae see a sausage.
Mum?
Mum!
Molly?
You're okay.
Oh, Molly.
What happened? Where are we?
Don't know, but there's no way out.
There's never no way out.
Where's Rocky?
I saw him back in that big room.
He saved us.
He did?
Huh?
Oh!
Come on. We can do it this time.
I can't hold this much longer.
Fetcher, quickly!
Find a ledge or a crack to grab hold of!
Righto.
Ooh! Not that crack.
Oh!
Face the facts, duck.
We need a miracle to get out of here.
Hey! Anyone down there?
- Dad!
- Rocky!
Do not tell him he's our miracle.
There'll be no living with him.
Rocky is on the case.
No! Don't jump!
What? What's that?
I can't hear you! Wait. I'm comin' down!
Don't jump!
Oh! Family hug!
Oh, I missed you guys.
Okay. Well, let's blow this henhouse
and head home.
Ah.
That's the way out, isn't it?
I am so sorry.
Molly, what's wrong?
This is all my fault.
I should have listened to you
and done what I was told.
Now everything is a mess.
Hey, where's my big, brave girl?
That girl's stupid.
You were right.
If we ever get home, I'll just stay there
and never leave. Ever.
Hey, no. Molly.
This is my fault.
I should not have told you all
of that ridiculous Lone Free Ranger stuff.
No, this is on me.
I used to hate being fenced in.
So why did I expect you
to be any different?
I guess I was afraid
you were so much like me.
What's wrong with being like you?
Nothing.
Because your mom is the best.
And she always has a plan.
Not this time.
He's here.
Are we ready to fry, Fry?
Five minutes, pumpkin.
- Make it four.
- Oh.
Where is she?
Hmm?
Them runaway chickens, uh,
have got themselves stuck in a corn silo.
In the silo, you say?
Excellent. I'll go and greet our guest.
Production starts in three minutes.
Three?
Looks like you've just run out of cluck,
little chickens.
Huh?
I think there's a grinder
at the bottom of this thing.
On the plus side, though,
we will all probably drown
before we're ground into tiny, wee pieces.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Popcorn.
Popcorn, everyone. Look.
Look, popcorn.
Rocky, I don't think this is the time to...
Ah.
The answer to all life's problems.
Of course.
Mac, we need heat.
- Lots of it.
- Oh.
Will this work?
Perfect.
Now, does anyone have a match?
Yeah, you and a raving lunatic.
You'll blow us all to bits.
Besides, we've used the last one.
Oh no.
That's my girl.
Um, can I once again raise
my health and safety concerns?
What is it?
Huh?
All right.
Oh!
Mm. That tastes nice.
Is there any more?
But guess what?
Just as Whizzbang Charlie
thought we were back in Blighty,
enemy fire at six o'clock.
Ye gods. It's raining popcorn?
Good old British weather.
Unpredictable.
You never know what's coming.
Outrageous.
Hmm?
- Get in there!
- We made it.
- Look.
- Whoo-hoo!
Fowler's only gone
and set up our escape route.
Well done, you old sausage.
Firm handshake will do, thank you.
Mission accomplished.
Now let's fly this crazy coop, huh?
Oh yes.
Oh, look, Nick.
Have we got snacks for the way home?
All right. On you go.
Mm.
Ginger, are you coming?
No, I'm not.
I'm going back.
For Frizzle?
For Frizzle and all the chickens.
Yes!
Just because where we live is cut off
from the world doesn't mean we are too.
No chicken is an island.
Hmm.
We are with you, Ginger.
Aye, me too.
Me four.
The rats are in.
Right. What's the plan, Mum?
Oh, well, I didn't think you...
Rocky.
Hey, Molly, um,
are you sure you're ready for this?
I was hatched ready, Dad.
She is a lot like me.
Dr. Fry!
What was that noise up on the roof?
Sounded like an explosion.
Looks like one of the silos
has blown its top.
Oh.
Maybe you shouldn't have put
those chickens
through the grinder, my love.
Don't be ridiculous.
Melisha,
all ready for the big day?
Oh yes, Reginald.
Everything is tickety-boo.
Jolly good.
My truck is ready to go.
We've got to move fast.
While Tweedy is busy
with her guest outside,
we sneak back in.
Molly, you take Bunty, Babs and Mac
to where all the chickens are.
Come on.
- This way.
- Ah.
Stay out of sight
and get ready to stop
the chickens going up that staircase.
Rocky, we've got
to get hold of that button.
And disable those collars.
As soon as the collars are off,
Molly's team leads the chickens
out of there.
We bust our way out.
Steal the truck,
then we're home free.
Well, what are we waiting for?
- All right. Let's do this.
- We're doing it today, are we?
So where was I? Ah, yes.
Whizzbang Charlie had lost
his undercarriage,
and the old crate was catching fire...
Actually, Melisha,
I have a little something for our big day.
Why, Reginald,
this is all very sudden.
Uh...
Ketchup?
Oh. No, no.
Something completely new.
I call it "the dip."
It's... sweet.
And sour.
Aren't we all, Reginald?
Dr. Fry?
Yes, my beloved?
Say those words I am longing to hear.
Get on with it, you idiot.
Ooh.
It's the funky chicken
and the ginger one too.
Oh no, my wife
will not be happy with this.
Come on here now,
you naughty little chickens!
Oh dear.
See you on the flip side, egghead.
You get it?
Dr. Fry? What's going on up there?
Quick. Come on.
Dr. Fry! Dr. Fry!
- Hello?
- Dr. Fry!
- Anybody there?
Dr. Fry!
Where are my nuggets?
Honestly, that man is about
as much use as a headless...
Chicken!
Ha ha!
Huh?
Let's make some nuggets.
Oh no.
Huh?
Ah!
No. This is not good, Mac.
- Oh, Frizzle. Where are you?
- Ooh!
My turn. Bye-bye.
Frizzle!
Lovely sunshine.
- No, wait.
- Hold on to her.
♪ We're goin' where the sea is blue ♪
Mac, hurry.
- Ooh!
- ♪ We've seen it in the movies... ♪
I got it. I got it.
I don't got it!
Rocky.
Huh?
♪ For me and you ♪
Go, Ginger!
♪ We're all goin' on a summer holiday ♪
♪ No more workin' for a week or two... ♪
Come on, everybody.
We're goin' on holiday.
No, Babs.
They're going to turn everyone
into nuggets.
♪ For a week or two ♪
♪ We're going
Where the sun shines brightly... ♪
Not now, mate.
♪ Where the sea is blue ♪
♪ We've seen it in the movies ♪
Please, Mac. Hurry.
Nearly done.
Just one more bit of jiggerypokery, and...
What happened? What's goin' on?
Frizzle, this isn't the best place ever.
You only get your own bucket
when they've chopped you up
and cooked you.
And you came back for me?
Of course.
It's me and you, kidda. All the way.
Time to go!
Try to push them back!
- There's too many!
- Ooh!
Is this one of the activities?
Ah!
Ooh!
Huh?
Whee!
- Whee!
Mum!
Ginger!
Whoo!
Look. There's all the buckets!
The button!
That's it.
Frizzle, get on Bunty's shoulders.
What?
Trust me.
Up ya get.
Good goin', Molly.
Good job, Molly!
Huh?
Ah.
Molly?
I got this, Dad. Help Mum.
Uh...
Molly, watch out.
Huh?
Ha!
What have we here?
- A little you.
- Mum, catch.
They're going over, Mum!
Ginger, we can't hold them!
Uh...
Uh-uh-uh!
You can't wait, Mum. Do it now!
Sometimes...
you've just got to take a leap.
No!
- Cock-a-doodle-doo!
- Huh?
- Ah!
No! No! No!
Oh!
Ginger!
Ah.
I got ya. I got ya.
Well, now.
I suppose you three
might make a bucketful.
Hmm?
Bye-bye.
Again.
Huh?
Come on.
Ugh. What's taking so long?
So much for fast food.
Hmm.
Ah.
That's funny. Sounds like a...
...stampede!
- Get your skates on.
- Move your tail feathers.
- Come on.
- Come on!
You sure you know how this works?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go, stop, and a spare one?
Come on! We have to go!
Full speed ahead!
Wrong way!
What gear are you in?
Oh, I call this "smart casual."
Ah, you there!
What kind of crazy henhouse is this?
Oh.
Melisha?
Why are you dressed like a nugget?
There's the exit!
Get her off!
Hmm?
I think they're gonna need
a bigger bucket.
- Chocks away!
- Huh?
Ha ha!
T.I. Fowler, Getaway Division.
Reporting for duty.
Where would we be without you, Fowler?
Darling! Darling!
- Blech.
- Darling!
The processor is dangerously overheating.
Oh.
Huh?
Uh...
Pumpkin, watch out for the, uh...
- Oh blast!
- What?
I think I left my umbrella
in there.
Oh! The best thing about going on holiday
is getting back home, isn't it?
Yes, it is. Isn't it, Babs?
Ooh!
- Oh!
- All fixed.
Just had a screw loose.
Good to have a bucket or two handy
in case you're feeling peckish.
Plenty for everyone.
This makes you happy
and brainless, apparently.
Oh yeah, I feel it.
It's amazin'.
Mate, I haven't turned it on yet.
Well, it looks like we've finally got
our happy ending.
Ah, let's just call this
our happy beginning.
Sergeant Molly,
reporting from reconnaissance.
Chicken farm, beyond the north field.
Thirty birds to a cage.
Poor little kiddas.
Right, everyone.
I don't like this one bit.
It's go time.
I've just got one question.
Is crowing back on the agenda?
Oh, definitely.
Ready, everyone?
- Ready!
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
♪ Let me tell you all about my baby ♪
♪ You will never find her misbehavin' ♪
♪ Oh, she's such a dime ♪
♪ I think I found the brightest star
Up in the sky ♪
♪ Just one little look
And she'll disarm ya ♪
♪ Everybody tells me she's a charmer ♪
♪ Never gets in trouble
She's the apple of my eye ♪
♪ She's so sweet ♪
♪ Like butter wouldn't melt, heavenly ♪
♪ With a little bit of hell I need ♪
♪ To keep her to myself, no need ♪
♪ What would I do? ♪
♪ Do ♪
♪ Without my sweet ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Cherry pie, buttercup
Sugar, little honeybee ♪
♪ Never thought
That I would love another ♪
♪ Words, they can't describe
The way I love her ♪
♪ She fills my cup all the way up ♪
♪ Can't get enough, I know ♪
♪ Sometimes she drives me crazy ♪
♪ I never could get mad at my baby ♪
♪ Don't want her changin' ♪
♪ I just want her by my side ♪
♪ For my whole life ♪
♪ She's the brightest light ♪
♪ In the highest ♪
♪ What would I do? ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Without my sweet baby ♪
♪ Cherry pie, buttercup
She's still got the world to see ♪