Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ I see the crystal raindrops fall ♪
♪ And the beauty of it all ♪
♪ Is when the moon comes shining through ♪
♪ To make those cobwebs in my mind ♪
♪ When I think of you sometime ♪
♪ And I want to spend it with you ♪
♪ Just the two of us ♪
♪ We can make it if we try ♪
- ♪ Just the two of us ♪
- Shh.
♪ The two of us ♪
♪ Just the two of us ♪
♪ Here in the hotel safe and sound ♪
- ♪ Just the two of us ♪
- Huh?
♪ You and I ♪
♪ We are together, you and I ♪
♪ Oh, how quickly the time flies ♪
♪ I wish nothing would change ♪
Whee!
♪ Just the two of us ♪
♪ We can make it if we try ♪
- ♪ Just the three of us ♪
- Huh?
♪ We can make it if we try ♪
♪ Just the three of us ♪
♪ You, you and I ♪
♪ Living in Hotel Transylvania ♪
♪ Just the three of us ♪
♪ You, you and I ♪
♪ That's right, just the three of us ♪
♪ We can make it if we try ♪
♪ Just the three of us ♪
♪ You, you and I. ♪
Here's to Hotel Transylvania!
Celebrating 125 years!
Hear! Hear!
- Way to go, Drac!
- Well done!
Yes.
So great.
Thank you, Johnny.
What a wonderful surprise that was.
But now it's time to start
the actual planned part
of the celebration.
- That was only the beginning, Drac.
- Huh?
You just sit back and enjoy
your anniversary party.
Relax, Dad.
Johnny worked so hard
to make this extra special.
He has everything under control.
Oh, no.
It's a Johnny takeover celebration!
Hit it!
- Send in the dogs!
- Dogs?
Happy hotel anniversary, Papa Drac!
Good boy.
Let's do it, Frank!
Isn't this great? Johnny taught me!
And we only had to replace
his hands twice during rehearsals.
Ice sculpture, go!
Pyrotechnics!
Oh, yeah!
"Very phine a..."
Ooh! Oh, no!
Oh! Huh?
Fire!
Oh, that's not good.
Okay, that's enough.
Wh...
Uh, Dad?
Oh, right.
Can't freeze other vampires.
Oh, hey, Mavey Wavey!
Just making a couple of tiny adjustments.
Dad, Johnny did all of this for you.
He was trying to make this day special.
Oh, you mean
by ruining my carefully planned party.
Wow, thank you, dear son-in-law.
- What was that?
- Oh, hey, nothing, honeybat.
Dad, I know you and Johnny
don't always see eye to eye,
but I love him
and I wouldn't change a thing.
Really?
You sure you wouldn't make
just a few teensy changes?
- Better, no?
- No!
He's perfect just the way he is.
Okay, okay.
Whatever you say, honeybat.
Now, let's continue this special day,
'cause it's gonna get
even more specialier.
All right, what are you up to?
What, me? Nothing.
Huh? Oh.
Whoa.
I guess I killed it.
All right, next up, we got...
Thank you, Johnny.
How wonderful.
And don't forget, precisely at midnight,
I will make a special
once-in-a-lifetime announcement!
In the meantime,
sit back and enjoy the band.
Yoo-hoo! You ready for
your big speech, honeyfangs?
Yes, I think so.
But Johnny is
giving me the greatest headache
of my entire existence right now,
like a giant wooden stake
right through my brain!
Oh, you know Johnny.
He just gets a little carried away.
Yes, exactly.
And ruins everything.
That's the problem.
Well, you're gonna have to
get used to things being done
a little differently around here
when you retire.
Shh!
...when you retire.
Retire?
Not so loud.
Mavis has supersonic hearing.
Why would she be listening?
Don't be so paranoid.
Yes, I-I'm sure you're right.
I just... I don't want
anything else to go wrong.
Everything has to be perfect
when I finally give the hotel to Mavis.
What?!
And Johnny.
Yes, and Johnny.
Oh, it is a big step.
I know how much this hotel means to you.
Ah, yes, but it is time to let go
and start a new chapter, together.
Well, you are just all sorts
of wonderful, aren't you?
Well, it's not for nothing
that they call me
Count Wonderful.
Oh. Do they?
And also
Dark Prince of Loveliness.
Mm-hmm.
Lord of Smoochy Time.
Oh, stop it, Drac.
Ew, ew. Ew-ew-ew-ew-ew-ew.
Whoa, cute ear, hon.
Holy rabies. Holy rabies!
You're never gonna believe it!
What? What's going on?
Johnny, you better sit down for this.
Babe, you're freaking me out here.
Dad is gonna retire
and leave us the hotel!
He's okay. He's okay.
Just a-a little too much sugar.
Whoa.
I didn't even know
he was thinking of retiring.
Shh. Neither did I.
Oh, my gosh, Mavis, I'm so happy for you.
You're gonna be amazing!
You mean we're going to be amazing.
Dad's leaving the hotel to both of us.
Really?
Both of us?
Are you sure?
Of course. Why wouldn't he?
Oh, uh, I don't know.
I-I guess I just never got the feeling
that he really thought of me as, you know,
part of the family.
What are you talking about?
Of course you're part of the family.
No, I know, but you know
how Cranky Fangs is sometimes.
I mean, it feels like I am,
but not really.
That's not true.
Well, not anymore it isn't!
Shh.
We can't spoil the surprise.
Right. Right, right, right,
right, right, right.
I better walk this off.
Hey, how's it going? Nothing to see.
Nothing much to talk about,
except for the greatest thing
happening in the entire universe.
Oh, oh, there he is.
Hey, Drac! Hey, Drac!
Oh, no. No.
Just keep it cool, Johnny.
There will be plenty of time
to thank him after.
All right, let's see here.
Uh, dearest family, friends...
and, uh, and honored guests,
I have started a new phase in my life,
and I feel it is time
to begin a new chapter
for Hotel Transylvania.
So, I am extremely proud
and honored to give
the key to the hotel to...
Drac!
I can't believe it. I can't believe it.
I'm gonna explode into
a thousand little excited bits.
And then those little excited bits
are gonna explode into
millions of tiny little excited bits!
- What?
- Oh, mighty king,
it is with all my heart
that I accept this great honor.
- Honor?
- With this mighty key,
I will unlock the future
and usher in a new destiny
for the great Hotel Transylvania!
- Yeah?
- Oh! So many great ideas.
I'm dizzy with hospitality creativity.
Like horizontal escalators
all through the lobby,
name tags for all guests
for more casual relations,
green-energy-saving options...
...stationary bikes in every room
for your own power source.
It's gonna be
the ultimate Johnny takeover!
Yah!
I can't do it!
I thought I could give the hotel
to Mavis and Johnny,
but he's going to ruin everything!
I have to get out of this. I have to.
I... I...
Ah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
Sir Johnny.
I think that there has been
a misunderstanding.
I actually...
can't give you the hotel.
- What?
- Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
It is an old, very, very old,
very ancient, very serious
real estate law!
- Real estate law?
- Yes, yes.
It says,
"No residence, whether it be
residential or commercial,
"shall ever be transferred to,
owned by or inherited
"to a human.
"For if it did, to wit,
then that property shall be
forfeited and repossessed unto it."
Whoa. Those are some serious "its."
I am truly sorry.
I would absolutely love
to give you the hotel,
but, you know,
you're not a monster, so can't.
But then what's the big announcement?
Huh?
Uh, uh...
Excited for the big announcement?
You have no idea.
Oh, think, think, think.
Oh, you've got to announce something.
There you are. You almost missed it.
Uh-huh.
Uh...
Uh, dearest friends and...
What is wrong with him?
- Boy, is he nervous.
- This is hard to watch.
Get on with it!
- Griffin!
- What? He's dying up there.
I know, but you have to be respectful.
Get on with it already!
I...
Dearest family, friends and, uh,
and honored guests,
I... I have started
a new phase, uh, in my life.
Here it comes.
And I feel that now is the time for
Hotel Transylvania to, um...
uh... uh...
Oh. Expand!
Yes!
We are expanding the hotel!
What?!
Yes, yes.
In order to address
the increasingly long lines,
I am pleased to announce
we will be adding
a new restroom to the lobby.
Can't never have enough bathrooms.
But...
but I thought I heard...
Oh, man, this is all my fault.
So, let's get on with the party!
Take it away, Blobby!
♪ We're gonna get funky, funky ♪
Oh, yeah.
♪ Everybody, clap your hands ♪
♪ Clap, clap, clap, clap your hands ♪
♪ All right, now,
we're gonna do the basic step ♪
♪ To the left ♪
♪ Take it back now, y'all ♪
♪ One hop this time ♪
♪ Right foot, let's stomp ♪
♪ Left foot, let's stomp ♪
- ♪ Cha-cha real smooth ♪
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Check it out.
♪ Turn it out ♪
♪ To the left ♪
♪ Take it back now, y'all ♪
♪ One hop this time ♪
♪ Right foot, let's stomp ♪
♪ Left foot, let's stomp ♪
♪ Cha-cha now, y'all ♪
♪ Now it's time to get funky ♪
♪ To the right now... ♪
Okay. That worked.
♪ One hop this time... ♪
Now you just have to get
your thoughts together
before you run into...
Ericka!
Uh, what happened up there?
Oh. Wh-What?
What was that, sweetheart?
The music... it is so booming.
Oh, yeah, feel it, baby.
Drac!
Whew, that was close.
- Mavis!
- A new restroom?
Really, Dad?
That was the big surprise?
There wasn't anything else
you were gonna announce?
Like what?
Like... I don't know... your retirement.
What?! Uh...
Oh! Listen to those, uh,
dope-tastic beats.
- Uh, shake a leg, honeybat.
- Dad, wait!
Oh, man, this is all my fault.
I ruined everything,
all because I'm not a monster.
So you want to become a monster, huh?
Van Helsing?
I can help with that.
I've got just the thing down in my lab.
The question is:
Where did I put it?
Whoa.
Ooh.
It's all organized very unique...
- Don't touch anything!
- Sorry.
Not there.
- Whoa.
- Ah, that's not it.
It must be in the back somewhere.
Come on, hurry up!
Right through here.
Keep up! Yeah!
Alley-oop!
Whoa.
I know it's around here somewhere.
Hello?
Van Helsing?
Aha!
Found it!
Behold, the Monsterfication Ray.
It turns any human into a monster.
Awesome!
But is it safe, though?
Great question.
What we need is a guinea pig.
Meet Gigi.
Aw. She's so cute.
Not for long.
Whoa!
Sign me up for teeth like these.
Ooh, and seven eyes
and laser vision and...
Oh, it doesn't work that way.
Who knows what sort of
hideous beast you'll become?
So let's find out.
Don't worry, Mavis.
This is gonna fix everything.
Lay it on me, bro!
Huh?
Huh, that's weird.
Nothing happened.
I don't feel so good.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Huh?
Uh-oh.
Dad?
Drac?
Honey? Sweetheart?
Dad?
Whew.
What is that?
Hello?
Van Helsing?
Is everything okay down here?
Huh?
Hello?
Who's there?
Hey, Drac, what's up?
Wha... uh, Johnny?
Yeah, it's me.
Whoa!
I'm a monster.
Check out these big feet
and these claws... ooh...
and these ears... they're so pointy.
And, look, I've got a tail!
Why...
Why did you... How did you...
I used Van Helsing's monster ray.
Now you can give the hotel
to Mavis and me,
just like you wanted.
Oh, my gosh. Mavis!
She's gonna love the new me.
Let's go show her!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
Mavis?
Oh, no. Mavis is going to kill me.
Mavis! Mavis?
I'll fix that!
Mavis!
I got great news!
Got ya!
Ooh, pardon me.
What?
I-I can't believe it.
The nightmare... it's over!
I'm human again!
Huh?
I better be careful.
There are monsters everywhere.
Oh, excuse me.
- Coming through.
- No, no, no, no, no!
Mavis?
This is gonna be the coolest surprise
when you see the surprise!
H-Hey! Tinkles!
Hey, Dennis. Hey, Winnie.
Dad? Is that you?
Yeah! Isn't it great?
I got to go show your mom.
Papa Drac, is that my dad?
That was not your father,
just some random monster.
Everything is normal.
Mavis? Where are you?
The party!
Mavis, I've got the best news ever!
Whoa-oh!
Oh, no.
Drac?
Oh, no!
Something's wrong!
Don't worry!
I got you, Drac!
Hey, Frank, relax.
It's not a contest.
- Huh?
Drac?
Hey, guys.
Johnny?
Is that you?!
Yeah, it's me.
Pretty great, right?
- Whoa. - What's going on?
- What happened to you?
Wait, where's Drac?
Help!
Drac?
Hey, come on down here!
Did you see Johnny?
He's a monster!
I know!
I can't fly!
Did he just say "Wow, that's a fly"?
No, he definitely
said something about pie.
Stop fooling around and come down here!
I'm not fooling around!
I...
Uh, guys, he's not turning into a bat.
Don't worry. I got him.
- Whoa.
- Hey.
Drac?
Y-You-you look, uh, uh...
You look terrible.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No!
It can't be.
Wow, look at us, Drac.
You're human and I'm a monster.
It's like Freaky Friday
but on a Tuesday, though.
Where is it? Where is it?
It's got to be here somewhere.
What is going on, Drac?
I need to find the ray!
You mean that one right there?
Ooh-hoo-hoo!
Come on. Come on!
Why isn't this working? Come on!
I think it might be broken.
No!
It can't be.
Hey, have you seen my dad?
Come on, Johnny.
We're getting out of here.
What? No way.
I got to tell Mavis
that her dream is back on.
You know, now that I'm a monster and all.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You will obey me.
You will come with me!
Hey, Mavis, I got great news!
Johnny.
Huh?
Hey, Drac, what's wrong?
Oh, it is the humanness!
Drac! Oh, my gosh!
Wh-What do we do?
Quick, take me to Van Helsing!
Oh, okay. I got you, Drac.
Do not tell Mavis!
Ooh! Ow-wee! The lab!
Hurry! I can feel my insides melting away!
Uh... wh-what just happened?
Hey.
Was that my dad?
No. What? Uh, no.
- Absolutely not.
- Nope.
Are you doing
something different with your hair?
Um, what is going on?
What's going on?
Um, Wayne here was about to
show off some new dance moves.
- Dance moves?
- Yeah, go get 'em.
- Whoa.
- Go get 'em.
Uh, um...
Yeah.
Oh.
Huh?
Okay.
Uh, well, if you see my dad,
please tell him I need to talk to him.
Oh, yeah.
Watch me now. Yeah.
Ow.
Well, it's broken.
The crystal's cracked,
and it's beyond repair.
Wait, what?!
Then get a new one!
Whoa. Someone's feeling better.
These crystals are very rare
and hard to come by.
It took me three years to find that one.
You see, I was a young
monster hunter at the time...
well, not too young, but I felt young.
Okay, don't need the whole story.
Well, luckily for you,
I was brilliant enough to install
a locator on the ray
for just this situation.
There it is!
- South America?!
- Oh, cool!
I was there once spelunking
with some Norwegian wrestlers.
We can just pop down there
and get a new one!
If it were but that simple, my friend.
First, you must travel through
the treacherous jungle.
Survival's doubtful.
Then down a perilous river...
Whoa.
...until you reach
the Cave of the Reflexión!
Where entering is deadly
and escape impossible!
It... it...
it cost me my right back wheel.
Uh, sorry for your loss?
Well, happy hunting.
This is a disaster!
Don't worry, Drac.
We'll get you back to your old self.
But first, I better tell Mavis
we're going.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
You can't tell Mavis!
Why not?
Uh, because, uh, you know, if you do,
then, uh, then she will
want to come with us,
and-and I was thinking that this could be
a-a father-son, uh, bonding type of thing.
Yes.
You know, just the two of us?
Really?
- Awesome!
- Hold up, hold up.
There'll be plenty of hugs on the trip.
All right, time to go.
Not a moment to waste!
Right.
Still human.
I-I don't know.
It took me by surprise.
It's, uh, kind of an improvement.
Right? I think Johnny looks
way better as a monster.
Yeah, there's a good-looking guy in there.
Ooh, and the green
really brings out his eyes.
Hey, it's Drac.
"Going to find crystal to fix ray
to turn us back to normal."
"Don't tell Mavis"?
Drac always does this.
I hate getting caught
between him and Mavis.
What should I write back?
How about, "No, we're not
covering for you anymore"?
Yeah, "Now that you're human,
you can't do nothing about it."
"Go do your own dirty work
for a change, buster."
Okay, got it. Send.
- What?! - What?!
- You actually sent that?!
Oh, man, we're in trouble now.
Nah, I just sent him a gif.
Oh, hey, Blobby, check it out.
That's a nice one, Blobby.
Hey, here's to Blobby.
No, Bl... No, Blobby.
I just said, "Here's a toast
to a bunch of great guys."
What does he think I said?
Cheers!
Huh? Whoa!
Something is happening.
Oh!
Oh.
Oh, no. No, nose, nose!
Uh, wh... why?
My stitches! Oh!
What the...
What's going on?
Huh?
What the...
My fur!
Oh, no, no. What's this, you guys?
Oh, I'm balding?
- What's happening?
- What the...
Naked!
Huh?
Wow.
What's up, fellas?
- Ooh.
- Oh, he got the worst of it.
Huh?
Wow.
Flying as a monster is so much better.
Right, Drac?
Feeling better?
Nervous flier, huh?
How is this plane even in the sky?!
What is that sound?
Do you smell burning?
Is that duct tape
holding the wing together?!
Okay, folks,
we've reached our cruising altitude.
We're not expecting any turbulence,
so sit back, relax and enjoy the ride.
Whoa, oh, oh.
Uh, hey, Drac?
I think you're turning back
into a monster.
I got to get to the bathroom!
Aw, are you feeling sick?
Yes.
I just need to...
Try spinning!
Huh. Maybe some food
will settle your stomach.
No? Or maybe some fresh air, then.
He seems better.
Yeah, thanks so much.
It's my job.
Dad?
I really need to talk to you.
Dad, are you in here?
Dad?
Where is he?
"...to give the key to the hotel
to my beloved daughter Mavis"?!
I was right!
Dad did want to give me the hotel.
But then what made him change his mind?
Oh, hey, sweetie.
Have you seen Papa Drac or your father?
That was not my father,
just some random monster.
Everything is normal.
Okay, yep, something's
definitely going on.
Whoa-ho-ho-ho-ho!
So cool!
Uh, are you sure
I can't help you with that?
I said I got it.
Huh?
The sun!
- Oh, no, the sun.
- Uh, Drac?
The sun won't fry you now.
You're human, remember?
It's totally safe.
The sun... it's...
magnificent.
I cannot believe that my whole life
I have missed this elegant splendor.
It's glorious.
It's wondrous.
It's... it's...
It's burning my eyes!
I'm blind!
Drac!
I can't see anything.
Whoopsie.
Is anyone there?
Ooh! Hello?
Johnny?
Whoa.
Huh?
Whoop. I got ya.
Pardon me!
Excuse me. Oops.
Coming through.
There you go.
Okay, you stay here.
I'll go get us a taxi.
Taxi!
Sorry!
Huh, that was weird.
I wonder what that was all about.
Huh?
Gigi?
Gigi!
Oops.
I swear...
you've gotten bigger.
Come on, Drac, join in!
Huh?
Why are we going so slowly?
Johnny?
Huh?
Your monsterness is weighing us down.
- We're getting nowhere.
- Really?
Whoa.
Don't worry, Drac.
I've got an idea.
Wait a second!
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah. ♪
Ooh.
All right, guys, coast is clear.
Have you seriously been naked
this whole time?
Uh, yeah.
Why would only my glasses be visible?
I-I don't get it. Why are we hiding?
'Cause if Mavis sees us,
she's gonna know something's up.
Look, Drac said he and Johnny
will be back with a cure.
We just need to lay low until then.
- Have you seen my dad?
- Have you seen your dad?
Huh?
No, I haven't seen him since the party.
Oh, hey, has anyone seen Wayne?
- Where is Frank?
- Shh!
He's been missing since the party.
Well, I haven't seen Frank or Wayne.
Yeah, has anybody seen 'em?
I hope they're not up to something.
I saw them on the dance floor...
Oops, almost forgot good old Blobby.
Frank?
Oh. Uh, hey, babe.
What's up?
♪ Sexy man. ♪
Frank, what did you do?!
And who are those guys?
Mavis, it's me, Uncle Griffin.
You don't recognize me?
Uh, no.
I've literally never seen you before.
Um, Murray?
In the 5,000-year-old flesh.
Oh, look at that. Well, that's fun.
I'm awake!
Wayne? Is that you?
Hey, where's Dad?
Um... your dad?
Uh, I don't know where your dad is.
I just got here.
I'm W-Walter.
Mom!
This is not funny, Wayne.
I'm not laughing.
I leave you alone for five minutes,
and you become a human?!
- Hey, chill.
- Cut it out.
Blobby's not dessert, okay?
Mavis, what is going on?
This just in.
Breaking news from our international desk.
Dad?
This was the scene
outside the local airport,
where an unidentified monster
saved a confused man
- dressed up in a Halloween costume.
- I got ya.
Wait, that looks kind of like...
Johnny?!
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Your dad's a human now,
and Johnny's a monster.
Oh, no.
I was not supposed to say that out loud.
Hey, thanks for the lift.
Huh?
Johnny. Johnny, hurry up.
Ah.
Adios, everybody.
Come on!
We don't have time for chitchat.
We've got to get through this jungle
if we're going to find the crystal.
Johnny, we are getting nowhere.
Don't worry, Drac.
I got you covered.
Huh?
And the final touch.
Now you're ready for the great outdoors.
Fine. Okay. Whatever.
- Can we please just get going?
- Hold up, Drac.
- Whoa!
- You forgot your trunk.
Okay, let's find that crystal.
Come on, Drac. You're gonna love hiking!
Aren't the sounds of nature soothing?
Ugh. What is that smell?
Oh. What is that?
Oh!
It's me!
Drac, chill. You just need a shower.
And where am I going to find a shower
in the middle of the jungle?
Huh?
Whoa.
Hmm.
Hey, I think you might have
a pollen allergy.
Nonsense. I...
Johnny!
How am I so wet
and yet completely dry?
How much further?
Huh?
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no!
We are never going to get there.
Whoa, Drac.
Isn't that something?
Water. Thank you.
I am melting.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold on, Drac.
You got to be extra careful
with strange bodies of water.
This one time, my friend Katmatchka and I
were backpacking in Thailand...
Drac?
Wahoo...!
Well, look on the bright side.
At least you're not hot anymore.
Ugh, I can't get through to them.
I'm not having any luck either.
I don't understand.
What are they doing in South America?
And how did they change themselves
in the first place?
Exactly. It's not like
there's a mad scientist
just living in the basement.
Oh.
Great-Grandfather, what did you... do?
Oh, no.
Great-Grandfather?
Oh. Hello, ladies.
A little busy at the moment.
What did you do to Johnny and my dad?!
Shh.
Lower your voice.
Is that... Gigi?
Turns out the ray is highly unstable.
The transformation keeps mutating
and won't stop until the subject becomes
a mindless, ravenous beast!
Keeps mutating?
Whoa!
Oh, no. Johnny!
Ericka!
Got it.
Hey! Gigi!
Over here!
We've got to find my dad and Johnny
before it's too late!
Ah, man.
Why didn't anyone tell me
that claws are so awesome?
Whoa.
Being a monster is super weird.
Yeah.
But being a human is the worst.
Ah, come on. I wouldn't say that.
Really?
Blisters, sunburn and swamp butt
aren't the worst?
What was that?
Mosquito!
Vampires of the jungle.
Hey, I resent that.
Yow!
They're everywhere! Yi!
Johnny, they're all over you!
What?
Monster skin.
Don't worry, Drac.
They can't bite me.
- Wha...?
- Hold still, Drac! I got him!
Johnny, wait!
Whoa.
- That is so cool!
- Yeah.
Ooh.
- Ooh.
- Whoa! Careful.
Yeah!
Wahoo!
Here, try this.
Seriously?
I look ridiculous.
Keep your shirt on, pal.
We've seen more than enough of you.
Me, on the other hand...
easy on the eyes.
- Ugh, please.
- Coming through!
Wendell, get down from there.
Wally, sweetie, uh-uh, don't touch that.
Wendy, no. Put that down.
Ow. Wesley, what did I just... Huh?
Oops.
My bad.
Whoa!
Hey!
Do not make me come back there!
I will turn this blimp around!
Sorry, Ericka.
Sorry, I didn't think leaving them
at a monster hotel would be safe.
Guess I didn't realize
your blimp would be such a, uh...
A monster-killing machine?
What? No.
Whoa!
Okay. Yeah, it's a death trap.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
All this... this is the old me.
Your dad helped me leave that all behind.
I hope he's okay.
Don't worry. We're gonna find them.
Okay, guys, we've made it.
Whoa!
It's enormous.
How we gonna find them in there?
I think I have an idea.
Well, we're gonna have to take
this search to the ground.
I have just the thing.
Oh, my hair!
Oh, my hair.
Where's Blobby?!
Okay, Mavis, what's the plan?
♪ Just the two of us ♪
♪ Father and son-in-law. ♪
Got 'em.
That way!
Oh! My head!
What? What's going on?
Have a good nap?
Nap? You slapped me so hard
I lost consciousness!
But I did get that mosquito.
Hey, where are we?
Just following the ping.
Let me see that.
Okay.
It seems like we're going
in the right direction.
Huh?
Wh-What's going on?
Oh, what's wrong with this thing?
We lost the signal.
- Why would it just...
- Whoops!
Whoa.
Huh. I think we took a wrong turn.
You took a wrong turn!
I can't trust you to do anything right!
Now put me down!
- No, Drac. Hey. Hey.
- Get your claws off me!
We're really high up. Whoa.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hey!
- Put me down! Put me down!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Put me...
Drac!
Ow, ow, ee!
- Johnny, your tail!
- Ah, sorry!
Your foot!
Your wings, Johnny!
Wings?
Johnny! You've got wings!
Flap, Johnny, flap!
- Fly!
- I can't! I can't!
Drac, what do we do?!
- Drac!
- Johnny, Johnny, calm down!
- Can you wiggle your nose?
- Uh-huh.
- Wiggle your toes.
- Okay.
Flap your wings!
I... I-I can't.
I can't do it.
You're doing it, Johnny!
You're flying!
What? I'm-I'm flying?
I'm flying!
I did it, Drac!
Drac?
Johnny!
You-you did it.
You're flying!
Yeah.
I'm really getting the hang of this!
- Wow!
- This is amazing!
Yeah!
Flap, Johnny, flap.
Right, right. Flapping. I'm flapping.
Wha... Whoa!
- Whoa!
- Johnny, sit down.
You're going to put out the fire.
Ah, man. Boy, that was fun.
Right. Getting lost
and almost falling to your death
is super fun.
Okay, Mr. Cranky Fangs.
Whatever you say.
What are you talking about?
Ah, no, it's ruined.
See? That.
That's what I'm talking about.
If you only see the worst in things,
you'll miss the best part.
Here, look, look, look, look.
At first, a tasty marshmallow.
Then...
Oh, no! It's on fire and ruined!
But blow out the fire...
and crack open the burnt stuff,
you'll find something
sweet and gooey inside.
You just have to look for it.
Mmm.
Gooeylicious!
I guess it's always been hard for me
to see the positive side of things.
You know, raising a daughter
on your own for so long,
you're constantly worried.
Always fearing the worst.
That's why I built the hotel.
To protect her.
To protect all of us.
It's...
It's part of our family.
Sorry.
Maybe... maybe it's this new me,
but I'm feeling a bit overwhelmed.
No, Drac, it's okay.
I totally get it.
The hotel... it's something really special.
And the fact that you would trust me
with something so important,
I just can't tell you
how much that means to me.
I... I need to tell you something.
What is it, Drac?
Johnny, the truth is
that there is no monster real...
Johnny!
Mavis?
It's you!
It is still you in there, isn't it?
Of course it is.
Hey, hot stuff.
Ericka!
Don't sweat it.
I love you inside and out.
Whew!
Ericka, what's going on?
I-I mean, what are you doing here?
She's not the only one.
Hey, hey, buddy.
Guys? You...
- I-I mean, you're...
- Human?
Yeah, we noticed.
Though in my case,
it's a huge improvement.
Can we move on?
I don't understand.
I mean, how did this happen?
That's what I'd like to know.
Johnny, why did you
turn yourself into a monster?
So we can keep the hotel in the family.
You know, 'cause of
the monster real estate law.
Monster real estate law?
I don't understand.
No, neither do I.
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I-I can explain.
It, uh, it all happened so fast.
You see, Johnny found out
that I was giving you guys the hotel.
But then he, you know,
had a Johnny takeover:
escalators, name changes,
blah, blah, blah.
And so I... well, you know.
I-I... I...
I...
I panicked!
And lied?
Wait.
There's no monster real estate law?
Well, then... then that means that this...
this was all a lie?
You didn't want to have
any bonding time with me.
You just didn't want to give me the hotel!
No. I-I mean, yes, but...
You hate me!
Johnny, no.
- I-I didn't mean...
- Dad, how could you?
After everything.
It's easy!
'Cause I...
not part of family!
Johnny, something is happening to you.
Johnny out of here!
Johnny, wait!
This is all your fault!
All Johnny wanted was to feel like
he was part of this family,
but you could never accept him.
All you care about is your stupid hotel!
Mavis, I was going to...
And now, because of you,
I might lose him forever.
Mavis, wait!
Ericka, let me know
when you find the crystal.
I have to find Johnny
before it's too late.
"Too late"? What does that mean?
Come on. I'll fill you in on the way.
Johnny's going to keep transforming?!
Until he becomes a mindless beast.
There won't be any Johnny left.
That's why we need to find
the crystal. Now!
That way!
Follow the river!
Whoa!
Uh, Drac?
Straight. Keep going straight.
Okay. Straight it is.
Wait, wait, wait. What are you doing?!
Well, aren't you just full of surprises?
That way!
Johnny?
Johnny, where are you?
Oh, no.
Oh, Johnny.
Johnny! Johnny, stop!
Huh?
Oh.
M... M-M...
Mavis?
Yes, honey, it's me.
Oh, thank goodness.
I thought I lost you.
- Mavis!
- I'm so sorry.
My dad never should've lied to you.
Dracula bad!
Whoa! Johnny!
Whoa.
That's it.
The crystal is in there.
We are getting closer.
...until you reach
the Cave of the Reflexión!
Where entering is deadly...
and escape impossible!
Okay, we get it!
Uh, you okay there, honey?
Oh, hey. Yes.
Everything is fine.
- Whoa!
- Murray!
Rocks!
Uh-oh. Look!
Whoa!
Whew.
Mom! Wesley's touching me!
She touched me first!
Yeah!
Oh, my shoes!
Ah, we're going down!
Sorry, Blobs, you're on your own.
I can't swim! I'm afraid of sharks!
Ow! Hey, that's my face!
- Ouch!
- You're stepping on me!
- Get out of my way!
- Ow! Hey!
Get off my h... Ow!
- Ow! Oh!
- Stop it! Ow!
Huh?
We found it.
Let me go first.
No, let me go.
Wow.
Dracula mean!
Dracula liar!
Johnny mad!
Johnny, please! You have to calm down.
Whoa!
Sorry, sweetie, got to take this.
Ericka?
Mavis, we found the crystal cave.
Oh, that's great news.
Okay, I'm sending you the location now.
Got it. I'll get him there.
Are you sure? Is he close?
Yep, pretty close.
Sorry about this, honey.
Huh?
Hey, sweetie.
Starting route to your destination.
Oh.
Okay, everybody,
the crystal has to be here somewhere.
We'll find it as long as we stay focused
and don't get...
separated.
Drac, where are you?
Murray, is that you?
Hey, Eunice, where'd you go?
I'm right here. Where are you?
Okay, just calm down. Nobody panic.
Guys? Guys, Blobby is freaking out.
- So am I.
- Murray?
He's right here. Oh, wait.
No, false alarm. That's a pointy rock.
Guys, Blobby's really losing it!
- Stay in one place!
- Frank!
- Where am I?!
- Uh, what's happening?
Someone, find me!
- What do we do?
- Where are we?
We're lost!
How do we get out of here?!
Which way?
Sorry, I didn't quite get that.
Calculating new route.
Make a sharp left.
Whoa!
Your destination is on the right.
Okay, honey, just wait here.
I'll be right back.
Hello? Dad? Ericka?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Murray?
Hold me. I'm scared.
Huh?
Blobby?
Whoa!
Mavis!
Ouchy.
Oh, Dad, it's you.
Yes, of course it's me.
Ow. I think my nose is broken.
What is going on?
- Did you find the crystal?
- Ugh, the crystal?
We can't even find each other.
It's cuckoo in here.
But wait. You've come back.
You're not mad anymore?
Of course I'm still mad.
But we need to save Johnny.
- Johnny?
- Oh, no.
Mavis!
- You okay, Mavey?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Go, go, go!
Keep moving, legs.
- Wendy, Wally, Wilma, Wyatt...
- Is this all of them?
Not even close!
Whoa!
Huh?
If he ruins my hair,
I'm never gonna forgive him!
Ooh.
Huh?
Oh. Huh?
Is that...
The crystal! Thank you, Johnny!
Go!
Please don't be too late.
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa.
Huh?
Hey, kiddo.
Thanks, Uncle Frank.
That's it!
I need to get up there!
Don't worry.
We got you covered!
What are you standing around for?
Go, go, go!
Stop moving.
- Ow! Watch it!
- Let me get balanced.
Ow!
Okay, Mavis!
Whoa!
Ready, Murray?
Murray?
Murray!
I'm awake! What are we doing?
Okay, Johnny, please still be in there.
What?
We're too late.
No! It can't be!
Huh?
Sorry about this, Blobby.
Johnny...!
Dad!
Johnny!
Johnny?
Johnny, you are the marshmallow!
Huh?
Wait, he had a marshmallow on him?
You said that if I only saw
the worst in things,
I would miss the best parts.
And you were right.
I was so worried that you would
ruin everything I cared about
that I didn't see...
I didn't see you.
Your-your kindness,
y-your energy, your...
your Johnnyness.
Before you, my life was like
a burnt marshmallow,
hard and crunchy and sad.
But you cracked it open
and became the ooey-gooey center
of all of our lives.
We're dead.
What I'm trying to say is that
you are part of the family.
My family.
I can't believe it took becoming a human
to finally realize it.
And I'm sorry it's taken me
so long to say it,
and maybe now it's too late,
but you taught me to look
for the good in everything.
And now I see that so much
of the good in my life
is because of you.
Dra...
Drac?
Johnny!
Drac.
Mavis!
Hey.
Not bad, huh?
Much better.
I miss being Walter. Ow!
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa! No-no!
You-you are keeping those on!
Don't be so uptight. I'm inviz.
Man, just because you're invisible
doesn't mean you get to be naked.
What is wrong with you?
All right, Blobby, you're up.
Uh... looking good?
Oh.
Go ahead. Now's your chance.
Hey, it was fun being a monster
for a little bit.
I wonder if Van Helsing
can adjust this thing
so that I'm a monster but still me.
- I don't think so.
- Ah, come on.
- How 'bout just a tail?
- No, Johnny.
You're perfect just the way you are.
Uh, Mavey? Johnny?
- Yes?
- Well, I-I...
I know a lot has happened,
but I was hoping that, uh,
if-if you're still interested,
I, uh...
I wanted to say that the hotel...
that the hotel is
- destroyed!
- JOHNNY and MAVIS: Huh?!
What happened?!
My... my...
my hotel!
My hotel, my hotel, my hotel!
My hotel!
My... my hotel.
My hotel.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, man, this is unbelievable.
Hi, Mama! Hi, Papa!
MAVIS and JOHNNY:
Dennis!
Don't worry, Drac.
We'll rebuild it just the way it was.
No.
Rebuild it the way you want to.
It's your hotel now.
Dad, are you sure?
It's time to begin a new chapter.
Okay, Drac, open your eyes!
The... the hotel!
I-I don't understand.
It-It's exactly the same.
Well, we just made
a couple of tiny adjustments.
Huh?
♪ That's what you needed ♪
♪ People you love to be there ♪
♪ To support and believe in ♪
♪ See, the best part is when you realize
you're not scared to find ♪
♪ To find, find the good, good inside ♪
♪ Don't let your fears
cloud your feelings ♪
♪ We all got bad sides ♪
♪ But all that matters
in front of your eyes ♪
♪ Love is not hard to find ♪
♪ If we believe in us ♪
♪ As hard as it can be ♪
♪ Remember by your side,
you got a family ♪
♪ No matter what,
we gonna love you for who you are ♪
♪ There's no limit ♪
♪ Open your eyes,
love is not hard to find ♪
♪ All around the world,
but home is where we are ♪
♪ We always believed in magic ♪
♪ If we just smile, we'll be fine ♪
♪ It's always the hardest to say goodbye ♪
♪ We all got bad sides ♪
♪ But all that matters in front of your eyes ♪
♪ Love is not hard to find ♪
- ♪ If we believe in us ♪
- Whoa! Ow!
♪ As hard as it can be ♪
♪ Remember by your side,
you got a family ♪
♪ No matter what,
we gonna love you for who you are ♪
♪ There's no limit ♪
♪ Open your eyes ♪
♪ Love is not hard to find ♪
♪ As hard as it can be ♪
♪ Remember by your side, you got a family ♪
♪ No matter what,
we gonna love you for who you are ♪
♪ There's no limit ♪
♪ Open your eyes,
love is not hard to find ♪
Yeah!
♪ As hard as it can be ♪
♪ Remember by your side,
you got a family ♪
♪ No matter what ♪
♪ We gonna love you for who you are,
there's no limit ♪
♪ Open your eyes,
love is not hard to find ♪
♪ As hard as it can be ♪
♪ Remember by your side, you got a family ♪
♪ No matter what,
we gonna love you for who you are ♪
♪ There's no limit ♪
♪ Open your eyes,
love is not hard to find ♪
Whoa!
Whoa! Yeah!
♪ Open your eyes ♪
♪ Love is not hard to find. ♪