[rain pattering]
[grass rustling]
[birds singing distantly]
[Grandma] Honor to the Exalted One,
the Worthy One, the Fully Enlightened One.
Honor to the Exalted One, the Worthy One, the Fully Enlightened One.
Ma, why are you praying here?
Do you even know whose plot this is?
Sort of. It's a prayer for the future.
I ask the sacred beings to bring me a plot like this one.
- [vehicle approaching] - Oh, I think they'll grant you your wish.
- For a million baht. - [car door opens and closes]
[M] Ma?
Are you done?
The owners wanna pay their respects.
[chair lift whirring]
[Soei] Oh.
Hold on just a second.
This way, Ma.
[wistful piano music playing]
Thank you. Thank you.
[firecrackers crackling and popping]
[Sew] You can be buried in a shared plot like this.
And be close to your parents.
It's comfortable and reasonable.
Please don't listen to her.
I'll buy you your dream. Getting a million is easy these days.
[Grandma] Get away from me. Your cigarettes stink.
- Mwah! - [Grandma groans]
[Grandma] Try paying me back what I lent you first.
You hear me, Soei?
It's a few hundred thousand, isn't it?
I don't know.
- I only remember the good things in life. - Isn't that practical.
- Hey. - Don't step over them.
And Sew, why do you always get this wrong?
You put the duck and chicken butts facing your grandparents' faces again.
How does it go? M?
YAFANG ZHENG QINXING ZHOU
- M! - M.
[gentle piano music playing]
[Sew] Come and help us.
I laid the mat down for you, Ma.
[Sew] You must be exhausted.
[firecrackers popping distantly]
- [M] Hmm. - Bad boy.
Wait for the ceremony.
Qing Ming is sacred.
We honor the dead, not silly games.
Give me a break. I'm here, aren't I?
His family couldn't bother.
[Pinn, over phone] Well, that's nice.
Very pretty.
- Yes, everybody came out today. - [Pinn] I see that. Is it hot?
Not bad, actually.
I guess you won't be coming? I'll light some incense for you, okay?
- Oh, Ma. Say hi to Grandma. - [Pinn] Rainbow, smile. Say hi to Grandma.
Morning, Grandma.
[Rainbow groans]
- Morning… - It's once a year, Kiang.
We honor our ancestors.
Rainbow and Pinn have never paid their respects.
[whispers] Wait a second.
[flies buzzing]
[Grandma] Scatter these on top.
[M sighs]
[Sew] What a face.
[gentle piano music playing]
Oh, I said scatter, not dump.
Can't you even try? Huh?
- So lazy. - What does it matter how we do it?
The ancestors are up in the clouds, Grandma.
[sighs]
Can you not be such a qi-chou for once?
Hmm?
A good-for-nothing slacker.
[firecrackers popping distantly]
[scoffs]
[Sew] Ma, you shouldn't be up there. You could fall.
They'll be scattered by the wind anyway.
[Soei] Stubborn as a mule.
[Sew] Come down, please!
[Soei] You're looking for trouble, Ma. Let him do that.
And!
[Sew] Come down before you break your neck!
- Well! Must! - [Soei] Hey, Ma!
[man] Someone from the family will need to fill out the forms.
- [Soei] Okay. - [man] Thank you.
Bye, Ma.
Sis, you gotta go fill out the forms.
I have to go.
I need to take Rainbow to the store.
I'll leave you guys money to pay for today.
I left my bike at your house.
- I need to get it. - Oh yeah.
Why don't I ride back to your house with you?
And then I'll come back and stay with her.
That's ridiculous.
I mean, Kiang lives out in the boonies. It'll take you too long.
I'll stay with her for now.
- All right. Okay, out. - Go.
M!
Are you going by the MRT, Uncle?
Yeah. Why?
Could drop me off there?
Now?
Oh, okay. Here. Let's go.
[Soei] Thanks. See you later, Sew.
[M] This place is full of talismans, guys.
[video game character panting]
Ah! Evil spirit!
Ah!
I'm scared of ghosts! Take that!
- Wait, where'd it go, guys? Where'd it go? - A measly four viewers, today?
Ma, everyone can hear you!
And…
Why don't you relax? You've been on your feet all day.
Did you read my text?
Another computer for gaming.
Why do you wanna use my card?
You have your own card. Use that.
It's maxed out. The bank threatened to freeze it.
I hope they do that.
Teach you a lesson.
And if your internet gets cut off again, I won't pay for it.
What did you say when you decided to quit school
to become a gamecaster from our living room?
You'd be rich in no time.
You would rent your own house.
That you'd give me an allowance.
I want to retire when I'm 60.
I know you do.
Don't kick a man when he's down.
It hurts.
[video game music plays faintly]
When Grandma went to the hospital…
she mentioned to the doctor that she's had stomachaches and blood in her stool.
So they did tests while she was there.
This morning, I got the results.
Grandma has cancer.
It's in the final stages.
She probably has 12 months.
You're dead!
Jeez, they won't listen.
- Man… - [Sew sighs]
Anyway, M, I expect you to spend time with her.
But don't mention her diagnosis.
I don't want her to worry.
What'll you give me to go see Grandma?
My time is money now, yeah?
- [chuckles] - [Sew sighs]
HONEYHANIYAH: GET THE GHOST
MUIII: THE TV'S ACTING UP AGAIN
MUIII: CAN YOU COME TAKE A LOOK FOR GRANDPA?
[bicycle bell dinging]
You need to keep updating the app. That's why it's freezing.
[Grandpa groans]
[M] Hmm?
[Grandpa groaning]
My grandpa says you need to eat more. You're too skinny. Hmm.
How do you know what he said? All his grunts sound the same.
[Mui] Actually, I made it up.
He probably said that you're blocking his view.
[Grandpa groans]
- [techno music playing on TV] - [M] Hey!
Whoa, Grandpa!
You still got it!
- [Grandpa chuckles] - [laughs]
Your diaper feels full. I'm gonna change it, okay?
[Grandpa] Mm-hmm.
We're going down.
[bed whirring]
You know you're a grandparent's dream, Mui?
A graduate from nursing school.
[Mui] Is that true, Grandpa?
Who do you love the most?
- [Grandpa groans] - [M laughs]
[Mui] Seriously?
- You're hurting my feelings. - [Grandpa chuckles]
Maybe I'll leave you alone tonight.
Do you ever think about doing something else?
When do you ever have time for yourself?
Grandpa gave me advice once.
He said to get a high-paying, easy job.
So why don't you?
I'm doing that already.
[heart monitor beeping]
[techno music playing]
[rapid beeping]
[heart monitor flatlines]
[gong reverberates]
[Oriental music playing]
[man singing in foreign language]
[music stops]
[woman] This belt is pure silver.
It's worth at least 10,000 baht.
- That's amazing. Thanks. - [woman] Your dad's not around anymore.
- But Grandpa wanted you to have something. - I'm very grateful.
And I will keep it safe for you.
You might pawn it for a computer.
And…
[woman] Grandpa was a sly fox.
He divvied up his inheritance a while ago,
but he didn't want to reveal anything until after his death.
Which means I'm the lucky one to get all the grief.
So did he leave me something else for helping him?
Helping him? You?
Of course not. He left almost everything to Mui.
Including the house.
Your dad's siblings didn't get much either.
Grandpa only left them a little bit of money.
[Tchaikovsky's "Piano Concerto No. 1" playing on piano]
[indistinct chanting]
["Concerto No. 1" continues orchestrally]
[music ends]
[birds squawking]
[gentle piano music playing]
[camera shutters clicking]
[gentle piano music continues]
[train horn blows]
[camera shutters clicking]
[PA system chimes]
[woman's voice over PA] The train heading towards Talat Phlu Station
has departed from Mahachai Station.
[gentle piano music playing]
[mewls]
[rain pattering]
[camera shutters clicking]
[M] Grandma?
HOW TO MAKE MILLIONS BEFORE GRANDMA DIES
[camera shutters clicking]
[scoffs] Damn ancient.
[police siren wailing distantly]
VINTAGE-STYLE SHOPHOUSE IN TALAT PHLU AREA,
NEAR GREAT FOOD.
CONVENIENT FOR COMMUTING, NEAR THA PHRA STATION.
CONTACT M THANAPAT
[Grandma] Who's that out there?
Hello?
Grandma.
It's M.
I just wanted to come and say hi.
- Oh. - I miss you.
You're the third.
Your uncles Kiang and Soei came by this week.
Yeah?
[Grandma] What's going on? Why the visits all of a sudden?
I came to see if your leg's healing properly.
Open up for your only grandson?
Uh…
- [M] So how are you doing? - [Grandma] Have you eaten yet?
Yeah, noodles.
I got some for you too. They're still warm.
[Grandma] It's not time for my meal yet.
- Where did you get the noodles? - [M] From that famous beef noodle place.
I had them specially make up a mix of offal that you love.
You have the tendons,
tripe,
some liver and flat-iron steak too.
You won't believe how tender.
I'll fix it up.
You know I pray to the goddess Guanyin.
I don't touch beef.
Well, what do you eat then?
[sizzling]
[woman] Fresh fish!
- [M] What is this, Michelin-star fish? - [woman] Fresh fish!
Who wants some hot fried fish?
With tasty sauce.
Fried fish!
Who wants some fish?
- Nice big fish! - One, two, three, four,
- five, six, seven, eight, nine… - [woman] And tasty sauce!
Fresh fried fish!
No grease! Just flavor! Try it!
[M] Whoa-ho-ho! Your favorite fish from Uncle's fish stand.
You managed that so fast.
There must not have been a line.
[stool drags]
He had two woks going at once. He was trying something new.
I've only gone to his stall for the last 40 years.
I haven't gone blind, you know.
Huh? I only go there because it's not greasy like this.
I'm not eating it.
[M sighs]
If you're going to eat fried food, you might as well have a little grease.
[sizzling]
I got what you wanted, Grandma! It's piping hot!
I'm already full.
What did you eat?
I had the fish you brought earlier.
[sighs]
Oh! Are you making some tea?
[Grandma] To offer to the gods, not for myself.
Let me do it for you.
[gentle piano music playing]
[microwave hums]
[microwave dings]
Hey. The water boiled already?
[M] Yeah, it did.
How come I didn't hear the kettle whistle?
I used the microwave.
For the gods' tea?
- Oh! - [M] What?
[Grandma] Take it down right now!
- Why? I boiled it. It's good. - [Grandma] Not the right way!
But this saves gas, and it's so much faster.
[Grandma] No, M. Take it down.
It's not right.
Yes, it is!
The modern ways are good ways.
You offered tea to them. The gods don't care how it's boiled.
[Grandma] If you do things just to get them done,
then don't do them at all.
I'll come back tomorrow to boil the water right.
[Grandma] Just go home.
[gate locks]
- Go. - I'll even use two kettles.
[Grandma] I don't need you.
You never came to visit. Why bother now?
Watch where you walk.
[man] Hello.
Thanks for coming.
I'm not sure she meant to, but Ms. Mui left this.
It'd be a shame to throw it out.
[Mui] Why are you so stubborn?
I don't want these things. They were supposed to be thrown out.
Now I'm stuck with them.
[violin music playing faintly]
If you came here to ask me for money like the others,
the answer is no.
That's not why I'm here.
I just…
want to say you did a great job with Grandpa.
You were the one who took care of him, so you should be rewarded.
Here. Give me that.
I also wanted to hear more about how I could get paid
for the easy work
that you mentioned.
[gentle piano music playing]
[Mui] I want to save the money I got from selling Grandpa's house.
So I'm renting this hotel room by the month.
The rent includes breakfast and daily housekeeping.
If I get bored, I can just move out.
You got a proper uniform for work?
I'm diggin' it.
[Mui] It's not real.
It's for my OnlyFans account.
Wearing a nurse's uniform gets me a higher rate.
Wanna subscribe?
Mm, that's all right.
Look at you all shy.
We've kissed before, remember?
When we were a lot younger
and our families would get together to play cards at Grandpa's.
You and I always played house.
I was the mother, you were the father.
And we cuddled under the blanket.
Uh, yeah.
I remember now.
We did.
So tell me why you want to look after your Grandma.
So I can get a place of my own.
It takes so long when you're not privileged.
Some people are just born with a head start.
They're rich or inherit a business.
So you think of Grandma as an asset?
[M] Hmm…
That's harsh.
Do you think it's so wrong…
what we're doing?
Hmm?
[Mui] Honestly?
I really hate Grandpa's kids.
They would come once a week for 15 minutes.
So why even bother?
It's time.
[M] Hmm?
Our time is what they're really craving the most.
It doesn't matter what we're there for.
How'd you skip over everyone?
And get to be number one?
Do you know what
older people want more than anything each day,
but most of their children are not willing to offer?
To not count the minutes.
But I was with her all day.
Did you think she smelled funny
when you were with her?
Old people just smell.
You notice it because you don't spend enough time with her.
You'll know you have when you stop noticing.
Grandpa was incontinent, but I became immune to it.
[tender music playing]
[camera shutters click]
- Whoa! - [objects crash]
[panting softly]
[sighs]
I'll buy you back when I get the money.
Wow.
[piano music playing]
So you're going to be moving in with Grandma?
I'm doing what you wanted, aren't I?
[humming]
[uplifting orchestral music playing]
Breaking into houses now?
I used the key that you gave to Ma.
What's with all this stuff?
I brought some,
and I bought some of it.
And this is for you.
I made it selling stuff online.
Tell me why everyone's visiting now.
If all those tests say I'm fine,
I don't need all this fuss.
[chair scrapes]
[woman on TV] But the traditional methods endure.
The charcoal-burning industry at Ban Khon Huay Nang is a mainstay…
They gave Ma the results of the tests you did.
The traditions have been handed down for generations.
Most things look good.
The industry is steady, but faces constant challenges.
But you have cancer.
Wood and sawdust prices have increased and added pressure.
And Ma and the uncles don't want you to know.
Prices for other materials used in the process have also increased.
Battery prices have gone up…
Is it serious?
- …by an average of 20%. - It's stage four.
They've given you a year.
But you don't need to listen to them.
Doctors, sometimes they think they can predict the future.
Remember what they told Yen down the street?
Six months if she was lucky.
And now it's been ten years, and she's still bossing everyone around
in that big house of hers.
However, the ancient methods attract tourists…
I had such a great time as a kid here.
You were so good to Ma and me.
These traditional work methods…
Now I think it's time I did something for you.
I have time.
I'd like to spend it with you if I can.
…a vital part of the local economy,
others see them as the beginning of the end for small family enterprises
who will not be able to compete
with the output from more efficient…
[Grandma] I'm off.
[woman, on TV] They used to light 100 kilns a day.
Now, they are able to light 200 to 300.
As for the prices of raw materials for the kilns…
I'll put this money towards the utility bill.
…due in large part to shipping costs,
making the charcoal stove business a fine balancing act for all involved.
I'll help you sell congee tomorrow. What time do you leave?
Five a.m.
- [M] What? - [Grandma] Five a.m.
Why so early?
[Grandma] Do you expect to sell congee late in the day?
[M] People eat congee at night too, you know.
You can eat congee all day.
The early bird gets the worm.
I don't think your generation has even heard that saying.
Have you ever heard the saying,
"The worm that wakes up at five will not stay alive"?
- He's the one that gets eaten first. - Hmm.
[M] You're scowling.
[low-key piano music playing]
[cell phone alarm rings and buzzes]
[groans softly]
[sighs]
[ringing and buzzing continue]
[silences phone]
[meows]
[peppy piano music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[M] Why didn't you wake me up?
[Grandma] I'm your Grandma, not an alarm clock.
[M sighs]
- [M] I'll do this bag. - [Grandma] Oh, fine.
Are you hiding it because you don't know what you're doing?
- [M] Please. - [train horn blowing]
[rain pattering]
[M] If you want, I can deposit your money at the ATM.
Then you won't have to walk to the bank now.
[Grandma] Stop meddling.
I take this walk to the bank every month.
[M] I thought you might like a break from going for once.
[Grandma] Grandma! Nope!
- [M] Who's that? - [Grandma] A friend.
Careful.
Hold this.
Thank you.
Oh, Ngek. How are you? Did they let you come back already?
- I got back yesterday. - [Grandma] Really?
They made me leave to give the bed to someone worse off.
[whispers] I've been hit as well.
Where is it?
[in normal voice] Intestines.
What stage?
It's four.
Mine too.
[both sigh]
- I'm here if you need it. - Same to you.
It must be a comfort to have your grandson.
- Sure. - You are so lucky.
You see?
I think your friend is jealous.
[Laughs chuckles]
- [Ngek] It's good to see you. - [Grandma] Good to see you too.
SIAM SAVINGS BANK
[Grandma] You stay out here.
You'll use my bank details behind my back.
Oh, so now you think your grandson's a thief?
- You watch too much TV. - Whatever. Stay there.
- So good to see you, ma'am. - I would never do that, Grandma.
Thank you so much. Are we making the usual deposit?
We are.
[vehicle horn blares]
[pigeons cooing]
[dings]
- [door opens] - [Sew] Whoa, Ma.
This is bad. The fridge smells like a garbage can.
Why do you insist on holding on to things that are expired?
[Grandma] It's not expired. I can still eat it.
No wonder you've got stomachaches, eating all this moldy stuff every day.
[Grandma] I'll bring it back, even if you throw it out.
How can you two bicker before breakfast?
Why are you sleeping in the living room instead of upstairs?
Grandma locks her room. She doesn't want me in there.
[Sew sighs]
You put your fancy clothes on today?
Fancy?
[M] Hmm.
Hold on. The last button's undone.
- You trying to show off? - Leave it. It's too tight.
I like it loose, so I can move.
[M] Yeah, 'cause it's so tight.
[Grandma] Why are you bothering me?
Hey, did you steal Rainbow's sandals? Those look way too small for you.
[Grandma] They fit perfect.
- [M] Perfect? - [Grandma] Yes.
- [M] That's a perfect fit? - [Grandma] Go away.
I can dress myself, thank you.
A perfect fit doesn't cut off circulation.
These are my feet, not yours.
If I can get my feet in them, they fit fine.
What about your shoes?
[M] Also a perfect fit.
So why are you dressed so nice?
She always dresses up on Sunday.
Everyone comes on Sunday,
which you would know if you bothered.
[tender music playing]
[Pinn] Here you are.
I ordered this chicken from the Montien Hotel.
It's where all the famous people go to eat.
[Soei, laughing] Whoa!
Rainbow, did you know,
when were growing up here, we had a pet chicken downstairs?
- Cool, huh? - I would like a baby chick.
- I think they're the cutest in the world. - True!
But your aunt and your dad used to chase that chicken around all day.
Until one Chinese New Year,
Grandma had to chop him up for dinner.
Chop, chop, chop.
And she made us steamed chicken, just like this one.
Except we were so sad, we gave all our pieces to the dogs.
- You've got the memory of an elephant. - Right, sis?
You remember whenever Kiang cried, he would blow snot bubbles?
- He would! - Can you stop?
I'm not here to have my baby listen to your stupid stories.
- Why don't we look at your stickers, okay? - Relax, bro.
Passing down the family history to the next gen is important.
[Grandma] Kids.
When we've finished eating, who's up for playing cards?
- [Soei] Hmm? - When's the last time we played together?
I see, you, Ma. you want to take your boys to the cleaners, huh?
Crack open your safe, I'm taking you to the cleaners.
I'd like to see you try, boy.
- [laughs] - Ah! The big talker!
You'll have to play without us. We have to leave.
Rainbow has a ballet class in a little bit.
Kiang, relax. You have time for a game or two before you have to leave.
- Yeah, bro. - [Kiang] There's traffic to deal with.
We need to go. Soei, you too.
You shouldn't be playing cards either.
Why not?
Because Ma needs to rest.
Ma, you still have pain in your stomach?
Yeah, are you hurting anywhere?
I know all about the cancer.
Huh?
[Grandma] M told me everything.
Well, Grandma has a right to know what's going on.
It's her body, and she can make her own decisions about it.
I'll see the doctor on my own.
I am not going to be a burden to you.
It's not a burden.
I'm glad you know because I think you should be getting treated, okay?
But they made me promise to keep it quiet.
[Kiang] What's that?
Don't try to make yourself look like the good son.
You barely visit, and you mooch off everyone.
Ah. Always with the finances.
I'd pay for more things if I had any money.
- That's because you don't work. - I do work, okay?
- It's been slow. - Please don't be starting that again.
- [Kiang] I have a job. - [Sew] You're not being fair, Kiang.
[Soei] I come here more than you do.
My job is very demanding.
Are you saying our work doesn't count?
[Soei] Mm-hmm.
When I go to school, I'll be a doctor so you can get better,
and we'll play cards.
[chuckles softly]
[tender music playing]
Don't worry, Ma.
My friend knows all the best doctors who deal with important people.
I'll foot the bill for your treatments, and you will beat this.
You don't need to worry about me.
Don't you be stubborn about this.
When you have appointments, I will take you.
It's my daughter's duty, Ma.
Hey.
Ma, when I took a dump earlier, I almost broke my neck.
I'll install handrails so you don't slip and fall, okay?
I am proud of my children and very thankful.
[Soei] No need to be so dramatic.
You'll get better soon.
Aren't you supposed to be working at the market?
Not until later.
I'll be doing night shifts for a while.
This way, I'll be able to take Ma to her chemo in the day.
I can't just take the day off when I want.
What are you expecting from her?
Expecting?
My mother has cancer. Don't you think I should support her?
Otherwise, I'll be seen as a terrible daughter.
This is the one and only time we do this. I'm not coming back here.
Don't you remember what the doctor told you about making sure you exercise?
I can walk on my own.
You took a day off of work for this, didn't you?
They'll replace you if you call too often.
Ma won't get fired.
She'll be working on the night shift for a while
so she can come to your appointments.
Really?
You work at night now?
Until what time?
What time, Sew?
Until dawn, Grandma.
- She works all night. - [Grandma] Oh.
That means you haven't even slept yet?
That's enough. Get me out of here.
We're here now. Stay.
Why can't you let me do something nice for you for once?
Because whenever I let you do things like that, it always backfires.
Like when you dropped out of school to help me sell congee.
Why are you saying that was bad?
I couldn't bear to see you work so hard while my brothers did nothing.
You broke your back for all of us,
working all those long hours with your cart.
You work harder than me, and look where it got you.
- Tired and wet. - If Kiang were available,
you'd be okay to come with him.
Oh. Right.
I'll make sure he knows that.
I'm not sure he'll be free, but I'll give him the message.
[Grandma groans]
Grandma's crying in the changing room.
That's impossible.
That woman's never shed a tear for me in her life.
[M] True.
You're always the one who sheds the tears.
All I know is the more you bicker, the worse she is.
I'll take Grandma in for her chemo from now on.
I'll be representing our family.
[somber piano music playing]
- [crickets chirping] - [exotic bird calls]
[Grandma] Did you turn off the lights in the house?
- [M] Yes. - [Grandma] Upstairs and down?
[M] Yup.
Mui.
Grandma,
this is Mui.
One of my cousins.
[in Teochew] Grandma, have you eaten?
Yes, thank you.
Where are you going, Grandma?
I'm going to see the doctor.
I'm going to drive you there.
Thank you.
[in English] You speak Teochew?
You suck-up.
You owe me one, M. I'm not a taxi.
Yeah, I got it.
[indistinct chatter]
You need to put your shoes at the end of the line, M.
They'll start calling patients at eight.
We woke up at four for this?
Grandma and I will go find a seat.
Wait for me here, Grandma. I'll find you a wheelchair.
[slow staccato piano music playing]
[metallic clattering]
[sighs]
Next time, go in and keep her company.
You'll get huge brownie points.
[light piano music playing]
[Grandma groans softly] My insides feel like they're on fire.
Hmm, goodness.
Go put this in the cabinet with the rest.
Sure.
- Hey! No, wait for me to help you. - Not a chance.
When you were a kid, you offered to let me hold your hand.
But your eyes were glued to the television,
and I banged up my shins.
I don't remember that.
- [Grandma] I'd rather climb on my own. - Come on.
Hold out both your hands.
Mui said I'm supposed to lead the way.
That way, we're sure you won't tumble backwards.
- She said that, did she? - [M] She did.
- Come on. Hands up. - Eyes on me, then.
Careful where you step.
[Grandma sighs]
That's good. Now get some rest.
[M sighs]
Is this Uncle Soei?
Uh-huh.
[scoffs]
[M, chuckling] Hilarious.
Hey.
You and Grandpa were pretty cool. You look like you were having fun.
[Grandma] Mm-hmm.
Back when you used to live here,
you were afraid of ghosts.
You would squeeze in right here, between your Grandpa and me every night.
- [M] I was afraid of ghosts? - [Grandma] Something awful.
I had to sing you at least three lullabies to get you to sleep.
Hmm? No way.
Hopefully, you outgrew all that.
Because your Grandpa
likes to come back and wander around downstairs every night.
If you see his ghost,
don't say anything to him.
[dramatic piano music playing]
- [ominous notes play loudly] - Shit!
[Grandma] I thought you said you weren't afraid of ghosts anymore.
I'm not afraid of ghosts. But you're real.
[sighs]
[Grandma] I needed to pray.
I had a dream about my parents.
They came to take me to stay with them.
M?
Do you think I'm about to die?
Grandma.
You worship the goddess.
It's been decades since you ate beef.
Cows should be praying to you.
You've got plenty of life left, I'm sure.
Yeah.
I guess so.
I'll go back upstairs.
- No more stairs. - [Grandma] You need your sleep.
No stairs. Save your energy.
We'll sleep together in here.
Come in. So the bugs don't bite.
You're kinda taking up the whole bed.
- [Grandma] Hmm. - [M] Can you scoot over, Grandma?
[M sighs]
[Grandma speaking Teochew]
[M] Are you insulting me again?
[Grandma] That means I thank you.
Are you sure you're Chinese?
You can't understand a single word.
[M] I'm Chinese-Thai, Grandma. Chinese-Thai.
[Grandma] Whatever. I'm going to sleep now.
[M] Okay.
Good night.
[mellow piano music playing]
Grandma?
Sing to me?
[Grandma] Keep doing this whenever you're free.
[M] Sure thing. But you'll be out of job soon.
[Grandma] You're not doing it tight enough.
I'm leaving some space so the vinegar can breathe.
[chuckles]
[woman] The counter is now open.
[indistinct chatter]
[M] Grandma.
Come on. Get up. Get up.
[wistful string music playing]
Are you finished?
[Grandma] Just a second.
Grandma?
[Grandma groans]
Hey.
What's wrong?
- [moaning] - Are you in pain?
No, no. Not so fast.
One…
Let's skip the market this morning.
I'm gonna give you a sponge bath. You're too warm.
I have to sell my congee.
Come on up. Bath time.
We'll turn around. Slowly.
Go on three.
- One, two, three. Up! - [Grandma moans softly]
[gas hissing]
- [flames flump] - [M gasps]
[M] All right. Arm.
[rooster caws]
[Grandma sighs]
You need to get underneath too.
- I'm sticky. - Whoa! You're taking it off?
Mm, I want to feel really clean everywhere.
I'm old, you know. I'm not embarrassed.
[M] Just give me a second. I've never done this.
Give a guy some warning.
[M groans]
[rooster caws]
[M groaning]
[Grandma] What's with your moaning?
Shit!
What? Did you see another ghost?
Was that bump I felt your nipple?
Are you that dumb?
I've got a mole.
Who has boobs that would sag all the way down there?
I don't know. H-How would I know?
Give me that. You might think my knees are my boobs.
[camera whirring]
[Grandma] What's with the camera?
It's for watching things.
I can't watch that.
No, I mean watching you.
If you fall or faint, I'll see it.
I could come and help.
If anything bad happens to you, I can see it right away.
Don't jinx me.
Don't worry.
Here. Check this out.
No!
You can't move the goddess like that.
Never.
- Why not? - It's just wrong.
Put her back and apologize.
Right this instant.
You can't shove her around. Where's your respect, M?
- There. - No. Like you care. That was sloppy.
She's all crooked.
Use both your hands, gently.
Yes. Very gently.
- Carefully. - Done. She's all set.
Right back in the same exact spot. It's like she never moved at all.
[low-key piano music playing]
[rain pattering]
[grunts]
[Soei] All done. Easy-peasy. The throne is secure.
You're done?
[Soei] Ma, move away. You hate the smell of smoke.
You should be resting.
Whoa.
Hey, Ma, the pomegranate's looking nice.
- Can I? - Don't touch it. It's not yours.
It looks too good. I'm taking it.
- [Grandma] You can't have it. - Why not?
- Ooh! - It's not yours.
Well, whose is it?
[Grandma] It's not yours, that's all.
[chuckles] Ah.
- [Grandma] What? - You're saving it for your favorite son,
Mr. Money Bags.
You have something to eat?
[Grandma] Take a look.
[Soei] Mm.
Hmm.
Hey, M, did you know that when they first met,
Ma thought Kiang's wife was a real dud?
[M] What do you mean a dud?
Shit.
You make me explain the simplest words. Did you sleep through school? Huh?
A dud sucks.
Like a firecracker that got all wet, or a total bore.
- [M] Ah. - [laughs]
When Pinn got her hooks into your uncle,
Kiang changed into a totally different person.
He became a snob.
All about image.
Sending his kid to an international school.
Shut your mouth, Soei. I can tell when you've been drinking.
- [Soei] He borrowed tons of money. - You have no filter.
[Soei] I haven't finished gossiping yet.
She protects her favorite.
Fine, I'll shut my mouth.
Anyway, my motto's always been, "Live within your means and be modest."
- But your favorite, he hoards it away. - That's enough from you.
The guy's loaded, but when people like me need a little handout, where is he?
Huh?
I'm short about a thousand. Help me out?
- Hmm? - No way.
- Please? - I spent it.
- If I find it, can I have it? - No.
- Come on. - [groans]
Hmm? Wild.
- Not today, Soei. - I'll kiss you 'til you cave.
Hmm, hmm, hmm?
[Grandma] With Soei,
it's best when he stays away.
Why's that?
Because it means that he's okay when he doesn't come around.
[gentle music playing]
[Mui] That's just how it goes.
Her kids versus her grandkids.
- She's loved them a lot longer. - [woman] There's a charge for extra sauce.
Can you rate your current position?
Who's your Grandma's favorite?
The number one spot is either Uncle Kiang or Uncle Soei.
One's too serious, and the other's a clown.
I think I've moved ahead of my mom, though.
Number three gets a big zero.
What about you?
How did you know you were top of the list? Did he tell you?
Most older people aren't that straightforward.
But you can feel it.
Feel what?
Not the love, if that's what you mean.
I just feel her sarcastic shit.
- [blows] - [laughs] Every day.
[Mui] Hmm.
I was sure I snagged the spot when Grandpa sang my praises
to the rest of the clan.
Mm, I guess.
[turn signal clicking]
[Kiang] We're almost there, Ma.
It's a bit far, but the air is better.
I'm sorry I haven't brought you here before.
[doorbell chimes]
[Rainbow] Welcome to our house, Grandma.
[Pinn] Welcome, Ma.
Show Grandma the picture you drew for her.
- [Grandma] Hmm. - Careful.
[faint singing over TV]
Do you like it, Grandma?
Very much.
Thank you.
Did you notice the bed? We got it specially for you.
Rainbow chose the red flowers.
The TV's internet cable.
You can watch Chinese opera.
I still have a house and business to run.
Oh, Ma!
Pinn and I want you to sell that house and move in with us.
Besides, there's salons, restaurants, a club.
The club has seniors' activities. There's tai-chi each morning.
What about her chemo appointments, though?
The commute is tiring.
Uh, I run my stock trading from home. I'll be around to take care of her.
Yeah, but there's her congee shop.
Her regulars are wondering why she's not there on Sundays.
I think it's time for Ma to be closed every day, don't you?
And I can support her.
Moving here is best. I can be there for her treatments.
But you're so far from the clinic.
You'll be getting up at two in the morning to make it work.
[Kiang sighs softly]
[zipper rasps]
[papers rustle]
[Kiang] M.
M!
Yep?
I appreciate the work you've been putting in.
And so,
I wanted to give you a little something for taking care of Grandma for us.
That's nice of you, Uncle.
But I'm not in it for the money.
So it wouldn't feel right.
[Kiang] Ma.
You raised your son right. I will take care of my mother.
I can't burden my nephew with your care.
[laid-back piano music playing]
And.
Let me do what a son should.
[train horn blows]
And you locked everything up?
Of course.
Rainbow.
It's big-girl time.
Please go ask Grandma if she's having fun.
I'm sure she would like you to sit with her.
- Can you do that? - Okay.
Ah!
- [Rainbow] Do you like the train, Grandma? - I love the train.
- I like riding places, don't you? - [Rainbow] It's so much fun!
Such a smart, pretty granddaughter.
You can make coffin donations at this temple.
We'll contribute for you.
Rainbow's friend and her mother came recently.
And her condition improved in no time.
You know what this reminds me of, Ma?
Taking the train when we were kids.
It brings back memories of when you and Pa took us on trips.
And you were so tiny for your age.
- [Kiang] Me? - Puny, but quick.
- [Kiang] I remember Soei running all over. - Of course. All three of you did.
[Kiang laughs]
[automated voice] May you all be blessed
- for coming to visit our temple today. - [Grandma] Seven.
- Eight. - We invite you to fill out…
Nine.
- [Kiang] Ma, are you good to climb up? - [Grandma] Ten.
- Eleven. - You can go ahead, Uncle.
We'll catch up to you.
[Grandma] Twelve.
- Thirteen. - [M] So have you made up your mind yet?
Are you gonna move in with Kiang?
[Grandma] Be quiet, will you?
I'm counting the steps. You'll mess me up.
- [M] Why are you counting? - [Grandma] For the lottery.
[M] Hmm. Do your feet hurt?
Take a break.
[Grandma] Back in the day, when Kiang was just a kid,
we came to offer prayers here.
When it was time to leave, his shoes were gone.
So I had to give him my sandals so he didn't go home barefoot.
It was a gorgeous day.
Sunny and bright like today. The ground was just as hot as today too.
Did he buy these to try to make it up to you?
Hmm.
[Pinn] Good, Rainbow.
Perfect.
- [M] Your name? - Let's go.
Start it with Missus, then Mengju Saejiew.
We're gonna put up our labels and then wait for you outside.
- Your wish? - I want to regain my health.
- Okay. - I have more.
You can't rush the wishes, you know.
- Uh… - Write.
[laughs] How many do you have?
[Grandma] I wish for my
eldest son…
my daughter…
and my youngest son…
to be healthy and strong.
- And have money and gold. - [M sighs]
Any more and we'll need another label.
[Grandma] Only because your letters are big as elephants.
[M] Hmm.
[Grandma] And I ask for my one and only grandson…
to have a very good job.
All right.
I'll put it up.
[Grandma] Thank you.
[M] Look, Grandma.
One.
Two.
Three.
Nobody made wishes for you.
Seems that Kiang's only pretending how much he cares.
It's all an act to get on your good side.
He has a family of his own.
He has to use his wishes for their happiness first.
[pounding table]
You're part of his family too, aren't you?
[thoughtful piano music playing]
MRS. MENGJU SAEJIEW: I WANT TO REGAIN MY HEALTH
M: MAY GRANDMA WIN THE LOTTERY
And.
Can you try to have your things ready to move by next Sunday?
I'll arrange your transportation.
[thoughtful piano music continues]
[Grandma] M, wait.
I want to buy some new shoes today.
These hurt my feet too much.
Here. Start with these.
How are they?
They feel big.
- They feel big? - Yes.
Hmm.
Honestly, you might get that perfect fit after all.
Hey, M.
Uh-huh?
Maybe you're just trying to get on my good side too, huh?
It's the same
as Kiang, in a way.
Let me do what a grandson should.
[M laughs]
You are absolutely full of it.
"Oh, you're so full of it."
I'm telling the truth, though.
I say we try these next.
One on each foot, so you can compare.
Hmm?
Oh my.
Are you taking pictures?
[M] Sort of. It's a filter.
Huh?
It's you, only a little sparklier.
I know you.
You're proud of your looks.
[chuckles]
And when your chemo's done,
I'm pretty sure you'll look something like this.
- [laughs] - [Grandma sighs]
[Grandma] What nonsense.
- [chuckles] - How? You look cool.
You look good.
And you won't have to wake up early to do your hair anymore.
[laughs]
Do you like it?
Uh-huh.
[M] It's good to see you laugh.
Get some rest.
Go on. Close your eyes.
[wistful music playing]
[Grandma] I want pork. Give me more pork.
- You only want pork? - [Grandma] Get me pork, and veggies too.
- You said you wanted only pork. - [Grandma] I meant give me a lot of pork.
Fine. Lots of pork.
[Grandma] Listen and learn, M.
Keep stirring.
In the future, my customers can be yours.
I can't wake up at four for the rest of my life, Grandma.
Can I sell at night?
As long as you remember that every kind of hard work
can bring a Zhuang-wen into existence.
You just have to practice your skill with intent.
Because that will allow you to have a comfortable life.
Like the Zhuang-wen have done for centuries.
Don't you have to be castrated to be one?
Those are eunuchs, silly.
You really slept through school.
[cards shuffling]
[M] I'm gonna take you to the cleaners.
[Grandma] Oh, yeah? Try me.
[laughing] Oh! Sassy!
You're on.
Uh-huh. Think hard.
Should you bluff?
Does Mengju from Talat Phlu
have what it takes to be the big winner tonight?
Shut your mouth, would you?
- You're jinxing my hand. - Hmm?
- Show it. - Go away.
[M chuckles]
I think I see where Uncle Soei gets his gambler's blood from.
During the ghost festival and on Chinese New Year,
we didn't know what else to do once we'd observed the rituals.
So we'd play cards late into the evening.
You've lived alone for a long time. Do you ever get lonely?
I wouldn't call it loneliness. It's part of life's process.
I do have a problem with the day after Chinese New Year.
When all the leftovers from the night before
are in the fridge.
And…
I know I'm going to have to eat them all alone.
Hmm. Back to the cards.
- Go. You show yours first. - Hmm. Okay.
Seven double score.
Let's see.
I got eight. Double score too.
Liar. You're a bad, bad cheater, okay?
Double score because it's two eights.
Your customers must rob you blind if that's how you count.
[both laugh]
And I forgot to count this one.
Huh? I'm the winner here, Grandma.
- Let's go. Hand it over. - What was it?
I see 20 baht right there.
You scoundrel. Taking advantage of your Grandma.
Whoa!
Do I complain when I have to pay you?
Nice try. Go again?
It's a blessing to have you here.
And you're fun.
[chuckles]
[gentle music playing]
You know I'm onto your stalling tactics.
[Grandma] Sure.
No cheating, okay?
[Grandma] We'll see.
[M] Uncle Kiang isn't answering. He's probably upset you didn't move in.
Uncle Soei's phone is turned off.
And Ma says she has to work because they're short-staffed.
I don't think anyone's coming today, Grandma.
Then please put all the food away in the cabinet
so the bugs don't get to it.
Okay.
Why is the lid loose?
Hey, what happened to all my money? It's gone.
- M! - Just a sec.
There's nothing in there.
I didn't touch it.
I didn't touch it!
I'm not a thief, I swear.
See?
He took the pork floss and stole all your money.
That's why his phone's off, I guess.
Was it a lot?
[somber piano music playing]
- Hey. - Shithead.
Have you ever even helped Grandma sell congee?
She only earns 10 to 20 baht a bag.
Do you know how many bags she has to sell to get 200,000 baht?
Where's your conscience?
My own mother's never told me off like this.
How much do you owe?
Huh?
A million.
A million?
So I'm…
gonna ask Ma to bail me out one last time.
[distant police siren]
[leaves rustling]
Uncle?
Here.
Huh?
What's that?
[M] Silver belt. Should get a good price for it.
[Soei] Awesome.
Bring it in!
You're a lifesaver.
Disappear for a while until you're sorted out.
[inhales sharply and exhales]
You deserve better, M.
You take good care of Ma for us, all right?
[mellow piano music playing]
Soei wasn't at his apartment.
His motorcycle wasn't there either.
I asked his neighbor if he'd seen him. He said he left town for work.
[gas hissing]
[man] Hello? Is anyone home?
[Grandma] Who is that?
I'll go see.
[man] Hello? Hello?
It must be someone Soei owes money to.
Hide somewhere.
I'll get rid of him.
[laughs] Hello, ma'am.
If you're looking for Soei, you're too late.
He's been ordained as a monk.
I'm just a humble housekeeper, and I'm not supposed to let anyone in.
Oh, well, I'm not looking for anyone named Soei, ma'am.
- Oh? - I'm here about the listing
I saw for this place.
I texted the seller, but he never replied to my message.
Uh, so I thought I'd drop by.
Oh, oh, thank you so much.
This house isn't for sale, sir.
- No. - Here's the internet post.
The seller is listed as M Thanapat, ma'am.
I don't suppose you recognize the name?
Mm, I don't believe I know that person.
Oh.
[melancholic piano music playing]
[M] Grandma?
Is he gone?
How'd you get him to go away?
Hmm, I told him I'm the maid.
[laughs]
Well, you can pull it off. You have the outfit.
And the scowl.
Now get to work, you silly maid. Enough sitting around.
[coins clink]
[Grandma] I bought you a new shirt.
It looks formal.
So you can look professional.
I don't know.
It's kind of old-fashioned.
[Grandma] Hmm.
You know,
I think the next chemo treatment could be the last one.
And then I'll be cured.
Then you won't be stuck here doing all of this.
[soft piano music playing]
Are you kicking me out?
When you were in elementary school,
people could see your potential.
You can do anything, but you have to try.
Huh?
Put in the effort and find yourself a proper job.
Hmm.
I'm just a slacker, Grandma.
I can't compete in the real world.
[wistful music playing]
[water trickling]
[birds chirping]
[Grandma] This pomegranate tree was planted to celebrate your birth.
It's just as old as you are.
They say that growing a pomegranate tree brings the child good health.
When I told you it was yours,
you asked me to promise that when the fruit was ready,
I'd keep it all for you.
Nobody else could have any.
Here. Eat.
I don't remember that at all.
I want to say I'm sorry
for calling you qi-chou all these years.
[sentimental music playing]
Would you let me use this as my hangout a bit longer?
I promise to leave when you beat this thing.
If that's okay?
Tomorrow,
there's someone I want you to meet.
[M] Your older brother lives in this mansion?
Why wasn't I born into this family?
[M chuckles]
Just look at this gate.
Wow.
[man crooning over speakers]
[people singing off-key]
[singing off-key]
- [music ends] - [applause]
[Grandma] The reason why my grandson and I are here today,
is because I have stomach cancer.
[man slurps]
And I'd like to get a burial plot to increase my chances.
Only I can't afford it right now.
Can you give me a million baht?
[sighs]
When we lost our parents,
you basically got everything they owned.
You got several million for the house.
I got nothing.
I've never asked you for a single baht.
I got what our mother and father wanted me to have.
You were there when this happened. Don't you forget that.
[Grandma] And don't you forget that I'm the one who wiped their butts.
I never received anything from them.
Ever since I can remember, whatever our parents had
always went to you first.
And there was nothing left over.
I did more than my duty.
And got nothing.
Why am I not entitled to something?
They respected our tradition…
and protected us.
Because that lousy husband of yours would have squandered it.
You might think he was lousy,
but he was chosen for me by tradition.
If you want the money so badly…
you should ask your children to help you.
Understand?
As for me, I won't give you a single penny.
Hey, M?
Let's go back home.
[indistinct chatter]
[chatter stops]
And don't you bother coming to my home ever again.
You and I don't share the same name anymore.
[somber music playing]
[train rumbling]
[woman on PA] Approaching Tha Phra Station.
Grandma, please.
We remind you to mind the gap between the train and the platform.
Tha Phra Station.
[birds tweeting]
[M] Why do you want a big burial plot so badly?
[Grandma] Because if I'm buried on a good plot of land,
then my children will be prosperous.
People will see it and think you guys have filial piety.
That's nonsense, Grandma.
It doesn't work that way.
Your parents are buried in one of those regular, small family plots.
But your brother still got rich.
When people die, they die. Game over.
The brain stops working,
and the body will either become part of the earth and help flowers grow,
or become part of the stratosphere.
You don't know from a burial plot how someone has lived.
Rich or poor doesn't make a difference.
Someday, when I'm dead,
if you dump petals on my grave carelessly,
I will come back to haunt you.
[M] Bring it.
Be a ghost.
I hope you come.
Only I don't think you'll know who actually showed up for you on Qingming.
Uncle Kiang might pay someone to do the ritual.
I could pull your plot on Google Street Maps
and pay respects through the screen.
[Grandma] But if I have a beautiful burial plot…
you all might want to meet up there.
[gentle music playing]
[man speaking indistinctly over PA]
[doctor] Hello. Please sit down.
Let's just see here…
After going over the results of your mother's treatment,
we unfortunately haven't seen any improvement.
[M] The doctor said that you're better.
You don't need any more chemo.
You told us that the chemotherapy would get rid of the cancer.
Is it possible that the results are wrong?
He said we can treat your pain as it comes along.
[Grandma] I don't need to complete the treatment?
[doctor] What I'd recommend
is to spend as much time as you can with her.
- It's very important for the patient. - It's all right.
The family needs to stay strong.
[Grandma] I didn't tell you.
Ngek's gone already. She died a few days ago.
She didn't finish her treatment either.
I have a right to know.
What did he really say?
[Sew sniffles]
[speaking Teochew]
Ma, what did she say?
[cries]
What did she tell you, Ma?
[sniffling]
"The rice grains have become cooked rice."
It's a saying that means accept what can't be changed.
[somber music playing]
[Sew crying]
[Sew whimpering]
[Grandma, sobbing] Baba. Ma.
Come and take me with you. It hurts too much.
[whimpering]
I want to join you and Grandma and the others.
[wheezing and sobbing]
Shh.
I want to die.
Grandpa.
Help me.
[M grunts]
[pen scratching]
Hey.
Is Ma getting worse?
They'll be running some tests. If there's nothing new, she can go home.
- Huh? - [Sew] Get up.
[Soei grunts]
Let's talk outside for a minute, Sew.
Do you know where the deed to her house is?
She hasn't been buried yet, Kiang.
Ma's not dead. Why are you asking about her house?
When we have buried her,
someone's going to have to take care of it.
If we do it while Ma's alive, it'll be much easier.
Pinn put you up to this business, right?
[sighs]
This is precisely why I don't want to be around you guys.
I'm not gonna let my wife be treated like she's not a member of this family.
Do you know where the deed is?
She keeps her papers in her bedroom closet.
Ma, if Uncle Kiang asks her to sign something, don't let her do it.
And!
Are you listening to me?
You better do this now, Soei.
You're the best, sis.
Grandma gave her house to your uncle.
[somber music playing]
[monitor beeping]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sighs]
[cell phone rings]
Just a second.
M, I need to go settle the bill.
Take her over to the taxi line and wait there.
Let's go.
M!
[M sighs]
PATIENT PICK-UP AND DROP-OFF POINT
You gave your house to Soei? Haven't you learned your lesson?
He'll always struggle more than the others.
Because you enable him.
That's why he's such a loser.
Your parents did the same thing.
Cutting out the caregiver.
I don't have anything else to give.
You don't have to look after me anymore.
I've been doing a good job, haven't I?
You have done good work.
Quite impressive, actually.
How come I'm not gonna be rewarded?
When I should be first?
[rain pattering]
Where do I stand with you?
Huh?
Tell me!
Tell me, Grandma.
[sobs softly]
Stubborn fool.
[thunder rumbles]
I should be first.
[footsteps recede]
[sorrowful music playing]
[music playing over headphones]
Die! Die! Die! Die! Your mom's dead!
You're mine now.
Have you even been to bed yet?
And!
Everyone can hear you.
Huh? You actually have viewers on at this hour?
Don't you know that expression, "The early bird gets the worm"?
Especially if the worm
is in another time zone.
The new owner of Grandma's house is going to start renovations.
Can you go help clean it out?
Everything can just go in the garbage.
What's that face?
That's not nice.
You're almost as bad as your Uncle Kiang.
You know what he said today?
That if Ma dies, he won't bother coming to the funeral.
It really is a blessing that neither of us got Grandma's house.
My favorite saying is, "It's better to give than to receive."
And it's true.
[M] Are you trying to cheer yourself up or what?
[Sew groans]
Weren't you hoping for Grandma's house?
Whatever gave you that idea?
Come on, why else would you have changed your work schedule
and gone to all those appointments?
So that I could be with her.
The house was a little too quiet
when you went to Grandma's, M.
Were you lonely?
It helped me understand
how once we had all moved out,
she must have found that hard.
[tender piano music playing]
[woman laughs]
[woman] Hi. You can bring the car into the garage.
Your room's waiting for you, Mui.
- Thank you, Auntie. - [woman] Of course.
[Mui] Last week, Auntie fainted.
It turns out something's wrong with her heart.
So she asked me to come and help her.
Her only son passed away several years ago.
And her daughter-in-law and grandkids moved away overseas.
We could do this as a team.
I'll be her nurse around here.
You take her to all her appointments.
When she makes me her number one,
I'll give you a share.
I really thought the house would be yours.
Grandma told me you worked hard
and took good care of her.
Do you ever dream of your grandpa?
On the day that we lost him…
he was eating and choked on his food.
I could have cleared his airway.
Except I chose not to.
At the end, he was always asking me…
to let him join his ancestors.
So I have to assume he's happy where he is.
Because he hasn't been in my dreams yet.
[soft piano music playing]
[tender music playing]
[Grandma sighs]
[Grandma] I humbly pay my respect to the benevolent goddess Guanyin.
Please deliver me from sorrow and illness.
[woman on TV] The important thing is to keep up the pace, all right?
We want the heart rate to be somewhat elevated.
[laughing]
[children shouting distantly]
[exotic bird calling]
NURSING HOME
[M, on phone] Ma, did you know Uncle Soei didn't take Grandma to live with him?
He put her in a nursing home.
I'm gonna go visit her.
- [woman 1] Hello. - [woman 2] Hello.
- [woman 1] Nice to see you. - [woman 2] Hi.
- [woman 3] Hi! - [woman 1] Hello.
Good afternoon.
Hello.
Hello! Are you visiting your family?
- Hello. - Hi.
- You have someone here? - Hi.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Chaiyapon, your nephew's here to visit.
- [Soei] I'll be right out. - [woman] Enjoy your time.
She's asleep, so you have to be quiet.
[M] Mm-hmm.
I got everything paid off.
But there's a little left over.
I want you to have it.
You can hold on to it.
Come on. It's for you.
No one's gonna rescue you when she's gone.
[groans weakly]
Who is it?
It's your qi-chou, Grandma.
[Grandma] Have you eaten yet, M?
That's better for showing myself off like I want.
[gentle piano music playing]
How about you come home with me, Grandma?
I'll make you congee for breakfast.
Let's go home.
[gentle music continues]
[wind chimes tinkling]
[rummaging]
[Okay] No!
Why are you keeping these things?
[Sew] They're fine.
Anyway, I learned that from you.
What are you even doing in here? You should be resting.
[Grandma] Go.
You shouldn't follow my example when it comes to food.
Eat things that are fresh and healthy.
Because cancer can be genetic.
Oh, I know.
Sons inherit the goods. Daughters get the genes.
Are you guys having a moment?
Or just gossiping?
Don't let me interrupt.
Your M…
All through my illness he's badgered me to answer…
which one of you
I love the most of all.
I don't know the answer.
But I do know…
if there's someone I most want to stay with, it's you.
[gentle music playing]
[paper crinkling]
MAY GOOD FORTUNE COME TO OUR FAMILIES
MAY YOU BE PROSPEROUS
[leaves rustling]
- Hello, Auntie. - Hi, M.
[Rainbow] Happy Chinese New Year, cousin.
Grandma's gonna be amazed at how much you've grown.
[Pinn] Let's go see her, Rainbow.
[M] Not sure if you know, Uncle.
Grandma told me the story
of how beef used to be her absolute favorite.
But you used to get sick a lot as a boy.
She prayed to her goddess to boost your immune system.
In exchange for Guanyin making you strong and healthy,
she gave up something she really loved.
[melancholic music playing]
Kiang.
Come inside.
You're making yourself sick with guilt.
Grandma.
Kiang came to see you.
Smile.
Huh?
Grandma?
Can you feel him holding your hand?
I see you have your blessings here.
M is a dedicated grandson.
[dramatic music playing]
[soft music playing]
[singing in Teochew] ♪ Rock, oh, rock ♪
♪ Rock my golden master ♪
[sighs weakly]
♪ May you grow up to be prosperous ♪
♪ Surrounded by servants ♪
♪ Waiting on you hand and foot ♪
♪ Rock, oh, rock ♪
♪ Rock my golden master ♪
♪ May you grow up to be prosperous ♪
♪ Surrounded by servants ♪
♪ Waiting on you hand and foot ♪
[sobbing softly]
♪ Rock, oh, rock ♪
♪ Rock my golden master ♪
[gasps]
[cries]
[insects chirping]
[lighter scratching]
[in English] I got tripe, liver, tendons, and super tender bits of steak, Grandma.
Have you seen the silver belt that I got at Grandpa's funeral?
I've been looking everywhere, and I can't find it.
[cell phone vibrates]
Hello?
Is this some kind of scam?
She passed away recently. What's this about?
MRS. MENGJU SAEJIEW FOR MR. THANAPAT THAWARAKUL
[M] I don't remember that.
It's been open how long?
[train rumbling]
[train whistle blares]
[leaves rustling]
All you do is play those games.
And it makes you slow as a snail. The bank'll close before we get there.
I only walk slow so you don't get too tired.
I'm starting an account at the bank for you.
Look, M.
We're going to put money in.
To celebrate your good grades.
I'm going to keep putting in deposits throughout the year.
[Young M] Can you keep putting money in until you die?
I want to have a million baht.
[Grandma] Oh. Are you jinxing me to die?
What would you do with a million baht?
[Young M] I would start by buying you a new house, Grandma.
'Cause your place is so old,
and bugs are crawling all over the food.
[Grandma] Well, that's harsh.
[Young M] Just talking about it gives me goose bumps. See?
[Grandma] My goodness. You got goose bumps?
You are absolutely full of it.
[leaves rustling]
I'll withdraw it all and close the account, ma'am.
[gentle piano music playing]
[tailgate creaks closed]
M.
Knock on the coffin and tell Grandma where we're going.
[knocks]
Grandma?
We're on our way.
[tender music playing]
[uplifting music playing]
[knocking]
[M] Grandma?
We're passing your congee shop.
[knocking]
Grandma?
We're crossing the old bridge.
[uplifting music continues]
[knocks]
Grandma?
We're almost at the big plot I bought you.
[uplifting music swelling]
[majestic music playing]
[knocks]
Grandma?
You're my number one.
[orchestral music playing]
[leaves rustling]
[firecrackers popping]
[Kiang] Rainbow.
What are you doing?
Here.
Go scatter the flowers for Grandma.
Soei, why don't you help lay out the food?
[Soei] I'm trying to win the 12,000,000 lottery, bro.
[Kiang grunts]
[Kiang] There.
Do a nice job for Grandma.
[Soei] Kiang, Ma was 78, wasn't she?
- [M] Rainbow. Here, let me help. - [Kiang] Seventy-nine.
- [M] Thanks. - [Soei] Seventy-nine…
[M] I'll show you how. Watch.
Ready?
Whoop!
[Sew] Jeez, guys. It doesn't matter what numbers you choose.
You'll never win.
Do you have 22?
[Kiang] Why 22? Ma was 79.
[Sew] It's from that one time
when Ma took a picture with the three of us.
[Kiang] Where did it say that?
[Sew] Let's do the kids' ages too.
[tender music playing]
[wind gusts]
[mellow piano music playing]
[wind gusting]
[gentle piano music playing]
[music ends]
[tender piano music playing]
[birds tweeting]
[piano music resumes]
[cat meows]
[music ends]
[introspective piano music playing]
["Suai ngam Samoe" by Billkin playing in Thai]
[song ends]