Our story begins
high over New York City...
in the luxurious
penthouse apartment...
of perhaps
the most unlikely genius
the world has ever known.
Oh. Sorry. You caught me
doing my yoga.
You were expecting
downward dog,
perhaps?
My name is Mr. Peabody.
And since we're going to be
spending some time together...
I'd like to tell you
a little bit about myself.
You see,
ever since I was a pup...
it was clear that
I was different.
I tried
to fit in...
No, thank you.
...but never could.
As I grew,
I saw more and more
of my littermates...
being chosen by
their new families.
But for some reason,
I never was.
Come on, boy!
Fetch the stick!
But why? Won't you
just throw it again?
It's an exercise in futility.
I don't want this one,
Mommy. He's sarcastic.
Wait, wait!
Come back!
Throw the stick.
I'll stay, I'll heel,
I'll even shake hands.
Bark, bark?
So, without
a family of my own...
I dedicated myself to
the pursuit of knowledge...
culture, and athletics.
I received my degree at Harvard.
Vale-dog-torian, of course.
Yay!
And then,
I devoted myself
to helping mankind.
I pioneered new techniques
in alternative energy.
Yay!
Resolved
geopolitical conflicts
around the globe.
And in my spare time...
I invented
the fist bump, planking,
tearaway pants...
Auto-Tune...
the backside ollie...
and Zumba.
Now go
Stop
Drop
Pause
But what I'm most proud of
is my son, Sherman.
Hi, Mr. Peabody.
Oh!  Have you
told them about the WABAC?
I was
just getting to that.
When I adopted Sherman,
I vowed to be
the best father I could be.
To prepare him for all
the wonders of the world,
present and past.
And so, Sherman
inspired the greatest
invention of my life...
a time machine.
Of course, time travel
can be a bit unpredictable.
There are bound to be
a few mishaps along the way.
Let's just say,
the Leaning Tower of Pisa
wasn't always leaning.
But there's
nothing like learning
the lessons of
history firsthand.
Right, Sherman?
Where are we going
today, Mr. Peabody?
Not "where," Sherman.
"When."
Whoa! This is
the biggest house
I've ever seen!
It's the Palace
of Versailles, home
of Marie Antoinette.
You know,
she was mostly
famous for one thing.
Cake!
I love cake so much.
Marie Antoinette
sure likes cake,
Mr. Peabody.
Oh!
Indeed she does.
Marie was a woman
with a prodigious
appetite...
for all things
covered with frosting.
But her expensive tastes
made her the target
of much criticism.
Why?
Because, Sherman...
during Marie's reign,
the common people
of France were exceedingly poor.
You've got any bread?
No! I'm exceedingly poor.
Now, can we have some cake?
Mais, oui.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
"May we" have some cake?
Mais, oui!
Maybe she can't hear me
through the hair.
Sherman, what
the queen means is...
Ah!
Let them eat cake!
When the queen
heard the poor of Paris
could not even buy bread...
she said,
"Let them eat cake."
No!
I heard it myself.
It's a scandal!
It's an outrage!
Down with the queen!
Down with the monarchy!
Wait!
What kind of cake?
Smashing party, Your Majesty.
But now, I'm afraid
Sherman and I must be...
Sherman? Sherman?
Sherman!
Sherman?
Sherman! Here,
Sherman.
Hey, Mr. Peabody.
What are you doing in here?
Trying these other cakes.
There's one in here
with whipped cream and
strawberries that's...
pretty fantastic!
Sherman...
don't you remember
why I told you to stay
close to me during
the French Revolution?
Because after
the French Revolution...
it was gonna rain?
Close.
I said, "After the
French Revolution comes...
the Reign of Terror!"
Round up the aristocrats.
The queen and her
aristocratic cronies...
must pay the price
for their gluttony.
We will slaughter them
like the dogs they are.
Starting with this one!
Mr. Peabody!
What should I do?
Nothing, Sherman.
Just stay right there.
But, Mr. Peabody!
Everything is going
to be fine, Sherman.
Just stay right there.
Off with his head!
Mr. Peabody!
A cantaloupe?
The lowest of the fruits.
Who dares to insult me
with this melon?
Get that dog!
Mr. Peabody,
how did you escape?
It's simple, Sherman.
I noticed the distance
between the sewer lids...
reasoned that there must be one
directly under
the guillotine platform...
noted the loose board
under the basket...
computed the angle at
which the setting sun
would bounce off your glasses...
momentarily blinding
the executioner...
and chose that moment
to swipe
the executioner's melon...
giving me the added weight
to tip the boards,
facilitating my exit.
That's amazing!
It's not amazing.
It was just a matter
of keeping my head.
"Keeping your head."
I don't get it.
There he is!
After them!
Come, Sherman, quick!
Oh, this
water tastes terrible.
Interestingly, that's not water.
Ha-ha!
I've got you now.
Indeed you have,
Monsieur Robespierre.
And what a master
of the chase you are.
Oh, you noticed?
Of course.
Doubling back on me like that.
That was genius.
Thank you.
I just hope you don't take
my little confederate, here.
I depend on him so completely.
Get over here, you.
Drats!
You're devilishly clever.
I know.
And much quicker
than you as well.
But are you quick
enough for this?
Ha-ha! See? Quick!
Quick, yes, but not too smart.
Oh! Another cantaloupe!
Your sword!
All right, Sherman,
looks like it's time
for a little pop quiz
in the art of fencing.
Go!
Attack! Parry!
Thrust! Repeat!
No.
Remise!
Good boy!
Oh!
Huh?
Ha-ha! You missed!
I never miss.
Hop on!
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
Yeah! Whoa!
Yeah!
Do you smell that, Sherman?
It wasn't me, Mr. Peabody.
I know it wasn't you.
It's the methane gas
in the sewer system.
And given
the fact that it ignites
at 306 degrees Fahrenheit...
we're about to use it...
to blast out of here!
Hang on!
Whoo!
Wow!
Nice landing, eh, Sherman?
Oof!
So, what did you
learn today, Sherman?
That French Revolution
was crazy.
How so?
All those guys
getting their
heads chopped off...
and nobody standing up
and saying it wasn't right.
And think, Marie Antoinette
could have avoided
the whole revolution...
if she'd simply issued an edict
to distribute
bread amongst the poor.
But then,
she couldn't have
had her dessert.
Why not, Mr. Peabody?
Because, Sherman, you can't have
your cake and edict, too.
I don't get it.
Where are we
gonna go tomorrow,
Mr. Peabody?
Ancient Rome?
The Wild West? 1492?
No, Sherman,
tomorrow we won't be going
to any of those places.
Oh. Why not?
Because tomorrow's adventure...
is one that you're
going to be taking
all on your own.
What do you mean,
Mr. Peabody?
Don't you remember?
It's your first day of school.
Oh. Can I drive?
Of course not.
Remember, Sherman,
"i" before "e,"
except after "c."
I know, Mr. Peabody!
And don't forget about
the commutative principle.
Two plus three
equals three plus two.
I know, Mr. Peabody!
And if you have to
go to the bathroom...
just raise your hand proudly
and say, "I have to go."
I will, Mr. Peabody.
And remember,
the No. 2 pencil is
standard for most uses...
but there are times
when a No. 1 comes in handy.
I left a little pencil chart
in your backpack...
which you can consult
if it ever
becomes a judgment call.
I think
I'll be okay!
Okay, bye, Mr. Peabody.
Wait.
See you after school.
Sherman!
I gotta go. I gotta
sign up for the clubs.
No one is more in
favor of participation
in fraternal
organizations than I.
But before you go,
I want you to have this.
Thanks. What is it?
A dog whistle.
It doesn't work,
Mr. Peabody.
It works fine, Sherman.
It's just a frequency
only dogs can hear.
Oh, cool.
Let that little keepsake
be a reminder to you...
that no matter what
challenges you face,
no matter how far
away I might seem...
Bye, Mr. Peabody!
...I'm with you.
George Washington.
Who can tell me who he is?
Oh, me! I can! I can!
Uh... Sherman.
The first president
of the United
States of America.
Good job.
And when President Washington
was a little boy...
what kind of tree
did he cut down?
Ooh! Ooh, me! Me! Me!
Penny?
A cherry tree.
Apocryphal.
What kind of tree is that?
It's not a tree.
It's a word.
"Apocryphal."
It means that story is not true.
Really?
Yeah.
George Washington
never cut down
a cherry tree...
and he never said
he couldn't lie.
People made those
stories up to teach kids
a lesson about lying...
but they're not true.
He did cross the Delaware River,
Christmas night, 1776, though.
My dad took me
there this summer.
We crossed it, too.
I fell in.
Looks like someone
really knows their
history, huh, Penny?
It's really great
meeting you guys.
Maybe you can come over
to my house sometime.
I could bring my new model.
It's a hydrogen atom.
You've only got one, huh?
Guess we'll have to split it.
Good one!
Check it, guys.
What do you got there,
Sherman?
Kibbles or bits?
Actually, I've got baby carrots,
organic apple juice,
and a tuna sandwich.
It's super-high
in omega-3s.
So, you eat human food, huh?
Yeah. Why wouldn't I?
Because you're a dog.
No, I'm not.
Sure you are.
Your dad is a dog,
so you're a dog, too.
I think you're confused.
It's an adoptive
relationship.
Zip it, Carl.
Okay.
Here, I'll show you.
Fetch!
Go on, doggy.
Go get your lunch.
Go on.
Go get it.
Ugh. The humiliation.
Sherman,
go get your food.
Make like a good little doggy.
Ruff-ruff!
What's this?
It's mine!
Give it back!
What is it? A whistle?
Ugh! Stupid thing
doesn't even work.
It's a dog whistle, Penny.
It operates at a frequency
that only dogs can hear.
Back up, Carl.
Okay.
Penny, that whistle
is my private property.
Give it back!
Jump, doggy,
jump.
I am not a dog.
Come on, Sherman!
Just admit it.
You're a dog. Say it.
Let me go!
Not until you beg like a dog.
Come on, Sherman. Beg!
Fight, fight, fight!
Mr. Peabody,
thank you for coming in
on such short notice...
to discuss
the problem with Sherman.
Oh, it's not a problem
at all, Principal Purdy.
I fully expected this.
You did?
Yes.
And, as with all
things Sherman-related,
I prepared for it.
Here's a curriculum
that takes Sherman's
advanced preparation
into account...
but won't require you
to have him skip
one or more grades.
Mr. Peabody...
Here are some
pre-algebra worksheets,
an advanced reading list...
and a link to
a website I created
so he can start
studying Mandarin Chinese.
It is, after all,
the language of the future.
Mr. Peabody!
I'm not saying he
shouldn't study French,
too, Principal Purdy.
I'm saying have him do both.
Mr. Peabody!
What? Not enough? Swahili?
Sherman got into a fight today.
Oh, dear.
Pictures were taken...
for insurance purposes.
He bit her.
I must say,
it doesn't look good
for you, Mr. Peabody.
After all, you are a dog.
Who, may I ask, are you?
I am Ms. Grunion from
the Bureau of Child
Safety and Protection.
We're required by
law to contact them
whenever there's an...
incident.
Sherman has never done
anything like this before.
I'm sure he must
have had a reason.
Well, the girl was being
a bit of a bully...
Quiet, Purdy!
It's normal for
children to tease.
It's not normal
for them to bite.
Clearly, it's because of
how he's being raised.
In my opinion,
a dog can never be
a suitable parent
to a little boy.
I must point out,
Ms. Grunion...
that I won
the right to adopt Sherman
in a court of law.
And the court can
take it away from you.
I'll be coming to your
home tomorrow evening
to conduct an investigation.
If I discover that
you are, in any way,
an unfit parent...
I will see to it
Sherman is removed
from your custody.
Permanently.
I hope I've made myself clear.
Crystal.
I'm sorry
I bit her, Mr. Peabody.
I won't do it again.
You're darn tooting
you won't do it again.
This kind of wanton violence
is totally unacceptable.
And rather uncharacteristic,
given how you feel
about Mr. Gandhi.
What on earth provoked it?
She called me a dog.
Well, all right then.
Thank you for telling me.
Try and get some sleep.
I love you, Mr. Peabody.
I have a deep regard
for you as well, Sherman.
Close your eyes
Have no fear
The master's gone
He's on the run
And your daddy's here
Beautiful, beautiful,
beautiful, beautiful boy
Say a little prayer
Every day, in every way
It's getting better and better
Beautiful, beautiful,
beautiful, beautiful boy
A hard road to hoe
Yes, it's a long way to go
But in the meantime
Take my hand
Life is what happens
to you while you're busy
making other plans
Beautiful, beautiful,
beautiful, beautiful boy
Mr. Peabody...
you are
a Nobel Prize-winning
scientist.
An advisor to heads of state.
A captain of industry.
Why would you
want to adopt a boy?
Because, Your Honor...
when I found Sherman,
it reminded me of how
I started out in life.
And now, I want to give him
the one thing I always wanted.
A home.
And you're sure you're
capable of meeting
all the challenges...
of raising a human boy?
With all due respect,
how hard could it be?
Very well, then.
If a boy can adopt a dog...
I see no reason
why a dog cannot adopt a boy.
Da-da!
No, Sherman, not "Da-da."
You shall call me
"Mr. Peabody."
Or, in less formal moments,
simply "Peabody."
That's right.
"Mr. Pea-baba."
Beautiful, beautiful,
beautiful, beautiful boy
What's cooking, Mr. Peabody?
Oh, nothing much.
Just a little Dungeness
crab with a passion-fruit
basil concassé.
Some truffled quails
in a juniper-berry reduction.
And Baked Alaska.
Wow! Is today some
kind of special occasion?
You could say.
It's not my birthday.
No, it isn't.
It's not your birthday.
Right again.
It's not Father's Day.
Is it?
Nope. It's not Father's Day.
Is the president
coming to dinner again?
No.
Oh.
So, who's coming to dinner?
Let's just say,
if the evening
is a success...
we can put this whole
"biting" business behind us.
The Petersons! Welcome.
So, he's literally a dog.
Paul!
No, that's all right.
Although,
I prefer "literate dog."
That's funny.
Isn't that funny, Paul?
He's not
a big laugher.
We're so delighted
you could make it
on such short notice.
Aren't we, Sherman?
Yeah, we're interested
in what's going on,
that's for sure.
Say hello to Penny, Sherman.
Hi, Penny.
Hello, Sherman.
Now, why don't you go show Penny
your mineral collection,
Sherman?
I'm sure she'll find
those new geodes
of yours fascinating.
Come on.
I am so glad you
accepted my invitation.
Now, the kids can
resolve their differences
before Ms. Grunion arrives.
You're barking up
the wrong tree, mister.
In fact...
if it weren't for Patty,
I would have pressed
charges already.
And I have to
tell you, Peabody...
where my daughter is concerned,
nothing is more
important than...
Hello. Sure,
I'll take a survey.
Everything going swimmingly?
Ugh.
Why didn't you tell me
she was coming over here?
Because I didn't
want you to worry.
Okay, because I
didn't want to listen
to your bellyaching.
Thank you for your honesty.
You're welcome.
I don't know what you
think we're supposed to
do in here anyway.
She hates me.
Share your interests.
Tell a witty anecdote.
Mr. Peabody...
I hate her.
Sherman,
every great relationship...
starts from a place of conflict,
and evolves into
something richer.
Bonne chance.
Make it work.
But don't tell her
about the WABAC.
Don't even
think about it.
Ah.
Peabody,
that was amazing!
Paul, wasn't that amazing?
I'm more into
rock-'n'-roll.
I meant flamenco.
Bagpipes?
Uh, didgeridoo.
Sitar.
Steel drums.
Trombone.
Xylophone.
Djembe?
Calliope.
Oboe. Piccolo.
Tuba. Dobro.
Slide whistle. Yodeling.
Hurdy-gurdy. Ocarina.
Harmonium. Musical saw.
You know what?
This has been great...
but a complete waste of time.
Now, let's get Penny
and go home!
Are you all right, Paul?
I'm... fine.
This happens
whenever he's tense.
Paul, if I might...
Stay away from me, Peabody!
Just get back!
I need traction.
You can trust me, Paul.
I'm a licensed chiropractor.
Ow! Huh.
Ooh...
Ah...
Peabody...
I feel great.
I...
I really feel great!
Peabody,
you're a miracle worker.
Ha-ha! Look at me!
I'm dancing!
You know, Penny...
Sigmund Freud says
if you don't like a person...
it's because they remind
you of something you
don't like about yourself.
What do you know
about Sigmund Freud?
More than you think.
Sure.
Just like you know
all that stuff...
about George Washington
not really cutting
down the cherry tree.
Ugh. What a crock.
But it's true!
How do you know?
I just know!
Did you read it in a book?
No!
See it in a movie?
Did your brainiac dad tell you?
No!
So, how do you know, Sherman?
How do you know?
He told me.
Who told you?
George Washington.
George Washington?
Yeah.
Ugh! Liar.
But don't tell
her about the WABAC.
He calls it the "WABAC."
So, where have you gone in it?
Not "where," Penny, "when."
Okay, smart guy, when?
Oh, 1965, 1776, 1620...
1492, 1215, 4.
Can it go back to an hour ago?
Why?
Because I could take it home,
pretend to be sick...
and not come to
this lame dinner party.
Ha-ha. Mr. Peabody says
you should never
use the WABAC...
to travel to
a time when you existed.
How come?
There would be two of you.
Oh, yeah.
I guess the world's
not ready for that.
Wow.
Um, well, now that
we've seen it, maybe
we should go back.
Are you kidding?
Where should we go first?
Mr. Peabody says
I'm not allowed to
drive it till I'm older.
Do you do everything
Mr. Peabody says?
Yeah.
You know what that
makes you, Sherman.
An obedient son?
Nope.
A dog.
Ooh!
Nice control.
Look at him go!
Take it, Patty!
Heads up, Paul!
Whoa!
Here you go. Zing!
Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Hey, look at that.
This is fun!
This is a little
homespun concoction
I like to call...
"Einstein on the Beach."
Yummy.
To the kids.
To the kids!
Mr. Peabody.
Sherman?
Can I talk to you a second?
Of course.
Excuse me.
I've really hit it off
with Penny's parents.
I think we can file this night
under "Unqualified Success."
Uh, I would hold off
filing it just yet.
What do you mean?
Where's Penny?
Uh... Ancient Egypt.
You used the WABAC?
What's happening,
big guy? We're running low.
I'll be right there, Paul.
How could you do such a thing?
She called me a liar...
for saying George Washington
never cut down a cherry tree.
So, you took her
to see George Washington?
Yeah. She was into it.
Hey, Pea-buddy.
Hey.
Where's Penny?
Playing hide-and-seek.
Pooping.
Playing hide and seek.
Well, which is it?
Uh...
Hey, what's going on here?
Yeah. What's going on here?
What have you done with Penny?
Penny?
Penny? Penny!
Oh, my gosh!
Where's our daughter?
It's hard to say, Paul.
She could be here, or here,
or here, or here...
or here.
That will hold them.
I learned that
trick from a swami
at the Begawan Giri
in Ubud, Bali.
Let's go!
Ancient Egypt.
Land of the Pharaohs.
A beacon of progress
on the horizon of humanity...
but a cruel and
barbarous civilization
just the same.
I just hope
Penny isn't suffering
too badly.
I got it.
What are you doing here?
We have come to take you home.
Ugh! What's the Egyptian word
for "tattletale"?
But that's beside the point.
Get your clothes on,
we're going home.
Who died and made you Pharaoh?
Now, bring on
the mani-pedi.
See, Mr. Peabody?
Lmpossible!
Indeed,
but watch what happens...
when an immovable object
meets an irresistible force.
Penny...
come here, right now.
Penny, come!
I'm not Penny anymore.
Now, I'm Princess Hatsheput,
precious flower of the Nile.
"Precious," perhaps,
but if you think
"we're going to
leave you here...
you are most
definitely in "de-Nile."
I don't get it.
Now, come along.
Unhand her!
What's the matter,
my sweet little
desert blossom?
Are these barbarians
bothering you?
As a matter of fact, they are.
Bow, barbarians.
As you wish, Your Highness.
Who's that, Mr. Peabody?
That, Sherman, is
the living image of Amun...
son of Akhenaten,
lord of the 18th Dynasty
of the New Kingdom...
King Tutankhamun.
Otherwise known
as "King Tut."
My boyfriend.
King Tut is
your boyfriend?
Mmm-hmm.
Would you like me
to have them skinned,
covered with honey...
and laid in
a pit of fire ants?
You would do that for me?
Anything, my desert flower.
Consider it a wedding gift.
What? You can't
marry this guy!
Why not?
Well, for one,
his name rhymes
with "butt."
I don't care.
I'm gonna have a big,
fat, Egyptian wedding.
Spoiler alert,
King Tut dies young.
Are you sure you've
thought this through?
Oh, trust me,
I've thought it through.
I'm getting everything.
The royal astronomers
have decreed...
the wedding must take
place tomorrow at dawn.
Who is he?
He is Ay.
He is you?
I am Ay. The Grand Vizier.
Yeah, that's his name.
Oh.
Oh, Grand Vizier,
would you mind telling
the precious princess, here...
precisely what it means
to marry the young Pharaoh.
Gladly.
It means she
will be bound to him
in eternity...
through the sacred ceremonies
of disembowelment
and mummification...
as described in the holy texts.
Um, hold up a second.
Can you walk me
through that, somebody?
What he means, Penny,
is that when I die
they'll kill you, too.
And then they'll rip out
your organs, stuff them
in canopic jars...
and then mummify
whatever is left.
Okay, I'm seeing this now.
Thank you.
I'm going to go with them.
There's no turning back now.
To the palace!
Let the wedding
preparations begin!
Mr. Peabody! Sherman!
Do something!
Don't worry, Penny!
We'll save you!
Hey, wait! You can't just...
Leave us here.
Mr. Peabody?
Yes, Sherman?
Can
I hold your hand?
Of course you can.
Boy, your hand
is cold, Mr. Peabody.
Sherman?
Yeah?
That's not my hand.
That's disarming.
Now, to find a way out of here.
Yuck!
Look around, Sherman.
These tombs
are lined with
hieroglyphics...
designed to assist
the pharaohs' souls
in their journey
to the afterlife.
And they may assist us as well.
Oh, this depicts the god Anubis
sailing the boat of Ra
to the underworld.
It appears the boats of Ra
are the key to our escape.
We must find them in time
to stop the wedding.
Well, if you ask me,
we should let her
marry that guy.
They deserve each other.
What's that, Sherman?
Tut? Give me a break.
Bald, wears a skirt, and makeup.
If I didn't know
any better, Sherman,
I would say you were jealous.
Jealous? Of what?
Tut's affection
for Penny, of course.
You think I like Penny?
Mmm-hmm.
Give me a break!
It's not like I
want to hold her hand,
or go to the park...
or watch her while
she's brushing her hair.
Or anything.
Hmm.
A-ha!
Quickly, Sherman.
Ah, ah, ah!
Careful, Sherman.
It's a booby trap.
What's so funny?
You said "booby."
One wrong step
and we're done for.
"The boat...
"of Ra sails straight...
"to day.
"Take the wrong boat...
man will pay."
All right, Sherman,
now it's your turn.
Do the puzzle exactly as I did.
Huh?
Think it through,
one step at a time.
The boat of Ra sails straight...
play.
Uh, I mean, "pay."
Oh, my.
Uh-oh.
Run!
The boats of Ra!
One boat is the way out,
the other will send us...
plunging into darkness
and certain death.
What?
Sherman, get in the boat.
As soon as I move
these blocks together,
it's going to move very fast.
Which boat, Mr. Peabody?
What?
Which boat
is the "not-certain-
death-plunge" boat?
That one!
We did it, Sherman!
Sherman?
Mr. Peabody!
What are you doing over there?
I thought you
pointed to this one!
Ahhh!
Sherman? Sherman?
Are you all right?
I'm good.
The sun god, Ra...
commands us to begin
the sacred ceremony!
Bring forth the blade
for the blood oath.
Where blade meets flesh
in this sacred rite...
We pay tribute...
to the sun god, Ra!
Wait!
Anubis!
The god of death!
The wedding
must not continue.
Why, Anubis, why?
Plagues. Plagues!
If this marriage
pact is sealed...
I will shower
down upon the land
uncountable plagues.
Oy, again with the plagues!
Why did I ever move to Egypt?
But, Anubis,
the sun god, Ra,
has decreed...
that this girl
is to be
the boy-king's wife.
That's so funny.
I was talking to
the sun god, Ra,
just the other day...
and he told me
he changed his mind.
Really?
Old "Flip-Flop Ra,"
we call him here
in the underworld.
But it's too late.
We've already paid
for the catering.
Too bad!
You're going to
lose your deposit.
More smoke, Sherman.
This canine
subterfuge is working.
Deliver the girl...
to the gates of the city,
and leave her there...
where the gods
will retrieve her forthwith.
Only in this
manner may the plagues
upon this land be avoided.
The girl must go!
Ow!
Anubis has spoken!
Take this girl to the gates!
Ow.
Anubis, you sound unwell.
Well, I have been feeling
a little under the weather...
but I'm feeling much better now.
Thank you.
Phew! Huh?
Penny, Sherman, quickly.
Come on, Penny.
Sherman!
Ah!
Runaway bride!
Stop them, you fools!
Ah!
Penny, Sherman, climb aboard.
Whoo-hoo!
They're getting away!
Ah!
Whoa!
I got it.
Whoo-hoo! We made it.
Where do we
go next, Mr. Peabody?
Home.
We've got to get back
to the dinner party...
before Penny's parents
realize she's missing.
We don't have to
mention the whole...
uh, King Tut
wedding thing, right?
Certainly not.
Anyway, as far as I'm concerned,
they get married too
young in Ancient Egypt.
Or, perhaps,
I'm just some old "Giza."
Huh?
Warning.
WABAC power supply insufficient.
Charge now. Warning.
Uh, what's the matter,
Mr. Peabody?
All this zipping about
the cosmos has drained
our power supply.
We're going to have to
make an unscheduled stop.
As luck would have it...
we have just enough
power to make it
to the Renaissance.
I can't even
tell my left brain
from my right anymore!
How many times
I got to tell you,
Mona Lisa?
I can't
paint the picture...
until you smile!
Leonardo, tell me one thing
I have to smile about.
The sunshine, the pasta.
All the things that make
Italy such a popular
tourist destination!
But I have not
seen any of them,
Leonardo!
Because I'm
sitting here all day
on my abbondanza!
I don't think
that means
"chair" in Italian.
Ah, Peabody, my old friend.
What a welcome interruption!
Believe you me,
this woman is
making me nuts.
So, how you been?
Good to see you.
What do you want?
We're in a desperate
hurry to get home,
but the WABAC
needs a jump start...
and we thought, who better than
Leonardo da Vinci to
help us on our way?
Peabody,
I would love to help you,
but you come at a very bad time.
I don't know
what I'm going to do
with this crazy woman.
You see what I mean?
What seems to be the problem?
"What is the problem?"
I am halfway done
with the painting,
she won't even smile.
Fine. I smile.
No! That's a fake smile!
Everybody knows that!
Why don't you
make it a real smile?
Why don't you say
something funny?
I paint the paintings.
I make the machines.
I don't tell the jokes!
Perhaps, I can be
of assistance. You see...
humor is not immune
to the laws of science.
Using algorithms,
we can extrapolate
what is universally
considered "funny"...
thus producing a formula that is
scientifically
certain to cause laughter.
Case in point, the pratfall.
Is everyone amused?
Hmm.
The data
was so clear. Ooh!
Don't worry, Mr. Peabody.
I got it!
Sherman... Ahh!
Oh!
Hold that smile!
Hold it right there!
No move! No move!
Well, Leo, if my
calculations are correct...
this machine of
ours should generate
enough centrifugal force...
to send us home.
I got one last piece
I gotta pound in place.
Sherman, why don't
you fetch the hammer
for Mr. Da Vinci?
Okay, Mr. Peabody.
Mr. Peabody!
Well done, Sherman.
But, Mr. Peabody!
Very helpful.
Sherman!
Yes, Mr. Peabody?
The hammer.
Da Vinci.
Oh. Okay, Mr. Peabody.
Oh!
Here you go, Mr. Da Vinci.
Ahh!
Do you need any help?
No, no.
That's quite all right.
Thank you.
Psst! Sherman.
Huh?
Let's go. Let's go explore.
Uh, well, I'm supposed
to be having
father-son time
with Mr. Peabody.
Wouldn't you rather
have fun with me?
Uh...
Okay.
Sherman...
where are you going?
Exploring.
But we need your help.
No, we don't!
I mean, we can manage.
Somehow.
He's a boy, Peabody.
Let him have his fun.
Let him go.
Thanks, Mr. Peabody!
He's growing up, Peabody.
Like a baby bird
leaving the nest.
Isn't it wonderful?
It's like a museum.
It's like a toy store.
Wow.
Check this out.
It's the world's
biggest model airplane.
It's not a model, Penny.
It's a prototype.
And we should probably
just leave that alone.
Okay.
But wouldn't it be cool
if we could fly it?
I don't think
Mr. Peabody would like that.
Well, Mr. Peabody
isn't here.
Just tell me how it works.
Please?
For learning.
Oh. Okay.
The thrust comes from
this kind of crossbow
doohickey here.
Then it shoots along
the track until the wind
catches the wings.
But how does it go?
Huh?
How do you take off?
Oh, you just
pull down that lever.
This one?
Oh, boy.
Ah!
Wow! Whoo-hoo!
This is crazy!
No, it's not Sherman.
It's fun!
We're gonna die!
Oh, stop being
such a party pooper and
enjoy it!
Ah...
Nothing is as beautiful
as an elegant equation...
translated into
perfect engineering.
Why can't children be so simple?
Because children
are not machines, Peabody.
Believe me,
I tried to build one.
Oh! It was creepy.
Here, Sherman!
You fly it!
But I don't want to fly!
Sure you do. It'll be fun!
No, seriously, Penny,
I don't want to!
I'm letting go. One...
Don't let go!
Two...
No!
Three!
Penny, fly the plane!
No, Sherman!
You're going to have to save us!
But I can't do it!
I'm serious, Penny.
I don't know how to fly!
You can do it!
I know you can!
Come on, Sherman.
Fly!
Ah!
Phew!
See? You got this,
Sherman.
You're right.
I have got this.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Da Vinci's at it again!
You ever see that child he made?
So creepy.
Papa. Mama.
All done up here, Leonardo.
And I am all done down here.
It is beautiful, isn't it?
Every piece in its place
doing precisely what
it's supposed to do.
Look, Peabody!
It's my flying mach...
My flying machine?
Sherman.
Sherman?
Sherman, what are
you doing up there?
I'm flying!
But, Sherman,
you don't know how to fly!
I don't?
No!
Turn!
Turn, Sherman!
Lean!
Oh, no!
Sherman?
Sherman! Are you okay?
That was pretty fantastic!
Oh! I can't believe it!
My flying machine!
It's work!
Sherman!
You are the first flying man!
Oh, you should be
very proud, Peabody.
Very, very proud!
"Proud" doesn't
begin to describe it.
Leonardo, will you please
fire up the mechanism?
Papa. Mama.
Mona!
The kid!
I'm sorry I broke
the plane, Mr. Peabody.
Well, you should be.
You could have been killed.
What are you talking about?
Sherman flew a plane.
He was amazing!
Sherman destroyed
a priceless
historical artifact.
Whatever. You
should be happy.
It turns out Sherman
is not a complete and
total loser, after all.
Yeah, Mr. Peabody.
It turns out I'm not
a complete and
total loser, after all.
Ms. Peterson...
stop turning my son
into a hooligan.
It's not my fault
he's a hooligan.
Yeah, it's not her
fault I'm a hooligan.
Well, it's certainly
not my fault!
I've spent the last seven years
teaching Sherman good judgment.
If you're such a great parent...
why is Ms. Grunion
trying to take
Sherman away from you?
Is that true?
Is someone gonna
take me away from you?
No, Sherman,
I'll never let that happen.
You just need to trust me.
Oh, dear, a black hole!
What's happening?
If I can't pull
us out of here...
we're going to be
smashed to smithereens
on the event horizon.
There's not enough
power to resist
the gravitational pull!
I've got to divert everything
to the reverse thrusters.
Why didn't you tell me?
Tell you what?
Why didn't you
tell me Ms. Grunion
was trying to take
me away from you?
It's not your job to
worry about these things.
You just didn't
think I could handle it.
We'll discuss it later.
Now, sit down.
I don't want to
discuss it later!
Sherman, sit!
You can't talk to me like that.
I'm not a dog.
What did you say?
I said, I'm not a dog!
You're right,
Sherman, you're not.
You're just a very bad boy!
T-minus 10...
Nine, eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four, three...
Two...
One.
Sherman?
Penny?
Sherman, are you okay?
Sherman?
He's gone.
Where are we, anyway?
Oh, no.
We're on the brink
of one of history's
most ferocious conflicts...
Delivery.
How are we doing,
heroes of Greece?
Feeling good?
Feeling strong?
Okay, let's get warmed up!
We don't want to pull
something out there.
Remember what
happened to Achilles.
That whole thing with his heel.
Looking good, Diomedes.
Menelaus, my man!
My man.
Are you ready
to get on the field,
Shermanus?
Sure thing, Mr. Agamemnon.
That's cute.
Shh.
Odysseus,
what news do you bring?
Someone left this for us.
A present. Nice.
It looks just like our horse.
Should I bring it inside?
It would be rude not to.
I did not see that coming!
Ugh! Jeez Louise,
what is that smell?
Oh!
Ooh. That is
the smell of victory.
Yeah! Victory!
Greetings, men of
Athens, Sparta and Thebes.
Peabody, here.
I've come for Sherman.
Do you know this guy?
I thought I did...
but now I'm not so sure.
Then he must be a spy.
Kill him!
No! No!
He's my dad.
Your dad?
Huh?
It's an adoptive relationship.
Aw!
Thank you for
taking such good care
of my son, Agamemnon...
but it's time for
him to come home.
Sorry, Mr. Peabody,
I've joined the Greek army.
Shermanus is one of us now.
He's a brother.
I'm his brother.
He's my son.
He took an oath.
I took an oath.
He's seven!
And a half!
All sons must
prove themselves
to their fathers.
Today...
Shermanus will prove himself
on the field of battle.
But he's only a child.
Your dad may not think
you're ready to
become a man, Shermanus...
but we do.
Yeah!
Yeah, Mr. Peabody.
Now, I'll show you
what I can handle.
FYI, a lot of heroes
have father issues.
My old man is a minotaur.
Half man,
half bull, all judgment.
Ajax, here, strongest
guy in the world...
but his father never
accepted that his real
dream was to sing.
I wanted to be
in the Greek chorus.
Uh, yeah, and
don't even get me
started about Oedipus.
Let's just say
that you do not want
to be at his house
over the holidays.
It's awkward.
Sherman, I'm concerned
you haven't
thought this through.
This is war.
Do you realize
what's about to happen?
I'll tell you
what's gonna happen.
We're gonna
destroy their houses!
Pull down their temples!
And make the streets
of the city run red...
with Trojan blood!
Yeah!
Blood!
Blood! Blood!
Zeus on three! One!
Sherman, I absolutely
forbid you to fight
in the Trojan War.
It's not fair! All my
friends are fighting
in the Trojan War.
Two!
Sherman, it's dangerous.
I'm wearing a helmet.
Three!
You're not going!
Oh, yes, I am.
Zeus!
Zeus! Zeus!
Eat my bronze, you Trojan dogs!
Eat my bronze, you Trojan dog!
Ahh!
Well, that's cutting it close.
This is why I ask you
to obey me, Sherman.
Because I'm your father,
and it's my job
to keep you safe.
But are you sure
Ms. Grunion won't
take me away?
Not as long as I'm around.
Mr. Peabody!
Help me!
Penny!
Smell my victory!
Smell it!
Hey! That's my ride!
Mr. Peabody...
hurry!
I'll take that.
You did it, Sherman!
Mr. Peabody helped.
Now, let's get to
the WABAC, go home,
un-hypnotize
Penny's parents...
finish that dinner party,
eat my Baked Alaska...
charm the pants
off Ms. Grunion...
and make sure none
of this ever happens
in the first place.
Sounds good.
I'm in.
Ah!
Sherman!
Penny!
Sherman, no!
Whoa!
Mr. Peabody...
Mr. Peabody?
Mr. Peabody!
Dad!
Oh, Mr. Peabody!
What should I do?
There's nothing
you can do, Sherman.
I just want to go home.
Home.
That's it.
I got an idea.
Come on!
Where are we gonna go?
We're going home.
There's only one person
who can help us...
and that's Mr. Peabody.
What are you talking about?
How is that even possible?
We've got a time machine, Penny!
I can set it so
that we'll get home
when Mr. Peabody
is still there.
But I thought
you're not supposed
to go back to a time
when you existed.
What choice do we have?
Error.
You are attempting to travel
to an era in which you exist.
This could alter
the fabric of space-time.
Error. Error.
Hang on!
This is fun!
This is a little
homespun concoction
I like to call...
"Einstein on the Beach."
Yummy.
To the kids.
To the kids!
Mr. Peabody.
Sherman? Penny?
Can we talk to you a second?
Of course.
Excuse me.
I've really hit it off
with your parents.
I think we can file
this night under
"Unqualified Success."
I'd hold off
filing it just yet.
What do you mean?
Why are you two dressed
like ancient Greeks?
You used the WABAC!
I did.
I know, it's terrible!
But why?
Penny and I got
into an argument
about George Washington.
So, I made him
show me the WABAC.
And I lost her in ancient Egypt.
And I got engaged to King Tut.
So, I came back
and got you.
Then we ran out of gas.
In Florence.
Went into a black hole.
And then you died
in ancient Troy.
Died? I have a hard
time believing that.
It's true!
But now you're here,
and everything's
gonna be okay.
I told you never to come back
to a time when you existed...
because there
would be two of you!
Yeah, but the other one
of me is in ancient Egypt.
Ahh!
Who are you?
He's you, but
from another timeline.
But I thought you said
never to come back to
a time when you existed.
Exactly!
I know.
But what was I supposed
to do? Mr. Peabody
died in ancient Troy.
Died?
I have a hard time
believing that.
Thank you.
What are we going to do?
Well, for starters,
both Shermans
can't stay here.
Why? We could
get bunk beds.
I was thinking the same thing.
That's so weird.
It's like we're twins!
I was thinking that, too!
Ow!
You see? We can't
have two Shermans in
the same timeline.
It puts too much strain
on the space-time continuum.
What to do?
The Petersons
can't know any of this.
Hey, Pea-buddy.
Hey.
How's it going?
Patty and I are
working up an appetite.
Mmm. The smells
coming from your
kitchen are yummy!
Especially that Baked Alaska.
So, what's going on here?
Yeah, what's with the getups?
Toga party!
Toga party?
Yes, it is a toga party!
Well, what about dinner?
I'm starving.
Why don't we head
into the dining room...
and tuck into those quails
you've been yakking about?
No!
Why not?
Because it's so fun right here!
Whoo-hoo!
Ms. Grunion!
How delightful.
We were having
such a good time...
I almost forgot
you were coming.
Oh!
Well, why don't
you join the party?
I'm not here for a party.
I'm here for
the investigation.
Good. Why don't
you start investigating
over here?
Or here, or here, or here...
Stop waving your hands around!
Sherman?
Wait! Is that...?
Sherman!
Dos Shermanos? What's
going on here, Peabody?
Oh...
Um...
Nobody move!
Sherman, I've got to
get you out of here
before you touch yourself.
Mr. Peabody!
You didn't die!
Of course I didn't die.
Thank you.
Hey. How did you get back?
Well, after a few
failed experiments...
I hit upon a combination
of bones, stone
and yak fat...
and constructed
a rudimentary WABAC.
You know what they say...
"If at first
you don't succeed,
Troy, Troy again."
This is no time for puns!
Even good ones.
Penny, Sherman, quickly!
You're not going anywhere.
I've seen quite enough
to remove the boy...
both boys,
from this home.
No, don't,
Ms. Grunion, please!
This is all my fault.
I started it.
I'm so sorry, Sherman.
You have nothing
to apologize for, Penny.
A dog should never
have been allowed
to adopt a boy
in the first place.
Now, come along.
Ms. Grunion,
be careful!
Ah! Oh!
What's happening?
Mr. Peabody, help!
Sherman!
Oh!
Hey! Where did
the other two go?
Our cosmic doubles
combined in order to
reconcile a paradox...
in the space-time continuum.
Okay, that makes sense.
I don't know what
just happened here...
but I know it was wrong!
This boy is coming with me!
Mr. Peabody!
No, Ms. Grunion!
Ow! Let me go!
Get back here!
Ow! Ow! You're hurting me!
Oh! Oh!
He bit me!
Yes, hello, police.
I'd like to report an assault.
A bite.
Mr. Peabody,
what are we gonna do?
Get here
as soon as possible.
Run!
He's kidnapping
the children! Oh!
I can't believe
you bit her, Mr. Peabody!
I know, Sherman, it was wrong.
"Wrong"?
It was awesome!
And now, to return
to our proper timeline
and erase this mess.
There he is!
He's got my daughter
in that giant space apple!
My face is numb.
Whoo-hoo!
Yes!
What's wrong?
Time travel failed.
Oh, dear.
What is it,
Mr. Peabody?
Our cosmic doubles colliding...
ripped a hole
in the space-time continuum.
That's why we didn't
get to the past.
Hey, Peabody!
Looks like the past
is coming to us.
Oof! I will get you, dog!
And your little boy, too!
Penny!
My bride!
What?
Oh, dear.
Follow that orb!
Incoming!
What sort of creature are you?
The name is Grunion!
I'm in love!
I just need to find a wormhole.
Hey, Einstein, it's a red light.
Hey, I'm walking, here!
Cake!
Mmm!
There they go.
Don't lose them.
I'm trying to find
another wormhole...
but they all lead
back to the present!
Time travel failed.
Whoo!
There he is. After them!
Penny, my queen,
I know you're in there.
We're coming, Shermanus!
Time travel failed.
Mr. Peabody!
Look out!
Whoa!
Shermanus, hold on.
We shall release
you from this egg.
Drop the saber
and step away from
the futuristic orb.
I take orders from no man!
Don't tase me, bro.
Come out, Peabody,
with your paws in the air.
Mr. Peabody,
you're under arrest...
for kidnapping,
reckless endangerment...
And a multiplicity
of major traffic violations.
You don't understand.
There's a rip
in the space-time continuum!
If you arrest me,
I won't be able to fix...
Blah, blah, blah.
For too long...
you've bamboozled the world
with your fancy jargon...
and that little
red tie of yours...
and look what's come of it.
Take him away!
Wait.
Mr. Peabody!
Sherman!
What's gonna happen
to Mr. Peabody?
Don't you know
what happens to
dogs that bite?
Let me go.
You don't know
what you're doing.
Please, before it's too late.
Wait!
Give him another chance.
He's through with chances.
Now, he has to pay
for his mistakes.
But I'm the one
who made all
the mistakes.
I'm the one
who used the WABAC
without permission.
The only mistake
Mr. Peabody ever made...
was me.
Sherman.
You're absolutely
right, Sherman.
What kind of a father
could this dog
ever be to a boy?
Maybe you're right,
Ms. Grunion.
But there's one thing
you haven't considered.
What's that?
I'm a dog, too!
If being a dog
means you're like
Mr. Peabody...
who never turns
his back on you...
and who's always there
to pick you up
when you fall...
and loves you no matter
how many times you mess up...
if that's what it
means to be a dog...
then, yeah, I'm a dog, too!
I'm a dog, too.
I'm a dog, too!
I'm a dog as well!
A poodle dog!
I am a dog, too.
Ditto on that dog thing!
I'm a dog, too.
I am a dog as well.
I'm Spartacus!
All right, fine,
you're all dogs, but
you can't change the law.
I know someone who can.
George Washington.
We hold these truths
to be self-evident...
that all men, and some dogs,
are created equal.
I hereby award Mr. Peabody
a presidential pardon.
Me, too.
I've done worse.
Huh?
Uh, Mr. Peabody, look!
Ahh!
Ooh!
It's getting closer!
What are we going to do?
This is the greatest
collection of geniuses
ever assembled!
Surely we can come
up with another way
of getting to the past.
I can build a catapult.
We go very fast.
But, remember,
as you approach
the speed of light...
gravity will get too strong.
Oh, indeed. "For every
action, there is an equal
and opposite reaction."
How about we just punch
that big hole in the face?
I have an idea.
Hey, everybody, I have an idea!
Yes, what is it, Sherman?
Why not go to the future?
The future?
I've never been there
before, so it's probably
not as messed up.
Sherman, that's it!
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Not usually.
It's exactly what
you all just said...
except the total opposite!
If we set
the WABAC for the future,
and go very, very fast...
we'll create our own
gravitational field...
that's equal and opposite...
to the rip in
the space-time continuum!
Oh, my...
I don't get it.
We're gonna fly up there
and punch that big
hole in the face!
Yes!
Sherman, you're a genius.
But, Peabody...
how far into
the future must you go?
Just a few seconds
ought to do it,
and then we'll
slingshot right back.
Are you sure this
is going to work?
Don't worry, Penny.
Just remember,
I'm a...
Genius!
Sherman...
I need to reprogram the WABAC.
All right, Mr. Peabody.
That means you have to drive.
In order to make the leap
into the future...
the WABAC will
have to go very fast.
Faster than it's
ever gone before!
Are you ready, Sherman?
I'm ready.
Come on, Sherman, you can do it.
Now, Mr. Peabody?
Sherman, we need more speed.
Now?
Just a little more!
Not yet, Sherman.
Not yet.
Now!
Whoa! Whoa!
Farewell!
Ooh!
You haven't seen
the last of me,
Peabody.
You'll make
a mistake eventually,
and when you do...
I'll be there!
The Grunion is mine!
Ooh!
Come on, Sherman. Come on!
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
If you want
to watch television
before I get home...
simply press
"input" three times...
and then use
the remote control
as usual.
Yes, Sherman.
And if you're worried
about making friends
at the PTA meeting...
consider bringing
snacks for everyone.
Bagels are always appreciated.
Yes, Sherman.
And remember,
Mr. Peabody...
I have robotics club
after school today.
Sherman, wait.
Yes, Mr. Peabody?
I...
I love you, Sherman.
I have a deep regard
for you as well,
Mr. Peabody.
Hey, Mr. Peabody!
Hey, Sherman!
Wait up!
No doubt about it.
Every dog should have a boy.
Oh!
Ooh!
Ah!
A-ha!
I now pronounce
you husband and wife.
You may kiss the Grunion.
Come here, soldier.
There's always time for living
Can we just do it again?
One more time
like it once was
way back when
You gave me
something to believe in
We were the best of friends
Well, I remember
the good times
way back when
Memories will fade
if you wanted me
to let you go
I've got you on your way
I feel it for you,
don't you know
We're superheroes and villains
When we used to pretend
We'd go wherever our minds
would take us way back when
Memories will fade
if you wanted me
to let you go
I've got you on your way
I feel it for you,
don't you know
It's a promise that I made
Never be afraid
I know we'll be okay
This luck we have,
it cannot go
'Cause you're on your own
You're not alone
I know I'll see you again Again
And if all these things
Come to an end
We'll always have
a way back when
Memories will fade
if you wanted me
to let you go
I've got you on your way
I feel it for you,
don't you know
It's a promise that I made
Never be afraid
I know we'll be okay
This luck we have,
it cannot go